(The world of fashion changes fast.)
(There is a store
that leads the fashion.)
- Yang Hun.
- Yes?
Put it on here too.
This is crazy.
- It's so stylish.
- It's Generation MZ.
You know I ran
a clothing store before.
(The mecca of Generation MZ,
Hip Jiri)
Fifty percent? Sounds good.
Isn't this nice?
For the new products...
None of them looks new.
- About the shoes...
- Hey.
We should offer the shoes for free.
- They are like free gifts.
- What else should we sell?
They are only one dollar anyway.
(They are like free gifts.
They are only one dollar anyway.)
- We can get 50 dollars for this.
- This one?
- It's just a dollar.
- We should get the story straight.
We shouldn't say different things.
If it's down by 80 percent,
what is the original price?
This one? The original price
was 300 dollars.
Was it 300 dollars?
Let's sell it for 20 dollars.
- It's 20 dollars.
- I ran a clothing store before.
And the shoes are expensive.
Hang on. Look at this.
It says it's down by 80 percent.
People will buy it for 20 dollars.
I guess they will. We can say
it's an 80 percent discount.
(A part-time clerk, Mr. Yang,
in charge of sales and marketing)
Let's sell it for 20 dollars.
It's 20 dollars.
And the shoes are expensive.
(CEO Ha, a shoe lover,
a moneygrubber)
- The shoes are over 100 dollars.
- All right.
Would you pay 20 dollars for this?
Just say Michael Jackson wore this.
- Suk Jin, why would he wear this?
- Michael Jackson...
We can say he wore this
in his music video for "Thriller."
This is expensive.
- You're right. It's pricey.
- They are designer shoes.
Let's say
they are brand-name products.
All these are brand-name products.
- Let's say that.
- They all are designer goods.
- All of these.
- They all are luxury goods.
(There's another store
right against it.)
I don't know anything about
luxury goods, but I'm working here.
I'm in trouble. Hang on.
(Elegance Yoo and Kim)
(An elegant luxury item shop
for female customers)
Even though we're to sell products,
we don't sell things
that don't suit you.
Of course not.
- If it doesn't look good on you...
- Exactly.
or it's not good enough,
we don't sell it.
We don't.
We don't force you to buy it.
And we barely look at our customers.
They are mostly for women.
Yes. Na Eun likes
stuff like this these days.
- Something like this.
- Na Eun would love this.
- Na Eun loves these.
- I bet she does.
You are wearing
tinted glasses today.
Yes. Since I'm working
at a luxury item shop today...
You're all dolled up.
(CEO Kim is all dolled up.)
You're dressed up.
I will rip some customers off today,
so I should hide my eyes.
I see.
- I can't let them read my eyes.
- Okay.
How much should this be?
We should make it expensive.
We are doing this
to make profits after all.
That's right.
But the prices are too low.
- My gosh. What's this "AGUCCIM?"
- What?
- Oh, dear.
- That's nice.
I like that. There are people
who like stuff like this.
(They should make as much profit
as possible in today's race.)
Who would wear this?
Go out and start touting.
- I'm serious.
- Come on in.
(They start touting
as soon as they open the store.)
- Come on in.
- Take a look.
- My gosh.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Hey.
- Welcome.
- All right.
- What? Song Ji Hyo is here.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- You're good at this.
- You are so pretty.
- Of course, I am.
- This is so...
- It's been a long time, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, come here.
Don't even look at them.
They are down by 80 percent.
- It's an 80 percent discount.
- Forget about it.
It's been a really long time.
- It says 80 percent.
- Don't look at it.
They are cheap things. Come here.
Ji Hyo, hip things are
very stylish these days.
What do you think of this?
It's an easy look.
This is Kanye West style.
It's popular in Milan.
- What?
- It's expensive.
- This is really expensive.
- It's designer clothes.
- It's a luxury brand.
- Really?
Yes.
Ji Hyo, it's true. I'm serious.
Wow, I love these shoes.
- All right.
- Sure.
- They are new.
- You have a good eye.
- I love them.
- Try them on.
They are perfect.
- I...
- What do you think?
- I love these shoes.
- Here.
Try them both.
- These boots...
- Throw these away.
- Look at you.
- Wow.
- This is...
- Amazing.
- Haha, how much were these?
- Ji Hyo, listen.
Take a picture of her.
You should see this.
- This is crazy.
- They look perfect on you.
Ji Hyo, I'm serious.
I'm cold now. Do you have a jacket?
- A jacket.
(I'm cold now.
Do you have a jacket?)
(A jacket? Got it.)
- A jacket.
- You need a jacket.
- I want a jacket.
Get me a jacket.
What about this one?
- Ji Hyo, take a look at this.
- It's 80 percent off.
Michael Jackson wore this
in his music video for "Thriller."
- What did you say?
- You know the song, "Thriller."
(They sell such a rare item
at extremely low prices.)
- This is crazy.
- Ji Hyo.
- This is unbelievable. Look at you.
Is she a human or a doll?
Pretend that you're
driving a motorcycle.
That's right.
You're on a motorcycle.
My gosh. That's beautiful.
Ji Hyo, you look great.
- You look like...
- It's only 20 dollars.
You can put this on.
This is it.
My gosh. That's perfect.
Mr. Yang, get her the belt.
- Belt?
- The belt.
- Put it on here.
- You should wear it like this.
This is fashion. It's really...
Ji Hyo, this is crazy.
I'm serious.
If she buys all these...
How much would it be?
- Ji Hyo.
- This is 70, and this is...
- This is 80. So it's 250.
- Okay.
- It's 250?
- Yes. Just give us 250.
- It's 250.
- All right.
- Here are three.
- Three. Hang on.
Count them well.
Ji Ho.
- You gave me 100. This is 100.
- Is it 100?
Let me see.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
- They are 90.
- What? They are 100.
One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven...
- They are 80. Look.
- Suk Jin.
- They are 100.
- One, two...
Three, four, five, six,
seven, and eight.
They are 80.
(She's getting robbed
with her eyes open.)
You'll be put behind bars.
- This is not right.
- Nine and ten.
And 11, 12, 13.
- They are 140.
- It's 140.
So you should give me 110 dollars.
- Give me 110 dollars.
- That's not it.
- This is 140 dollars.
- I got 140 dollars.
- So it's 110 dollars.
- I...
- Then it's 250 in total.
Give me 110 dollars.
Two, three...
(She pays more money
just like that.)
Four.
Five.
It's 15, 16, 17, 18, 19,
- and 20. It's 20 dollars.
- It's 20 dollars.
Give me another 20.
- You don't have it?
- I do have it.
- Give me another 20.
- Just give me that.
Why?
All right. This is enough.
Why is it enough?
We just need another 20.
Put it in the safe anyway.
Give me another 20.
Then give me 10.
You can give me 10 dollars.
- Okay. I'll give you ten and...
- All right. Pick one.
- No. Not one.
- Are you done?
Here's your receipt.
This is the receipt.
(Crude)
Hey, this is...
In this IT era, how can you
issue a receipt like this?
- It's a receipt.
- This is what they do in Milan.
- Right?
- Yes. We do that.
Thank you.
And I'll pick two things I want.
- Just 1.
- No. I'll pick 2.
- Go ahead and take what you want.
- Hang on.
Now that she paid,
you're being mean to her.
- Why are you...
- Just go.
- Go away.
- He's changed.
He already got the money.
This place looks like a luxury shop.
(Elegance Yoo and Kim)
You look pretty.
(They offer quality service
claiming to be a luxury shop.)
- Me?
- Can you get me a cup?
- A cup?
- This is how it works.
This is really nice.
- It's pretty.
- I know. It looks good.
Here. Take a look at this.
- On this...
- So beautiful.
Put this on first, and...
try a jacket on this.
- So very elegant.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Yes.
- Look at this.
- When you go to a party...
- I love it.
- I'll wear it like this.
- Exactly.
That's right.
That's it. My gosh.
- You look great.
- I...
- You look amazing.
- I don't think it looks good.
I don't like it.
(Elegance Kim,
trying to humor his customer)
It looks perfect on you.
- I like this one.
- It looks really good.
Can you get me something
more colorful?
- Of course.
- I don't think it's right for you.
- That's not true.
- Recommend me some accessories.
Accessories for this dress?
Hang on a second.
This will go well
with what you're wearing now.
(He puts it in her ears.)
This is a headband.
You don't know
how to wear a headband.
- Is she wearing headphones?
- What about this?
Are you wearing headphones?
- It looks nice.
- I actually like this.
- It looks good.
- Isn't this nice?
I can go clubbing.
(Carried away)
- So Min.
- Yes?
Be honest with me.
- You're not buying it, are you?
- I'll buy it.
Of course, I will.
- I don't think you will.
- This is...
(She will try everything on
and leave without buying anything.)
(While So Min is carried away...)
So Min is in trouble.
We should stop her.
They are frauds.
- She got carried away.
- She'd give them her house deed.
- They should go to jail.
- This is ridiculous.
What's that?
So Min shouldn't buy this,
but she seems to like it.
- Too bad we don't have a jacket.
- By any chance...
- I want to try this on.
- Yes.
- Try it on?
- So...
- Do you want to put it on?
- No, it would be too much work,
so can you try this on for me?
- I want to see how it looks.
- Of course, we can do that.
- I'd like to see it.
- Sure.
- Trainer Kook will try it on.
- Wait.
- It would look better with black.
- Of course.
- You think? This one?
- Yes.
- Go ahead and try it on.
- I'll see how it looks...
- and buy it.
- Will you buy this?
- Yes.
- Me?
- You can get changed in here.
- Here?
How much is this?
- Which one?
- This tiara.
This is...
I'll be honest with you.
What sound is this?
Is everything all right?
Are these stockings?
- I think it will look good on you.
- Yes. I love it.
- So this is it.
- Isn't it a little too much?
It's like you're not
wearing any bottoms.
What do you think?
- These look great.
- They look nice.
- I know.
- You look amazing.
- I love them.
- You should wear them at work.
(He's impressed
by the elastic leggings.)
These are nice. What do you think?
- What do you think?
- I love them.
- Do you like them?
- Yes. I'll have...
these and the dress from earlier.
- This one.
- Yes.
- This is...
- And this.
- This one is pretty.
- It looks great.
I'll give you two scarves for free.
And it will be 300 dollars in total.
- Is it 300 dollars?
- Yes.
The leopard-print leggings.
That's right. This is a gift.
- She got me a gift.
- Right. I bought it for him.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Bye.
(The luxury shop made 300 dollars
thanks to her.)
We made money anyway.
We managed to sell them.
She bought a lot of weird stuff.
Did you buy this jacket there?
Darn it. They fooled me.
I need to get a refund.
- I want a refund.
- You should. This is fake.
But the owners are
not easy to deal with.
What?
- Gosh, what's that?
- I guess someone's here.
- Welcome.
Gosh.
(The one who knocked
on the door so hard is...)
My goodness.
- Gosh.
- Hang on.
(Actress Jin Seo Yeon)
(The charismatic scene-stealer
from the movie "Believer.")
(And her charisma continued
to the drama, "Wonder Woman.")
(So Min's older sister,
Jin Seo Yeon shows up.)
- Well...
- Gosh.
Why is Jin Seo Yeon...
(She takes a seat while
the owners are frozen with terror.)
- I...
- I want a refund.
- My sister doesn't like...
- I want a refund for all of them.
(Frozen and polite)
Why do you want to get a refund?
- Wait. Is your sister drunk?
- No.
Is your sister...
- Is she a thug?
- No.
She's a nice person.
Why do you want to get a refund?
The price is ridiculous
for this fabric.
This one?
We offered reasonable prices.
We even got her some free stuff.
We sold them below cost.
- Shall I take a look?
- Yes.
Hang on.
Why are you doing this?
(She turns the shopping bag
upside down like a tough girl.)
Why are you doing this?
- Wait.
- Why do you turn it upside down?
You can't do this.
Our products will be...
They are our products.
What does this have to do
with a refund?
You don't have to do this.
- I'll go through them.
- Okay.
This is from Dongdaemun Market.
- It's 20 dollars.
- Gosh.
This is from Namdaemun Market.
It's 18 dollars.
- What?
- My gosh.
What are you talking about?
This is...
- five dollars.
- Why do you...
- But, Seo Yeon, this is...
- Who recommended this?
I want to wear this.
- She really liked it.
- I want to keep this.
You'll wear this
when you go clubbing?
If you dance with a guy
in this dress, he will get grazes.
(If you dance with a guy
in this dress, he will get grazes.)
Why would she dance with a guy?
- I'm sorry, but...
- The fabric is not right.
When she dances with a guy...
Anyway,
I want a refund.
Then, except for this one...
Not this one.
And I heard you got leggings.
That's true.
- Can I see them?
- It was...
- my gift for him.
- This is...
- It was my gift for him.
It's just that So Min is...
- Could you come here for a second?
- Sure.
She got hooked on this gentleman
with a nice body.
I think that's why.
My, you do have a nice body.
- Oh, thank you.
- Then...
- This one too. I'm sorry.
- Yes.
- This one too?
- She won't give you this as a gift.
- No, wait. I bought this for him...
- I'm sorry. So Min.
I bought it for him as a gift...
You shouldn't date a man
just because he has a nice body.
But I bought it...
(So Min's friend takes
the improv comedy seriously.)
- That's ridiculous.
- I gave him...
- She didn't go out with him.
- Don't do that.
- I'm saying that she's trying to.
- She talked about a sexy dance.
- I think she got us wrong.
- So Min saw me wearing it.
- But listen, So Min.
- Then just buy what you want.
- We don't...
- Do you like this dress?
- Yes, I like it.
- This should be five dollars.
So you have to give her 255 dollars.
- Did she say 255 dollars?
- Oh, I was wrong.
(Does 300 minus 5 equal to 255?)
- It's 295 dollars.
- I guess she's not...
- I guess she's not good at math.
- She...
- She's charismatic, but...
- Wait. Hold on.
- It's 295 dollars.
- She's not good at math.
Give her back 295 dollars, please.
- It's 295 dollars.
- But this one is...
Right. This one and...
- My, hello. Please come in.
- Yeo Jin is here.
- Ja Yeon is here too. Come on in.
- Welcome.
- Come on in.
- We have a lot of hip items.
- Yeo Jin, it's been a while.
- It's been a really long time.
(Actress Ok Ja Yeon,
Model Choi Yeo Jin)
Did you give the patient epinephrine
without a doctor's order?
(Ok Ja Yeon, the marvelous actress
with overwhelming charisma)
(And this tough girl has the members
in the palm of her hand.)
(She goes wild
once she receives a mission.)
(The girl crush-worthy lady is
perfect for Running Man.)
(The scammers are getting excited
to see new customers.)
- Was it you? Or you?
- What?
It's been a really long time.
(The palm attack)
- Why...
- Who are you...
- to rip Ji Hyo off?
- Calm down, Yeo Jin.
- What are these?
- What are you doing?
- What's wrong with you?
- I brought Yeo Jin here.
- Hey, Yeo Jin is here.
- These are luxury items.
- Why would you...
- This isn't hip-hop style.
What are you wearing?
This isn't hip-hop style.
We're not just selling
hip-hop clothes.
- This jacket was...
- What's wrong with you?
- worn in the music video...
- What's with her?
- of the song "Thriller."
- She got an 80 percent discount.
- What's the problem?
- Yeo Jin, why...
- You practically robbed her.
- What's this?
We didn't do that.
- You're wearing underwear.
- Underwear?
- What are you talking about?
- What are you doing?
- Did you call it "underwear?"
- She drives me nuts.
- You know nothing about fashion.
Even my grandpa never wears that.
He's a grandpa!
- He's actually a grandpa.
- He's a grandpa.
How do you even sell clothes?
You must know nothing about fashion,
Yeo Jin.
- Yeo Jin.
- I know nothing about fashion?
- Just give me my money back now.
- Why should we?
- Give me back my money.
- Don't be ridiculous.
You already put it on
when you walked out of here!
- We can't give you a refund.
- You put it on me!
- It was a new one!
- We should do something about this.
- A new one?
- You made it a second-hand jacket!
A new one?
- This won't work.
- We should beat them up.
- They won't just leave.
- Hey, look.
- I'll knock some sense into you.
- Hey, guys.
- Obviously, it wasn't a new one.
- How could you push me like that?
- Hey, calm down.
- My gosh.
- Did you just hit him?
- Hey, call the police.
- We should call the police.
- I didn't hit him.
- This is ridiculous.
Listen. We'll give you back
half of the price of one item.
- Are we good?
- Give her a refund for one item...
and half of the prices of the rest.
- Gosh. She's practically a thief.
- That sounds good.
Come on. What are you doing?
Who are you?
- I'm an evil spirit.
- An evil spirit?
- An evil spirit? This is crazy.
- I'm an evil spirit.
- She's scary when she turns.
- What?
- Aren't you a Level Four spirit?
- You're an evil spirit?
- No wonder. The rumor...
- You look like an evil spirit.
- So the weird rumor was true.
- Right.
- The weird rumor was true.
- It was true.
We're not running a charity here.
We need to make a profit.
- They're acting like beggars.
- Here's our offer.
- Listen.
- A refund for the jacket...
and a 50 percent discount
on the belt.
- No. I want a refund...
- That's fair.
- for the shoes and the belt.
- Give me that. You saw it.
- Okay. Then 100 dollars...
- No. Just give her 110 dollars.
- Okay. We'll give you 110 dollars.
- Take it and leave.
- We'll give you back 110 dollars.
- This is the final offer.
- Fine. Give me the money for now.
- You have the money there, right?
- Give me the money.
- We can't give you any more.
- One hundred and ten dollars.
- I'll count. One.
(He skips again.)
- Hey, what are you doing?
- One, two, three, four, five, six,
- seven, eight, nine...
- He paused.
- Come on.
- Wait.
- Hey.
- Don't interrupt him.
- Here's 110 dollars.
- Wait.
You gave me 100 dollars.
- Just take it and leave.
- That's it.
That's it.
Then we'll give you 20 dollars
for the dress and the leggings.
- Twenty dollars?
- Yes.
- But our store...
- So...
- please give her 280 dollars back.
- So 280 dollars...
How about you take
those two pairs of shoes as well?
We'll give you that dress
as a free gift.
We'll charge you 100 dollars
for them and give you 200 dollars.
- We won't negotiate anymore.
- Then...
But...
- Give me 220 dollars.
- Okay.
- So Min.
- Seo Yeon.
- You should get 280 dollars.
- But...
You two must be a duo.
- She's good at fighting.
- Pardon?
- She's like a former gang member.
- So Min.
- Yes?
- Make it 270 dollars.
- The tone of her voice...
- I'm intimidated.
- She said 270 dollars.
- I'll come back without her.
- Okay.
- Come back without her.
- I'll do that.
So Min,
give this to the gentleman...
(Give this to the gentleman...)
Tip him and get his phone number.
(She wants to get
the shop assistant's number.)
Who is she, really? Why would she...
Oh, thank you.
- Text me, okay?
- Okay.
(Clicking her tongue)
- Gosh, seriously.
- I feel sick.
- Excuse me. Hey.
- I really like this dress.
Yes?
(Come on.)
- She's tipping him too.
- But I'm so offended.
Why do I get only 1 dollar
when he got 10 dollars?
- Please.
- I'll give you one more dollar.
- Two dollars. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I think we're done now.
- It was a good deal.
- Yes.
We'll pack these for you.
- Right. We should clean up.
- We should clean up.
That was so funny.
We'll have Whatever Penalty Project,
Part Three today.
- I wonder what penalty we'll get.
- Oh, right.
- I'm stressed about the penalty.
- Today is an important day.
- I had a dream about it.
- How many stickers do I have?
Today's race we'll have
with the charismatic actresses is...
- Be Strong For My Way.
- Oh, dear.
Just as you did earlier,
we'll have a match...
- between Team Boy and Team Girl.
- I see.
The team that gets
more penalty coins wins the race.
The winning team can exchange
the coins they got...
for penalty stickers...
and put the penalty stickers...
on the boards of any members
of the other team.
You heard the rules
of the first mission, right?
The margin that the guys made
after selling fashion items...
is their mission fund for Team Boy.
As for Team Girl,
the money they got back...
is their mission fund.
(So both of the teams got
their first mission funds.)
- We got a lot of money back.
- Really?
- Had she come to us,
- we would've given her a refund.
- We would've been intimidated.
She was so charismatic
in the movie "Believer."
- She's so fabulous.
- Indeed.
- We couldn't argue with her.
- So you gave her a refund.
- Yes, we did.
- You couldn't look her in the eye.
- I mean, her eyes...
- We gave her a refund.
- She's intimidating.
- Look at her outfit.
- She's really tough.
- She's charismatic.
- I thought she was drunk.
- Really?
As soon as she walked in,
she intimidated us.
As a result of the improv comedy,
Team Boy got 212 dollars,
and Team Girl got 358 dollars.
- Didn't you keep any money?
- We couldn't do it.
How intense was she to scare them?
She walked in with bleary eyes.
What could we have done?
- I see you had no choice.
- You should've kept the money.
- Did you keep your money?
- Yes, we did.
- We got more than 100 dollars.
- We made a big profit.
- I think it was 170 dollars.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You did a good job.
A penalty coin is 50 dollars.
Team Boy will receive
four penalty coins.
- And Team Girl will receive...
- Oh, gosh. I'm worried.
- seven penalty coins.
- Oh, yes.
- See?
- Gosh.
You can put the penalty coins
in the coin box.
- This is just the beginning.
- Right. This is just the beginning.
- We'll move after you get changed.
- Got it.
- Let's go.
- Okay!
Come on. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- I think I'll get a penalty.
Let's go.
I guess that's the case
You see, I think Ok Ja is...
- Her name is Ja Yeon.
- How could you?
Are you talking about the movie
"Okja" or what?
- Why would you call her Ok Ja?
- How could you call her Ok Ja?
- I'm sorry.
- That's not her name.
- It's okay.
- The way he said "I'm sorry."
- My friends call me Ok Ja.
- Exactly.
- I wanted to be your friend.
- Her name is Ok Ja Yeon.
- He wasn't entirely wrong.
- Right.
- That's right.
- I thought, "How did he know?"
- Of course, I know. I did research.
- Some people have such nicknames.
The name "Ok Ja" sounds catchier
for some reason.
- Right. It's catchy.
- It's more friendly.
- Yes. You should change your name.
- It's Ja Yeon.
- Gosh. You've crossed the line.
- What's your problem?
- Change your name to Ji Seok.
- Change it to Seok Sam.
How about "Hyun Ok Ja?"
Ji Seok doesn't suit him.
It's too cool for him.
Seo Yeon, I've been a big fan
since I watched "Believer..."
Stop talking about "Believer."
- This is the second time.
- Talk about something else.
- I've been a big fan since then.
I thought, "My, why haven't I seen
such a talented actress until now?"
- I was amazed...
- And she's older than you.
Nonsense. Don't lie to me.
You should address her
as your senior.
I don't mind doing so,
but I'm sure...
- she's not older than me.
- How old are you?
- Suk Jin, how old are you?
- I was born in 1966.
"Suk Jin, how old are you?"
- She's good at it.
- She knows how to react.
- She's good.
- Indeed.
- Seo Yeon is good.
- Yes.
- "How old are you?"
- She's the best.
Seo Yeon went to the same school...
- Who?
- as So Min.
- They went to the same school?
- You mean, college?
- Dongduk Women's University?
- Yes.
- Hello! Dongduk Women's University!
- Do you know many of them?
- Broadcast and entertainment Major!
- Gosh. Stop it.
- Hey, stop it, will you?
- Student number, 20051756!
- Jeon So Min...
- That's enough.
- So Min told me...
- Practical music.
that those who were born in 1983
and studied the same major...
- Why did he stutter?
- What were you saying?
She said many of those who were born
in 1983 were so cool.
- That's right.
- Oh, that's right.
Suk Jin is close friends
with those who enrolled in 2002.
- Why?
- True.
- We just...
- They call themselves...
- Rainbow Seven Princesses.
- What?
- But there were...
- I know them.
- only ten of us called BF.
- BF?
- I heard about Seven Princesses.
- Including A Joong.
Kim A Joong, and I...
- A Joong enrolled in the same year?
- Yes.
Oh, I see.
Who were in Seven Princesses?
I've never heard about them.
Why are you asking me?
- Why are you asking me?
- That's funny.
- I just heard it.
- Who are your friends?
- "Why are you asking me?"
- "I've never heard about them."
- I don't know them well either.
- I think you're mistaken.
- Hey.
- I mean...
Seo Yeon really is charismatic.
- He stuttered again.
- That's funny.
- He's taken aback.
- Right.
The first mission is a game of wits
that Jae Suk likes.
A game that I like?
- Yes.
- Okay.
I'll give you a topic,
and you should answer quickly.
- It's Know Yourself Game of Wits.
- Okay. Great.
You have to say a word
that's related to the given topic,
and you should avoid
saying the same answer as others.
- But...
- I'm good at games like that.
It's similar to the game
where we hold the thumb.
Yes. But your answer should have
one more syllable...
than the answer of the player
in front of you.
- Oh, I see. Okay.
- That's easy.
- I specialize in it.
- That's unusual.
Starting with a 1-syllable word,
increase 1 syllable every time.
- Okay.
- That sounds fun.
- It sounds fun.
- That's interesting. Let's do it.
After you made it
to a five-syllable word,
decrease the number of syllables
from 4 to 1.
- Okay.
- Got it.
If more than one person speaks
at the same time,
if the number of syllables isn't
right,
or if the word is not related
to the topic, you fail.
And you lose one point.
- Okay. Let's begin.
- Got it.
Since it's a team match,
we'll tally the scores.
- Oh, right. It's a team match.
- We're on the same team.
We're all wearing yellow.
- Don't say the same word as mine.
- Be witty.
- We're on the same team.
- We shouldn't say the same word.
- I see.
- No.
- We can say the same word.
- I'll give you the first topic.
- Yes.
How do you think
others would portray you?
Dung!
- No. We should raise our hands...
- Cutie!
- "Cutie?"
- Alluring.
(1. Dung, 2. Cutie, 3. Alluring)
Girl crush worthy.
Irresistible.
Magnificent.
Intriguing.
(2. Gums)
- Gums.
- Mandarin.
- What's with gums and mandarin?
- What's with mandarin?
- As refreshing as mandarin.
- Why mandarin?
It's sour and refreshing.
Team Boy lost one point.
- Why didn't you say anything?
- Are you stupid?
(It wasn't related to the topic,
and Jong Kook didn't answer.)
Why didn't you say anything?
There is something about Haha
that's similar to mandarin.
- No.
- Right. I'm bubbly.
- You're more like a kumquat.
- Right.
I'm the bubbliest
among all 44-year-old men.
So this is how we play the game.
It was a practice round.
Here's the next topic.
How would you feel
if you run into your ex?
- Spit...
- They spoke at the same time. Okay.
(They spoke at the same time.)
- Okay.
- Let's raise our hands.
I didn't say my answer.
- You said "spit."
- No.
- I didn't...
- You said it.
- Let's be quick-witted.
- Have you ever...
run into your ex-boyfriend?
- My ex-boyfriend?
- Yes.
- No.
- I have.
- Me too.
- You have?
- Yes. I'll tell you what happened.
I acted cool and said hi to him.
Then he...
He saw me. He has good eyesight.
He looked at me for a while.
"Well... Who is she?"
(Who is she?)
- I got so upset.
- My gosh.
So Min, he must have been
put off by you.
- Exactly.
- Why do things like that happen...
- to her so often?
- I was so upset.
- Why do such things happen to her?
- I wanted to punch him.
- That's how upset I was.
- Were you alone?
No, I was with my friends.
He got even cheekier.
After he ignored me,
his eyes met my friend's eyes.
My friend said
that he had winked at her like this.
- Gosh. What's that?
- My friend said...
(Gosh. What's that?)
- That's so upsetting.
- What's that?
- He's a jerk.
- Right? Isn't he cheeky?
What's his problem?
Seo Yeon,
have you ever run into your ex?
- I've seen him.
- Right.
You know, you can recognize
a person even from a distance...
- after dating him for a long time.
- Absolutely.
I was about to open a glass door
when I saw him.
I turned around right away and left.
- You turned around?
- Yes, right away.
Are you sure it was him?
- Yes, I'm sure. I felt his energy.
- I bet she recognized him.
- It's better not to see your ex.
- Of course.
I had no choice
when I saw my ex-girlfriend.
- Really?
- You should've just ignored her.
It's what I regret the most.
When I saw her,
- You should've said hi to her.
- I was going to say hi casually.
- But I used honorifics.
- "Hello?"
"Oh, hello."
- I still regret it so much.
- That's so lame.
You know, right?
I regret it so much...
- that I want to turn back time.
- I know.
- You must've been upset.
- I could've said, "Hey."
Okay. Let's move on.
What did you hear
when you broke up with your ex?
(What did you hear
when you broke up with your ex?)
- Go.
- Get lost.
(1. Go, 2. Get lost.)
(3. Go away.)
- Go away.
- I was going to say that.
- I miss you.
- That's a lie.
I loved you.
(4. I miss you, 5. I loved you)
I'm sorry for everything.
You jerk.
- Right.
- Gosh.
- Team Girl lost one point.
- It's possible.
- Why?
- Okay.
- All the guys said answers.
- I see.
- Didn't we finish first?
- I didn't say an answer.
- Every member should say an answer.
- It's okay.
- I didn't know that.
- We pulled it off.
Next topic. What's the cutest thing
you can say?
Phew.
Bleh.
Hi-ow.
(Phew)
(Even "bleh" was accepted too.)
(But what does "hi-ow" mean?)
- She's so cute.
- Hold on. I have something to say.
Isn't "hi-ow" too old-fashioned?
- Didn't people say it in the past?
- What does that even mean?
- That's not acceptable.
- What was that?
- This is driving me crazy.
- Since I have a child,
the words "hi" and "meow" were mixed
in my head.
- "Hi-ow."
Can we try the same topic again?
- The same topic?
- Yes.
What's the cutest thing you can say?
- Yo.
- Boom.
So Min?
(So Min)
Purr.
- I missed you.
- My goodness.
(I missed you.)
- That was so funny.
- He failed.
- Suk Jin failed.
- Why?
- That wasn't cute.
- Why not?
- I missed you.
- Gosh. Hey!
- Team Boy lost a point.
- You failed.
- Why?
- That wasn't cute.
He deserves to lose 100 points.
- I missed you.
- "I missed you."
- Slap him in the face!
- Hey.
Take this.
Look at those teeth
with nicotine stains.
I hate the sight of his teeth
Oh, gosh. That's so hilarious.
What are you doing?
What's with the pose?
- What's that?
- The upside-down V pose.
- I really hate it.
- I mean, he sounded...
- a bit weird and cheerless.
- I hated it so much.
"I missed you."
That was just weird.
Ja Yeon,
why didn't you say anything?
I can be very cute.
- I don't think so.
- Show us.
- Do all five answers by yourself.
- Start with a 1-syllable word.
- A 1-syllable word?
- Yes. Ready. Go.
- Ready. Go.
Um.
Two syllables.
- Slap her in the face!
- Take this.
Hey, Ja Yeon,
why didn't you keep going?
- I can't be cute.
- Cute.
- Hey, So Min will show you.
- Let's let Seo Yeon try it.
- So Min will show you how to do it.
- So Min is the best.
So Min, say cute words
starting with a one-syllable word.
From 1 to 5 syllables. Ready. Go.
Oh.
(She starts
as soon as Haha finishes.)
(Baby sound)
(Acting cute
while making baby sounds)
- So Min is...
- My gosh.
- What's with the baby sounds?
- It was So Min.
Punch her in the face!
- What's with the baby sounds?
- It was So Min.
(Punch her in the face!)
- Take this!
- Behead the man!
Ja Yeon, watch him.
Seok Sam will show you how to do it.
Watch Seok Sam.
- Don't make me do that.
- Try it.
Give it a try. Show us.
(The prepared, talented man looks
for a camera first.)
- I don't think I can watch this.
- Oh, my.
- I can't watch this.
- Let's turn off the camera.
He found that camera.
- Ung.
- Oh, my.
- Let's turn off the camera.
- Ah-ing.
People will switch the channel.
(The guilty pleasure that catches
their eyes even though they hate it)
- What have you been up to?
- Die!
(Summary justice)
(Die!)
My gosh.
- "What have you been up to?"
- Die!
- Slap him...
Slap him in the face!
Gosh, those teeth
with nicotine stains.
Those stained teeth.
I got my teeth scaled.
- Seo Yeon, give it a try.
- Those stained teeth.
- Which camera should I look at?
- From 1 to 5 syllables.
- Look at this camera.
- This one?
- Yes. Ready.
Ready. Go.
Ang.
Kkurung.
(Kkurung.)
- Kkurung.
- Good. You're doing great so far.
Good.
Ho-ae-ing.
Four syllables.
Ppula-ppula.
Five syllables!
- What's "ppula-ppula?"
- It's like "kukkuruppingppong."
Kkukkuruppippi.
Those are all gibberish
that she would say to her baby.
- It's gibberish.
- It works every time.
"Kkurung" was so funny.
- Babies like such sounds.
- Absolutely.
- All babies like it.
- Ji Hyo, try it just once.
- Show us, Ji Hyo. One syllable.
- Ji Hyo, try it.
(Baby sound)
Two syllables.
Three syllables.
(Staring into space)
- I'm so cute.
- Four syllables.
(Unexpectedly, she keeps going
without hesitating.)
I am Ji Hyo.
Five syllables.
My name is Ji Hyo.
Jong Kook, do it just once.
- I don't want to.
- Just one sentence. Come on.
Stop it.
- Say, "Give me a barbell."
- "Give me a barbell."
"Give me a barbell."
- Say, "Give me a barbell."
- Please.
- "Give me a barbell."
(Give me a barbell.)
(He demands a barbell
while clenching fists.)
"Give me dumbbells."
"Protein shake."
"Chicken breast, please."
- "Protein shake."
- My goodness.
- "The Smith machine."
- "Protein shake."
"I'll pump up my muscles today."
"Work out your back muscles."
Team Boy won.
- Okay!
- Yes!
- We're done.
- We won.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- This is...
- It says "Danger."
- I'll put it here.
- It looks like...
I wonder what this is.
It looks like a place
for an escape room game.
I wonder what we'll do here.
This wall reminds me of the show
"The Great Escape."
This place looks very big
since I haven't been here in a while.
I told you...
that the penalty coins would
play a big part, right?
- Yes, you did.
- Yes.
After every mission, each team will
receive the same number of coins.
Plan a strategy
of dividing the coins...
and then deceive your apposing team.
The winning team will...
have a chance to interrogate
two members of the other team.
After that, you can choose
two members and take their coins.
- Okay.
- No touching, right?
The losing team can choose...
one person on the other team
and take his coins.
- Gosh.
- It's a mind game.
Now, please divide the coins.
Okay.
I'll hold on to my coins.
Consider yourselves informed.
We should let one of us
have all the coins.
- Right, we should do that.
- Yes.
- Okay. Good.
- We'll win.
- You're right.
- Which one of us should keep them?
- What should we do?
- Exactly.
Shall we choose the person randomly?
- Yes, we should do that.
- Let's play...
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
How about we...
play rock-paper-scissors to decide?
- Then one of us...
- Half-and-half.
(One of us...)
(One of the three of them.)
- Then one of us...
- Half-and-half.
and 1 of the 3 of them.
- That's a good idea.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's divide the coins in half.
(One cast member and one guest will
keep half each.)
- Okay. Let's do this.
- Let's do it.
- The loser? Rock-paper-scissors.
- Yes.
- Me?
(Among the guests,
Seo Yeon keeps coins.)
- It's better than carrying it.
- Right. Let's do that.
(Ji Hyo or So Min has
the rest of their coins.)
- Psychologically.
- Seo Yeon?
- You can keep a poker face, right?
(Meanwhile, Team Boy has to decide
whom they should interrogate.)
Seo Yeon...
I'm sure they divided their coins.
They didn't give all to one person.
- They divided the coins.
- Yes.
- Ji Hyo must not have any coins.
- I think Seo Yeon has some.
(Correct.)
- But Seo Yeon is so intimidating.
- How about Ok Ja?
- Shall we pick Ok Ja and Seo Yeon?
- Right.
Ok Ja must be really smart.
She graduated from SNU.
But this is different.
Let's pick Ok Ja and Seo Yeon.
- But Seo Yeon is scary.
- We should pick So Min.
- She gets confused easily.
- Teasing her is fun.
So Min?
Let's pick So Min and Ja Yeon.
- Are we going that way?
- That's the best.
- So Min and Ja Yeon.
- We should get more coins.
Let them in, please.
- Did you want to see me?
- Please have a seat.
- Please sit down.
- You're walking lightly.
I guess you don't have any coins.
- She seems a little worried.
- So Min.
Let's not make this complicated,
okay?
- It's because...
- We don't have all day.
So Min, who did you give the coins?
(He asked
a straightforward question.)
(The first question was asked
so suddenly.)
- She's smiling.
- You must answer our questions.
- Must I?
- Yes. Who was it?
- You must tell us.
- Tell us. Yes.
Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, right?
- Yes, that's what we expected.
- So it's not Ji Hyo.
- So Min,
if you tell us the truth...
You said Ji Hyo, right?
She touched her nose
while saying her name...
and that's a tell-tale sign.
- Me?
- That's right.
You look uncomfortable too.
- Do I look uncomfortable?
- Yes, it shows.
I couldn't be
more relaxed right now.
You're saying this is relaxed?
- Normally...
- Your eyes aren't smiling.
This is how I always smile.
Your eyes aren't smiling.
They sure are.
No, it's just your eyes.
Seo Yeon has coins, doesn't she?
(Right on the nose)
- I do not know.
- That's a yes.
- Seo Yeon has coins.
- There we go.
- "I do not know."
- Noted.
- Seo Yeon has coins, doesn't she?
- I do not know.
- Ji Hyo has coins, doesn't she?
Judging by how nervous she is,
- she must have coins herself.
- Answer us!
She must have coins herself.
Answer us, Ms. Jeon!
They may have given some to her...
- thinking that we'd rule her out.
- Exactly.
(The variety show detectives
squeeze her for answers.)
(Either Ji Hyo or So Min
has the coins.)
- Look at her.
- Right.
- At the sound of her name...
- Why...
Your mouth.
- Your gums seem dry.
- She can't seem to answer us.
- Get talking.
- Your gums are dry.
- You should answer us.
- Why aren't you saying anything?
This is no place to be cheeky!
- What the...
- She hasn't been cheeky.
This is no place to be cheeky!
But she hasn't been cheeky.
She isn't saying anything though.
- But that's her character.
- What's with you?
You're being cheeky and audacious.
- Wait.
- What now?
What the... Are you insane?
(What the... Are you insane?)
How did you know that?
- She's crazy.
- We all know that.
How did you know that?
- I'm crazy, yes, I'm crazy
So let me free
That's it.
That...
(Jeon "Dam Bi" So Min responds
in a peculiar way.)
- You're a good dancer.
- Of course.
- You're quite the dancer.
- I'm impressed.
You have your own style of dancing.
- She's like a frog.
- That's something I like.
- Sure.
- You know that, right?
Jeon So Min.
- Get out already!
- You may leave.
- I'll get lost, then.
- Good.
Gosh, this is confusing.
Would they have given her coins?
- No way.
- Not So Min.
- Not her.
- No way.
- So Min...
- I think Ji Hyo has the coins.
This is nauseating. I might be sick.
- Your lips...
- I danced for too long.
- Your lips lost their color.
- You danced?
(Jeon "Dam Bi" So Min
is out from confinement.)
Even at the smallest movements.
They questioned
the twitching of my fingers.
(Who is currently holding the coins
for Team Girl?)
- She...
- I'm sure Ji Hyo has the coins.
- Ja Yeon, have a seat.
- Take your seat.
She's already in character.
- Hey!
- Are you already at stage four?
Take your seat.
Let's watch our manners, shall we?
Right back at you.
You had one person
take all the coins, right?
- So Min told us.
- She told us.
Is that what you chose to do?
No, that's what So Min told us.
Just answer this.
How many of you have the coins?
- Does Seo Yeon have coins?
- Wealth and fame...
- How many of you have the coins?
- How many?
- Two?
- Give us a number.
- Just tell us that.
- We split the coins...
among the five of us.
Do you have any of the coins?
(Do you have any of the coins?)
Hold on a second.
She just inhaled sharply.
And then she crossed her legs.
How about this?
I'll say "yes"
if we have that in common.
- In common with us?
- Yes.
(What they have in common?)
Does only one of you have coins?
- Wait.
- This isn't right.
This isn't how it should be.
- I almost fell for that.
- How dare you.
- I mean...
- Are you kidding me?
- No wonder you graduated SNU.
- Is that a no?
- It's a no.
- I do not know.
Did you let the two of you
take the coins?
How many of you have coins?
We haven't even split our coins yet.
- It's either 1 or 2 for them.
- I agree.
- One or two.
- Right.
- Two seems about right.
- Seo Yeon and...
Not really.
- Did you see her reaction?
- Listen.
- Ja Yeon.
- One from Running Man...
and one of the guests.
(One from Running Man
and one of the guests)
(Detective Kim is right on point.)
I think they're getting to Ja Yeon.
I told her to talk like a robot,
but...
She's letting them get to her.
- One from Running Man...
and one of the guests.
- Seo Yeon has coins, right?
- I bet Ji Hyo has coins!
(The fake detectives
corner Ja Yeon.)
Who do you think has the coins?
- Tell us.
- Not you at least.
- Why not?
- Not you.
- You don't have the guts.
- That's right.
- You're a coward!
You wouldn't have been able
to speak up.
You and So Min, I mean.
- Not the two youngest members.
- It's not them.
- You may leave.
- Go!
- Get out.
- Jae Suk's right.
She's back looking like
a lost puppy.
Your eyes are glistening.
- Did they get to you?
- Were they harsh?
- They must've scolded her.
- I know.
Did they yell at you?
- Because she's the youngest.
- It was split 4, 3, and 3.
No one on that team is capable
of calculating probabilities.
Gosh, it's way too easy.
It's time to make your decision.
- Already?
- Just like that?
Choose the two members
who you think have the coins.
- Seo Yeon.
And...
(Will Seo Yeon be caught?)
- No, let's discuss this.
- That we should.
(Sighing)
- Who do you think it is?
- Ja Yeon.
No way. I think it's Yeo Jin.
That's out of the blue.
We never mentioned her.
Seo Yeon and Yeo Jin.
Yeo Jin's one of the older ones.
Because she's charismatic,
she would've avoided
getting the coins.
- Seo Yeon for sure.
- Let's get Seo Yeon up there.
- And Ja Yeon.
- No.
- Ja Yeon.
- Seo Yeon...
- Ja Yeon? No, it's Seo Yeon.
- Ja Yeon.
- It's Ja Yeon.
- No, it's Seo Yeon.
It has to be the Yeon sisters.
Seo Yeon gulped just now.
- You're like that too.
- It means she's nervous.
- It has to be Seo Yeon.
- I'm sure of it.
I don't think
they gave her any coins.
They would've seen her
as the easier choice.
Can we choose two people?
They would've seen her
as the easier choice.
Can we choose two people?
- It's Seo Yeon.
- The coins were split 4, 3, and 3.
- Because...
- It's Ji Hyo.
- Why is she not saying anything?
- Ji Hyo and Ja Yeon.
Yes, Ji Hyo. I second that.
- Out of the five...
- Ja Yeon and Ji Hyo.
- No way.
- One...
- Ja Yeon and Ji Hyo.
- That's it.
- Because at the end,
- they watched their expressions.
- Ja Yeon and Ji Hyo.
Ja Yeon and Ji Hyo.
- Why?
- Get up here.
- Hold on.
- How is this done?
- Get over here.
- Unbelievable.
- You're busted.
- Why me?
- We got you.
- I saw Ji Hyo's expression.
- Me too.
- I know you're quick-witted.
- What's the reason?
- But she could be faking it.
- I saw her.
She could be faking it.
Seo Yeon,
we read your darting eyes.
All right.
Please take out your notebooks
and open them for us.
- It's Seo Yeon for sure.
- If we're wrong, so be it.
It's Seo Yeon for sure.
Can't you see she's acting? Gosh.
Let's check their notebooks first.
All right. In one...
(Does Ji Hyo have coins?)
- Are we wrong?
- Two.
Two.
Three.
(Open!)
(None)
- Nice!
- Yes!
(Team Girl manages
to defend their coins.)
Seo Yeon, right?
I told you that it's Seo Yeon.
- It must've been Seo Yeon.
- Seo Yeon.
- I told you that it's Seo Yeon.
- See?
- Seo Yeon and Yeo Jin.
- I said Seo Yeon and Yeo Jin.
How could they be completely off?
- I can't believe it!
- Seo Yeon had the coins, right?
- I said Seo Yeon and Yeo Jin.
- Seo Yeon was one of them.
Yes, Seo Yeon.
Team Boy lost and won zero coins.
I had six of the coins.
(The correct answer)
- And...
- See?
- Me.
- It was Seo Yeon.
And I had four of them.
- So Min?
- So Min, my gosh.
Why didn't you listen to me?
The losing team will now choose
one person from the opposing team.
We only get to choose
one person, right?
We could've answered correctly.
- Why are they...
- What's with Haha?
His eyes say everything.
(Who on Team Boy
has the most coins?)
We should go for anyone
who most likely has any coins,
- and that is Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- We only get to choose one.
Team Girl, please choose one
from the opposing team.
One, two, three.
- Suk Jin.
(They choose Suk Jin.)
- He could be acting.
- He may not have any.
- This could be an act.
- Get up there.
- It must be Jae Suk.
- I think we got him.
Why did we even bother?
It was all for nothing.
(Could Suk Jin have the coins
even though he's putting on an act?)
How many do you have?
In 1, 2, 3.
(Open)
Suk Jin didn't have
any of the coins.
(Suk Jin has 0 coins)
(Team Girl fails to obtain
any coins.)
We chose...
- Haha.
- It was me.
(Haha who put on a show
had all 10 coins.)
- All ten?
- We let him have all of them.
Yes, all ten.
This next game combines
Speak With Your Actions...
and Cry in Silence.
It's Act in Silence.
- Sounds like fun.
- Speak in Silence?
After seeing the title
of the TV series or the movie,
you will explain it
with just your actions.
(Gosh)
- What the...
- And...
- What was that?
- Seriously?
Are you reacting that way
just because it's Hyung In?
- It's not like that.
- Enough is enough.
To the next person? Goodness.
The next person will guess
which TV series or movie it is...
and yell a key line...
to the next person in line
while wearing headphones.
If the last person in line
guesses the title correctly,
you will win one point.
- Gosh.
- This...
- Can the lines be repeated?
- Of course.
- Then...
- We'll have to stay focused.
- This...
- It sounds hard.
- We must know many titles too.
- Right.
I'm not good with titles though.
I've watched a lot of movies.
- I'm bad with titles.
- The three of us.
Each team will get three minutes,
- so score more points to win.
- Okay.
- Sounds easy enough.
- The men will go first.
- Okay, good.
- We got it.
I'd love to get an idea
of what we're facing,
but we've been asked to go first.
- Se Chan knows a lot.
- Really?
- He's knowledgeable.
- I see.
He knows a lot of lines as well.
- First, we should...
- Who wants to guess?
Shouldn't you be the one to guess?
The one guessing must know
a lot of the movies and series.
- The same goes for the others.
- The lines for me, actions for you.
- Se Chan will relay the title.
- Got it.
Will there be a strategy?
- Of course.
- So for Korean movies...
We'll bow for Korean movies...
and do the okay sign
for foreign movies.
- Okay.
- This for foreign movies.
- This for Korean movies.
- Right.
- Korean movies.
- Okay.
- Okay, that seems good enough.
That much we should agree on.
The right ear.
- Just the right?
- Yes.
The right.
(Music playing)
- Right.
- Like this.
I can't hear a thing.
- Jae Suk.
- The song is playing.
Why?
- I already can't hear clearly.
- What's the matter?
- Jae Suk, can you hear?
- Yes?
Turn up the volume for him.
Turn up the volume for Jae Suk.
It's playing now.
Should we guess movie titles
over there?
- Yes. The titles.
- Movie or drama titles.
Drama titles?
- Famous movie or drama titles.
- Movie or drama titles.
Jae Suk, it's movie
or drama titles.
There are drama titles too.
I can't hear you.
What?
There are drama titles too.
- Drama?
- Yes. Movie or drama titles.
Movie and drama?
You can take them out to listen.
- Drama.
- What did you say?
There are drama titles too.
- I can't hear you.
- There are drama titles too.
Get ready.
Go.
(The first question is revealed.)
(Do I have the face of a king?)
Yes. A famous line like this.
(Se Chan has to explain
with action.)
(Looking at one's face,
"The Face Reader!")
- "Iron Man?"
- He's good.
- "Iron Man?", "The Mask?"
- Se Chan is good.
(It's a Korean movie.)
A Korean movie?
A foreign movie? A Korean movie?
The face? What's that?
What's with the face?
"It's amazing."
(Changing from "The Face Reader"
into "Nameless Gangster")
"It's amazing."
- I see.
- "It's amazing."
What's that?
I see.
(Suk Jin mistook it as "Nameless
Gangster: Rules Of The Time" too.)
What's that?
- That's where it goes...
- Wrong again.
(Staring)
- Hey.
- Let go of me.
(Haha has no idea.)
(It's a Korean movie.)
He has to speak.
- Hold on.
- He can speak.
You should say the line.
You should say it.
(It's a mess.)
"Look here."
"Do I have the face of a king?"
(It went wrong in the middle,
but he mysteriously got it right.)
- Is it this one?
- "Do I have the face of a king?"
Can I say the answer?
"The Face Reader?"
(Incorrect?)
- He cheated.
- Why?
- What? It's not?
- He used his hands.
- He knows.
- What is it?
You can't use your hands
when you say the line.
You should say the line only.
Should I say the line only?
He should only speak?
You should just speak.
- I could read your lips.
- I did it like that after that.
It's that one.
The one with Choi Min Sik.
No. It's "The Face Reader."
- It's "The Face Reader."
- Is it "The Face Reader?"
This was not "It's amazing."
It was the face reading.
- It's because of the gesture.
- He said "It's amazing."
- When did I do it like this?
- I thought it was that.
- So...
- "It's amazing."
- It's not this one.
If it's "The Face Reader..."
- I didn't know.
- you should point at your face.
- "It's amazing."
- Come on.
- We should switch.
- Okay. Come here.
- I got it.
- You got it, right?
- It was easy.
- You should say the line.
Ready. Go.
Go.
("Extreme Job")
(There was no flavor like this.)
(Is this galbi or chicken?
This is Suwon Big Galbi Chicken.)
- This is Suwon Big Galbi Chicken.
- This is so hard.
This is so hard.
- It's hard.
- How can he explain with his body?
(The line is easy, but the action
isn't easy for this movie.)
(Explaining the fried chicken)
What's the famous line?
"There was no chicken like this."
(A scene where he takes an order
on the phone)
The famous line. Okay.
I know what it is.
The Suwon Big Galbi thing.
(He exactly got
the Big Galbi Chicken!)
Suwon Big Galbi.
Can I have Suwon Big Galbi?
- What's the action?
- Suwon Big Galbi.
I know it.
He knows?
(Frying the chicken)
(Taking an order)
(There you go!)
"It can't get better than..."
- What was it?
- Hey.
(The professional mistaker
appears again.)
- You said you got it.
- "There was..."
- "There is..."
"no better chicken." You know it.
- Louder.
- "There was no better chicken."
"To your taste..."
"There was no..."
- "There's no better chicken."
- "Is this galbi or chicken?"
- What?
- "There was no better chicken."
Say it louder and clearer.
Chicken.
- Chicken?
- Chicken.
Chicken.
- Chicken?
- Chicken.
(Shouting)
(Did Jong Kook finally get it?)
"She's..."
(That's not it.)
"She's On Duty."
"More than..." That one.
- "She's On..."
- "Duty."
(Frustrated)
- Three.
- "She's..."
- Two.
- No.
He's on duty and...
It's over.
- It's "Extreme Job."
- Isn't it "She's On Duty?"
- "Extreme Job?"
- What was the line?
- It's "Extreme Job."
(The harmful consequences
of watching American dramas only)
"Is this galbi or chicken?"
"This is Suwon Big Galbi Chicken."
I thought it was that. But I thought
the title was "She's On Duty."
I said,
"There was no better chicken."
- It was similar. It was good.
- It was so close.
We could get it right
if it goes well.
- You should've gotten it right.
- Why didn't I know "Extreme Job?"
- It's a pity.
- Try it. We can do it.
- Let's go.
- We can do it.
Go.
(The third question is revealed.)
(I'm going to have
a glass of Maldives...)
(in mojito.)
- It's hard.
- Action is easy.
Action is...
(Turning his wrist)
(He demonstrates the massage
himself.)
It hurts. I know.
- But I don't know the line.
- The line.
- It's the title.
- I know.
But I don't know the line.
(It's a Korean movie.)
"I have..."
(Empty Head cheated in an instant.)
(I have something to say
to you guys.)
- Did he do the action?
- "I'm going to make a charge."
A charge against whom? What's this?
L, O, V, E, love.
(Turning his wrist)
(I see!)
I know it, but what was the line?
What was the line?
"I'm going to have a glass
of mojito in Maldives."
(He said the line
after a long time!)
It's the other way around.
- "I'm going to have..."
- Okay.
"a glass of mojito in Maldives."
(Answer: "I'm going to have a
glass of Maldives in mojito.")
- Isn't it obvious?
- Right.
(The mojito guy corrected the line.)
(Hold on.)
"In mojito..."
He can't remember the title again.
- "A glass."
- He can't remember the title.
The title.
(That's right!)
- Shouldn't Se Chan be last?
- Wait.
- I can't remember the title.
- Hey.
Wait.
(What's wrong with him?)
- Come on.
- Seriously.
Hey.
- It's Lee Byung Hun this time.
- He knows.
- Yes.
- Why...
- You must know it.
- It's that one.
- Come on.
- That thing.
(They're so frustrated
that they might go crazy.)
- It's that one. Yes.
- It's that thing. That's it.
- It's that thing.
- Mojito.
- He doesn't know the title.
- It's that thing.
- Incorrect.
- He doesn't know the title.
It has four syllables, right?
- Four syllables.
- It's "Inside Men."
- "Inside Men."
- Four syllables.
- Is it over?
- Is it not?
- "Inside Men."
- "Inside Men." Oh, right.
What's interesting...
is that it was getting farther from
the answer, but it went back.
- It goes back to the correct one.
- It's very interesting.
But he doesn't know the title.
It's amazing.
- He's so bad, but he gets it.
- Why do you not know the title?
- Why did I not know "Inside Men?"
- Let's go.
- Let's do a cheer.
- We got this.
Get ready. Go.
(The fourth question is revealed.)
(The ones that live for tomorrow die
by the hand...)
(of those living for today.)
(The scene where he shaves his head)
- I see.
- He got it.
I see. What famous line is there?
"I'm the mister."
"The ones that live for today
don't know about tomorrow."
Is it this one? What was it?
"The ones that live for today
worry about nothing."
"But those who live for tomorrow
have no worries."
What was it?
"The ones that live for today..."
"The ones that live for today
would worry about nothing."
"But those who live for tomorrow
would have a lot of worries."
Is it this?
(The answer is slightly different.)
"This is bulletproof glass."
Is it a bulletproof vest
or bulletproof glass?
- I don't know.
- Bulletproof glass.
You can't discuss with me.
"This is a bulletproof vest."
Is it glass?
- "This is bulletproof glass!"
- He can't remember.
"This is bulletproof glass!"
(Laughing)
"This is bulletproof glass."
(The way he said it
sounds like a eunuch.)
- "This is bulletproof glass."
- Tell him that's right.
"Those who live for tomorrow..."
"I live only for today."
"But those who live for tomorrow..."
"Those who live for tomorrow
would have a lot of thoughts."
"But I live only for today."
(The line changed again.)
"This is bulletproof glass."
- Gosh, what is this?
- "This is..."
- "This is bullet..."
- Do you not know this?
- It's driving me crazy.
- "This is bulletproof."
- Do you not know this?
- The line.
(Describing the scene
where they shot the gun)
Goodness, what a sight.
You must act it out.
You can't just mouth it.
You can't mouth it.
(It's a Korean movie.)
There are so many scenes
like that in a Korean movie.
Is it "Shiri?"
- Gosh.
- What is it?
What is that?
- Oh, my.
- What?
(Oh, that?)
- You got it, right?
- Of course.
There's a famous line from it?
I'm not sure.
You know, the one that starts
with, "I only live today."
"You probably have another day."
Oh, I got it. Okay.
"This glass is bulletproof!"
- "This glass is bulletproof!"
- "You see this?"
"This glass is bulletproof!"
Won Bin!
- "Ajeossi!"
- All right!
(The answer is "Ajeossi.")
All right!
You got me mouthing it, right?
That one was difficult.
(After Se Chan got the answer...)
(Last Question: "Squid Game")
(Okay!)
(A real squid describes
"Squid Game" with his body)
- "Squid Game!"
- All right!
All right!
- He's on a roll.
- He's so good.
He's good.
- Goodness, that was hard.
- What a bummer.
I should watch more Korean movies.
(Team Girl gives it a go next.)
(The music is being played.)
You can't hear anything at all.
- Are you ready?
- We can do it!
- Let's go!
- Ready, set, go!
("Parasite")
(The famous line:
"So you have plans.")
- Oh, it's this one.
- You can do this.
- Oh, I shouldn't tell them.
- Why did you tell them?
Why did you?
Thank you, Suk Jin.
You saw it?
You saw it? Darn it.
That was...
He's so funny.
What's wrong with him?
- I didn't think she'd see me.
- Ready.
I can't remember the line.
This is bad.
- Oh, the line...
- It's "So you have plans."
Why do you keep saying it?
- She didn't hear it.
- Oh, my. What's wrong with him?
She can't hear me.
(Remembering)
Jjapaguri!
- That one's more obvious.
- Jjapaguri?
Jjapaguri!
- She can't recall.
- As long as he doesn't tell.
- If he tells more, then it means...
- Jjapaguri.
That's not a line, though.
- It should be a line.
- It must be a line.
You add beef brisket
to it to make jjapaguri.
No, it's not about a recipe.
You should say it's famous line.
- You're sharing the recipe?
- You're not supposed to do that.
- You should say the famous line.
- Jjapaguri.
You should say something like,
"So you have plans."
- What's wrong with you?
- How can you tell the answer?
- She can't hear it anyway.
- Why do you keep showing off?
- She can't hear me.
- My gosh.
- Why does he keep showing off?
- "So you have plans."
Tell him to stop, seriously.
My gosh, Suk Jin.
What did I do?
You love showing off.
- Gosh, it's jjapaguri.
- Wait.
I bet she has no idea. She turned
without knowing the answer.
(What's the answer?)
- It must be frustrating.
- I can't think of any. Goodness.
- She should do the action.
- She doesn't know.
- Oh, the noodles?
- She shouldn't describe that.
- She should've done this.
- That's right.
- Come on! Stay still.
- Stop that.
What's wrong with you?
- She can't see us.
- What do you mean?
(She clearly saw them.)
The eyes?
She managed to see it.
Gosh, Suk Jin. Seriously!
It's impossible that she saw us.
- Of course she can see you.
- How so?
She can see you with her side eyes.
She has no idea what the answer is.
(I got it!)
- Oh, my.
- She figured it out.
It's all ruined because of Seok Sam.
- It was like that from the start.
- It's over.
I'm sure they don't know
the famous line.
You're talking about this, right?
Hold on.
How did she figure it out?
- You're the one who told them.
- You told them.
You told them.
- Even if I tell them...
- That's great.
"Ma'am! Make us jjapaguri!"
Jjapaguri!
- "Ma'am! Make us jjapaguri!"
- That's right.
What about it?
She has no idea.
Or it could be...
She should say something else,
like, "So you have plans."
- Stay quiet!
- What's wrong with you?
- They can't hear us.
- Put on their shirt and join them.
They can't hear us anyway.
"My husband is in the basement."
- I see.
- They can't hear us.
"Parasite!"
They got it.
(Thanks to Ja Yeon's clear
pronunciation, they got the answer.)
What is this?
Seriously... Come on.
- They heard us? They couldn't.
- Well done.
Next question.
Gosh, Seok Sam.
Didn't you give them too much time?
Get ready, set, go.
("Nameless Gangster:
Rules of the Time")
(Famous line: You see!
I had dinner with your boss!)
(Okay? We went to a sauna too!)
- This one is difficult.
- We went to a sauna too!
(He has many minions.)
That's great.
(She describes the main character
walking with his minions.)
"Do I have the face of a king?"
- That's it.
- She's impressive.
- The one where he appears.
- "Snowpiercer?"
- "Do I have the face of a king?"
(She knows it.)
- She doesn't know.
- Oh, I can't remember the title.
Yes. As long as you don't get it.
- You don't have to remember it.
- It's this one.
"You punk!"
"You live in Namyeong-dong, right?"
- "I go to sauna with your dad too!"
- "You punk!"
- "Okay? You punk!"
"I went to your school too!"
- Why would he go to their school?
- Choi Min Sik?
Choi Min Sik.
The movie, "Nameless..."
"Nameless Friend."
"Nameless Friend" sounds fun.
I don't like "Nameless Crimes."
(Actress Choi is doing her best
to act it out.)
(Oh, that!)
I got it.
They know it right away
because they're actresses.
- I know.
- I know. They know it.
- "You still got it!"
- See?
(You still got it!)
"Nameless Gangster."
(It's correct.)
It's so annoying.
I'm sorry, but let's have
Seo Yeon act it.
- Let them switch.
- Suk Jin...
I find this kind of behavior absurd.
He told them all the answers,
but now that they get it...
Why did you get it so well?
You just need to keep your eye
on him. You'll get it fast.
- Just look at his mouth.
- Is that so?
- Then we'd be tied.
- We're tied?
Let's start with the last question.
Ready, go.
("Architecture 101")
This one is hard.
(How will she act out
"Architecture 101?")
Oh, it's this one.
But the action itself is hard.
- But this is...
- There's no famous act.
How can you act it out?
- There is one.
- There is.
- The one that Cho Jung Seok did.
("Rub it. Rub it hard.")
That's right.
That's it.
I'm sure they'll get it for sure.
- Do you get it?
- "Breathless."
You're doing well.
Oh, I get it.
I can't remember the title.
- "Breathless."
- You know it?
Oh, I see. She knows it.
"Architecture 101."
- No way.
- "Architecture 101."
No way. She knows everything.
- She knows a lot of movies.
- You should know the famous lines.
But this isn't allowed on public TV.
Can I still do it?
- Try it.
- It's one of the acts.
I'm sure they'll censor it.
"Rub it hard!"
- No, only words are allowed!
- "Rub it hard!"
(No actions!)
- Hey!
- Only words are allowed!
You can only say the words.
What's wrong with you?
Just say the words.
- I mean...
- The tongue...
A snake.
- Look at her.
- "Rub it hard."
It's allowed. The line exists.
- It's a famous line.
- It's hilarious.
"Rub it hard." You got it, right?
She's good.
- She's good.
- She's good!
- Seo Yeon is good.
You've never kissed anyone, right?
The tongues rub each other
super hard like snakes.
They rub hard.
They just...
That's right. It's hilarious!
- That's the line!
- They rub hard.
- She's good.
- That's the line.
- I get it now.
- Ji Hyo shouldn't have seen it.
- Right.
A fly?
That's right. She got the fly part.
- "Breathless" by Yang Ik Joon.
- They got it!
"Breathless" by Yang Ik Joon.
Ji Hyo didn't see
Seo Yeon's detailed acting.
Ji Hyo doesn't know this part.
I see!
- I got it!
- She just got it.
- You can't mouth it.
- A fly?
- A bird?
(Why would you rub your hands?)
- My gosh.
- But it's a fly.
Why is she doing that?
- Are her hands cold?
- Why did she say she got it?
- She's doing it.
- What's with her?
- She has no idea.
- She's acting out a fly.
She must've thought
it was "Breathless."
You need to move on.
- Turn her.
- You're running out of time.
This won't be fun
if you act like that.
Begging as if your life
depends on it!
Don't tell me the answer.
- Begging.
- No, tell it to her.
You thought wrong.
But Yeo Jin might get it.
A bird. A fly? A bird?
- Finish it.
- What's the answer?
- Tell us the answer.
- Five, four, three,
- It was fun.
- Is it a Korean movie?
- two,
- one.
- Tell us the answer.
- "A Fly?"
- "A Fly."
- There's no such movie.
- "Lovers in Paris."
- Seo Jin did well, though.
- Is that the answer?
- It's "Architecture 101."
- What?
It's "Architecture 101."
What does a fly have to do with it?
- But Ji Hyo knew...
- Cho Jeong Seok's character...
But Ji Hyo knew,
but it became "Breathless" with her.
- This acting...
- Oh, Cho Jeong Seok's character?
The kissing scene.
"Rub it hard."
Your scores are tied.
- We're tied?
- Yes. Since it's tied,
- Since it's tied.
- let's play one more time.
- Okay.
- It's about time you'll be hungry.
Let's have lunch first.
The female members will eat inside,
and the male members
will eat outside.
- Good.
- You can go around to ask.
All right.
I think it'll be something good.
Let's distribute the coins first.
How shall we distribute them?
Let's distribute them randomly.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
If we do, they'll be so confused.
There'll be no strategy.
- Or a winner...
- Point them.
can give out the coins.
Only one of us can do that.
- Then we won't know for real.
- He'll distribute them?
Yes, he will.
Just the winner
will distribute them?
Okay. It's up to him?
- Even we won't know.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Darn it.
- It's us.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Oh, no.
- This is fun.
- I want to lose.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Darn it.
- You go and distribute them.
- We won't know.
- We'll be eating.
- We'll have no idea.
- I should go eat.
- Only you will know.
- Gosh, I get to distribute them?
- Yes.
(Only Jong Kook will be able
to distribute the coins.)
My gosh.
I should go eat.
My, what's this?
My gosh, it's been a while.
- It looks good.
- Rice will be so good with this.
(A buffet of canned meals
makes a nice feast for the holiday.)
It looks delicious.
My kids love this.
Thank you for the food.
(They begin eating together.)
(What?)
(My goodness.)
(Middle-aged men describe the taste
in a strange way.)
It's really tasty.
(They have a hearty lunch
for the first time in a long while.)
I usually don't eat this much.
(Jong Kook joined them
after finishing up the task.)
- You don't need a sauce.
- You should eat this.
You should eat this.
- Good.
- It's so tasty.
It's so tasty.
What's this?
Haha.
Please put one in my bag.
(Se Chan loves canned meat.)
(He tries to smuggle it.)
They will have to interrogate you
if they want to know the truth.
(They forgot about the interrogation
since they were busy eating.)
Jae Suk, you have been summoned
to the interrogation room.
- Speak the truth.
- When you receive them...
- Jong Kook, you are up.
- Me?
(Jae Suk and Jong Kook
get summoned to Room of Truth.)
- We outsourced the task.
- Right?
Someone else distributed the coins.
- We don't know what he did.
- Someone distributed them.
You must be nervous.
You are shaking your legs.
- It means you are lying.
- I am not lying. It's the truth.
(Team Girl's interrogation ends.)
- What's this?
- Tell us who you want...
to interrogate in person.
- We don't need that.
- We will go with our hunch.
Let's go with our hunch.
- Okay.
- Hold on. I have an idea.
Let's decide by flipping a coin.
- Shall we do that?
- Someone we picked earlier...
- or...
- Let's do this instead.
Let's write down the 5 names
and pick 2 at random.
- What do you think?
- Okay.
- Shall we have a draw?
- Let's have our luck decide.
- We have no way of knowing.
- It's impossible.
- Seo Yeon, Ji Hyo, Ja Yeon...
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
It's the people
who picked earlier, right?
You and Ok Ja.
Ja Yeon?
You can't meet my eyes.
Okay. You got caught.
I think it really is them.
Ja Yeon and Ok Ja.
Hold on.
Ok Ja is Ja Yeon.
- Ok Ja and Ji Hyo.
- Aren't Ok Ja and Ja Yeon the same?
I think it really is
Ok Ja and Ji Hyo.
Okay. Let's go.
- Okay.
- Let's have a draw.
- Throw them in the air.
- Let's ask them to pick.
- Hey.
- So Min.
- Pick one.
- So Min, pick 2.
- Pick 1.
We will pick those people.
- Two.
- Okay. Give them to me.
Give them to me.
- Who are they?
- So Min.
(The result is So Min and...)
- It isn't So Min.
- Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
- No.
- They don't have the coins.
- Just go with them.
- Come on.
- They don't have the coins.
- Let's exclude the two of them.
- Exclude them.
They don't have the coins.
Listen to me.
- I think it's So Min.
- There is no way she has the coins.
- Just go with the two of them.
- They don't have the coins.
- We agreed to do that.
- Let's pick two ourselves.
Why did you make her pick two?
- Why did you make her pick two?
- Seriously.
- Ji Hyo and Ok Ja.
- Here. Pick two.
- I will pick 1.
- Here. Pick 1.
Let's see.
- Seo Yeon.
- Ja Yeon.
- I am sorry, but...
(Seo Yeon and Ja Yeon?)
I am sorry, but you will keep going
until you get what you want.
- This won't end.
- Whose names do you want?
You will keep going
until you get what you want.
We should go with the first picks.
I am telling you
that they don't have the coins.
- Let's go with So Min and Yeo Jin.
- Really?
- I don't think that's right.
- It isn't So Min.
Pick Ok Ja and Yeo Jin.
One of them has the coins.
- Pick two.
- Again?
(They pick the names again.)
This isn't random at all.
Team Girl will send the members
to the Judgment Stand first.
- We have no idea.
- Seriously.
We don't even know
how many people have the coins.
We pick...
- Jae Suk and Se Chan.
- Se Chan.
(Jae Suk and Se Chan)
- Okay. Go up there.
- Okay.
- We don't know.
- We really don't know.
Why did you pick the two of them?
I think the older members
are dissatisfied...
with their protruding mouths.
Come to think of it,
both of them have protruding mouths.
They don't like protruding mouths.
We really have no idea.
They picked the two...
- with protruding mouths.
- Right?
Jae Suk and Se Chan,
open your notebooks...
- on the count of three.
- Okay.
- We don't know.
- I am curious.
One,
two,
three.
One, two, three.
- Do you have coins?
- Se Chan has them.
- What?
- Hold on.
Se Chan has them.
- Jae Suk has them too!
- They have coins.
- What?
- How did this happen?
Why did you give me coins?
(Jae Suk has 5 coins.)
I have four coins.
(Se Chan has 4 coins.)
- Why did you give me coins?
- How...
I gave most of the coins
to the two of them.
I gave one to myself.
How many is it?
(They got 9 out of 10 coins.)
Jae Suk had 5 coins
and Se Chan had 4 coins.
Team Girl acquired nine coins.
(Team Girl gets ahead
by studying the faces.)
I picked you guys at random.
How did they do that?
- It's our turn.
- Let's pick well.
Ja Yeon, go up.
- Ja Yeon has to go up.
- Ja Yeon.
- Seo Yeon, go up.
- Go up.
- She doesn't want to do it.
- Ja Yeon and Seo Yeon.
I think they are feigning...
- anxiety.
- Yeo Jin.
Let's do Yeo Jin.
Yeo Jin is looking at us.
- I think it's Yeo Jin.
- She doesn't have coins.
- I am poor.
- It might be So Min.
- Those two have coins.
They went up the stand too quickly.
- But...
- Did you make up your mind?
Not yet.
We will pick So Min
instead of Seo Yeon.
So Min?
So Min, go up the stand...
- while taking Yeo Jin's hand.
- Go up there.
- What?
- Yeo Jin, go up the stand.
- Me?
My goodness. You have no intuition.
- See? She is suspicious.
- What?
- All right. Let's go with them.
- It's them.
Yeo Jin has coins.
So Min and Yeo Jin have coins.
Yeo Jin behaved strangely.
- "You have no intuition."
- Yes. She is suspicious.
- Yeo Jin and So Min. Let's go.
- It was a useless comment.
- It wasn't a useless comment.
- Yes, it was.
I think she was just being
easygoing.
- Let's just go with them.
- Let's go.
- Let's go with them.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Let's see.
- No regrets. We picked together.
- Yes.
- One,
- Yeo Jin has coins.
- two, three.
(Yeo Jin and So Min's notebooks
get revealed.)
Three.
One, two, three.
- So Min has a lot.
- I have coins.
- She has coins.
I do.
(So Min has 6 coins!)
We got all of them!
- We got all of them!
- Take them!
We got all of them! No way!
- I told you so. She was suspicious.
- Yeo Jin.
We got them.
- It was a useless comment.
- We did it.
You have no intuition.
You found all ten coins.
- You had no luck.
- You found all ten coins.
- Okay.
- All right.
- We caught them both.
We caught them both.
- We got them.
- We won.
- Unbelievable. They found nine.
How did we pick the two of them?
- No way.
- Interrogation is meaningless.
- It was insane.
- No way.
Let's pick at random
the next time too.
- That's right.
- We never picked at random.
- Picking at random is the way.
- We picked at random just now.
- That was how we got them.
- That's right.
- Seriously.
- They are so annoying.
The last mission of the way...
involves going on an intense journey
to find an answer.
It's Go the Distance to Answer.
For a balance
of strength and stamina,
three Team Girl members
and two Team Boy members will play.
Okay.
All players will start
at the bottom.
(All players will start
at the bottom.)
They will go up the soapy slope,
arrive at the quiz zone on the left,
and sit down on the answer.
- Jae Suk and Jong Kook.
- That's right.
The quiz involves identifying
the people in the photo.
You will see a morphed image
of three people.
Sit down on the number
of a person who is in the photo.
- Three people.
- A morphed image of three people.
(Sit down on the number
of a person who is in the photo.)
- Se Chan and Jong Kook should go.
- I have good eyes.
There are 3 correct answers
and 2 incorrect answers,
so picking a number first
will give you an advantage.
The team will receive a point
for every correct answer.
The team that acquires more points
will win.
- Let's get ready.
- Okay.
- So we sit down on the answer.
- That's right.
- Okay.
- We need to go up there quickly.
We can have a scuffle, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Excuse me?
- What?
- Don't be rude to a big sister.
- I was just dancing.
- Right?
This is nuts.
Let's do this. Roar.
Those who will enter Round One...
should stand at the starting line.
- Suk Jin and I will go.
- Okay.
This is no joke.
- My goodness.
- Yeo Jin, Ja Yeon, and...
Those three?
It's so slippery.
It will be impossible to go up.
- We can't go up.
- It will be impossible to go up.
We can't go up.
- A run-up wouldn't help.
- It's really slippery.
- Listen.
- We have done it before.
- We need to work together.
- Se Chan.
- We need to push each other.
The middle one is the longest.
Are we going against these three?
- See? It's impossible.
- How will we go up?
- My goodness.
We have to get
the middle rope first.
They are sprinkling
more soapy water.
- Come here.
- I can't even get close to it.
Ji Hyo and I will hold them back.
Grab the middle rope at all costs...
- and pull us up.
- Okay.
- All of us need to go up.
- Go up...
and give Ja Yeon a hand.
Okay. Let's go.
The round will begin
when I blow the whistle.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Okay.
Who is it?
You need to see it first.
- Who are they?
- Don't you recognize the faces?
- I don't.
(Cho Bo Ah, Han Ji Min,
Chun Woo Hee,)
(Han Ye Seul, Park Min Young)
(They need to guess 3 people
in the morphed image.)
- Just go.
- Who are they?
- Han Ji Min.
Han Ji Min, Chun Woo Hee,
and Park Min Young.
- Let's go up first.
- Is Min Young in there?
(They begin to climb up the slope.)
- Who else?
- This is impossible.
- Let's go up first. Hey.
- Step on me.
Hold on.
- Hey.
- Good.
(Jae Suk charges forward
while Team Girl members are busy.)
(He gets pulled back down.)
- All of us will fail.
- How are we supposed to go up?
All of us will fail.
(She marks Suk Jin.)
is there no way to go up?
(While everyone is looking
for a way to go up)
- I don't think Bo Ah is there.
- Ye Seul.
- No. Min Young isn't there.
- Woo Hee isn't there.
- Woo Hee might be there.
- Ye Seul is.
- I think Woo Hee is there.
- Ye Seul is definitely there.
- Ye Seul.
- Ji Min.
- Look at Jae Suk.
- Ye Seul is the most prominent.
- That's the best way, right?
- That's the best way.
That's the best way, right?
- What are you doing?
You can't come up this way.
You can't do that, Yeo Jin.
Yeo Jin, you can't do that.
- It's so slippery.
- Yeo Jin, you can't do that.
(She attempts to play dirty.)
Be careful.
(Suk Jin climbs up the slope
by holding on to a bar.)
That old man.
What are you doing?
You can't come up this way.
- How did you go up that far?
- I am going up.
(Suk Jin runs away...)
(and Ja Yeon chases after him.)
- Yeo Jin.
- I have no idea.
(At that moment!)
- Jae Suk grabbed a rope.
- Good.
- Jae Suk.
- Ji Min.
Ji Min and Ye Seul are there.
- Okay.
- Ye Seul and Ji Min.
- Ye Seul.
- Push off Ok Ja.
Okay.
- Let's go.
- Who?
- No way.
- She is really strong.
- No.
- Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk, come back. Yeo Jin.
- You need to come back.
- No.
- You need to ignore him.
(The determined tiger moth
has arrived.)
- Let's go.
- Push her down.
Yeo Jin, grab him.
Nice.
(The tiger moth is out.)
- Suk Jin!
- Gosh!
No!
(Slipping)
I will get rid of Ok Ja.
- Hold his hand.
- Ok Ja.
Jae Suk, you might fall down
as well.
Get rid of Ok Ja.
- Climb up.
- Hold on.
- Come here.
- Hold his hand.
- Hold on.
- A rope.
- Give me a rope.
- She is so strong.
- A rope!
- She has so much stamina.
(A rope!)
- Suk Jin, you need to come up.
- A rope!
(The old man is hanging on
by his toes.)
A rope!
It will be meaningless
if you don't come.
Jae Suk, just sit down.
(Slipping)
For goodness' sake.
(His toes couldn't hold on.)
- Suk Jin is useless.
- Hold them.
- Suk Jin, hurry up.
- There you go.
(He begins the tearful climb again.)
(Jae Suk is struggling
against two tiger moths.)
Yeo Jin! They are no joke.
(The two of them are formidable.)
I warned you about Ok Ja.
- Hey.
- She is no joke.
- There is craziness in her eyes.
- Ok Ja.
(The game changer with crazy eyes)
Jae Suk, you need to grab a pole.
(Jae Suk can't win against them.)
- That's so funny.
- You need to grab a pole.
Suk Jin, hurry up.
(Panting)
I am holding on.
(The old hiker is having
a difficult fight by himself.)
(He finally manages to arrive
at the railing.)
(Breathing hard)
- That's so funny.
- You need to grab a pole.
- I am coming.
- Suk Jin, hurry up.
(He arrived at the top
while no one was looking.)
You need to push Ja Yeon
down the slope.
She is taller than me.
- My goodness.
- She grabbed a rope.
- Ja Yeon and Yeo Jin...
- Let's go.
- Come on.
- Are you grabbing a rope?
(Getting ready solemnly
while holding a rope)
(Breathing hard)
(They are having
a 1-on-1 match too.)
Hey. Go down. Okay.
Give me a rope.
- Ok Ja is cool.
Hold on.
What is Ji Hyo doing?
Ji Hyo, what are you doing?
(One member is still at the bottom.)
(From now on)
(You will lose a smile)
(Look at this steep path)
I think Ji Hyo is filming
a separate show.
She can't go up the slope.
It isn't easy.
Look at this steep path
- Okay. I got her.
- You are cool.
(He jumps to the rope.)
- That's my rope.
- What?
No!
Okay. I got her.
- That's my rope.
- What?
(He grabbed Suk Jin's lifeline.)
- That's my rope.
- What?
- No!
(That's my rope.)
- Oh, yes.
- Ji Hyo.
- Why were you holding it?
- Grab the rope.
Ji Hyo, hurry up and come here.
Just sit down.
- Where?
- Just sit down.
- Everyone needs to go up anyway.
- Don't worry about me.
- Everyone needs to sit down.
Just sit down.
It won't end until she gets here.
- Let's sit down.
- It won't end until she gets here.
Ji Min.
Ji Min and Ye Seul.
Two, four, and five.
- I don't know the last one.
- Me neither.
- Ji Hyo, come on.
- I think it's Woo Hee.
- Where?
- Two and four.
- Suk Jin.
- Hurry up. I don't know one.
- Two.
(Ja Yeon changes her mind
from number 3 to number 5.)
I don't know the last one.
- Suk Jin, what's your number?
- I sat here.
- Two?
- Three.
- The answers are...
- That might be correct.
- I sat here.
- Three.
(What are the correct answers?)
The answers are 2, 3, and 4.
- We got them right.
- I knew Woo Hee was there.
The answers are 2, 3, and 4.
- We got lucky.
(Yeo Jin, Suk Jin,
and Jae Suk were correct!)
(They changed the seats
at the very end.)
Team Girl got 1 point
and Team Boy got 2 points.
- Hey.
These two are no joke.
- They are no joke.
- Seriously.
- They are so strong.
- Haha and Se Chan.
- I will go with Se Chan.
Haha, mark Seo Yeon.
(The two little men
were confident at first.)
This is hard.
(But tiger moths pulled them down.)
Get Seo Yeon.
(Meanwhile, the oldest member
reaches the top easily.)
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- What are those punks doing?
- Hold on.
- What are you doing?
- What's up with her?
- She is too strong.
- Hey.
- Sit down.
The answers are 3, 4, and 5.
(Team Girl gets
all the correct answers.)
- Really?
- My goodness.
- The last game ended.
- Okay.
The combined points...
- made Team Girl the winner.
- Why?
- Oh, yes.
- Yes.
You will get ten coins each,
- so distribute them as you want.
- Okay.
You will pick the two members
one last time.
- That's a good idea.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Let's use the same strategy.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Thank you.
We should leave it to one person.
- That's right.
- One person?
- We should do that.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- No.
- It's correct.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- I won.
- Who won?
- Suk Jin.
- Go with your instincts.
I will distribute the coins.
Give them to me.
I just need to write it down, right?
- The loser should do it.
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Gosh.
(Ja Yeon got chosen.)
It happened in one go.
(All the coins go to Ja Yeon!)
Here.
I will take care of them.
- He will take care of them.
- I will take care of them.
- Good luck.
- Excuse me.
Two Team Boy members
will go up the stand first.
- We have no idea.
- Please pick two.
You can ask us questions.
We don't know anything.
Why would you say that?
- He wants a close-up shot.
- He has a condition.
- Ask away.
- It's nice that we don't know.
Right? We don't know.
I don't know anything either.
Let's pick one member
using our hunches.
- My hunch tells me it's Suk Jin.
- We need to pick two.
- Could it be Haha?
- Suk Jin.
- We need to pick two.
In that case,
the other one will be...
Let's pick Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Who else?
- Suk Jin.
- Me?
- Okay.
- You don't know, right?
- I really don't know.
- Suk Jin and Jong Kook.
- Take your bag.
- You need your bag.
- Don't tell me you know.
- I don't know.
- I think he knows.
- I think he has coins.
- You look flustered.
- Suk Jin.
You look flustered. Am I wrong?
- It's not like that.
- Your face turned red.
Maybe Suk Jin has all the coins.
Seriously.
- All right.
- Are they your choices?
- Yes.
- Suk Jin makes me anxious,
- Now,
Jong Kook and Suk Jin,
- hold up your notebooks.
- I am anxious.
Open them on the count of three.
To be honest, I mixed them up
without thinking.
- Does Suk Jin have coins?
- One, two...
- Let me give you another chance.
- No, thank you.
You have coins, right?
- One, two...
- You have coins, right?
- Let me give you another chance.
- No, thank you.
- One, two, three.
- Suk Jin knows.
(What will be the result?)
(They don't have any coins.)
(0 coins)
- Who has them?
- Jae Suk.
- Really?
- I don't have them either.
This is how you make a bet.
- Okay.
- It was a war of nerves.
I mixed them up without thinking,
- but I saw the name...
- Bang!
- as I put in the coins.
- Really?
All right.
- Thank goodness.
- Now, Team Boy,
please pick one Team Girl member.
- I gave them to many members.
- Just one.
We went all in.
(Unlike Team Boy,)
(Ja Yeon distributed the coins
to multiple members.)
I really hope things go
as I planned.
Please look this way.
- Let's do this.
- Team Girl is leading...
by two coins.
- We...
- We just need to find the coins.
You need to find two or more coins.
- Cut us some slack...
- We just need to get one.
- Just one.
- Let's have a draw.
- Seriously.
- Let's not redo it.
- For real.
- We are picking only one.
- Only one.
- Who is it?
- Are you stupid?
- Go with it.
- Who is it?
- Go with it. Just go with it.
- Go with Yeo Jin.
- Just go.
Let's do that.
- Just go with it. What we got...
- Choi Yeo Jin.
(What they draw is Choi Yeo Jin.)
- All right. Let's go with it.
(Yeo Jin gets on Judgment Stand.)
- My goodness.
- We have no choice.
- Just go.
- Look at Ja Yeon's face.
- Let's just go with it.
- That's it.
(Ja Yeon has a mysterious look
on her face.)
Ja Yeon seems relaxed.
- Me?
- Please go on the stand.
- I think it's Ja Yeon.
- My gosh.
Yeo Jin, show us your coins
as I count to three.
Please. It has to be her.
Choi Yeo Jin!
- It's not Yeo Jin.
- Yes. One person.
- Can she go down?
- No.
- The light is on.
- Let's just do this.
Just go with her. We have no choice.
- It must be Seo Yeon.
- We can't be sure.
- Right.
- It's Seo Yeon.
Now...
- One, two, three.
- Look at her smile.
- We have no choice.
- She should have two or more.
(If Yeo Jin has 3 coins or more,
Team Boy can turn the table around.)
- Three.
- Ta-da.
(She has 1 coin.)
One.
(She has only 1 coin!)
- One?
- One.
- The difference is only one coin.
- Right.
It's only one coin.
(Team Boy failed to turn the table
around because of 1 coin.)
Just one.
- Ta-da.
- How many does Seo Yeon have?
So the final score is 16 to 15.
Team Girl wins.
- What about Seo Yeon?
- Yes!
She should have two or more.
The three guests
who lead their team to victory...
will get the prize.
Please bring in the prize.
This is all about good luck.
- My gosh.
- That's amazing.
- What's that?
- My gosh.
- Abalone?
- Abalone is in season now.
- So we got you some abalones.
- It's abalone.
(It's a gift for the tiger moths
who tried their best today.)
- That's nice.
- Team Girl...
gathered 16 coins today.
You can change three coins
into one penalty sticker.
So Team Girl gets...
- five penalty stickers.
- That's a lot.
Come here and change them.
- What about us?
- We don't get any?
- Because we lost?
- We can put them on anyone we want?
They will give us
the penalty stickers?
Yes. They can put the stickers
on the members they want.
- We should be nice to them.
- I don't know.
If I act silly now,
they will pick me.
I have a lot of stickers.
It will be fun
to give him more stickers.
I got four stickers last week.
- It was last week.
- To only one person?
It will be fun to give
Haha more stickers.
- Go ahead and do it.
- I have only one.
Okay.
- So this is...
- When does this end?
- Next week.
- It will end next week.
- We have only one week left.
- It won't be fun...
- if you give them to one person.
- Whatever Penalty Project.
- Jae Suk and...
- I don't think they will do that.
Jae Suk and Se Chan have none.
That's just ridiculous.
- Se Chan has nothing.
- Let's have the guests decide.
Actually, considering
the average number,
I think Se Chan needs some.
(Let's give
all the stickers to Se Chan.)
Let's give
all the stickers to Se Chan.
But why?
Because...
- this is not fun.
- And you were...
- Why not?
- being annoying today.
- Jae Suk also has zero stickers.
- Jae Suk.
- You were very annoying.
- Boombastic.
Jae Suk has none.
Se Chan was annoying,
so I'll give it to Se Chan.
- Just wait.
- Let's give them all to Se Chan.
No, don't say that.
- What's with her?
- You got two.
(Startled)
- We just met.
- She's...
What do you mean?
We did many TV shows together.
But why would you...
- Se Chan, you're...
- Why is she being like this?
- Don't do that.
- He's so annoying.
- This is surprising.
- Things have been so easy for you.
Ja Yeon, you're next.
I'll follow their opinion.
- Good.
- What's wrong with her?
(Yang Se Chan gets all the votes.)
Do you know me? What's with you?
- What's with her?
- Pick Jae Suk.
- Right. So Min is...
- Jae Suk has nothing.
Jae Suk has no stickers.
(Nervous)
If you pick me,
there will be a war next week.
- Think carefully.
- Think of what you did to me today.
- You were being so annoying.
- Seriously, why would you do that?
(An expressway to the penalty)
- Jae Suk has nothing.
- You can come from behind and win.
Seriously?
- Seo Yeon.
- We have one person left.
- We've never met before.
- Just go with Se Chan.
- What do I do?
- Pick Jae Suk.
You should let him win.
- Are you done?
- It's four to four.
Give Jae Suk one.
Seo Yeon is acquainted with Haha.
Then... Gosh.
- It's Seo Yeon's turn.
- Hey.
You're not supposed
to pick your acquaintance.
This has nothing to do with that.
- Seo Yeon is close to Haha.
- They think this is a prize.
- No.
- You two are close.
- We need a balance here.
- My gosh.
- What should I do to make it fun?
- Let him take the lead.
- But...
- You get more stickers next week?
- Yes.
- We will. We still have chances.
- But there won't be a lot.
- There will be more.
- Jae Suk needs one though.
- He needs a sticker.
We can't be sure
there will be five stickers.
- Seo Yeon, isn't this interesting?
- Jae Suk...
Don't you want to make it
more interesting?
- Five in a row.
- It will be interesting.
- All the stickers...
- You know what?
It's more interesting
when it's neck and neck.
- Exactly.
- Right.
- What?
- That's...
- Ji Suk Jin?
- That's a good idea.
He will be the next big thing.
- Good job.
That's not a bad idea.
This is plausible.
- Make it a three-cornered fight.
- I'll...
I want Suk Jin
to be on TV for a long time.
Right. He'd love that.
That's right!
- I think this is better.
- That's right!
(She chooses Ji Suk Jin.)
She's really good.
- A good choice.
- Nice.
What about Jae Suk?
He got four stickers today.
- What's this?
- Look at this.
Yeo Jin.
Today's race is over now.
- Thank you, everyone.
- Thank you.
We will give
more stickers next week.
(Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Jong Kook,
Haha, Ji Hyo, Se Chan, So Min)
(The finale of the penalty project
with the scenery of fall)
(It's a gourmet trip to Gangwon
Province, the land of plenty.)
- Hello.
- Let's dance.
(There could've been a trip,)
(but it's suddenly changed
to My Heart in Gangwon Province.)
(The worst penalties are
finally revealed.)
(Even the heavy rain
can't stop the battle.)
(They have to bet their everything.)
(Apologize to your parents.)
(With the Olympic spirit
of Gangwon Province,)
(they will have the final race
of the Whatever Penalty Project.)
(They want to avoid the penalty
at all costs.)
(And the race is overheating.)
(Yoo Jae Suk
Specialty: Playing pranks)
(Kim Jong Kook, Specialty: Bluffing
Jeon So Min, Specialty: Daydreaming)
(Song Ji Hyo Specialty:
Abnormal behavior)
(Ji Suk Jin Specialty: Yelling)
(Yang Se Chan, Specialty: Empty head
Haha, Specialty: Throwing a tantrum)
(We Want to Go to Gangwon)