Hello.
- Let's go in.
- Haha.
- Hello.
- You look cute today.
Are you wearing modern hanbok?
So Min, you came early.
- You've been waiting.
- Hello.
Hello, Buddhist monk.
- Welcome.
- Hello, Buddhist monk.
(Buddhist Monk Dong Hoon
at Running Temple)
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Your mind is water,
and water is your mind.
What does that mean?
- May you attain Buddhahood.
- Nice to meet you.
You've come a long way.
- Yes.
- All right.
Can we have some tea?
What is she doing?
(So Min makes a deep bow all of a sudden.)
(She even turns her palm up.)
Is this what you're supposed to do?
(She came to the temple
to treat her craziness.)
- So Min is good.
- Hello.
- I guess you're new here.
- You're here.
- Yes.
Hello, Yoo Jae Suk.
You are back after your ascetic practice.
Yes.
Do you even know what ascetic practice is?
I have no idea.
I'm Christian.
(I'm Christian.)
(A surprising twist
about Buddhist Monk Ha)
- Your mother is a minister.
- Right.
He is Christian.
I'm sorry, but I'm a deacon.
I'm a deacon.
(He practices religion somewhere else.)
I see.
Suk Jin has good news.
- That's right.
- It's the music charts.
He topped the music charts.
- I love the song.
- As soon as he arrived...
- He's the producer.
- As soon as he got here,
when the assistant
directors didn't even ask,
"I topped the music charts."
No one asked.
"We topped the charts."
- He called me at 10 p.m. yesterday.
- No one even asked.
- At 10 p.m.
- Really?
He sounded quite serious.
- "Jae Suk."
- Did he sound urgent?
"Yes?"
"Did you check the charts?"
(Suk Jin last night:
"Did you check the charts?")
- When you didn't even ask?
- Did he say that?
Hey.
- Why would you bring that up?
- Seriously?
- At 10 p.m.
- Was it that urgent?
I was going to the gym
after checking the charts.
- My gosh.
- I'm so happy for you.
- Congratulations, Suk Jin.
- This is great.
When you were on "How Do You Play?"
you got to show the process...
- of making the song.
- Right. It was a good promotion.
But this wasn't the case. You
promoted the song only on our show.
- That's right.
- We hardly promoted the song.
- Running Man made it popular.
- That's amazing.
- Is it because of Running Man?
- But...
the YouTube channel of
"How Do You Play?" introduced the song.
- It did?
- Yes.
We introduced it a little.
You're an investment genius.
- That's not true.
- Hang on.
- You made a profit.
You keep trying to give
"How Do You Play?" credit for that.
You keep saying that.
You should step up.
- You're right.
- What can I say?
Running Man did the same thing.
- I mean...
- I'm grateful to Running Man.
I was trying to give
Running Man credit for that.
I thought Running Man
made the song popular.
But he suddenly said that
"How Do You Play?" helped too.
- But it's my opinion that counts.
- Of course.
- I'm more grateful to Running Man.
- Exactly.
I'm serious.
- Nice.
- I'm thankful to Running Man.
You played the entire song
during the opening.
Seriously, I even called
Bo Pil to thank him.
- You can't say that.
- Let's not pick sides.
Your new song was released at 6 p.m.
And our YouTube channel posted it...
- at 6 p.m. as well.
- Hang on.
Stop talking about it.
- Can't we just talk about our show?
- Let's just go with this.
Why do you keep talking about it
when no one knows?
Let me tell you one thing.
Let's fight.
The 2 of us are being criticized
on the 2 shows every week.
- I don't know what to do.
- You should just...
- stay quiet.
- Okay.
Jong Kook, Producer Park Chang Hoon
was born in 1977.
Really? He is a year younger than me.
(Really? He is a year younger than me.)
He should be aware of my power.
He does sound polite
when he talks about you.
He should know about me.
- He's from Anyang.
- We have another news.
Our captain attended the staff meeting.
- Congratulations.
- You're the captain.
That's right.
- He is the captain.
- Let me tell you...
how I felt at the meeting.
- There was nothing special.
- What did you do?
They just let me sit in the center.
(February 24, 2:00 p.m.,
SBS Running Man Meeting Room)
(Running Man's captain, Ji Suk Jin)
Gosh, this is...
Hello.
(Captain Ji enters.)
It says captain here.
- Who drew this?
- Yeon Ju did.
Yeon Ju, you're very talented.
Do you know who Yeon Ju is?
Hey, Yeon Ju... She's our writer.
(Writer Lee Yeon Ju has been
working on Running Man for 3 years.)
She must be our writer.
Thank you, Yeon Ju.
I feel really uncomfortable in this seat.
Next week, we will have...
Cha Jun Hwan.
- Is Cha Jun Hwan joining us?
- Yes.
- That's great.
- And Jin Ji Hee.
Jin Ji Hee?
What are they going to do?
(The first meeting is
off to a rocky start.)
You know what?
I thought about this meeting last night.
I gave serious thought
to the future of Running Man.
It's been 12 years. So I had this thought.
Whatever Running Man does
is what Running Man is.
Everything we do is Running Man.
I thought about it.
(That's how the captain started
talking about his philosophy.)
Here's what I thought.
We should find
what we don't have on Running Man.
What is it we don't have?
What do you think?
Yeon Ju, what do you think we don't have?
The writers of Running Man
need to take a break.
Everything we do is like a joke.
Right? It's just like a joke.
You should let us take care of it.
You don't have to come up
with new games every time.
Don't you think so?
We don't have to...
- play games every time.
- Right.
- Then what do we do?
- Like what?
We should think about it now.
(We should think about it now.)
(The meaningless meeting will be
revealed on our YouTube channel.)
So did you give your opinion?
Of course I did.
- What do we have for lunch today?
- Did you come up with a new idea?
What are we having for lunch?
- Lunch?
- Are we having lamb?
Well...
- You can look forward to it.
- You will be surprised.
- Really?
- What is it?
- Do we get our own lunch?
You should look forward to it.
Is it tteokbokki?
- It can't be sashimi.
- It will be nice.
It's nothing bad.
It should be really delicious.
For your information, it is
my mom's favorite dish.
- Is it a box lunch?
- A box lunch?
- It is a box lunch.
- A box lunch by your mother-in-law?
I bring this when I visit my mom.
This is her favorite.
- Really?
- It's eel.
My gosh.
- What is it?
- It's eel.
My gosh.
- It's eel, right?
- Per serving...
(It's eel, right?)
Per serving...
He's 100 percent sure.
- I just...
- How did you know?
- I just know him so well.
- He knows a lot about Suk Jin.
I know everything about him.
- He knows everything.
- You are just like Suk Jin.
Does he study me or what?
Do you tell him everything about you?
- I like eels.
- How much do you tell him?
- I know everything.
- I like the menu.
- Where?
- He's really good at this.
There are only a limited number
of dishes Suk Jin can come up with.
- And it's an eel in most cases.
- That's his favorite.
- It's an eel.
- Is it that Jae Suk is good...
or that Suk Jin is simple?
- How did you know?
- How did he know that?
We will begin today's race then.
We have guests today.
I know.
I know. I read articles about it.
Here are today's guests.
Is Jun Hwan coming?
Jun Hwan and Ji Hee.
- He's the prince.
- I know.
I'm nervous.
(I'm nervous.)
- I'm nervous.
- Were you nervous in the Olympics?
It wasn't this bad.
(It wasn't this bad.)
(And...)
My female friends called me
when they heard he would come.
He turned out so well.
At the 2022 Beijing Winter Olympics,
he made new history
in men's figure skating.
He was amazing.
He's the figure prince, Cha Jun Hwan.
(Figure Prince Cha Jun Hwan)
- He's so cool.
- He's over there.
Where?
(He's over there.)
- Cha Jun Hwan.
- Jun Hwan.
(National figure skater, Cha Jun Hwan)
Welcome.
(The 2022 Beijing Winter Olympics)
(The figure prince flew up beautifully.)
(The best score in the Korean
history of men's figure skating)
- That was perfect.
- He did it so well.
He did it. I knew he would make it.
(Korea's national figure skater,
Cha Jun Hwan)
(The figure prince is on Running Man.)
He's grown a lot.
Hello.
- My goodness.
- Gosh.
Suk Jin really bothers me.
- He hugs him right away.
- My gosh.
He's the prince.
Hello.
(The figure prince gets a warm reception.)
He's the prince.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- He really bothers me.
- Look over there.
Let's take a photo together.
- Hang on.
- What?
When Jun Hwan came in...
Suk Jin.
- Look over here.
- When Jun Hwan came in...
- Do you know what he did?
- What did he do?
He was like...
What are you talking about?
I did that because
he reminds me of my son.
- He's not your son.
He is a year older than my son.
My son was born in 2002.
- You were born in 2001, right?
- Yes.
You're just like my son.
- Your son?
- What?
I just adore him.
- Your son?
- Did you say your son?
- Don't say that.
- I just adore him.
- He's a national hero.
- You shouldn't talk too casually.
- You just want to be with him.
- You don't hug...
even your own son like that.
You're not his dad.
He's the worst.
- You don't even hug Hyun Woo.
- That's true.
- I knew it.
- It's fake.
He's the figure prince.
We have Cha Jun Hwan here.
(Figure Prince Cha Jun Hwan)
(He shows a lousy jump
to imitate Jun Hwan.)
- That's not right.
- I just can't do it.
This is what Jun Hwan does.
- Ina Bauer.
- You just look like Yoo Hyeok.
Jun Hwan, please say hello to our viewers.
Hello. I'm Cha Jun Hwan, a figure skater.
- This is crazy.
- He's so cool.
He looks like a painting.
- This is nice.
- He's very tall in the flesh.
- I know.
- He's really handsome.
- So...
- He turned out so well.
Jun Hwan looked like
a young boy until just recently.
He still has the innocent charm,
- but now he looks like a grown man.
- I agree.
- He looks mature.
- He's like a cartoon character.
- He is so cute.
How old are you?
I'm 22.
(He's 22 this year.)
- He's so young.
- I know.
- He's mature now.
- It's a beautiful age.
What is the age difference
between Suk Jin and him?
Is it like 40 years? No?
Hey.
- Isn't it 40 years?
- He's like his son.
Ji Hyo just said,
"He's 20 years younger than me."
It's not that bad.
- It's not 30 years.
- I agree.
I'm not sure if Ji Hyo remembers.
I met Jun Hwan...
- at an awards ceremony.
- I remember that too.
He said his ideal type was...
- Ji Hyo.
- He said Ji Hyo. Right.
Jun Hwan, I hear
your ideal type is right here.
- It's Ji Hyo sitting over there.
- Over there?
Ji Hyo?
(Jun Hwan confessed
that he was a big fan of Ji Hyo.)
Jun Hwan, I wish you were a little older.
I'll see you later.
Why is that?
The thing is,
I watch Running Man a lot.
She has her unexpected charms.
- I see.
- She does.
We should let Ji Hyo
kick him in the buttocks.
He should spend some time with her.
- Or she should throw him down.
- Or his hair.
- She should grab him by the hair.
- Exactly.
- That's her unexpected charm.
- By the way,
I heard you were glad
when you were invited to our show.
Yes, I was.
I've always wanted to join Running Man.
I loved this show as a kid.
This is what we often hear...
- from our guests these days.
- What?
They don't say,
"I enjoy watching this show."
"I used to watch this show
when I was little."
That's true.
That means
we've done this for a long time.
- It's been so long.
- It must feel surreal to you.
Why would you talk to him like that?
What's wrong with you?
- Don't be ridiculous.
- What's with you?
- Hey.
- My gosh.
He's unbelievable.
- Excuse me.
- I'm sorry, Jun Hwan.
- He watched our show as a kid.
- Even I don't talk down to him.
He's a hero.
- He's a Running Man kid.
- Stop it.
- This is embarrassing.
- I'm ashamed.
Just because he's a Running Man kid
doesn't mean he likes you.
- You should know that.
- I'm not that old.
- He's like an embarrassing uncle.
- What's your problem?
- I was just so excited.
- Who was your favorite member?
She was my favorite.
- I guess he liked only Ji Hyo.
- Who else?
- Who was your favorite male member?
- You didn't like Suk Jin, right?
- Of course not.
- Who was your favorite male member?
- I liked Jae Suk.
- I knew it.
- I loved the Yoo-mes Bond special.
- He called you by your name.
- There were two episodes.
- Yes.
He called you by your name
like a big brother.
- I'm jealous.
- Of course. We've met before.
Jun Hwan and I know each other.
- Well, he calls me by my name too.
- He didn't mention Suk Jin.
- What was Suk Jin's ranking?
- I'm curious about it too.
He's like your uncle, right?
- You don't have to answer that.
- He's like my father.
Right. He's like your father.
- That's true. I'm like his dad.
- His father?
It's okay. You can treat us all
like big brothers.
(I'm like his dad.)
It's okay. You can treat us all
like big brothers on a TV show.
- Treat us all like big brothers.
- Why are you so disappointed?
- He seems so disappointed.
- Look at his face.
He couldn't hide his feelings.
(He couldn't hide
his disappointment at all.)
Aren't you the one...
- who acted so confident earlier?
- I'm okay.
- "Hey, come over here."
- It's just the beginning.
I'm fine.
(The captain of Running Man's
popularity rating is quite low.)
- He pushed himself too hard.
- He can't hide his feelings.
All right. We've met our guest Jun Hwan.
- I believe we have another guest.
- That's right.
The other guest has met Jun Hwan before.
- Let's watch the video first.
- Haven't they kept in touch?
- Let's watch.
- I watched this.
Hello. I'm Cha Jun Hwan,
and I'm 11 years old.
- My, how adorable.
- Hello.
- I'm Bbangkku Ttongkku Jin Ji Hee.
- She's so cute.
It's nice to meet you all.
(Jun Hwan and Ji Hee appeared in
a figure skating variety show...)
(11 years ago.)
- He's so cute.
- Oh, my.
(The 2 of them appeared on
the same show 11 years ago.)
- She's so cute.
- She's really cute.
- How adorable.
- Do you remember this, Jun Hwan?
- Do you?
- Yes, I do.
Did you know that I was Bbangkku Ttongkku?
No.
She's so cute. Look at Ji Hee.
That's weird.
Those who live in Korea,
but don't know my character are all pies.
She said, "pies".
- "Pies"?
- What are you talking about?
- You mean, "spies", right?
- Right. That's what I meant to say.
- Pies are delicious.
- Do you remember that?
This is fun to watch.
They're so cute.
Jun Hwan, do you remember that?
Yes, I remember that vaguely.
He looks just as he did then.
That's interesting.
Oh, no. Wait.
Ji Hee was leading the team
as she was older than him.
Oh, my. They're so cute.
- Gosh. Did she twist her leg?
- Oh, no.
Are you okay? Do you think
you can walk just a few steps?
- I can't.
- Try to stand up.
Let's take a break over there.
He's taking care of her.
I twisted my ankle.
(Jun Hwan was Ji Hee's teacher
as she hadn't tried figure skating.)
Are you okay? Can you continue practicing?
- They're so cute.
- Indeed.
(Lifting him up)
They're really cute.
(The koala lift,
a contrarian figure skating move)
They're so cute.
(Laughing)
- They're so cute.
- Indeed.
That was cute.
They're so cute. My goodness.
(The 2 of them were loved so much
by the viewers.)
- They're both so adorable.
- They're really cute.
- They both grew well.
- Right?
- You haven't changed at all.
- Indeed.
They haven't changed at all.
- They haven't...
- I'm jealous.
- Now, Ji Hee, please come out.
- She's coming out.
- What's going on?
- Where is Ji Hee?
- Now, Ji Hee, please come out.
- What's going on?
(They haven't seen each other
for the past 11 years since then.)
- Ji Hee.
- She's coming down the stairs.
Hello.
(Jin Ji Hee, age 13, actress)
(She was a cheerful child back then.)
(They will meet each other again
after 11 years.)
- She looks so pretty.
- What's this?
- She hasn't changed either.
- Hi, Ji Hee.
What's this?
(Rome-hee Jin Ji Hee
and Jun-liet Cha Jun Hwan)
What's this?
(They met each other again as adults.)
- Ji Hee.
- Oh, my. What is this?
- Hello, everyone.
- Ji Hee.
- We met her four months ago.
- Right.
But she looks very different today.
- I'm back.
- She's all dressed up today.
- You look so pretty today.
- Can you do that pose for us?
- Ji Hee.
- I just watched that video too.
- Oh, that's why.
- Yes.
- As if she'd popped out of there.
- Exactly.
She's so cute.
(I can show, yo)
I can show, yo
(The old man got excited
and started singing.)
- I can show, yo
- What are you doing?
- That was funny. I liked it.
- Right?
- It was good.
- I can show, yo
- I mean, the two of them...
- Exactly.
- still look just the same...
- They look so lovely.
- I'm embarrassed.
It's as if they have popped out of
the screen.
- Exactly.
- Please strike this pose again.
- But...
- Please do it for us.
- They're very young.
- Yes.
But... We met for the first time
in many years.
- Hello.
(But... We met for the first time
in many years. Hello.)
(They bowed politely.)
- What was that?
- Why did they bow to each other?
- "Hello."
(The members are taken aback
as they greet each other awkwardly.)
- Let's shake hands.
- Okay.
- Haven't they met in a while?
- Hey...
When you two were eating together
in the video,
- You two looked so close.
- you looked like best friends.
- They joked around with each other.
- Right.
- What happened?
- Haven't you met in a long time?
- We haven't met in 11 years.
- Really?
- You didn't keep in touch either?
- No.
Why didn't you stay in touch
with each other?
- You lost touch with each other.
- We don't have each other's number.
- I see.
- That's understandable, but...
- Since they were little kids then,
- It's understandable.
they could've exchanged numbers
without worrying about others.
- I'm here to get his number today.
- Really?
- They're awkward around each other.
- By the way,
- as we talked about it earlier,
- Ji Hee came here four months ago.
- Yes, she did.
- But she looks different today.
- Indeed.
- She looks very different.
- She looks calm and graceful.
- Last time, she dressed casually.
- Right.
Today, she dressed so nicely.
- She's all dressed up.
- Yes.
- She looks a bit different today.
- She looks different.
- She paid extra attention.
- Yes.
- I tried to look stylish.
- I see.
- I can tell.
- They're awkward around each other.
- But...
- Don't you remember it, Ji Hee?
Of course, I do. The video clips
from the show went viral,
so I've been watching them.
They brought back old memories.
How much older is Ji Hee than Jun Hwan?
May I ask how old you are?
Oh, my. She's awkward around him.
(They use honorifics
when talking to each other now.)
- What's going on?
- This isn't what I expected.
Jun Hwan is 22.
- I thought they'd hug excitedly.
- Exactly.
I was excited to see them reunite,
but that wasn't what I expected.
- "How have you been?" Like this.
- You see,
- you need to understand them...
- Yes.
because they haven't seen each other
for the past 11 years since then.
- Right. It must be awkward.
- Yes. Of course.
- It's natural.
- It's because So Min usually...
hugs a guest so excitedly
even when he's just an acquaintance.
- She hugs him and spins around.
- So Min...
So Min wouldn't just walk toward him.
"Hey."
She would hold him tightly
and spin around.
She would hop
as if she were on a Pogo stick.
She would be so excited.
She always does that.
While watching TV, I go like,
"Gosh. What's with her?"
- It happened many times.
- That's how I show my affection.
I would be even more excited
if I ran into Jong Kook.
- Really?
- Of course.
She'd definitely do that
if she ran into you in real life.
- Of course.
- Oh, I see.
In fact, they told us how they felt.
But they talked to each other
only when they greeted.
They won't even make eye contact.
They're still awkward around each other.
- They feel awkward.
- But it's understandable.
We saw you two in the video. Ji Hee,
- what was Jun Hwan like back then?
- Yes.
He was a strict teacher.
- But he was kind at the same time.
- I see.
He was so strict when he taught me...
- while we were practicing.
They met each other after many years
like in a drama.
Personally, I wish...
- they could be...
- You met Eunhyuk again here.
- But...
- Forget about it.
- Isn't this just like in a drama?
- Why didn't you get excited...
- when Eunhyuk came on the show?
- That was totally different.
- You two went to the same school.
- Exactly.
But their situation is more dramatic.
Actually, when it was reported
that I was going to be on this show,
- all my female friends called me.
- Of course.
- Yes.
- What did they say?
They told me how jealous they were,
and asked me to tell Jun Hwan
that they were his fans.
- Relay their messages?
- Yes.
- I see.
- He has a lot of fans.
- Both of you...
- They grew up well.
- Exactly.
- I'm not sure how this may sound,
- but you two grew up so well.
- I agree.
- Yes.
- They grew up to be decent people.
Their parents must be so happy.
Some of us don't look
as handsome as we were as kids.
- Don't say who they are.
- Okay.
- Some of us did.
- Okay. We'll keep it a secret.
- I looked better when I was a kid.
- That's not true.
- I looked so cute as a kid.
- You...
You look so much better than before.
- I mean, when I was a little kid...
- We all looked cute as a kid.
Take a look at everyone's old photo.
We all looked cute as a kid.
- Really? I've never seen yours.
- Yes.
- Jong Kook also...
- I was really cute as a little boy.
- Really?
- He looked like a prankster.
Se Chan became more handsome
as he grew up.
You looked so cute
in your old photo though.
When I was a little boy,
my mouth stuck out more.
I'm relieved that I had it fixed.
- Is that true?
- It stuck out this much.
Were you a bird?
Exactly. Just like a beak.
- You had a beak?
- It looked like a beak.
There are couches here
for us to sit down, right?
- Shall we sit down?
- Shall we?
Oh, I see.
- We should've sat down earlier.
- Please sit.
- Let's all sit down.
- You can sit here.
There might not be enough room
for all of us.
- Good.
- Oh, my.
- Right.
- I'll tell you about the rules.
Okay.
Before the race begins,
each member will...
- receive 100 dollars.
- That's a lot.
And Suk Jin will receive
extra 100 dollars on top of it.
- It's good to be the captain.
- Captain Ji.
- That's great.
- Oh, my.
- Only for the captain.
- I wish I were the captain.
- You're lying.
- What a shame.
The person who has the most money
left at the end will win the race.
I'll definitely win the race.
Out of the money you'll be given,
write down the amount you want to
give to Jun Hwan and Ji Hee...
as an allowance, and we'll give them
without revealing the amount.
- Well... I'm afraid...
- They won't know the amount?
- Correct.
- they will be disappointed in us.
I'm pretty sure we won't get
a lot of money.
- We should give them enough money.
- How much will we receive?
You'll receive 100 dollars,
and you can give down to 1 dollar.
- I see.
- We can give down to one dollar?
- I have 200 dollars, right?
- That's correct.
- You see,
- Can I split a dollar?
we just have to make sure they have
as much money as we have.
- Since they're our guests,
- You mean, the total amount?
we should be generous.
- If each gives ten dollars to him,
- Ten dollars from each of us.
- he'll get 70 dollars.
- It should be at least 10 dollars.
Hold on. Ten dollars from each...
This is the first round.
It's just the beginning.
- We shouldn't be too stingy...
- He'll give them only ten cents.
We can't split one dollar.
- Listen to me.
- Can you use it wisely?
- Of course. I'm thrifty.
- You're wrong about that.
I'll give each of them
more than ten dollars.
- Really?
- Yes, I will.
How much do you want
as an allowance, Jun Hwan?
- Tell me.
- Two hundred dollars.
Two hundred dollars?
Hey, don't be too greedy.
That's all I have.
I think this is a reasonable amount.
- Hand it in if you're done.
- Jong Kook...
Jong Kook looks like a PE teacher.
- Me? I see.
- He really looks like a PE teacher.
He looks like a coach.
- I think he can coach me.
- I look like a coach, right?
He totally looks like a coach.
- Okay.
- I wrote a reasonable amount.
- Give me a second.
- Right.
- You should be generous.
- Gosh. I gave them...
- They're our guests.
- I...
- Ji Hee and Jun Hwan are here.
- Exactly.
Don't be so stingy.
It's not even real money. It's R money.
Gosh, he's such a weakling.
He's still contemplating.
(Captain Ji who has 200 dollars
has made up his mind as well.)
We've tallied the amount
that each member gave away.
The two guests will begin the race...
- with the money they gave them.
- I bet you'll get a lot of money.
- Isn't this your first time?
- I think so.
We prepared today's race
for Jun Hwan and Ji Hee...
who met again after 11 years
as all Koreans hoped.
It's Because This Is
My First Time to Be a Captain.
- I see.
- Are they team captains?
As you could assume,
Jun Hwan and Ji Hee will be...
the captain of each team.
(They'll be the captains of each of
the team of 5 and the team of 4.)
The members will be divided into
2 teams of 4 and 5 members.
Starting with the captain
with a smaller amount of allowance,
- they will recruit members 1 by 1.
- Okay.
The one with less money will go first?
Before that,
We'll reveal the seven numbers
for each guest.
- What?
- What do you mean by that?
(The members are taken aback
as the amounts will be revealed.)
- We won't reveal your names.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Of course.
(Only the amount of money given by
the 7 members will be revealed.)
- Show me.
- This is for you, Ji Hee.
- Thank you.
- Oh, gosh.
- Thirty dollars, one dollar...
- Who gave away only one dollar?
- Who gave him 2 dollars?
- Only 1 dollar? I can't believe it.
(Ji Hee's allowance:
lowest 1 dollar, highest 20 dollars)
Only one dollar? That's so mean.
- Who gave him 2 dollars?
- Only 1 dollar? I can't believe it.
- Who did that?
- Only two dollars?
- That's so mean.
- I can't believe it.
- Two people gave me one dollar.
- My gosh.
- Gosh, 1 dollar? And 2 dollars?
- Seriously.
(Jun Hwan's allowance, which is also
shocking, has been revealed too.)
(Jun Hwan's allowance:
lowest 1 dollar, highest 30 dollars)
(Even Captain Cha who participated
in the Olympics didn't get much.)
- Only one dollar? Are you serious?
- Seriously.
Those who gave away only one dollar...
- should be isolated.
- I agree.
- That's not right.
- Hey, guys.
- Don't even speak to them.
- Exactly.
- Unbelievable.
- Indeed. I can't believe them.
- It's embarrassing.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Who gave away only 1 dollar?
- Gosh, only 1 dollar?
Based on the different amounts,
you can guess who gave you more
and recruit that person.
Ji Hee who received less money will
go first.
Choose one person you want on your team.
I wonder who gave me 20 dollars.
Oh, 20 dollars?
(She's trying to figure out who gave
her the largest amount.)
(I did.)
Hello, Buddhist monk.
(The little Buddhist monk claims
that he donated 20 dollars.)
- Buddhist monk, hello.
- Your mind is water.
- And water is your mind.
- Please stay seated.
I'll tell you honestly.
I gave you ten dollars.
- It's true.
- I like your honesty.
I gave you 20 dollars.
- That's a lie.
- I gave her ten dollars.
I gave you 20 dollars.
Think about it. I had 200 dollars.
- Ji Hee, please choose a member.
- Okay. I'll choose one.
I choose...
(Captain Jin Ji Hee will choose
her 1st team member.)
I choose...
(Who will Ji Hee choose?)
I choose Ji Hyo.
- What?
- Oh, I see.
- Ji Hyo.
- What?
- Why did you choose her?
- Did you see Jun Hwan's face?
- He looked upset for a moment.
- "That's a shame."
- But Ji Hee...
- I guess you don't know about them.
Ji Hee, why would you create...
- a situation like this?
- You can't do that.
People become more affectionate
when they're separated.
- Even so...
- That's harsh.
(If Ji Hyo is on Ji Hee's team,
I'll probably...)
Look how happy So Min is. That's so funny.
Look how happy So Min is.
- No, it's not like that.
- Look at her.
If Jun Hwan doesn't pick...
- So Min either...
- I hope so.
That's the best-case scenario.
He'll never pick So Min.
- "Let's destroy it."
- Jun Hwan won't...
- Jun Hwan, I gave you 20 dollars.
- Jun Hwan won't pick her.
- Jun Hwan...
- You just pointed two dollars.
No.
- This is me, I'm telling you.
- I bet she gave him one dollar.
Next, Jun Hwan, it's your turn.
I wonder who he will choose.
- I lost her.
- You feel pressured, right?
(What could be Captain Cha's choice?)
- Well...
- You know who gave you 30 dollars.
One of them gave you thirty dollars,
and one of them gave you one dollar.
- I gave him 10 dollars.
- Only 1 dollar.
- I wonder...
- I really gave you 20 dollars.
- I gave you 10 dollars.
- I wonder who gave me 30 dollars.
- He gave you ten dollars.
- Isn't that obvious, Jun Hwan?
Who else could it be?
Then I'll choose...
(Jun Hwan's fans are nervous.)
- Jae Suk.
- Of course.
- I knew it. Mister, move.
- You shouldn't have picked him.
(They feel bitter.)
- Mister, move.
- You shouldn't have picked him.
- Come on. Mister, move.
- Hey, Jun Hwan.
I gave you a big hug when you came in.
- I welcomed you so affectionately.
- I knew he'd pick me.
- I can pick more members.
- I knew it.
He's not the only member on my team.
- Oh, my. Because you can pick more?
- He could've...
He could've picked So Min,
but he picked me.
So Min is...
- He chose him over me.
- I feel bad for you.
- I hope Ji Hee will pick So Min.
- I mean...
- He picked...
- Ji Hee, it's your turn.
He picked Jae Suk without
considering the gender ratio.
- Well...
- Ji Hee...
Because I like honest people,
- I'll pick Jong Kook.
- Okay.
Good. That's great. Nice.
(It's not hard to see which members
the captains avoid recruiting.)
Why do they...
- I think...
- Hey, seriously.
Can you two still not see?
- Pardon?
- Who do you think gave you...
more than ten dollars?
I had 200 dollars, you know.
- Try to think rationally, Jun Hwan.
- Oh, he had more money than we did.
- He's looking at Suk Jin now.
- He had more money than we did.
- Be honest with me. How much?
- Twenty dollars isn't a lot.
- Me?
- Yes.
Thirty dollars.
- I honestly gave you 20 dollars.
- I gave you 30 dollars.
- It's true.
- It's not a lie.
- I...
- He's still very young.
"I..." Captain Cha seems to have
made up his mind.
- Okay.
- He'll announce his decision.
(Captain Ji said he had given him
30 dollars.)
(So Min said she had given him
20 dollars.)
Then I will pick...
Se Chan.
Oh, my. I'm impressed.
Thank you.
(He picked Se Chan.)
(Jun Hwan is so good at creating a twist.)
- What a twist.
- That was good.
- Jun Hwan.
- This is great.
- Hey, come with me.
- What a twist.
- Good job.
- Come over here.
- While looking in this direction...
- I gave him 20 dollars.
- You know how to make a show funny.
- While looking that way,
- Hold on.
- But he chose me.
- he said, "I'll choose Se Chan."
- Can I...
- He must've watched the show often.
- get my money back?
- Whoever gave you more money...
- Can I get my money back?
- because he or she felt bad.
- No.
- So Min...
- Ji Hee.
- I mean, I gave him 20 dollars...
- How could he...
- That was so unexpected.
I can't believe you.
- Look at So Min.
- Hey.
Look at her.
- What are you doing?
- Don't pick So Min.
So Min...
Next up is Captain Jin.
- It's my turn now, right?
- Yes.
- She wrote, "It was me."
- Right.
- We have no choice.
- Hey, Ji Hee.
What's the largest amount?
- Twenty dollars.
- But...
- That's me.
- Honestly...
- Did you really give me 20 dollars?
- Yes.
- Why not?
- Then I've made up my mind.
(Then I've made up my mind.)
- Who?
- I'll choose Haha.
Thank you.
- I'll do my best.
- That was good.
- Okay.
- That's great.
- That was funny.
- Good job.
- It was good.
- They grew up well.
- They're talented.
- Thank you for growing up well.
- Jun Hwan, you're really talented.
- Thank you.
The members who haven't been picked
are So Min and...
Just the two of us.
- I'm impressed.
- I mean...
How did I end up like this? I regret
giving him 20 dollars.
What happens to the last person remaining?
- That person will join that team.
- Automatically?
Oh, that member will be on the other team.
- Her team has five members.
- I see.
- Oh, and we have four members?
- Jun Hwan, just do as you want.
- Right. Just do as you want.
- I'll choose...
(The last member to join
Jun Hwan's team is...)
(I choose So Min.)
I choose So Min.
(Laughing)
Oh, my. Aren't you adorable?
He looks happy.
- He's happy.
- He's just adorable.
- Suk Jin...
- Then Suk Jin,
- you'll be the weak link.
- He's a weak link?
- Isn't he our captain?
Am I the captain or the weak link?
- The captain is the weak link.
- This is ridiculous.
- I mean, I'm the captain.
- Will you be a weak captain?
Oh, we're eight people without him.
Suk Jin, aren't you the captain
of Running Man?
A weak captain.
I'm the captain and the weak link
at the same time.
We'll give you your allowances now.
We'll let you check the names.
Please take it off.
- What? Is it written underneath?
- They'll know...
- They'll check the names?
- They'll know... Oh, no.
- I guess they'll see.
- Are their names written here?
- I really gave you 20 dollars.
- That hurts my feelings.
Exactly.
- I wasn't lying.
- No.
- Hold on.
- I gave you 20 dollars.
I knew it was Se Chan
who had given her one dollar.
- Right.
- Suk Jin wasn't lying.
- Oh, I see.
- See?
(The weak link really gave her
20 dollars.)
- That's right.
- See?
So Min gave him 20 dollars.
She really gave him 20 dollars.
I really gave him 20 dollars.
- She really gave him 20 dollars.
- Exactly.
- This is unexpected.
- Suk Jin gave him 30 dollars.
- Yes, I gave him 30 dollars.
- Oh, man.
(Se Chan was the one
who gave Captain Cha 1 dollar.)
- That's what we do...
- Hey, Se Chan.
- I'm disappointed.
- at the beginning of the show.
- I can't believe him.
- That's how it works, Jun Hwan.
(Embarrassed)
Gosh. Se Chan, how could you
give her only one dollar? It's...
- Se Chan.
- Hey.
Se Chan, how could you give her
only one dollar?
- Come on, Ji Hyo.
- Se Chan, how could you...
- give her only...
- Ji Hyo, Se Chan came over here.
- I'm on this side now.
- Right. I'm sorry.
- You do know Haha's name, right?
- I'm here, Ji Hyo.
Haha, how could you...
- give her only 1 dollar?
- Yes, I gave her 1 dollar.
Monk Ha, shouldn't you try to
let go of attachment?
- Well... Life is...
- This is unexpected.
- It hurts.
- Ji Hee, see how it turns out.
As always, we got an offer
for a product placement...
that will help us get more money
for making the show.
It's a fried chicken brand.
- Oh, I see.
- Really?
Please have it for breakfast...
Fried chicken is the best food
for breakfast.
while I'm explaining the rules.
- But Haha is modeling for...
- Yes.
Exactly. It was hard for us
to decide what to do about it.
Haha is the face of
another fried chicken brand.
- I made the decision.
- But Suk Jin gave us...
a wise solution like King Solomon.
- What was the solution?
- That's right.
Suk Jin, we'll do
a product placement that day.
- What kind of product is it?
- It's a fried chicken brand.
- I see.
- But we have a problem.
We get the most offers from
fried chicken brands, but Haha...
We don't know how to make it
look natural without Haha.
How should we exclude Haha?
Won't he exclude himself
of his own accord?
Right? He'll exclude himself
of his own accord.
I mean...
- Was that your idea?
- It was...
- It was the captain's idea.
- It was your idea?
- It was Captain Ji's idea.
- I see.
- You see...
- He should exclude himself.
- That's right.
- He's modeling for another brand.
- Anyway...
- Don't worry about me.
I started eating only raw grains
and vegetables.
(Monk Ha would quit eating meat
for money.)
I don't eat boiled food anymore.
- Maybe I should shave my head too.
- I don't eat deep-fried food.
- That makes him look so funny.
- Indeed. He looks so funny.
Haha, please step out for a while.
- Haha, you should go.
- Exclude yourself.
Watch us from afar.
You can watch us, right?
- My, it smells so good.
- Oh, my.
- Look at that.
- My, it looks so delicious.
- Oh, my.
- The pros are gathering.
- It looks so good.
- My goodness.
- It smells incredibly good.
- What's this?
- Is it fried chicken?
- Let's eat.
- This looks incredible.
- Thank you.
So this is how they do
fried chicken these days.
Are you letting us eat right off the bat?
(The sight of protein
excites Trainer Kook.)
- Is it good?
- This...
- If I may say so...
- This one's too cold.
(The youngsters aren't familiar
with product placement.)
It writes history
in the fried chicken industry.
- They look delicious.
- Is it good?
How can you say that
without tasting any of them?
They look incredible.
(They look delicious.)
- This looks amazing.
- Can I have a drumstick?
Fried chicken.
You must be on the fence
about ordering some right about now.
What?
Let us try some for you.
The client wanted Jae Suk
and Jong Kook to enjoy it.
My goodness!
All right. Dig in, everyone.
- Fried chicken.
- My gosh.
If you're going to have dinner,
I urge you to choose fried chicken
that is full of protein.
Please don't overdo it.
Don't overdo it?
- You'll be reprimanded.
- Was I on YouTube mode?
- But this...
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
- This is baked, not fried.
- Is it baked chicken?
- Yes.
- Baked chicken.
- Baked is better.
The chicken is baked
and the sauce is delicious.
- Isn't it spicy?
- My gosh.
- No.
- This is baked, not fried.
(The youngsters easily slip
into a comfortable conversation.)
- This is nice.
- The chicken is baked...
and the sauce is delicious.
But...
Please listen to the rules while you eat.
After each game,
you will be given prize money...
depending on how well your team did.
The captains will distribute it
as they please.
- Really?
- Yes.
- But...
- What did he say?
What are the rules?
(Monk Ha listens from behind the cameras.)
Haha, we'll fill you in later.
The team members are at a disadvantage...
if they are only allowed
to receive what they're given.
Of course.
If you think that your captain
has given you the lowest amount,
you may challenge him or her
by taking a stance.
You will swap amounts
with your captain if you are right.
(Swap amounts with the captain
if the challenge is reasonable.)
What if we were wrong
to challenge the captain?
You will lose the money given to you.
(Your money will be cut in half.)
It's up to you to make the right call.
- I believe in my captain.
- Sure.
This is good.
The weak link of the team of five
is Suk Jin.
After every game,
the captain of that team...
can send one person to the other team.
Then the other team will have
that choice after the next round.
You can get rid of the weak link.
After each game,
kick out the most useless member.
That person will lose ten dollars.
(The weak link
will automatically lose 10 dollars.)
You'll change and gather at the location.
- Sure.
- Got it.
(The one with the most money
will win the race.)
Isn't it hilarious to see them
be awkward around each other?
- What's your blood type?
- Me? Type AB.
- Type AB? What about you?
- I'm Type O.
- Type O?
- I get along well with that type.
- Really?
- Yes.
Who asks blood type these days?
Ask about their MBTI instead.
What's your MBTI?
I'm an ISFJ.
- What about you?
- I'm an ENTJ.
- Really?
- Look at So Min.
Her age showed
when she asked them their blood type.
I'm an INFP.
An INFP? I get along with that type too.
- I'm an INFP.
- I get along with INFPs too.
(- Yes!
- All right!)
(She forced a bond between them.)
As if that really matters.
Well, I'm an ENFP.
Look at the youngsters
easily become friends again.
Yes, we're talking casually now.
Do you call her "noona?"
- Ji Hee, I mean.
- Yes, I do.
- Of course.
- Of course he does.
Mr. Weak Link.
- Mr. Weak Link?
- Don't you think he's...
Captain Weak Link!
Shouldn't he be standing at the far end?
Did you watch me film
the opening for Running Man?
- I did.
- Dowdy, wasn't it?
What is the concept anyway?
Will it be played during the show?
- Like this.
- It's hilarious. Ji Suk Jin's...
- Running Man.
- That just gave me the creeps.
We were by his side when he filmed that,
but he asked if we saw it.
(During the break)
Ji Suk Jin's...
- Running...
- Ju Eun!
Seriously?
Can't you see
I'm filming something important?
- Really? I didn't know.
- Move over!
I apologize.
- Really?
- Let me try that again.
And cue!
Ji Suk Jin's Running...
(Here's your fried chicken!)
- Unbelievable.
- He wants us to acknowledge it.
(Captain Ji still asked
if they saw him film the opening.)
You're being told to resume the show.
- Ji Suk Jin's Running Man?
- Bo Pil...
- What is it?
- He's saying that...
Jun Hwan agreed to dance
during the opening today.
- Really?
- Why didn't you do it?
We requested something, you see.
- Let's see it then.
- I can't wait!
Jun Hwan, let's do this.
- Let's see you dance.
- Go ahead.
Dancing is all that
Running Man has to offer.
- I can't wait.
- I thought he had forgotten.
Good luck.
He starts swaying to the rhythm.
- Go, Jun Hwan.
- Here he goes.
- Nicely done!
- Seriously, Jun Hwan?
(His healthy joints
fuel his powerful dance moves.)
Seriously, Jun Hwan?
He's adorable.
- He's adorable.
- Never did I expect this.
- He's not like any other dancer.
- You look adorable.
- Isn't he adorable?
- How cute is that?
Look at him go.
(He ends the show with a sweet body roll.)
- That was adorable.
- Yes, adorable.
The TikTok Geezer loves it.
That is tailor-made for social media.
- Exactly.
- Hold on.
It's not like how he dances
when he's on the ice.
- It was adorable.
- I found him adorable.
- That was great though.
- His moves are big.
- That was adorable.
- Big moves.
- Like this.
- Wasn't that adorable?
Ji Hee, what about you?
- You can dance as well.
- Let's do this, Ji Hee.
What should I dance to?
- Go for it.
- I...
- You should dance to...
- Can I check my phone first?
- What for?
- Sure. Go ahead.
- She came prepared.
- Just a second!
Let's do this. Ji Hee, come on!
- All right.
- Let's dance!
How does it go again?
- Like this.
- This?
Nice.
- What is it?
- What is it this time?
- I was being enthusiastic.
- What's wrong?
I was only looking.
- Nice!
- You must've...
gotten on his nerves.
(Dancing)
What do I always tell you?
Haha goes crazy
over anything that seems hip.
He'll even taste dung
if someone says it's hip.
You're absolutely right.
That's exactly how he's like.
- Gosh. He is...
- He has an incurable disease.
He goes crazy over anything young.
- Sorry about that.
- He loves to show off.
I'm back.
- She's back.
- Here.
He'll do anything that seems hip.
Haha's hilarious.
Ji Hee's back!
She's actually a good dancer.
- She is.
- Ji Hee, show us.
- Good luck.
- Here I go.
Cue, music.
- This.
- I'm stuck on that as well.
- I can't hear the music.
- Hold on.
- Over there...
- That's what you're dancing to?
Yes. Let me try this.
- Hold on.
- But the tempo...
Are you sure about this?
- When it comes to dancing...
- It's like dancing to no music.
- Are you sure, Ji Hee?
- Yes.
- Then I respect that.
- She's bold, isn't she?
(Bouncing)
(She begins with gentle body rolls.)
She couldn't care less
about the others around her.
She's bold, isn't she?
- This is more my style.
- We should keep it down.
(The members can't really hear the music.)
(She begins to dance.)
This isn't the response I was hoping for.
You're quite good.
Nice!
- Aren't you an actor?
- Are you taking classes?
Of course.
Your instructor taught you well.
Ji Hee, are you taking dance classes?
She's quite good though.
She definitely took some classes for it.
(The dance machine wraps up
her promotional dance.)
- She definitely learned this.
- I saw this move a lot.
Yes, I practiced my body rolls.
It was the same as dancing to no music.
Ji Hee, are you interested
in being on variety shows?
Yes, I want to do well.
- Nice!
- Treat me as poorly as you want.
- I love that attitude.
- Go, Ji Hee!
- Can we treat you poorly?
- Yes, go ahead.
- Then I'll kick you in the butt!
- Sure.
(Out of nowhere)
(Once)
(Twice)
(Two kicks came flying out of nowhere.)
(She got what she asked for.)
I love it. Bring it on!
Nicely done, guys.
- Nice.
- Do it again if you want.
Ji Hee's ecstatic.
So Min smacked Sae Ho
on the back of his head last week.
She no longer has any boundaries.
What's gotten into you these days?
(Take that!)
- You're on a roll.
- Nice.
She has been staying at home for too long.
She's looking for a fight.
Let's begin the first game.
The first game...
not only depends on your memory...
but the power of
your opponent's memory too.
This is Darn Your Memory.
- Right.
- We all have a good memory.
One from each team will compete.
You must remember the words
that appear in front of you.
The words?
I have good short-term memory.
While memorizing the words in order,
if you feel like your opponent
has lost track,
you may attack by pressing the buzzer.
Once the buzzer is pressed,
the opponent must list the words.
If your opponent guesses correctly,
he or she will win a point.
If the opponent gets it wrong,
you will win a point instead.
- I see.
- Right.
Boldly press the buzzer...
if you think your opponent has lost track.
The later the better, right?
Your opponent might force you
to list the words though.
- Okay.
- It's time for the first round.
- Who'll go first?
- For our team,
- it'll be Jeonsobari.
- Good!
- Then...
- The captain will decide.
- Really?
- The captain should decide.
Captain Cha.
- How about Jeonsobari?
- Jeonsobari?
Why are you controlling him?
- That's not the case.
- Jun Hwan, seriously?
Let Jun Hwan decide.
You'd call this a regency.
Right.
- The King is young.
- Yes, he is.
When the King is too young,
- someone acts as regent.
- Who's up for our team?
- Anyone will do.
- How about the weak link?
Yes, the weak link.
- The weak link.
- Go ahead.
- It's the weak link.
- Here I go.
(Round 1: Suk Jin versus So Min)
The weak link is out!
Are you good at memorizing things?
- I can't say I'm bad at it.
- Really?
For the first round,
you will see the names
of our staff members.
- What?
- This is a hard one.
- This is a tricky one.
- This won't be easy.
This isn't something
Suk Jin is strong at.
- I'll probably lose.
- So Min will definitely win.
She at least knows half the names.
This isn't difficult at all.
- You can do this.
- Okay, let's do this!
I'll crush Jeonsobari.
Here comes the first member of the staff.
Cue.
It should be someone they both don't know.
- They know who that is.
- Of course, they know.
(Choi Hyung In)
(First word: Choi Hyung In)
Of course, I know her.
Hyung In, where are you off to?
- Wait.
- That was a weird walk.
- Of course, they know her name.
- She's on TV a lot these days.
- They know her too for sure!
- We know her.
(They're familiar with
the producer's name.)
She's on TV a lot these days.
(He says it a little too late.)
(Eyes fixated on her)
Of course we know Choi Seon Myung.
We must mention the surname, right?
Isn't she Namkoong Seon Myung?
- Of course we know Choi Seon Myung.
- Namkoong Seon Myung.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Hey!
- What do you think you're doing?
- You are Gong Yoo?
(Gong Yoo)
(A director comes out with
a name tag that says Gong Yoo)
Hey, Nam Joong.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Nam Joong.
Choi Hyung In, Yoo Seon Myung...
That was brazen of him.
- What?
- Kwak Cheol Yong?
Who is he?
Is your name really Kwak Cheol Yong?
No, it's not. You're not Cheol Yong.
We have to memorize the names
from their name tags?
- What?
- Lionel Messi.
Lionel Messi.
I can't remember.
All right. Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin has to name
the staff members in order.)
- Of course he knows.
- Of course.
Choi Hyung In,
- Of course he knows.
- Yoo Seon Myung,
Gong Yoo,
Kwak Cheol Yong,
Lionel Messi.
That's it.
- Why can't she memorize this?
- Why can't she?
Didn't he say Kwak Cheol Young?
- No, he said it correctly.
- Kwak Cheol Young?
You pressed the buzzer really fast.
- It's 1 to 0.
- All right! That was great.
(Suk Jin: 1, So Min: 0)
- Yes!
- You're doing great, weak link.
- You couldn't beat a weak link.
- Our weak link is good.
(Laughing)
- She couldn't beat a weak link.
- Our weak link is good.
All right. Here's the second round.
(Round 2 starts.)
Start.
(Lee Myung Jae)
He is Myung Jae.
Is he?
- He's Myung Jae.
- I see.
- Lee Myung Jae.
- Next.
(Second word: Na Dong Geun)
- It's Dong Geun.
- When did you become Dong Geun?
- But these guys...
- Dong Geun's surname was Na?
- You didn't know?
- No.
Lee Myung Jae, Na Dong Geun...
- What's with you?
- Darn you.
- You are V now?
- You call yourself V?
(Former Gong Yoo came out as V.)
(They all complain.)
- You'll be in big trouble.
- You call yourself V?
Next.
(Yoon Eun Hye)
(Yoon Eun Hye?)
Eun Hye!
(Eun Hye!)
- Where are you going, Eun Hye?
- I'll call you.
I'll call you, Eun Hye!
"I'll call you?"
(Gang Dong Won)
(Gang Dong Won
appears from behind the curtain.)
- Director Yoon.
- What?
- Seriously...
- Director of Jimmy Jib.
Director of Jimmy Jib.
- Mr. Jimmy Jib. Come on.
- Mr. Jimmy Jib?
- He has a figure of Ho Dong.
- Next.
- I forgot their names.
- What?
- Go Chul Bong?
(Sixth word: Go Chul Bong)
- I've never heard of her.
(Buzzing)
Go for it.
(Suk Jin attacks So Min.)
- All right. So Min.
- Go for it.
I couldn't memorize them
because they talked at the back.
(He was the loudest one.)
Lee Myung Jae, Na Dong Geun,
V,
Yoon Eun Hye,
(Lee Myung Jae, Na Dong Geun,
V, Yoon Eun Hye...)
Go Chul Bong.
- It's wrong.
- There was one more.
- There was one more person.
Gang Dong Won.
(Suk Jin succeeds in attacking So Min.)
- You did it!
- There was one more.
So Min's gotten dull.
- So Min, you've become...
- Hey.
(Suk Jin wins Round 1
after earning 2 points first.)
Knock, knock. Are you there?
(Empty Head was completely defeated
by the weak link.)
I was so confused because you guys
talked at the back.
- They made it so confusing.
- For Round Two,
the Olympic athletes will enter
in the order of their countries.
- Memorize the countries in order.
- I'll do it.
- Destroy them.
- I'll play later.
- But this is...
- Jae Suk knows many countries.
- Destroy them.
He does.
I feel reassured.
The Olympic athletes are entering.
- Memorize the words in order.
- All right.
- This one will be hard too.
- Athletes, please enter.
Jong Kook memorizes names well.
- Oh, my.
- The Republic of Korea.
(First word: The Republic of Korea)
- Okay.
The Republic of Korea.
(Ethiopia)
Ethiopia.
I've never heard of such a country.
Next.
(San Marino)
San Marino.
- There's such a country?
- San Marino.
Next.
- The Bahamas.
Was it Santiago?
It's already confusing.
(Ghana)
Ghana.
It was Ashley and Santarama.
- It was Ashley and Santarama.
- Santarama?
- Venezuela.
I think I forgot one.
The third one.
- Next.
- Venezuela.
- Mauritius.
- Go for it.
Go for it, Jong Kook.
Attack him.
Darn it.
Press it! You got it.
(Jae Suk presses the buzzer first.)
Jong Kook.
There was a country called Suction too.
- The Republic of Korea.
- Okay.
Ethiopia.
- San...
- You can't tell him.
- The Bahamas.
(Bursting into laughter)
- He's done for!
- The Republic of Korea.
- He's done.
- No!
- Ethiopia.
- Espresso.
- San Marino.
(The Republic of Korea, Ethiopia,
San Marino...)
- Ghana.
- It's wrong.
- No, it comes out later.
- All right!
- Yes!
- It was tough.
- It was the Bahamas.
Wasn't it Ghana?
It was tough.
(So Min goes over to the other team
to tease them.)
It was the Bahamas.
- The Bahamas
(Singing out the Bahamas to celebrate)
It's 1 to 0.
All right. This is hard.
It's hard to memorize
the names of countries.
- It's hard.
- He can't remember more than five.
Next athletes, please enter.
- All right.
- Go.
- Luxembourg.
- Luxembourg
- Luxembourg, Argentina
- Ecuador.
- Ecuador! Luxembourg, Ecuador.
- The thing is,
if the names are hard,
it's hard to remember them.
- Next.
- Luxembourg.
- This is hard.
- Liechtenstein.
Einstein.
(Even his team member is confused.)
Liechtenstein.
- Uruguay.
- Come at us!
- Come!
Uruguay.
Gosh, seriously!
Press the buzzer
when the next person comes out.
(The scaredy-cat Jae Suk
presses the buzzer first.)
There are only four.
- We won!
- There are only four.
- Don't tell him.
You have to keep quiet.
We can't tell him
because we can't remember.
- Well done.
- All right.
Jae Suk pressed the buzzer...
when he couldn't remember anymore.
He was like, "Darn it!"
When he couldn't remember it,
- he just pressed it.
- This is hard!
- It is hard.
- It's Jae Suk's attack.
The Republic of Korea, Santiago.
- Laminate.
- Come on.
Americano.
Wait.
- Luxembourg.
- Okay.
- Let's see.
- Einstein.
- Three, two...
- Wonstein.
(Luxembourg)
One.
(Jong Kook runs out of time.)
Liechtenstein.
Liechtenstein!
Einstein.
You didn't even memorize anything.
It was Ecuador.
- What?
- Ecuador.
- It was?
- Yes.
- Jae Suk, it was Ecuador.
- Ecuador.
I asked you if it was correct.
It was something that began with E.
(So Min provokes them again.)
I thought he was going to
press the buzzer.
I couldn't remember the second country.
- Do you want to play, Ji Hee?
- I'll give it a try.
We need to take the lead again.
Jae Suk didn't memorize anything.
- He didn't memorize anything.
- You want to play with me?
- Next is Jun Hwan.
- Jun Hwan.
Let's go, Jun Hwan.
- Ji Hee and Jun Hwan.
- Should I give it a try?
It's just our suggestion,
but can Se Chan go first?
Do we have to listen to you?
He's looking down on me for sure.
I'll listen to him.
- What?
- Are you looking down on Se Chan?
- Ji Hyo should play.
- Go for it, Ji Hyo.
Se Chan versus Ji Hyo.
I'm good at memorizing.
Press the buzzer
if you think you can't memorize them.
Se Chan, you can do it.
It's hard.
Start.
(Revealing the question)
- What?
- Who is it?
- John Navarre.
- John Navarre?
- Who is it?
(John Navarre?)
- John Navarre?
- What is this?
- The staff's name is John Navarre?
- Are we allowed to say this?
It's an actual person's name.
It's a football player's name.
- John Navarre?
- Is it okay to say this?
- What do you think you're doing?
- It's a football player's name.
- It's a football player's name?
- John Navarre.
- Next.
- There's such a player?
Oh, he's a football player?
- Park Gyeok Po.
This is easy.
- John Navarre, Park Gyeok Po.
- John Navarre.
John Navarre, Park Gyeok Po.
Yeo Si Yeon.
Is that her real name?
- Yeo Si Yeon.
- Yeo Si Yeon?
- It's hard.
- Mark Zucker...
- Oh, it's Mark Zuckerberg.
- We know Mark Zuckerberg.
- Of course he knows.
- Mark Zuckerberg? Okay, got it.
- Next.
- What was after John Navarre?
What was after John Navarre?
- Who is it? I can't see it. Yoon...
- John Navarre.
- What does it say? Yoon...
- Yoon Jong Seo.
- It's Jong Seo.
- It's confusing.
- All right.
- It's Jong Seo.
It's confusing.
She pressed it.
Se Chan, say the names.
John Navarre.
(John Navarre)
- Park Gyeok Po.
- All right.
(John Navarre, Park Gyeok Po)
- Yeo Si Yeon.
- There you go.
(John Navarre, Park Gyeok Po, Yeo Si Yeon)
- It's a foreigner's name.
- He can't remember it.
- It's hard.
- He doesn't know the name?
- He doesn't know.
- You don't know him, do you?
Mark...
That's it.
He doesn't know.
- Mark...
- He doesn't know.
Zuckburger?
(Wrong)
(Mark Zuckburger?)
How can you call him that?
What is he, a burger?
- What is he, a burger?
- Zip up?
What do you mean by Mark Zuckburger?
What's his name again?
- It's Zuckerberg.
- Oh, right. It's Zuckerberg.
Gosh, darn it!
I'm sorry, Jae Suk.
What do you mean by Mark Zuckburger?
- Zuckburger?
- We can beat them.
- Mark Zuckburger.
- This is great.
We're doing well!
- Se Chan, remember this.
- Okay.
When you're confused,
she'll be confused too.
- Okay.
- Got it?
- When I'm confused,
- Press the buzzer then.
Ji Hyo is confused too.
- As if!
- All right.
- Just press the buzzer well.
Let's see how well he does.
- You'll win if you press it well.
- Here's the second question.
You don't have to memorize them
as long as you press it well.
- It'll be the names of countries.
- All right!
- It's countries?
- Countries.
- It's hard.
- I'm confident.
- Okay.
- The names of countries are hard, no?
I just need to press the buzzer well.
Athletes, please enter. The first athlete.
What could they be?
- Mauritius.
- You can't forget Mauritius.
- Haiti.
- Oh, I know that one.
M and H.
- Haiti of Africa.
- M and H.
- Mauritius and Haiti.
- Haiti.
- Next.
- It's Mauritius.
Uruguay.
- Uruguay is an easy one.
- Mauritius, Haiti, Uruguay.
- Next.
- What's next?
- Australia.
- Haiti...
- It's Australia.
Australia.
It's Australia.
- Next.
- Australia.
- Mozambique.
- M, H...
Mauritius, Haiti...
- You should press it.
- Because of Mozambique?
(Ji Hyo presses the buzzer first.)
(Se Chan fails to press
the buzzer first again.)
Why did you... Seriously!
He can't remember after Uruguay.
At some point,
he didn't even look at the names.
He only stared at Ji Hyo.
What was the last one?
- It was perfect timing.
- You can do it.
- Show us!
- The last one was confusing.
- It was Argentina.
- He doesn't know?
- I don't think so.
- We won.
You must remember the answers.
You can remember them.
- You can't remember them?
- This one is easy.
- He's indeed Empty Head.
- He can't remember the first one.
- Show us!
- The last one was confusing.
Moritius.
- That's not it!
- Hey!
(Moritius?)
- What was that?
- Moritius?
It's Mauritius!
- He said Moritius.
- He didn't know that!
- What on earth is Moritius?
- It's not Moritius?
- It's wrong!
- I couldn't remember.
- It's Mauritius.
Hey, even I memorized them.
Mauritius, Haiti, Uruguay,
Australia, Mozam...
- What's the last one?
- We won! Ji Hyo is good!
- That was great!
- We won.
- Well done!
Next players.
- Let's go.
- Jun Hwan!
- It's between captains.
- All right!
- Yes!
- It's Jun Hwan!
- It's between captains.
- Let's go!
- It was so hard.
- Ji Hee is playing?
- Yes.
- We'll win for sure.
Jun Hwan is playing for our team.
- Jun Hwan is playing.
- We'll take this round.
What do you mean he'll win?
- I'll play relaxedly.
- Relaxedly.
Just beat them.
Take it easy.
The game you're playing next
is in a different category.
We invited special helpers
for the next game.
Who are they?
Special guests, please come in.
- We have special guests?
- We have more guests?
- Is it Hyung In?
- No way.
- Who are they?
- Who could they be?
- We have more guests?
- Who are they?
- They're coming. I heard something.
- There can't be more guests.
- They're coming down.
- What's going on?
(The special guests
slowly reveal themselves.)
- It's Ms. Yeom. It's been so long.
- What?
(Wait, she is...)
What?
You must do whatever I tell you
as though your life depends on it.
- Yes, ma'am.
(It's Granny aerobics instructor
who taught the members...)
(of "Infinite Challenge" harshly
14 years ago.)
It's only the beginning! Get up!
(It's only the beginning! Get up!)
(The maestro in the aerobics world,
Director Yeom Jung In)
- How have you been?
- Ms. Yeom.
(What is Ms. Yeom doing here?)
Hello.
(The music starts to play out of nowhere.)
- Hello.
- What? What do we do?
(She skips greetings and
gets ready to do the aerobic moves.)
Ms. Yeom.
(She skips greetings and
gets ready to do the aerobic moves.)
Gosh. What's this?
You're still working with her.
- What's this?
- She's still working with her.
- My gosh.
- Oh, it's aerobics?
Three, four.
Follow along! What are you doing?
- Okay.
- Four.
- Three.
- Wait.
- I don't think she knows the moves.
- I think she's doing it wrong.
She's not that good.
- Follow me!
- Follow her.
What are you doing?
How can we follow you
when you got all the moves wrong?
- Just do it!
- How?
- She startled me.
- Ms. Yeom.
She sounds like Kwang Hee.
Follow me!
(Shouting out of nowhere)
- We must memorize the moves.
- Follow me.
This way.
One, two.
- It's easy.
- Three, four.
Three, four.
One more time. Three, four.
- Three, four.
- Your mic.
(Ms. Yeom's assistant
steps out to put on the mic again.)
What's going on?
(What's going on?)
- Ms. Yeom doesn't know the moves.
- Ms. Yeom!
Ms. Yeom doesn't know the moves.
Follow me!
- All right.
- What are we supposed to follow?
Ms. Yeom, you don't know the moves.
She's going freestyle!
Okay.
(The assistant is back.)
It's going great!
(They end up learning the moves
from the assistant.)
Oh, gosh.
- Why is she yelling at me?
- Isn't this the move?
Let's go!
Look at me.
We're all looking at her, not at Ms. Yeom.
Ms. Yeom went freestyle.
- No one looked at her.
- What are we supposed to memorize?
Ms. Yeom, how have you been?
Thanks to "Infinite Challenge,"
I've been doing well.
But it's been so long
since "Infinite Challenge" ended.
Since I made a living thanks to
"Infinite Challenge,"
- now, I'll do the same...
- Through "Running Man?"
for 30 more years through "Running Man."
Ms. Yeom.
Your eyeliners are higher than before.
They got stronger, right?
It looks like
you don't know the moves well.
It's not that I don't know them.
I was overly excited.
It's so funny. She told us to follow her,
- but she didn't know the moves.
- You could just...
"Follow me!"
(Her words don't match her actions.)
"Is this the move?"
I could do it well,
but I couldn't do it earlier.
- "Follow me!"
- Okay.
Can you show us one more time?
Ms. Yeom was anxious.
- When the assistant...
- Why are you so dispirited?
Why do you look dispirited
when you worked hard?
Gosh, it's so funny.
All right. For the fourth question,
the maestro of aerobics world, Ms. Yeom,
will give out the question.
(The fourth round
will be joined by Ms. Yeom.)
Ms. Yeom will show you the moves in order.
- Oh, we're starting now?
- You can attack your opponent...
while memorizing the moves.
Okay, I got it.
- You got it, right?
- While memorizing the moves.
He can memorize moves well.
- Be on your toes.
- Okay.
If you get it too easily...
If you dance better than me,
then I'll deduct your points.
- Even if we do better?
- We shouldn't do too well.
If you dance better than me,
- then I'll deduct your points.
- We shouldn't do too well.
But if you don't do well,
your points will be deducted also.
Don't try too hard
to dance better than me.
- Okay.
- Got it.
She's scolding me so hard.
Jun Hwan and Ji Hee,
you'll do the moves...
- to the music.
- Okay.
I'm bad at memorizing moves.
What's the first move? Okay.
Give us the music.
Three, four!
(1st move)
- Two.
- Three, four.
Three, two!
- Four, two.
- Let's go!
One, two,
- three...
- Jun Hwan is indeed good.
Let's go. Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two.
(3rd move)
- Three, four.
- This is hard.
- It's hard!
- I love it!
- It's hard.
- I love this one.
- Five, four.
- You know,
everyone is looking at her.
- No one is looking at Ms. Yeom.
- It's that move.
- Four, three.
- You got this.
Jun Hwan, just press the buzzer.
- Press the buzzer.
- Press it!
(Seeing Jun Hwan press the buzzer,)
(Ji Hee presses it right away.)
- He pressed it!
- All right.
- You should just press the buzzer.
- What do we do?
- What was the first move?
- He pressed the buzzer.
She can't remember the first move.
- The first one was...
- What was the first move?
Now, Ji Hee will show the moves.
Ms. Yeom, please watch her
and see if she got the moves wrong.
- It's so hard.
- It's this, right?
- It goes like this, right?
- Yes, that's it.
That was the move.
(1st move)
(2nd move)
(3rd move)
(4th move)
Please watch Ji Hee
and see if she gets the moves wrong.
- Give us the music.
- I need to dance to the music?
Music, cue.
What's the next move?
(She pulls off the first move.)
- She's good!
- That's it.
- It's exactly the same.
- Isn't this the move?
Two, three, four.
It's exactly the same.
It was something like this.
She's so good at it.
(She pulls off the second move as well.)
That's it.
What's next?
This one.
(She only needs to pull off
the last move.)
(The last move)
(Will she be able to pull off
the last move as well?)
(Whatever!)
- Yes!
- She failed.
- All right!
- It's too hard.
- Well done.
- It's hard.
You did well.
- Jun Hwan earns a point.
- All right!
She can't remember more than three moves.
All right. Here comes the second question.
- Wait. What's next?
- It's "El Dorado."
- What?
- We're dancing to "El Dorado."
We're dancing to "El Dorado?"
No, we're not.
- Yes, we are.
- We're dancing to "El Dorado?"
- Really?
- You don't even know.
It looks like she has no clue.
No, I wanted to finish dancing
with the previous song.
- Oh, with the previous song?
- It's "El Dorado."
- It's "El Dorado".
- Okay.
- I'll do it.
- Just follow the one on the right.
- Get ready.
- We need the music.
Music, cue.
- We'll start with the first one.
- Okay.
It's "El Dorado."
Here we go!
- Let's go!
- Three, four.
This one is easy.
Two.
- Three, two.
- This is really easy.
- Let's move on.
- It's covering the face move.
- Covering face.
- It's the next move.
- Six, two.
- Three, four.
- Three, two.
- Stretch out your right arm.
- Three, four.
- Covering face and stretching arm.
Two.
- Shaking your hips.
- This one is easy.
- Three, four.
Covering face and stretching arm.
Shaking your hips.
Stretching your arms.
Ji Hee, let's press the buzzer this time.
All right.
Press the buzzer, Jun Hwan.
- Ji Hee.
- Press the buzzer.
- Press it.
- Press the buzzer, Jun Hwan.
(Will she be able to press it this time?)
- Jun Hwan, press the buzzer.
- Press it.
(Jun Hwan was faster this time as well.)
You see?
- Yes!
- I knew he would press it.
- She pressed the buzzer first.
- She didn't press it properly.
- I pressed the buzzer first.
- I know you did.
You should have pressed it properly.
This is unfair
because she pressed it first.
- To be honest...
- Ji Hee.
Tell us right away
if she gets the moves wrong.
- Ji Hee, do you remember this?
- This is the first move.
- Ji Hee, look at this.
- Ji Hee.
Don't look in that direction.
(The other team
continues to distract her.)
Music, cue.
Then comes the hip move.
That's right.
- All right.
- Music.
Move to the rhythm.
Ji Hee.
Do the Dog Leg Dance.
One, two, three, four.
- Not yet!
- "Not yet!"
Two, three, four.
- One, two, three, four.
- It begins here.
- Okay.
- Open your hands.
- That's good.
- One, two, three, four.
- The next move.
- The right arm.
The right arm. That's good.
- You are doing well.
- That's good.
Then comes the hip move.
- Yes.
- The hip move.
- That's good.
- No.
- That's correct.
- Out.
You shake your hips.
(Ji Hee failed.)
- Show us.
- You shake your hips.
- We will give it a try.
Music, cue.
- Go easy on me.
- Listen up.
There are criteria.
Your fingers need to be
in the correct position.
- I did this.
- Ms. Yeom.
- You are so strict.
You didn't do that earlier.
You did this earlier.
That's different.
- You danced haphazardly.
- How dare you talk back to me?
(She yells at them when she is cornered.)
I mean...
I am the law.
- You didn't do this earlier.
- You got the move wrong.
- I got the move wrong?
- Ms. Yeom, you did this earlier.
(Blatant cheating)
- All right.
- Let's see it.
If Jun Hwan succeeds, give him two points.
- Okay.
- Music, cue.
- All right. Do the moves cleanly.
- Jun Hwan, good luck.
Let's get it.
Have fun.
- Have fun.
- Okay.
Oh, yes. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- One, two, three, four.
- That's good.
- He is doing the move cleanly.
- Spread your legs.
- The textbook example.
That's good.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Oh, yes.
- That's good.
- He is on another level.
- Let's go.
- Heave-ho.
- He is good.
- Is that correct?
- That's correct.
- Out.
(Out)
- That's correct.
- No, it isn't.
- Then what's the correct move?
- Isn't this it?
- This is it.
- This is the correct move.
This is it, right?
- Isn't this it?
- No.
Isn't this it?
- Ms. Yeom, isn't this it?
(It turns into a comical dance.)
- You might be right.
- Isn't this it?
If I remember correctly...
(Ms. Yeom begins to get confused.)
What he did was close.
Would you show us the moves?
Can you redo them?
- Can you redo them?
- Of course.
- Please show us the moves.
- Show us.
Please show us the moves.
Shall I do it without music?
- No.
- Please do it by yourself.
All right.
Ms. Yeom, this is the third move.
- No. Hold on.
- This is the third move.
- Ms. Yeom, this is it.
- What was it?
(She asks her assistant for help.)
- Don't look.
- We need to cover her.
- Cover her.
We need to cover her.
(Grandmaestro is on her own now.)
Let's go.
- One, two, three, four.
Is this it?
Keep going.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- She doesn't know.
- She keeps stealing glances.
The next move.
(She begins the 2nd move.)
It looks strange.
- It looks strange.
- Let's go.
(She begins to do a silly dance.)
- That's wrong.
- Ms. Yeom.
You don't know the moves.
How are you supposed to judge
when you don't know the moves?
Where did this move come from?
- I was on "Infinite Challenge."
- Where did this move come from?
I was on "Infinite Challenge."
That was insane.
That was unbelievable.
What was the move? What was it?
- That was so funny.
- Was that the move?
Ji Hee was close.
- I was close.
- Seriously.
- Ji Hee was close.
- I was close.
Ji Hee was close.
I am sorry. All right.
Three points to them.
She was correct.
Really?
This is the move.
- She was correct.
- Let's move on.
I was correct, right?
- She did well.
- I was correct.
She was correct.
Since it was a bad call,
the score is 1 to 1.
- The last round.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- Let's win.
- The last round.
I think we will win
if you press the buzzer first.
- He has a bad memory.
- He can't remember the moves.
You should press the buzzer
after the fourth move.
- The fourth move.
- This is hard.
- Here comes the last round.
All right. The next song is...
"We Will Rock You," okay?
"We Will Rock You."
(The song for the last round is
"We Will Rock You.")
- The third song, cue.
- The music...
The music hasn't started yet, right?
Bam, bam, bam.
(1st move)
It's cool.
(2nd move)
(3rd move)
Rock you.
(4th move)
These moves are hard.
- You should hit the buzzer.
- I forgot the moves already.
(Flinching)
- That's good. Okay.
- Hit it.
- Okay.
Jun Hwan, Ji Hee attacked you.
- Jun Hwan.
The moves were simple.
Music,
- cue.
- Your fingers are important.
We are set.
- We are set.
- Out.
- Why?
- We won.
Out.
- Why?
He should have begun
as soon as the music started.
- You had an interval.
- No, I didn't.
Earlier...
- You didn't begin right away.
- Yes, I did.
- She began right away.
- I said, "Bam, bam, bam."
You shouldn't show them the move.
You should cut him some slack.
- I won't do that.
- She is a tyrant.
- Ms. Yeom.
- He worked hard...
at the Olympics.
She should receive a doping test.
- You know who he is, right?
- Cha Jun Hwan, a skater.
Sorry.
(She didn't know who he was.)
(Grandmaestro didn't have
much interest in her students.)
- Ms. Yeom...
- I...
She only cares about
"Infinite Challenge" and herself.
I only care about myself.
It's so funny
that she didn't know who he was.
- I thought...
- You know now.
he was an idol singer.
I thought he was an idol singer.
With a score of 2 to 1, Team Ji Hee won.
Okay.
You did well to hit the buzzer.
- Yes.
- You did well to hit the buzzer.
Good job. It was hard.
- It was hard.
- It was good to see Ms. Yeom again.
It was good to see Ms. Yeom again.
Let's give a round of applause
to Ms. Jang Yoo Ri too.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- I laughed so much.
- Thank you for your hard work.
You are the best.
- That was so much fun.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- She was so funny.
- Thank you.
- That was fun.
What?
Ms. Yeom.
(She walks into a wall.)
- Ms. Yeom, it's this way.
- You can head out this way.
- It's this way.
- I mean...
- Do you want to go this way?
I will draw the curtains.
You can go this way.
- Until the end...
- You can go this way.
- All right.
- I will help you.
- I won't go further. Bye.
- She left.
- Good job.
Good job.
(Se Chan saw her out.)
That was so funny.
- That was so funny.
- Seriously.
You did a good job of seeing her out.
- I helped her out.
- That was so funny.
- All right.
- I laughed so much.
With a final score of 8 to 4,
Team Ji Hee won.
(Team Ji Hee won the first mission.)
- Nice.
- We won.
- It was the 1st game.
- Other games remain.
- Thus,
- Captain Ji Hee gets 300 dollars.
- What?
- You get 300 dollars.
Ji Hee, you are the best.
- Captain Jun Hwan gets 150 dollars.
- Okay.
Ji Hee, you are the best.
All right. Please decide on the amount...
- you will give to each member.
- You need to distribute the money.
Please write it down secretly.
- However,
you can't give the same amount of money.
You can't give ten dollars to each member.
- The amount must be different.
- I see.
- Please write down the amount.
- We believe in you.
Here is what other members will do.
If you think you will receive
the smallest amount of money,
put the revolt card into the envelope...
- and put it down.
- Come on.
- We don't need to do that.
- It won't be me.
There is no need for a rebellion.
We should keep things peaceful.
- I believe in my team members.
- We should keep things peaceful.
Think about it.
- I won't do such a thing.
- Who would do that?
I won't do such a thing.
I rooted for you so much.
- Jun Hwan, we trust you.
- We trust you.
That's right.
(How will the two captains
distribute the money?)
Ji Hee, I won't revolt.
Of course not.
- Why would you do that?
- I won't revolt.
She will give us
the right amount of money.
This makes me think.
I can't consult Captain Cha, right?
(The two captains started off
with a small amount of money.)
She will give us
the right amount of money.
Then we can thank her.
Jae Suk, I think Jun Hwan will give us...
a lot of money.
- Of course.
- It's the first time,
so he won't give someone a dollar...
- and someone else 50 dollars.
- That's right.
Thus...
(Did Captain Cha distribute the money
as Se Chan predicted?)
Are you done already?
- Are you done already?
- Why...
(Captain Jin
hurriedly distributes the money.)
- Put it down.
- All right, everyone.
Pick up one envelope.
Okay. Here is my decision.
There is no need to revolt.
He looked at me with his kind eyes.
That's right.
Make sure other people can't see
your envelope.
(What did Captain Cha's smile mean?)
This is nerve-racking.
Look me in the eye.
I made an effort
to distribute the money evenly.
- You made an effort.
- Now,
Captain Cha will reveal the amounts first.
Captain Cha, we trust you.
Captain Cha, please reveal the amounts.
How much?
- How much?
- What are the amounts?
He gave 35, 30, 33, and 50 dollars.
- Did he give me 32 dollars?
- What?
He gave a lot of money.
- He gave a lot of money.
- That's a lot.
- Why did he give so much?
- There was no reason to revolt.
- Hold on.
Ji Hee's facial expression changed.
He distributed 150 dollars pretty evenly.
Please reveal
whether or not you will revolt.
One, two, three.
(Captain Jun Hwan)
(If Se Chan decided to revolt,
the amounts will be switched.)
I chose to revolt.
(I chose to revolt.)
(Se Chan's prediction was spot on.)
I got additional 18 dollars.
That's great.
Captain Cha has 32 dollars...
and Se Chan has 50 dollars.
You are too much.
I couldn't help it.
Next.
Captain Jin, reveal the amounts.
I trusted you.
- Let's see the amounts.
- Okay.
- What are the amounts?
- She gave 70, 40, 80, 30,
and 80 dollars.
(Suk Jin received the smallest amount.)
- She gave a lot.
- Did I get 30 dollars?
Haha got 40 dollars.
- She gave a lot.
- Suk Jin got 30 dollars.
Why did I get 30 dollars?
Ji Hee, he answered
the most number of questions.
I did my best
and led to a score of 3 to 0.
- It means...
- Ji Hee.
- Ji Hee just doesn't like him.
- I feel so betrayed.
Ji Hee, I didn't do much.
Please reveal
whether or not you will revolt.
- Okay.
- I said that I am very trustful.
One, two, three.
(Haha chose to revolt.)
Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
- This team is ruined.
(Captain Jin got backstabbed
after trusting Suk Jin.)
- I know what you are thinking.
- I thought it would be me.
Jun Hwan and Ji Hee are too nice.
They are nice.
Had I been the captain,
everyone would have gotten
less than a dollar.
- Seriously.
- I would have given...
- something like 30 cents.
- I would have given nothing.
Haha, you will receive half the amount.
How about me?
Suk Jin will receive 80 dollars.
- Ji Hee will receive 30 dollars.
- The amounts got switched.
Okay.
Captain Jin, you can send
one member to the other team.
- I will do that.
- Okay.
Me?
I will do that.
(She sends Suk Jin without hesitation.)
- Like I said...
- It doesn't have to be me.
- Okay.
- It can be someone else.
- It's okay. Bye.
- Are you certain?
Jun Hwan.
(His attitude changes right away.)
- Bye.
- I came back to you.
We are set.
- Good job.
- Dad and son.
- Suk Jin.
- They are together again.
Now, Team Jun Hwan has 5 members
and Team Ji Hee has 4 members.
In this mission,
you can win some bonus money.
It's the Sticky Slap-Match.
- Okay.
- It's the game of slap-match.
But we...
- We will be fine.
You will have 5 rounds
of the 1-on-1 slap-match game.
Unlike the regular slap-match game,
- you will use clay.
- Clay?
You will throw your clay first.
Then you will win if you can lift up
the opponent's clay with yours.
You need to make them stick.
(You will win if you can lift up
the opponent's clay with yours.)
- You will win if you can do that.
- I get it.
- You need the other piece.
- You need to make them stick.
- It will require a good aim.
- Okay.
That's right.
Please decide on the order.
Suk Jin will go first.
- Okay.
- Who will go first?
Shall I go first?
I guess Ji Hyo is confident.
She wants to go first.
- Please put it on the floor first.
- It might come off.
Make sure it doesn't happen.
He is the weak link.
Let's begin.
- Like this.
- Will he be able to succeed?
- Watch.
- Would you root for me?
- Okay.
- For goodness' sake.
Aren't we a team?
Suk Jin!
For whom does he fight?
- He is an individualist.
- I will fight for Jun Hwan.
- Is he on our team?
- Jun Hwan.
Here I go.
It's weak.
He is on our team.
- Hold on.
- He is on our team.
- What are you talking about?
- Is he on our team?
- I am sorry.
- We are teammates.
- It's weak.
- Make a square.
- Here I go.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
- He got it.
(He hit Ji Hyo's piece!)
- I got it, right?
- Separate them.
- They stuck together.
- They should stick together.
- I just need to lift it up.
- He got it.
- They stuck together.
- He doesn't know the rules.
They stuck together.
Okay.
(Suk Jin succeeded.)
The score is 1 to 0.
Next players, come forward.
Okay.
- So Min, do you want to go next?
- Sure.
- Who are the next players?
- We will have a referee.
- So Min, this is how you do it.
- When you are playing defense,
you shouldn't do this.
Shall I go next?
- Do you want to go next?
- Use your strength.
Shape the clay like this
when you play defense.
Make a square
so that they can't lift it up.
(Ignoring)
- No.
- So Min, play rock-paper-scissors.
- It will stick better.
- You should do this instead.
- So Min, it will stick better.
Do this instead
so that they can't lift it up.
That works too.
What is this?
You should aim to attack first.
That's too...
If you do that,
it will be easy to lift up.
(She doesn't listen to her teammates.)
So Min is doing well.
This is ours, right?
(Polite)
You know, Ji Hee and Jun Hwan
met again after 11 years,
but they aren't having a conversation.
- This is strange.
- We don't have time to do that.
We are busy playing games.
- They met again after 11 years.
- Shall we have a match?
- Let's do that.
- Let's have a match.
You should do this instead.
- Have you done this before?
- No.
That's good. They won't get it.
It's my first time touching clay
since elementary school.
I didn't even use it in elementary school.
You should do this instead.
Let's begin now.
This would work if you play offense.
- It's a snake.
- So Min.
It's a snake.
It looks like a boa constrictor.
They won't be able to lift it up.
She did well.
Just make it stick.
You got this.
- Good luck.
- That's good.
- All right.
- Let's see what happens.
- What?
- No!
(Haha missed.)
(The expert of the slap-match game
embarrassed himself.)
There is no need to throw so hard.
- Good job.
- Go ahead and make it long.
- What happened?
- Hold on.
- Let's go.
- Just envelope it.
- What?
(So Min doesn't listen.)
- Here I go.
- Hurry up.
So Min...
is bad at games,
but she is unbelievably stubborn.
- Seriously.
- Hurry up.
(A 37-year-old who doesn't listen)
You didn't listen
to your parents, did you?
Be quiet!
You didn't listen
to your parents, did you?
(The daughter who is
going through puberty explodes.)
- It's over.
- Be quiet.
- Why did you miss it?
So Min.
- Will you shape the clay again?
- Shape it.
You should have done that in advance.
You should lump it together.
You should do that when it's your turn.
Mind your business and...
use that method when you play the game.
Stop telling me what to do.
Gosh, I am so annoyed!
(The big brother is annoyed
because of his younger sister.)
If you do that...
- Go ahead.
- If you do that, they will get it.
- You got it.
- Go ahead.
- They will get it.
- You got it.
- Lift it up.
You got it.
- Did you succeed?
- Come on.
- Turn it upside down.
- Go ahead.
- You can do that.
- You succeeded.
- It counts.
- He grabbed it.
- I used techniques.
- Okay.
- The next players.
- Jun Hwan.
- Why don't you listen?
- All right.
- Who will go next?
- Ji Hee should go next.
- Next.
- I will go next.
- They met again after ten years.
They finally met again after 11 years.
- Ta-da.
- They will go against each other.
(They will go against each other
after 11 years.)
They finally met again after 11 years.
- Okay.
- You took a long time.
- Hit it.
- There you go.
(Team Jun Hwan attacks first.)
(How well can Jun Hwan
control his ttakji?)
That's it, Jun Hwan.
- Hit it.
- There you go.
- You will miss.
- That's it, Jun Hwan.
(What?)
(Jun Hwan's clay didn't even go near.)
Jun Hwan.
(Laughing)
That was cute.
- He missed.
- All right, Ji Hee.
- It was right there.
- Jun Hwan.
- It's hard, right?
- You need to throw it down.
Don't act like you are good at this game.
- I should roll it up.
- All right.
I should roll it up too.
- I think it will be easy.
- It won't be easy for Ji Hee.
It's the hardest
when it's shaped like a worm.
- He is spreading it.
- When it's shaped like a worm...
Ji Hee will win.
- Ji Hee will win.
- It won't be easy.
- Ji Hee.
- Ji Hee will totally win.
- She won.
- She won't lift it up.
(She hits his clay!)
- She will lift it up.
- No.
- Grab the end.
- Lift it up.
- Don't press it down.
- She won.
It's over.
- Lift it up.
- It's over.
- Don't press it down.
- Okay.
- Hold on.
(She failed.)
He pressed his clay on the floor too much.
- That's not true.
It's sticking too much.
That's not true.
- You didn't say anything earlier.
- You are just wrong.
Unbelievable.
He pressed his clay on the floor.
- No, he didn't.
- No?
- Then we will do the same.
Okay.
We will stick our clay on the floor
so that you can't lift it up.
- I will do that.
- If you hit it,
- you will succeed.
- Aim well.
I will spread it like a pancake.
- A bit more.
- Are you listening?
- What?
- I will spread it like a pancake.
- Okay.
(The slap-match thug became absorbed.)
I don't know
why I am playing so diligently.
- That's good.
- You should play diligently.
Ji Hee is diligent in everything.
Good.
- Good.
- All done.
- Jun Hwan, just hit it.
- Hit it.
Okay.
- Jun Hwan.
- Jun Hwan, just hit it.
Hit it.
(He misses again.)
- Jun Hwan, it's okay.
- It was cute.
- You are done.
- Hey.
You are as bad as me.
(You are as bad as me.)
- Jun Hwan, it's okay.
- It was cute.
You just need to hit it now.
You are as bad as me.
It must be because there is no ice.
- With this...
- Yes.
Ji Hee.
- My hands...
- Look at my hands.
- We haven't even had our turns.
I did well to pick the white clay, right?
Your hands will turn white.
The white color is fine.
(The white color is fine.)
(Teasing tone)
(For goodness' sake.)
It's better than orange.
- Jae Suk.
- It isn't so apparent.
Please go against Jong Kook.
- Good.
- He is unbelievable.
Our clay looks like a dumpling wrapper.
That's right. It's fine.
The white color is fine.
The white color is pretty.
Our clay looks like a carrot.
How is that a carrot?
- It's a thin carrot.
- A carrot.
It's the worm poop.
It looks like a sweet potato stem.
I can't tease Jun Hwan.
- Attack, Ji Hee.
- Hurry up.
- Spread it and hit his clay.
- We are equally bad at this.
Spread it and hit his clay.
- Keep it close.
- Okay.
Think of hitting it with your hand.
- Put it on your palm.
- I will use my palm.
- That's it.
(She hits it!)
- Did I get it?
- Good job.
Lift it up,
- Don't press it down.
- I won't do that.
- She won't press it down.
- Hurry up.
- Hold on.
- That's good.
- Okay.
- That's how you do it.
- That's good.
- Okay.
That's how you do it. Good job.
- You did well, Ji Hee.
- All right.
- It was fun.
Okay.
- Jae Suk, you go.
- Okay.
You should show them something.
You're the king of slap-match.
Okay. Bring it on.
One on one? Okay.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Jae Suk, you have to win.
You should win. Prove yourself.
Show them something.
You have a snake around your neck.
- Good luck.
- This isn't right.
You should do this.
(You should do this.)
This is what you should do.
- Good luck.
- That's gross.
Okay. I'll listen to music.
My goodness.
(He's wearing
his new Bluetooth earphones.)
- It looks real.
- It looks so real.
You look good.
- Okay.
- My gosh.
(He calms himself down
by listening to music before a match.)
- Okay.
- All right.
You can't touch your clay when you defend.
- Okay.
- We can't touch it.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(A surprise attack)
(Startled)
Why?
- What's wrong?
- Is that what we're doing?
- Okay. Rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay.
- He lost.
- He lost again.
- Good luck.
- Why did you lose?
Okay.
Place your clay.
You should do that.
- Go ahead and do it.
- All right.
- This is perfect.
- It looks good.
This is so easy.
- Do it.
- This is no big deal.
Right on here...
- Do it.
- This is no big deal.
Right on here...
(He fails to hit Jae Suk's clay.)
Leave it as it is.
- It's Jae Suk's turn.
- Leave it as it is.
- Just leave it be.
- This isn't easy.
- I mean...
- It's not easy.
- I know. I agree.
- Okay.
- Go ahead and do it.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- This is a chance.
- I can do this.
- It's not easy.
- Give it a try.
- Gosh, this is...
Spread it thin.
A little...
(Touching)
(Pressing it down)
(Grinning)
Why are your hands sweating?
What did you do?
Did you just press it down?
- What did I do?
- I think you pressed it here.
- Where?
- What is this?
- What about it?
- You can't press it down.
- It has your fingerprint.
- Hang on.
- Look at this. It's stuck.
- I didn't press it.
My goodness.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
- What did you just do?
- I can't believe this.
- Hey.
- Did you press it?
- What?
Did you just press it?
- You can't do this.
- Stop fighting.
- You're not supposed to press it.
- Don't fight.
Why are you doing this to us?
- My gosh.
- Stop fighting.
Did you step on it?
It has your footprint on it.
The three of them stepped on it.
It has three different footprints.
- They did it on purpose.
- You can't do that.
- Go ahead and do it.
- Here I go.
- Hurry and just do it.
- Okay.
- Hurry.
- Hurry and throw it.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
- Yes.
(It sits right on Jong Kook's clay.)
(Embarrassed)
- It's done.
- All right.
- It's stuck.
- This is perfect.
- Okay.
- All right.
(Yoo Jae Suk wins.)
Nice.
- Gosh, this is so upsetting.
- Okay.
- Let's do it one more time.
- I'm really mad.
- Good. You can do this.
- It shouldn't be too hard.
- A moderate amount of strength.
- It's stuck.
Okay.
It needs a moderate amount of strength.
It shouldn't be too hard.
- It doesn't have to be so hard.
- All right.
You get 50 dollars from each round.
You won 2 rounds, and they won 3 rounds.
Okay.
- Yes.
- Nice.
Jun Hwan, don't give me this time.
I don't deserve it.
Ji Hee, give me a lot.
- I did a good job.
- Okay.
- I'm just...
- Well...
I believe in Jun Hwan.
Let's be honest.
One of us must be the last.
I think so.
I bet he will give you
the least amount of money.
I think so.
Because I have a lot of money now.
- You have a lot of money.
- I think so.
What about you?
You don't need the revolt card.
So Min, you don't need the revolt card.
She got the revolt card.
I think that's better.
They try to get
the revolt card every time.
These two... I've been watching them.
They pick the revolt card every time.
Captain Cha, I think you have
a lot of revolts on your team.
I know.
The captains are done
distributing the money.
- We've made our choices.
- Are you done picking your card?
Captain Jin, show us the amounts.
My gosh.
- Ji Hee gets 60 dollars.
- My goodness.
- It's Ji Hyo.
- It's 20, 30, and 40 dollars.
(Ji Hyo received the smallest amount.)
(Ji Hyo gets the lowest amount.)
Okay.
- Well done.
- This is good.
- This is nice.
- I thought you would understand.
All right. You did a good job.
- Should I go first?
- One, two, and three.
- Good job.
- We love you, Captain Jin.
- I love my team.
- Well done.
Captain Cha, show us the amounts.
(Captain Jun Hwan)
It's 30, 20, 20, 14, and 15 dollars.
It's So Min.
(So Min received the smallest amount.)
- It's So Min.
- You should've let me pick it.
See? I knew it. They told me...
Open your cards.
- Okay.
- Open your cards.
- I love you, Captain Cha.
- I love you.
Suk Jin failed to revolt.
- Mine was 15 dollars.
- My gosh.
(She didn't revolt one time
and runs into trouble.)
- You...
- I should've picked it.
- Suk Jin is not the last.
- You told me not to pick it.
It's So Min. She gets 14 dollars.
- Okay.
- I'll get my own way from now on.
Before you have lunch,
Captain Cha can let go of
one of his team members.
Captain Cha, who would you like to let go?
Captain Cha, listen to me.
If we have to release one of us,
it should be someone
who can interrupt the opponents.
None of us will interrupt them though.
- Just pick one.
- Interrupt them...
I pick So Min.
- But...
- Am I the weak link?
Pick So Min.
They are trying to release So Min.
So Min?
- Don't do that.
- Don't be like that.
What's with all the conspiracy?
- Jong Kook.
- This is for the game.
- You can't do this.
- Why not?
Why not?
Just send Suk Jin.
- Just send Suk Jin.
- We want Suk Jin instead.
Send Suk Jin to us.
We already have judges here.
We have our judges here.
- Who?
- I pick So Min.
(I pick So Min.)
All right. Jeon So Min is the weak link.
We don't want her. She's not cooperative.
Go interrupt them.
- She's not cooperative.
- She's...
not cooperative nor good at games.
She's not good at games.
And she's not cooperative.
We already have our fair share
of dumb members.
We don't want her.
She keeps picking the revolt card here.
- I don't want her.
- So Min, you're a spy. Okay?
- Welcome, So Min.
- Take her.
My goodness.
- Don't do this.
- Jun Hwan is really funny.
He didn't even hesitate.
He was firm.
- Gosh, Jun Hwan.
- Jun Hwan.
Now you can have lunch
before the next game.
Captain Ji Suk Jin
decided the menu for you.
- All right.
- Look forward to it.
I'll tell you the exact words he said.
"Jun Hwan, Ji Hee, and
I will have the rice with grilled eel."
"The rest of the members
will have a box lunch."
My goodness.
Can you give...
the grilled eel
only to Jun Hwan, Ji Hee, and me?
What about the rest of the members?
They will just have a box lunch.
I see.
- My goodness. You can't do that.
- You can't treat us differently.
All right. We will bring in the food.
- I did this for you.
- I'm really disappointed.
This is upsetting.
What did we do wrong?
Captain Ji, this is...
We all are supposed to eat well.
He's the only one who gets the eels.
Then I'll have some cup noodles.
- No, you can't.
- It's up to Captain Ji.
- It's just cup noodles.
- Why not?
- You can't have it.
- I need to eat.
- Can I buy one myself?
- No.
- We can eat cup noodles.
- Why can't I buy one myself?
- Let us eat cup noodles.
This is a democratic country.
- Just eat your lunch.
- This is ridiculous.
- What's wrong with cup noodles?
- Why would you eat cup noodles?
- I want to eat it.
- You should eat a box lunch.
Why can't I eat cup noodles?
I was going to give you
rice with some dried laver.
- I can't believe this.
- This is a democratic country.
- Seriously...
- Just eat your box lunch.
- No.
- I don't allow it.
- I want cup noodles.
- Just eat this.
I will eat my own cup noodles.
- We will...
- I need some soup.
Do you want some cup noodles?
I'd be happy to eat it,
but are you done fighting?
Get me three. We will have cup noodles.
Can't I eat my own cup noodles?
You can't.
- You can't have it.
- Why not?
(They were being so childish that
we fast-forwarded the conversation.)
This is so confusing.
My brains are shaking.
I want to eat grilled eels.
- You can't.
- Sit with your team.
I need cup noodles for this box lunch.
You can't have it.
Give me one!
No! I don't want to.
Why can't I have cup noodles?
- You can't.
- Why not?
It's the captain's call.
The rice is dry, so I need some soup.
No. Just eat the dry rice.
He said he'd cut down on the cost.
- What?
- To cut down on the cost...
Then he should quit!
(Then he should quit!)
I want to eat cup noodles.
- I want one.
- Hey!
Good luck.
There's no discipline in Running Man.
(There's no discipline in Running Man.)
Hey! Why did you
elect the captain in the first place?
I have to attend the meeting
in Mok-dong once a week!
I can't believe this.
You should look forward to next week.
Next week, you all...
will have to dress up as women.
I will dress up like a tough man.
(What will happen to Captain Ji
with no leadership at all?)
(The last match between
the two captains finally begins.)
I hear the bell.
(The unique race that
you couldn't even watch at the Olympics)
(The battle between the captains
is getting fiercer and fiercer.)
(Who will be the winner?)
(And...)
(A song that has inextricable link...)
(with Running Man)
(They passionately sing the song
instead of the original artists.)
(What are we going to do today?)
(The BTOB Special...)
(without BTOB)
(A powerful blow...)
(to get rid of all the disappointment)
(They stop at nothing to win the race...)
(with their great chemistry of 11 years.)
(It's been so long.)
(The BTOB Special without BTOB)