(A day
with the typical fall weather)
(They are going to Cheorwon,
which has been put off.)
(The meeting place is
a tofu restaurant in Cheorwon.)
(It's 9:04 a.m. now.)
(Peeping)
So Min, can you open
the car door for a moment?
Why?
(Why?)
Just open it, please.
- It won't take long.
- But I have...
something personal in my car.
I couldn't sleep a wink
on my way here. I need some sleep.
Just open the car door.
- Why? Hang on a second.
- Okay.
- I need to put on some clothes.
- I'm not wearing any bottoms.
- Okay.
(She keeps saying useless things
without opening the door.)
Hello.
- Hello.
Thank you for coming
all the way here to Cheorwon.
- You don't have to get off.
- Why not?
You just need to make a choice
before you start a fun trip.
(You just need to make a choice
before you start a fun trip.)
(Make a choice?)
Choose between go and stop.
(Choose between go and stop.)
Why?
(She's suddenly told to make
a choice between the two.)
Just make a choice.
What if I say Go?
Am I going somewhere?
I can't tell you that.
- Choose...
- Stop.
Stop?
(She doesn't know what it is,
but she chooses Stop.)
- What's going on?
- Hello.
Hello. What's going on?
- You don't have to get off.
- Okay.
Thank you for coming
all the way here to Cheorwon.
Why has Running Man
changed like this?
(Why has Running Man
changed like this?)
Choose between go and stop.
Go and stop?
I should say Go whatever
the result may be. But why?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Go or stop?
(The suspicious quiz
makes him hesitate.)
I bet Jae Suk will say go.
And So Min will go straight.
Go!
- Stop.
- Go!
(They choose different answers.)
Se Chan, you chose Go.
You should go straight
to the opening place then.
- Is that it?
- And, Se Chan,
you are not having breakfast.
- What?
- While those who chose Stop...
enjoy spicy tofu jeongol
at a restaurant,
you will go to the opening place
eating some gimbap.
Darn it. That's ridiculous.
I should've said stop.
So am I eating this?
I'll put the microphone on you.
Oh, no. If I said Stop,
would I have gone there?
(He narrowly missed his chance
to visit the famous restaurant.)
(The first choice was
about breakfast.)
So Min, you chose Stop.
You will stop here for a moment...
and enjoy some healthy foods
before you go to the opening place.
That's nice. What would've happened
if I chose Go?
Myung Jae, am I really leaving?
Yes.
Stop joking around.
Am I really going?
Please hurry and go.
(Laughing)
Let's go.
(She sounds firm telling him to go.)
Okay. You wait and see.
Let's do this.
My goodness.
(With one choice, he gets kicked
out of the restaurant.)
(Meanwhile, So Min
who chose Stop is...)
I'm glad I chose Stop.
This looks delicious.
(Spicy tofu jeongol)
Look at the tofu. It looks so tasty.
(Savory pan-fried tofu)
(A decent meal you can enjoy
only when you choose Stop.)
It's been a long time
since I had such a healthy meal.
(She starts eating happily.)
I should eat this when it's warm.
(This is nothing like cold gimbap.)
(Savoring it)
It tastes so good, ma'am.
(Looking around)
I wish I could have some makgeolli.
(I wish I could have
some makgeolli.)
What do you think?
- That's Jae Suk's voice.
- When you were filming the front...
What do you think?
When you were filming the front,
I came out from the back.
You all look flustered.
What is this?
Go or stop? Choose one.
You know what? I always go.
I go no matter what. I never stop.
Okay? Go!
- Are you choosing Go?
- Yes.
What is this?
Jae Suk, you will have
gimbap for breakfast.
- What about Stop?
- While other members enjoy...
spicy tofu jeongol here...
you will move to the opening place
eating the gimbap.
If I said stop,
I would've gone in here?
(If I said stop,
I would've gone in here?)
Gosh, I have no luck today.
Where's the opening place?
It's a 20-minute drive from here.
A 20-minute drive from here?
(Laughing)
My goodness. Let's go.
Gosh, seriously...
Darn it. I'm so unlucky.
I would normally choose Go.
I go whatever the result may be.
(I go whatever the result may be.)
But I feel like I should say stop.
(But I feel like I should say stop.)
- Go!
- Okay!
Haha, you chose Go.
You should go straight
to the opening place.
(He gets gimbap.)
Why? What would've happened
if I chose Stop?
You would've eaten here
if you stopped.
- Gosh, are you serious?
- You should eat gimbap instead.
(Disappointed)
- Gosh.
- Seriously?
- They are serious.
- This is so upsetting.
- Did you choose Go?
- Yes.
I'm so upset.
Go or stop?
(Jong Kook also faces
the moment of choice.)
I'm not good at the go-stop game.
I just stop betting
once I make some money over a bet.
Make a choice between go and stop.
Really?
Go and stop?
Go or stop.
(What did the three members choose?)
(Laughing)
I wonder who's in there.
Jong Kook.
Hey.
Hey, So Min.
- Jong Kook, this is amazing.
- Is it?
It tastes so good.
- You know what?
- Try this.
I don't know how to play go-stop,
but...
(Card Shark Kim is not bold enough.)
As I said,
"I always..."
"call Stop
once I win enough scores."
"I don't like to take risks."
This is
tofu grilled on a caldron lid.
- Can we get another bowl... Yes.
- Rice?
Hello.
The broth is so refreshing
like a spicy fish stew.
- Wait. Is someone in there?
- Ripe kimchi and shrimp.
- Oh, my.
- Ji Hyo.
- I knew it.
- I knew you'd choose Stop.
Ji Hyo, come and join us.
- I was right.
- Come. I'll scoop some for you.
Jong Kook, how did you know
I would choose Stop?
I'm sure that Suk Jin chose Go.
Please choose between Go and Stop.
Go and Stop?
I'll definitely choose Go.
(He chose Go right away.)
Of course, I choose Go.
What is it?
What is this? Gimbap?
Suk Jin,
you will have gimbap for breakfast.
Gosh. What is going on?
You should leave now.
(Reckless Seok Sam will also
have gimbap.)
Gosh. What was I thinking?
Why did I decide without thinking?
Darn it.
It's good, right, Ji Hyo?
Yes, it's so good.
It's really good.
Oh, right. So Min, I called you.
Why didn't you pick up?
- I was on the plane.
- You were? Oh, I see.
- You both turned off your phones.
- I think you called me then.
I couldn't call you back because
we started shooting once we arrived.
- And...
- In the preview, I saw you two...
- I know this for sure.
- riding in a convertible.
I'm not sure about you two.
But I'm sure that Haha and Suk Jin
would've cried.
- Trust me. It was so scary.
- Really?
You know the glass bridge...
- in "Squid Game," right?
- Yes.
I felt like
I was crossing that bridge.
A strong wind was blowing too.
There wasn't even a safety net
under it.
I'm sure it was doable
because you knew you wouldn't die.
(I'm sure it was doable
because you knew you wouldn't die.)
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
I don't feel scared
when my safety is guaranteed.
Both of their phones were
turned off.
And it made me think,
"What?"
"Will they stay in Yeosu for a while
after the shoot?"
- That's what I thought.
- What?
- You thought we'd stay for longer?
- Yes.
Actually,
we have children now
thanks to the trip.
We have two children.
People might get the wrong idea.
What do you mean by that?
On observational reality shows,
they put a doll...
- next to a cast member.
- Yes.
Just like that, the staff members
put frog dolls next to us.
And the dolls were so cute.
So I suggested that we adopt them
as our children.
I adopted children during that trip,
Jong Kook.
(She said it confidently.)
(Sighing)
You see...
I don't know how to react
when you say something like that.
I usually go along
with others' jokes.
(While Jong Kook and So Min are
suffocated by each other's jokes,)
(the other members moved
to the place for the opening.)
Hey, hurry up and come!
- Gosh.
- Hurry up!
(The members who chose Go
had gimbap.)
You guys chose Go, right?
Go, Jae Suk
- Gosh. This isn't fair.
- Go
- Go, Jae Suk
- Go ahead no matter what
- Go
- Gosh, seriously.
- Oh, man.
Wasn't Go the obvious choice?
Why would anyone choose Stop?
- My gosh.
- By the way,
- I can feel autumn in the air.
- Indeed.
(Today,
I can feel autumn in the air.)
How nice.
A cool breeze is blowing too.
This is driving me nuts.
- Right.
- This is driving me nuts.
I want to pack up and leave!
- Where do you want to go?
- These days...
Aren't we going to shoot
for two days in a row?
What's with him?
- Haha...
- Yes.
Haha has been a little...
- stressed out.
- He wants to escape his daily life.
Well, I wouldn't call it that.
He just wants to spend
some time alone.
Spending some time alone?
Suk Jin.
Didn't Suk Jin choose Go?
- Hello.
- Suk Jin.
- What's wrong with your eyes?
- Why?
- Your eyes are so puffy.
- They're puffy.
It happens from time to time.
Do yours never get puffy?
- Suk Jin.
- Why?
- Hyung In and Hyo Im are upset.
- Why are they upset?
I mean, you should've kept yourself
in good condition for this show.
You went to a foreign country
to shoot another show.
- But I...
- Now, you look so tired.
- I'm not tired at all.
- It's so obvious that you're tired.
- I feel so energetic.
- Exactly.
- He looks like he worked all night.
- Then run around this place.
Yes!
Run faster.
- Not like that.
- Run in a bigger circle.
(He said he was in good condition,
but his running course is so short.)
- What's that?
- He understood what you said.
I'm excited!
He's faking it.
- The four of you chose Go.
- But...
- I can't believe we all gathered.
- You see, I...
- Seriously.
- This is the worst.
- I chose Go without thinking.
- We...
We always push ahead
like tiger moths.
- We push ahead no matter what.
- I chose Go without hesitating.
- You chose it right away, right?
- Of course.
I chose it right away too.
- I said, "Okay. Go!"
- My gosh.
It's so windy like in Denmark.
- Hey.
- Did you choose Stop?
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Yes?
You should put it on
for the opening.
I love this outfit.
- No.
- This is my favorite style.
- You should put it on.
- No.
- Or wrap it around your waist.
- Should I put this on?
- I really like this style.
- Should I put it on?
I really like this style so much.
I like the size and everything.
- You do? Rip this off and keep it.
- Yes.
You're the only one who likes it!
- Isn't it so nice? Look at this.
- He does look so excited.
It's perfect. Right?
The new outfit is so pretty.
- Se Chan.
- Gosh. She's at it again.
- What's going on?
- She drives me crazy since Yeosu.
Oh, is that the doll
you told us about?
- What? She's bringing a frog doll.
- What's with her?
Hey, our babies...
- They're crying.
- What's wrong with her?
(He laughs and says,
"What's wrong with her?")
- Don't just leave them with me.
- I heard a little about the trip.
- I almost died.
- Right.
Oh, she had babies?
- Hey, you gave birth to frogs?
- What's going on?
You can't make me look after them
all by myself.
(The mother of the frogs was
looking after the babies alone.)
- Hey, don't get overly immersed.
- Hello.
- I mean...
- Go to your daddy.
Go to your daddy.
- Let me hold my niece.
- Hey...
- Ji Hyo.
- It strangely looks like them.
So Min always...
- continues the story she made up.
- I can see that.
- Are they twins?
- They have the family name Yang.
- As we conceived them in Yeosu...
- Oh, Yang Yeoguri?
It was a short trip,
but it happened that way.
- Hey, look after your baby.
- It happened that way.
The babies came out so quickly.
- This is driving me crazy.
- So she...
She gave birth to them
in only ten days.
- That's amazing.
- Not even in ten days.
- In only one day.
- I must say...
- So Min.
You are really something.
Haha created an atmosphere for us.
- Oh, you...
- Hey.
- You played Cupid.
- Did he?
- But they...
- Don't do that on a TV show.
- Right.
- They ate so well for a penalty.
They went there to get a penalty.
Then why did they get to eat well?
- That's true, but it didn't help.
- They needed to eat well.
- Suk Jin, the penalty was...
- No way.
- no joke.
- You would've cried.
- I'm sure of it.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Suk Jin,
there wasn't even a safety net.
- I can do it easily.
- It was so scary.
Send him there to try it.
- No way. I wasn't chosen.
- You should try it.
- I rested up thanks to you.
- He's too busy...
doing his show on TV CHOSUN.
- Oh, that show? Right.
- What kind of show is it?
- He's too busy...
- The one he stole your idea for?
- Yes, that's it.
- He stole your idea for it.
- I didn't steal his idea.
- Straw Ji!
Straw Ji!
- Straw Ji?
- Straw Ji.
Straw Ji.
- I like that nickname.
"I'll suck all your ideas."
- "I'll suck all of them."
- Straw Ji.
- That's so funny.
We finally came to Cheorwon,
Gangwon Province.
- We canceled it due to the rain.
- Oh, we're in Cheorwon.
I really wanted to come
to Gangwon Province.
- The sky is so clear today.
- Yes, indeed.
Today, we'll have Go, Stop Race...
- that we had to cancel last time...
- Yes.
- due to the typhoon.
- I should've chosen Stop.
- The food was delicious.
- This week,
for you guys who must've been
stressed out because of the penalty,
- we planned a relaxing trip.
- Sounds great.
- That's nice.
- Great.
- That sounds so great.
- I'm already excited.
Today, all you have to do is
enjoy the trip.
There's only one rule
in this relaxing race.
Just as your choices determined
what you ate for breakfast,
- Yes.
- you have to choose...
between Go and Stop...
- and enjoy the activity you chose.
- Really?
- But there's...
- I see. We have to choose again.
no relation between our choices
and the activities.
We'll keep choosing Go.
It will be hard for you to choose
without knowing what it is.
So you will play a simple game,
and those who are ranked high...
- will get a sound hint.
- A sound hint?
- That's great.
- I like the idea.
- We'll let you hear it.
- Nice.
- I like that. It sounds reasonable.
- Now, I'll explain to you...
about the game Egg Smash
where you can get...
- the first hint.
- What is it?
- Egg Smash?
- I think we'll smash some raw eggs.
- We'll place eggs here.
- Okay.
While all of you are standing
in a circle around the eggs,
- spin a bottle. When it stops,
- Yes.
the member
that the bottle points at...
- becomes the tagger...
- Yes.
- and throws eggs at the others.
- This is popular on social media.
This is popular on social media.
- Really?
- Do people play it these days?
- Some get hit on the head and fall.
- You know that he would...
- They throw raw eggs?
- even eat poop if it were popular.
It won't be popular anymore
since he knows about it.
The member who gets hit by an egg
gets eliminated immediately.
(The member who gets hit by an egg
that the tagger threw is out.)
But if the tagger fails
to hit anyone,
- the tagger gets eliminated.
- Oh, I see.
- One member is out in each round.
- We should run immediately.
- Only the final two...
- I see.
get a hint on the different choices.
(Only the final two get
a sound hint.)
- That's why we should wear this.
- That's right.
- This is a waterproof jacket.
- I see.
- Because of raw eggs.
- I understand.
- We'll begin the first mission now.
- Okay.
- Please bring the props.
- Let's go.
Attention
- Aim at the body.
- It won't be easy to do so.
I have a question.
What are the rules
for running away from the tagger?
- You can start running right away.
- Can we just run in any direction?
- In any direction?
- Run that way.
- No, that way.
- I see.
- We have cameras over there.
- Okay. Got it.
- We should run in a zigzag...
- Toward Cheorwon Station?
so that the tagger can't hit us.
Do you want to have a practice round
or begin the game now?
- We'll begin now.
- I'll throw eggs at your bodies.
- I'm scared.
Who will spin the bottle?
- Then...
- How about Ji Hyo spins it?
- Me?
- Yes.
- Ji Hyo, get ready.
- Here we go.
- Spin it hard.
- Spin it as hard as you can.
It has begun, right?
(She spun the bottle.)
Get your hand off me.
(The person that the bottle
points at becomes the tagger.)
Who's the tagger?
(The other members start running.)
(What?)
(The game rule:
They must run in this direction.)
(Only Jae Suk and Jong Kook
ran in the right direction.)
(The rest ran
in the directions they wanted.)
- It's me.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- I'm the tagger.
Why didn't it break?
Oh, Haha is the tagger?
I'm the tagger.
- Gosh. I didn't know that.
- Who got hit?
- You all must run that way.
- Se Chan got hit.
That way?
- I didn't know he was the tagger.
- He's out.
- I almost threw an egg at him.
- Why?
- How about you start over again?
- This is...
I'm relieved.
Guys, let's start over again. Okay.
Who got hit?
We should start over again.
- Why?
- Why should we start over again?
The rule...
- Who got hit?
- Why?
Hey, he hit someone.
- He hit one of us.
- Exactly.
- You didn't understand the rules.
- We should've run that way.
- Only the tagger...
- Who didn't know the rules?
- That's his fault!
- He didn't know I was the tagger.
- The tagger throws eggs.
- That's his fault!
- He should've known the rules.
- Right. He should be out.
- And... Listen. That's not all.
- It's his fault!
- I asked you to run that way.
- He's out.
- Who ran this way?
- I did.
- You should've run that way.
- She told us to run that way.
- Then 2 of us are out.
- Yes, 2 of us are out.
- She told us though.
- He was eliminated.
- You can't go easy on him.
- Exactly.
- Listen to the director!
- Well said.
- We'll do it again.
- Are you kidding me?
How can you not know the rules?
(We'll do it again.)
- How can you not know the rules?
- How stern of her.
- Yes!
- Nice!
She's giving you an advantage
because you went to Yeosu.
What was that pronunciation?
- It sounded like "ad-fantasy."
- I'll spin the bottle.
- That's just wrong.
- It's for real this time.
Here we go.
I'll spin the bottle.
- Here we go.
- Make it spin.
What if it lands in the middle?
Nicely done.
What the...
I'm it!
(A sharp U-turn)
(I'm it!)
Ji Hyo, you're out.
(Ji Hyo has been eliminated.)
(Chuckling)
It's over.
She ran when she was it.
Why did she run away?
- Who?
- Ji Hyo.
I started to run away.
I tried to make a run for it.
Is it that hard
to understand the rules?
Why are we so bad at playing games?
- Okay.
- Let's do it.
- Hurry on back.
- Gather around.
- You'll then move out.
- Remember that I'm out of the game.
Right.
- What the...
- Gosh.
(Jong Kook will throw the eggs.)
- What the...
- Gosh.
(They run looking intimidated.)
- What the...
- Gosh.
(Jong Kook's target is So Min.)
(He throws the egg at her
since she's still in range.)
(He misses.)
It didn't make contact.
(Jong Kook is out.)
- It didn't make contact.
- Jong Kook, you're out.
(So Min came back from the dead.)
Did he get you?
No, he didn't.
- I'm out of breath.
- This isn't easy at all.
- I was in too much of a hurry.
- Right.
This is nerve-wracking.
- Should I spin it?
- So Min,
you must run
toward Cheorwon Station.
- You...
- Who's going the wrong way?
- It's you, isn't it?
- Eliminate her.
- You must run this way.
- Once more, and you'll be out.
- You'll be eliminated.
- You must run this way.
Gather around.
- I'll spin the bottle.
- What on earth?
- Get back here.
- No.
Come on.
Here we go.
Get back here.
(The bottle spins!)
- It's me.
- What are you all doing?
(Three members head for the eggs.)
(He throws it as hard as he can.)
- It's me.
- What are you all doing?
(It wasn't even close.)
He didn't get anyone.
(Sighing)
It's hard to hit people with eggs.
(He would've gotten her
had he not been greedy.)
- I got confused.
- What happened?
- I could've gotten her.
- Suk Jin, you're out.
Didn't he get anyone?
I could've though.
(His greed got the best of him.)
It's because
you went for the eggs too.
You should've done better.
- Only two more to go.
- Haha, spin the bottle.
- Sure thing.
- Did you go the wrong way again?
- No, I ran that way.
- In 1, 2...
Our feet...
- Okay.
- So Min, you're out.
So Min's out.
(He hit So Min on her side.)
- Did it make contact?
- That's all you need to do.
- Yes, it made contact.
- Yes.
- Only one more to go.
- Only one.
Okay.
We were all on Team Go.
- Go for it.
- Go!
- Go.
- Spin the bottle.
Right?
(They only need to eliminate
one more person to get the hint.)
(Se Chan is it.)
(Fumbling)
Throw it. You're too late.
- You got him. Nice!
- It made contact.
Did I hit Jae Suk with it?
- Really?
- Yes, it made contact.
I got him!
(He calmly aimed a fastball at him.)
You got him.
(It hit Jae Suk's
left bottom cheek.)
- I got him!
- You got him.
- Nice!
- Jae Suk, you're out.
- You actually got him.
- Can you believe it?
I actually got you.
- Accurate, wasn't I?
- How did you manage it?
- I don't know.
- Nicely done.
How did you hit him with it?
- You reminded me of Park Chan Ho.
- I know.
- I sounded old just now.
- How did you do it?
- I almost made it.
- Park Chan Ho?
You reminded me of Ryu Hyun Jin.
(The MVP's victory ceremony)
Only the two of you...
- will receive the hint.
- Okay!
(Se Chan and Haha receive the hint.)
Please choose between Go and Stop.
We can choose one each
and share the information.
- Choose Go. I'll choose Stop.
- Will they team up?
Okay.
Let's share the information.
(They agree to share
the information.)
Go.
(What will he hear?)
(The hint for Go)
Is this rated R?
It must be something weird.
- Get your mind out of the gutter.
- That's...
- Next up is Stop.
- I'd choose Go no matter what...
since that was the wrong choice
in the earlier round.
What are the odds
of it being a bad choice again?
- I...
- I'd choose Go.
(The hint for Stop)
Se Chan, get back here already.
- What is it?
- Hey.
- Okay.
- Get back here.
- What did you hear?
- Hold on.
- Is that the hint?
- Is this...
- what we'd get for Go?
- What is it?
- What was it?
- What's going to happen?
- After hearing that...
- We should know that at least.
You can take the Go route...
or the Stop route.
Hey, mister. Why are you out here?
- What are you doing?
- Are you on Team White?
- What?
- I mean...
- I'm not.
- You're wearing all white.
- I'm Team Blue.
- Team Blue?
(While Jae Suk
keeps talking nonsense)
What I heard
was the subway line number one.
- What about you?
- Is that for real?
- Of course.
- I heard someone panting.
I get it now.
You'll each choose
either Go or Stop.
What did Haha hear?
- Are you choosing Go?
- He knows both options.
- I...
- Did he hear both?
I heard people kissing.
- What?
- More than anything...
You'll be choosing individually.
Of course. I...
- Let's not help them out.
- We could be lying.
Did you hear the hint for Go?
- Who knows?
- Beats me.
- Then...
- Why don't you tell us?
We'll brainstorm with you.
Did you hear a couple in love?
- I think so.
- That must be it.
- A couple in love?
- Yes.
I haven't experienced that
in a long time.
- It's hot.
- You seem excited.
A lot, actually.
My wife texted me yesterday.
- Why?
- Who's next?
- The month...
- She's not going to the US.
Why not?
- After watching the show?
- Rather than going...
(2 weeks ago,
Suk Jin received good news.)
(His wife...)
(will go on a trip to the US.)
(Chuckling)
(He denied it,
but he couldn't stop laughing.)
After watching the show,
she canceled her trip.
(She canceled her trip to the US.)
She wanted me to cancel her flight.
- Really?
- She texted me while I was abroad.
- For real?
- So I texted that I would.
- This is hilarious.
- Really?
- For real?
- She'll still go.
I'm sure she will go.
- She wants me to cancel it.
- Really?
That's understandable.
- My wife said this.
- What?
"Tell me your true intention."
"Were you that happy about it?"
(Not even his wife of 20 years
knew what he really wanted.)
So you're not going to the US.
If you stay in Korea,
you'll be able to save your family.
Happiness and love.
A happy home makes all go well.
Starting with Jong Kook,
you'll privately choose
either Go or Stop.
- Kook Jong.
- Why am I being called first?
We'll start with Suk Jin, then.
No, I'll go first.
You're a weird one.
- Help her out, will you?
- Exactly.
(The suspicious Detective Kim
goes first.)
I chose Stop earlier.
Thanks to that,
I ate a hearty breakfast.
How can you Stop
when you're here to sightsee?
Maybe choosing Stop means
you'll be doing something here.
(He changes his attitude.)
Choosing Go
will move you to another location.
I can't choose Stop all day though.
However, choosing Stop
benefited me earlier.
The better option
wouldn't instantly be Go.
That's why I'll choose Stop.
Because one would think
you'd choose Go.
(What will he choose?)
Go or... I'll choose Stop.
It's my turn now.
- Sure.
- Go ahead.
(Haha's up next,
and he heard the hint for Go.)
This is insane.
(What will Haha choose
after hearing the panting?)
(Se Chan heard the hint for Stop.)
(And he also chooses Stop!)
I'll choose Stop.
(Ji Hyo and So Min
also choose Stop.)
The prankster's back.
No matter what, he'll choose Go.
Go.
I made my choice.
(Jae Suk is the man
who'll always choose Go.)
(And so is Suk Jin.)
My first choice wasn't beneficial.
- Do I go that way?
- Right.
- You all made your choice.
- Sure.
- Go ahead and check the result.
- Let's see what we chose.
This is course number one.
Please!
Please let Go be more beneficial.
- Not two times in a row.
- Please.
Those who chose Go...
are Suk Jin and Jae Suk.
- Really?
- Just us two?
- See?
- Well,
let's see what's in store
for Team Stop.
The two of them...
- on Team Stop means...
- Seriously, you two are...
- We heard.
- We got the hint.
- This is your problem.
- Why?
You don't know that.
The hint could've been a trap.
Please.
(Everyone but Jae Suk and Suk Jin
chose Stop. What is it for?)
Stop. "Those who don't want
to sweat will take the monorail."
- I knew it.
- That's right.
(They get to ride the monorail.)
- All right.
- Okay.
I don't want to sweat
on a day like this.
Stop is a good thing.
Jong Kook got it right away.
(What is Go for then?)
- I see.
- Gosh.
- The observatory on Mount Soi.
- They walk to the observatory.
- Okay.
- This is the worst.
(They will walk
to the top of the mountain.)
- This is the worst.
- Okay. It's hot today.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Right.
- It won't even be fun to watch.
- Hang on. This is...
- Listen.
It's good exercise.
Go wasn't a good thing before,
so it should be good this time.
That's not true.
- And the worst part is this.
- What?
It will take a long time to walk
to the top of the mountain,
- but it won't be fun to watch.
- It's no fun.
So you should make it fun.
You guys should hold hands
and kiss each other.
- Try anything.
- You know what to do.
It took us an hour and a half
to shoot his YouTube video.
And we got three episodes.
I know.
You should make it fun
as you walk. It's your thing.
- This is so annoying.
- It's your thing.
The hint for Go was...
a voice of a dying person.
This one?
(The hint for Go)
(The hint for Stop)
This is nuts.
If things go wrong, I will
have to carry Suk Jin on my back.
(Luggage)
All right then.
Let's go enjoy the first course now.
- Okay.
- Seriously, this is the worst.
- I just ate.
Which monorail train are we taking?
(Team Stop go to enjoy
the monorail train.)
Let's hurry and go.
Go.
This reminds me of the time.
When we went to Switzerland,
- we took the train.
- I wasn't there.
So Min wasn't there.
- Switzerland?
- Let's talk about Switzerland.
- My gosh.
- So Min, you weren't there?
I wasn't there.
She wasn't.
- Hello.
- The middle one?
This is like the one
at an amusement park, right?
This is nice.
Get in the front seats.
You should get
in the front seats with Se Chan.
- In the front.
- Good.
- No, Jong Kook. We're just friends.
- I'll go back.
- I'll sit in the back seats.
- I know.
- I know you two are friends.
- We're friends.
- No, I'll sit here.
- Okay.
- Fasten your seat belt.
- Your seat belt.
Do we have a seat belt?
Se Chan, we need you
to sit in the very back.
Really? Here?
(She's alone again.)
Like this?
- Hey.
- This is good.
He didn't do it on purpose.
- I have no choice.
- He didn't intend to do this.
- This is not what he intended.
- Go.
Shall we go now?
Yes. Let's go.
We should look ahead
when the train leaves.
(We should look ahead
when the train leaves.)
- You should look ahead.
- Look straight ahead.
- It's dangerous.
- So Min, this is about our viewers.
- Don't care about us.
- We'll just stay here in the back.
Our viewers would want
to see your face.
Let's go.
Go.
(Sighing)
So this is what Cheorwon looks like.
(When the monorail train leaves...)
This is really nice.
The weather is nice.
What is this field for?
Is it for perilla seeds?
- Are they perilla leaves?
- I think so.
They are perilla leaves.
Now you two will walk from here
to the observatory.
- You should know this.
- You're being so mean.
In a variety show,
it is hard to make...
scenes about hiking interesting.
- It's no fun.
- But we will make it interesting.
(But we will make it interesting.)
Hey, what are you talking about?
- You...
- You just stay still.
- When you went to Macau Tower...
- I'm talking here.
- with Kwang Soo,
- Just stay quiet.
it aired for 1 minute and 30 seconds
while it took you 3 hours.
It was the worst back then.
Seriously, it was terrible.
- Because I have a fear of heights.
- Give me the camera.
Isn't this for us?
- The thing is...
- Why are you holding this?
- I can carry it.
- This is for me.
It's mine.
It's mine!
Suk Jin, the captain
should carry this.
- You're not the captain.
- I'm the captain.
You know I'm a YouTuber.
I'm used to stuff like this.
Suk Jin. You do it...
only for advertisements.
You can't call yourself a YouTuber.
Hello, everyone.
We are at the foot of Mount Soi now.
What is the trail called?
(The prankster is here.)
Stop it.
What is the trail called?
I think I just heard it.
This is Garosu-gil.
Everyone, this is Garosu-gil.
- You didn't know...
- It's a tree-lined street.
there was a trail like this
on Garosu-gil, right?
(He loses the camera
to Jae Suk again.)
Gosh, why are you
swinging the camera?
Nice shot.
Hello, dear viewers.
We are on a beautiful road
in Cheorwon, Gangwon Province.
In the beautiful forest... Hey.
(He keeps saying his opening line
over and over again.)
Get off me. This is my opening line.
- Suk Jin, that's...
- This place is...
called Sayo-gil.
Look at this. You know
the famous meme of mine, right?
What is it?
What are you doing?
Oh, that thing. I think I saw it.
It was from the 2000s.
I saw the meme.
Something like this will help.
What you are doing is...
- Hello, dear viewers.
- That doesn't help at all.
We just compared Jae Suk's photo
from 20 years ago...
with the one of now.
He's aged a lot, right?
Gosh, how could he...
No one's laughing.
I'm not trying to make you laugh.
(Seok Sam is trying to make this fun
without making people laugh.)
Darn it. Gosh, seriously.
(Sighing)
Why are you doing this?
Why are you yelling at me?
- I'm not yelling.
- You've become quick-tempered.
I'm not yelling.
(Covering his microphone)
Gosh, you're being so annoying.
(Gosh, you're being so annoying.)
Why am I here with him?
(While these two are struggling
to make this show interesting...)
It's going up.
Look at the weather. It's so nice.
It's great. Cheorwon is so nice.
I love Cheorwon!
The weather is beautiful.
What do we do?
Isn't this too slow, by the way?
It should be slow
so we can appreciate...
- the view.
- Exactly.
It was this slow when we took
the train in Switzerland.
- Switzerland?
- The speed is perfect.
It doesn't have to be fast.
- And you can open the windows.
- You should enjoy the scenery.
- Switzerland?
- Yes. It was really nice.
- Swiss.
- It is read the same when flipped.
- Straight or flipped.
- Yes.
It was amazing.
Do you remember that?
We met the chef in Italy...
- Of course.
- Oh, right.
- When?
- You mean, at the hotel?
Yes, at the hotel.
- You mean Tom Cruise's chef?
- Yes.
We had that thing there.
Something like
the Mediterranean menu.
What? Mediterranean?
I think you're eating your hair now.
(She can't get
into the conversation with them.)
We had the truffle there back then.
- Right, the truffle.
- Back then...
Se Chan made a video call.
- What call?
- A video call.
Did he do that?
No. So Min, look ahead.
(No. So Min, look ahead.)
You should sit straight
in the monorail train.
Our viewers would want
to see your face, So Min.
- Our...
- Myung Jae, why did you...
tell Se Chan to go back?
Am I even on screen now?
Of course, you are.
- You look the biggest now.
- You're getting a close-up shot.
Shouldn't I sit in the back?
You look the biggest on screen.
Actually, he could've sat here.
Really?
Nice.
I thought it would be
too cramped here.
- You did?
- Yes.
- I need to talk to you later.
- You're with us.
- Why are you feeling lonely?
- Right. So Min, you're with us.
I will need to talk to you
when we get off.
We are all together here.
So Min, look far ahead.
- Right. Otherwise, you'll get sick.
- Look far ahead.
- This is nice.
- Looking at green is good for you.
It is nice.
I wonder where
Jae Suk and Suk Jin are.
- This is nice though.
- Hang on.
We walked only this much.
What's so nice about that?
Suk Jin! Everything
you say is fake.
- It's not fake.
- We walked only this much.
- Do you not like it then?
- Gosh.
This is my first hike
in about 20 years.
And we shouldn't be too slow.
We should hurry.
No, wait.
- Let's walk slowly.
- Why?
That's the mission. Don't run.
But it will take forever.
(Humming)
Singing
- Gosh.
- Why did you stop already?
I'm tired after only a few steps.
(What he just did was also fake.)
(Jae Suk runs first.)
Shoot.
(Humming)
(Groaning)
Go!
- Gosh, that prankster...
- Go!
Why is he so energetic?
- Let's go up. Come on.
- Hey.
- Hey, come on.
- Just walk.
(He even forces
the production crew to run.)
My goodness.
- Hurry and come here.
- Hey.
You will get exhausted
at the beginning then.
I won't get exhausted.
How long will it take?
We should go up there.
This is nice though.
(Even the production crew
are getting exhausted.)
It's nice to have a walk
after a long time.
Hiking makes your legs strong.
You should take care of Suk Jin.
See? This is like
a short track race.
You should come together.
What?
Take care of Suk Jin.
- Are you all right? Are you okay?
- Yes.
Please take care of Suk Jin.
Look at you.
Why did you suggest this
when you can't even pull it off?
Suk Jin, hurry!
(Panting)
Gosh, I'm tired.
(Seok Sam faces a crisis
only 20 minutes into the hiking.)
How can he be so energetic?
My goodness.
(He comes down to help Suk Jin.)
Have some soft music ready.
Put it on the turntable.
Why?
This should look touching.
What do you mean?
I'll go up the hill
carrying you on my back.
- Hey.
- It will be touching.
- You can't do that. I weigh 72kg.
- Suk Jin.
- Let's make this touching.
- What are you talking about?
We should make a good scene
that runs for at least five minutes.
- Okay.
- Let's say you're exhausted.
Have the music ready.
I can't walk anymore.
- I can't go.
- Suk Jin, we have to go.
- No, I can't. I give up.
- Don't worry.
I can't.
(When he is about to give up,)
(his colleague offers his back
to help him up.)
Hey, I don't think you can do this.
To you
(When his eyes lose focus...)
(and death stares him
in the face...)
- You're strong.
- I know.
This is enough.
All right.
Let's go to the car.
No.
(Now that he's got enough air time,
he finishes it up.)
Suk Jin.
- A car is coming.
- Let's hop in.
- Can we hitchhike?
- Keep going.
- Let's hitchhike.
Let's do it.
(Passing by)
- He passed us.
- Who was in the back?
Gosh.
Is he just leaving?
You should hop in.
(Jae Suk wants to keep walking.)
Let's get a ride.
- How far do we have to go?
- I think we can walk there.
It's not that far.
Then let's just go.
You should get a ride.
(He has no plan to get a ride.)
(Sighing)
You should get a ride.
(Everyone is dying except
for the grasshopper.)
Just get a ride.
How far do we have to go?
(How far do we have to go?)
You should get a ride, sir.
Because of that punk.
(So the painful march begins.)
Because of that prick.
Don't you think...
Suk Jin would ask for a ride?
He'll be like, "Did we get enough?"
- Right.
- He'd totally say that.
- But Jae Suk would never allow it.
- Yes.
He'll be like, "Suk Jin.
We can't do that."
(They even got
how Jae Suk would react.)
The air is fresh here.
It's really pretty.
Enjoy phytoncide.
- Phytoncide.
Sweet.
- It's sweet.
- It's delicious.
So Min. Did you spend
a night in Yeosu?
No, I went home that night.
- When we went to Switzerland...
- Right.
(Bringing back the memories
from Switzerland again)
When we were in Yeosu...
- Do you remember?
- To be honest,
- I liked New Zealand better.
- Me too.
- I prefer New Zealand too.
- New Zealand was...
- nothing compared to that.
- It was the best in my life.
I'm curious.
Did you all go to New Zealand?
- Yes.
It's nothing compared
to New Zealand.
- The wind...
- Do you have your phone with you?
- If we take a photo here,
- It'll be hard to walk up here.
- it'll look like New Zealand.
- The trees.
Like New Zealand?
Myung Jae. Take a photo of us,
and see if it looks like
New Zealand.
So Min. Why don't you take
a photo of us?
- Should I?
- Right. Take a photo of us.
Do you want me to? I'll do that.
I'll take a photo of you.
I will do that. Just wait.
Here.
(Tilting)
- Wait.
- No. You shouldn't be in the photo.
- There's a ghost.
- So Min.
(A photo by an uninvited guest)
One, two, three.
Forever our memory.
We just made a memory in Cheorwon,
So Min.
- The mountains are beautiful.
- Right?
- The mountains in New Zealand...
- Hey!
Listen to what New Zealand was like.
It was just...
(The train heads to the peak
with the story about New Zealand.)
I think we're here.
- It's going up.
- It's steep.
Is it because we're near?
This is it.
Is it because it's dangerous?
- We're almost there.
- It must be very high.
Cheorwon.
It'll be fun when we go down.
This is what I'm talking about.
- Are you scared?
- What?
He's scared.
- Are you scared?
- Really?
- I was thinking...
- Hey. Look here.
the train moving back
due to a broken brake.
I was thinking about the same thing.
- You're very imaginative.
- Right?
Se Chan. Wasn't it this high
when we walked?
- Yes, it was about this high.
- It was really high.
Hey. Navis Swing was...
(Talking about New Zealand again)
- Seriously.
- That...
- Don't even get me started.
- That was incomparable.
- So Min. Navis Swing is...
- That was like 63 Building.
- only for heroes.
- Yes.
- Are we taking this again later?
- It's worth coming to Cheorwon.
- Yes.
- Let's hop off.
(Meanwhile, the walking team)
(Panting)
Don't worry about me. Go ahead.
Give up on me.
- Give up on me. Abandon me.
- Come on.
- Leave me here.
- Let's go.
- Leave me.
- Come with me.
Leave me.
Look.
Director.
Are you walking backwards?
The audio director.
- If you do that, what would I do?
- She's walking backward.
You don't have to keep the mask on.
Hey. How heavy is that?
(Hey. How heavy is that?)
I'm an ordinary man.
He's the weird one.
(Panting)
Try walking backwards.
It's a lot better.
This is good exercise.
(The steep hill continues.)
It's steep.
("Steep" by Ji Suk Jin)
Why are you so steep?
- Suk Jin. Come on.
- Steep.
How come...
you never compromise with the world?
Hurry up.
No. I know...
how to take care of my mind.
I'm not tired. Okay.
I'm not tired.
I hike every morning.
- This isn't enough to exhaust me.
- Hurry up.
Mind control.
Yes, I can control my mind.
(Suk Jin brainwashes himself
to keep going.)
The one I took was an easy course.
How far does this go?
(How far does this go?)
Hyung In!
Why are you holding us back?
From the start. Why?
Hey! Have you reached this age?
- Suk Jin's starting to get mad.
- Hey.
She's acting like
she didn't hear us.
- She's pretending not to hear us.
- Hey! Give us a hint.
- Look at her back.
- You should've given us a hint!
You should've sneaked up...
- and told me to stop...
- That's funny.
(Stop...)
Hurry up.
(Panting)
It's definitely a go next time.
It's a go no matter what.
I'm telling you now.
- I'll do the opposite.
- I'm only going to say go.
Haha. Is it awesome?
(Team Monorail reached
the observatory.)
- Is it awesome?
- This is unbelievable.
It's like a postcard.
(Exclaiming)
It's a hot place.
Are you sure this is Korea?
It's an observatory.
It's pretty.
(You can only see golden
Cheorwon plain...)
It's worth posting on social media.
It's beautiful.
(On top of Mount Soi.)
This is amazing.
Can you believe it?
It's pretty. The sky is perfect.
It's wonderful.
I didn't know how beautiful
Cheorwon was.
(Everyone exclaims at the view.)
It's marvelous.
(Taking a selfie)
It's beautiful.
I think I've seen a drawing
like this before.
- It's amazing.
- I think I've seen it.
- Jae Suk.
- You're here.
It's magnificent.
(Speechless)
- It's beautiful.
- Yes.
It's great.
This is really...
- Should I step up here?
- No, it's okay.
Will you move?
(Getting in the way)
It was perfect.
Then some guy came in.
Excuse me.
- Some guy barged in.
- Jae Suk.
(Some guy barges in
and ruins the trip.)
- Jae Suk.
- Hey.
You pricks.
It's wonderful.
Having fun?
- The audio team's in the back.
- Hey.
Having fun?
Okay. One more time.
- Seriously.
- Oh, come on.
- Get out of there.
- No.
(Even though he's exhausted,
he still wants to get in the photo.)
- It's amazing.
- I feel like I'm on a trip.
- Hey.
- By the way...
You should try walking.
It's worth it.
- It's worth it?
- Yes.
"You should try walking.
It's worth it."
Sir.
- It's really nice.
- It's beautiful.
It's very nice.
- It's nice.
- It really is.
Suk Jin. Your wife...
didn't go to the US.
You should bring her here.
- I should bring her here.
- Yes. It's only an hour and a half.
- Her trip to the US is canceled.
- Yes.
- It takes 11 hours to the US.
This is only an hour
and a half away.
Are we playing a game here again?
It's going to be a simple game.
I'm telling you now
my answer is a go.
- What?
- My answer is a go.
- Go?
- Because...
I've been saying go.
What if I change it now,
and it turns out Go was
the best option?
Are you going to take responsibility
for my life?
- Why should I?
- Are you?
- Why are you betting your life...
- Suk Jin.
- on go?
- Try it at least three times.
Right? Try it at least three times.
It has to be a go now.
I have no other choice.
- Okay.
- This is a simple mission.
It's going to get difficult now.
I'm going to give you cards.
Draw two cards each.
Three people with the highest sum
will get the hint.
(You'll draw 2 cards, and 3 people
with highest sum will get a hint.)
- Nice.
- That's nice.
Give them to me.
(Getting up)
You see...
I'll mix them up.
Do you like playing cards?
- Do you play cards often?
- Yes.
He couldn't hold back
after seeing the cards.
- The cards...
- When I was in the army...
You're very good.
- You're good.
- When I was in the army...
- He's the son of Jeongseon.
- Were you a dealer?
- Yes.
I'm the son of Jeongseon.
- Did you take lessons?
- Yes.
- The son of Jeongseon.
- His eyes shone after seeing them.
- I'm the son of Jeongseon.
- When he saw the cards...
I'll distribute them.
Distribute them randomly.
- When you do this,
- Sit there.
- the bottom cards are the best.
- He's looking at them.
You can't cheat.
- What are you doing?
- I wasn't cheating.
- Who cheats like that?
- Jae Suk.
- You should've done it in secret.
- Right.
- Who cheats like that?
- I'm sorry.
(Pretending to mix them up)
I'm getting nervous.
I'll give you one each.
- Like this?
- Yes.
Don't we get to choose?
Why don't we open one?
- What?
- I'll open mine.
Why don't we put it up
on our foreheads and exchange?
- Shall we?
- On the forehead?
Now...
- We'll pick one now.
- Let's pick one.
- Pick one.
- Okay.
(They'll pick the second card.)
I wonder what it is.
In the last month,
Suk Jin never...
- looked so...
- He's so excited.
I'm the son of Jeongseon.
I think I got it.
You did? Look at it nicely
if you want to be on TV.
- It's me.
- Se Chan. It's too low.
- Let's reveal one each.
- Yes.
One.
Two.
(Revealing the first card)
- Three.
- Four.
Six.
- Two.
- Three.
Four size. It's only nine.
- Two.
- I can't believe I got a two.
- Mine isn't that bad.
- This is terrible.
- It's nice.
- You and I will get the hint.
- You and me.
- Next.
Let's reveal the next card
one by one.
Starting with Haha.
One, two, three.
- Six.
- That's terrible.
- Se Chan.
- One, two, three.
- Eight.
- It's out.
- So Min.
- One, two, three. It's 11.
- Eleven.
- You are number one so far.
(So Min: 11)
Suk Jin.
It's 14.
- Ji Hyo.
- It's ten.
It's ten.
- Jong Kook.
- It's ten.
Jong Kook.
Oh, yes.
- It's 19.
- Gosh,
it's a king card.
(Jong Kook: 19)
(Jong Kook ranks 1st.)
(Jae Suk will be in the top 3
if his total is 11 or higher.)
It's a king card.
- A king card.
- It's ten.
- You and me.
- We are picking the top three.
- The top 3.
- My total is 11.
So Min, Jong Kook, and Suk Jin
will listen to a hint.
Choose if you want a hint
for Go or Stop.
Go all the way.
I chose Go all along.
Thank goodness.
A hint will help me a lot.
I will listen to a hint for Stop.
I will listen to a hint for Go.
A hint for Go.
(Suk Jin chooses a hint for Go.)
Go all the way.
You want to make sure your hand is
on the T grip at all times.
Good, wide paddle grip.
And your feet are wedged
at all times.
If you wedge your feet
and paddle aggressively,
you will tend to stay in the boat.
- Can I listen to it again?
- No.
Gosh.
- Was it a hint for Stop?
- I would know if I listen again.
I will choose a hint for Go
since he chose a hint for Stop.
- It was a hint for Go.
- His facial expression... Really?
- Yes. You have an advantage.
- A hint for Stop.
I will listen to a hint for Stop.
Hold on.
(Listening to a hint for Stop
for the 2nd course)
- Is that it?
- Yes.
Did you listen to a hint
for Go or Stop?
- A hint for Stop.
- Stop.
- What was it for again?
- For Stop.
(Listening to a hint for Stop
for the 2nd course)
What's this sound?
Did you listen to a hint
for Go or Stop?
Stop.
- It was a hint for Stop, right?
- Yes.
- I will choose Go.
- Go.
We should choose Go this time
because we had two Stops.
Haha, please go first and choose.
(Haha goes to choose
either Go or Stop.)
You should let me hear it.
- It's so confusing. The sound...
- Suk Jin, was it a hint for Go?
- Yes.
- I have no idea.
So Min, you have no idea, right?
I have no idea. The sound...
It was... But it didn't sound good.
I was so flustered.
I was flustered too.
I wanted to listen to it again.
Were you flustered too?
It hit me so fast.
I didn't understand anything.
Maybe there isn't a twist.
Maybe choosing Stop is always good.
Is it time to choose Go?
We had two Stops earlier.
(Confused)
I chose one.
(So Min was torn
after hearing a hint for Stop.)
I am nervous, but...
It was the sound of wind.
It was the sound of strong wind.
(Jong Kook guessed it to be
the sound of wind too.)
What will you choose?
What?
- I will choose Go.
- Really?
- I bet Suk Jin will choose Stop.
- I know.
Suk Jin will choose Stop
no matter what.
Why would I do that?
I would choose Go.
He chose Go.
Think about it.
(Jae Suk chose Go
3 times in a row.)
Go.
- I chose Go.
- Did you choose Go again?
I will choose Stop.
- Go.
- Did you choose Go?
- Everyone chose either Go or Stop.
- It was the sound of the wind.
I will give you the board
for the second course.
- This is driving me crazy.
- This is bad. What did you choose?
- Did you choose Stop?
- I chose Go.
- Then you will be fine.
- Those who chose Go are...
Haha, Se Chan, Jae Suk,
and Suk Jin.
- That's unlucky. This is bad.
- Stop.
- This is a disaster.
No, I am sure Go is a better choice.
Those who chose Stop are
Ji Hyo, So Min, and Jong Kook.
- I...
- Team Go, come here.
- I chose Stop.
- He sounded like a pilot.
- Reveal Go first.
- Go.
(Go gets revealed first.)
Go.
(Stop was a better option 2 times.
How about now?)
I bet Go is an easy one.
Go.
(2nd course)
(Go: Ride a rubber boat.)
- "Ride a rubber boat."
- What does that mean?
(A rubber boat?)
You will go rafting at Hantan River.
(Rafting at Hantan River)
- Thank goodness.
- We will get wet. We will fall.
(Rafting will be thrilling
in the strong current.)
- Thank goodness. I am glad.
- We will get wet. We will fall.
We dodged the bullet.
- Hey.
- We dodged the bullet.
- Rafting?
- For goodness' sake.
- Go was a bad choice twice,
- Hyung In.
- so it should be a good choice now.
- Stop it already.
- Three Stops are ridiculous.
- What was the English?
- It was the instructions.
- The instructions of paddling.
- What's Stop?
(Suk Jin heard a hint for Go.)
You are paddling a boat today.
You want to make sure your hands
cover the t-grip at all times.
Good, wide paddle grip.
And your feet are wedged
at all times.
- The instructions of paddling.
- What's Stop?
Stop changing into another outfit.
Enjoy a relaxed motorboat ride.
- A motorboat.
- A motorboat is a good idea.
Three Stops are ridiculous.
- Why isn't there a twist?
- That's insane.
(They can enjoy a motorboat ride
as they look at the view.)
(Jong Kook heard the hint for Stop.)
(It was the sound of calm waters.)
Three Stops are ridiculous.
Why isn't there a twist?
- There should be a twist.
- I told you not to do that.
Stop it already.
Jae Suk,
you should choose differently.
You should choose differently.
- Stop being stubborn.
- Jae Suk.
- Seriously.
- For goodness' sake.
Jae Suk and Suk Jin
are so bad at choosing.
I thought it was the zip line.
- This is ridiculous.
- What if...
What if we choose Stop at the end...
only to have everyone go home
except for us?
- Team Stop might have to stay.
- Stop.
- That would be the worst.
- That might happen.
- "Visit the dam before going home."
The members have been divided
into rafting and a motorboat ride.
- This is fun.
- Let's move on.
- For goodness' sake.
- This is why we brought underwear.
Not giving a twist is fun.
- Let's go.
(Suk Jin's original seat)
- Why did you sit over there?
- I will tell you.
- Just let it go.
- Is it because of the sun?
- It's because of the sun.
- Hey.
- He moved because of the sun.
- That was the reason.
- Unbelievable.
- He is the worst.
- Also,
he doesn't think
it will be a long ride.
- My goodness.
- That's why he sat here.
My goodness. So Min.
- Unbelievable.
- Suk Jin didn't take that seat.
Why not?
- The sunlight.
- I see.
I hope his side gets the sun
as soon as we hit the road.
I am sure
that side will get the sun.
Suk Jin is so funny.
It's cool.
The weather is so hot today.
He said, "It's cool."
We talked about watching
the FIFA World Cup on December 24th.
- No.
- What do you think?
No. I want to watch it
with my family.
I don't want to watch it with you.
I will buy you dinner.
Will there be a camera?
- No.
- Then I will go.
Why would there be a camera?
Isn't it a shoot
for "Ji Suk Jin World?"
I wouldn't do that.
- Actually, that's a good idea.
- You might do that.
Is it for "Ji Suk Jin World?"
- No.
- You might do that.
- "Ji Suk Jin World."
- It isn't for my channel.
It will take about 20 minutes
to get there.
- You can relax during the ride.
- It's pretty long.
Okay. Is there a game?
- No.
- Is it really a therapeutic trip?
Can we relax?
This is a therapeutic trip.
- You can talk among yourselves.
- That's good.
This would be therapeutic
for Team Stop.
Three consecutive Stops
make no sense.
This isn't therapeutic at all
for Team Go.
- It's so nice.
- Did you choose Go?
How many more times
are we choosing Go or Stop? Twice?
You will choose once for a meal.
Then one more choice remains.
- Twice more.
- Really?
- Seriously.
- It's about time it's Go.
- But...
- Seriously, Go...
- It can't be Stop all the time.
- I know.
Those who chose Go all along
can't switch to Stop now.
- I know. It's impossible.
- I will keep choosing Go.
I will choose Stop the next time.
- I will choose Go.
- I can't do this anymore.
What's that saying?
"Push forward no matter the result."
- Right. I would be so upset.
- Choose Go.
Go.
(Where are you?)
- You are thorough.
- He heard the song.
You are thorough.
- "Confession."
(He gives an encore performance
as he wrinkles up his face.)
- The title sounds like "Choose Go."
- "Confession."
You are thorough.
Let's make a two-line poem.
If we travel a bit more,
we will reach North Korea.
Suk Jin, you should go.
- You should go.
- Hey.
- Is that for Go or Stop?
- Suk Jin.
- You should go.
- Go.
- Defect from North Korea.
Defect from North Korea.
Let's go.
I never said I will go there.
Haha, if you defect from a country,
- it means you escape.
- Is it "Escape from South Korea?"
- What is it then?
- "Defect to North Korea."
- For goodness' sake.
- "Escape from South Korea?"
You are so ignorant.
- I said it.
- This is driving me crazy.
Why did you suddenly bring that up?
The North and South used to be one.
Make an acrostic poem
with the syllables of Cheorwon.
- Do that.
- C.
Come on and get more mature.
- W.
- Won Cheol.
- Won Cheol?
- Suk Jin.
It's my friend's name.
- Good job.
- Come on, Suk Jin.
- Jae Suk. C.
- Give me the first letters.
- Go ahead.
- Chul Soo.
- Wo.
- Won Chul went somewhere, right?
- You focused on the tone.
Seriously.
- Se Chan.
- Are you North Korean?
Since we are close to North Korea,
I used that accent.
- C.
- Haha. C.
Chul Sook.
- You are acting.
- W.
Everyone is using a funny tone.
- Chul Sook.
- W.
Won Chul is here.
C.
Keep going and you will reach it.
It's "Keep."
- It's okay.
- You can't do that.
W, to Wonju.
Suk Jin, come on.
- From Cheorwon to Wonju,
- You can't do that.
- the distance isn't long.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
- Give us an acrostic poem. C.
Childish behaviors
won't get you anywhere.
- Good.
- W.
Wimp.
(It comes out of nowhere.)
- That was sudden.
- Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
- That was sudden.
- It was the Gen Zers' style.
It was so cold
that I almost teared up.
- It was scary.
- It was so cold.
She put her emotions into it.
She suddenly became emotional.
Jong Kook. C.
Childish one.
- O.
- One, two, one, two.
- One, two.
(Sudden attack)
- You prepared it.
- You got me surprised.
You prepared it.
- "One, two, one, two."
- That was nice.
- Isn't it nice?
- It's good.
- One, two, punch.
- That was nice.
- "Childish one" was...
- "One, two, one, two."
It's under a shadow here now.
- What did you say?
- It's under a shadow now.
- S.
- What?
So many restaurants here
have delicious food.
- D.
- Definitely going to the one...
we always visited.
What was that?
He...
- It's...
- Can you do it then?
It was like a video letter.
S.
Say what you did
the day before yesterday.
- D.
- Don't stay at home all the time.
(Confused)
What's with that North Korean
accent?
- You try it then.
- Is it because we're close to it?
- Yes.
- Just bring it on.
- S.
- He said, "Bring it on."
Such an old...
- D.
- Dude.
(Such an old...)
(Such an old dude)
- Well done.
- I was going to say that too.
- It's over.
She kept looking at me.
- "Such an old..."
- She wanted me to ask her.
It was the best one.
It's nice.
Let's see how you guys do it.
It's funny.
Those who chose rafting
should get off.
- See you.
- You got this.
- Okay.
- See you later.
Good luck.
I should wear a cap.
Give us some suncream at least.
Gosh, it's so pretty.
Look how clean the water is.
That's true.
Look how pretty it is.
Isn't it so pretty?
(The view near the river is as
refreshing the wide field.)
It's cool.
(The view near the river is as
refreshing the wide field.)
- I guess he likes water.
- That's unusual for him...
to say it's pretty
after seeing something like this.
- I always liked stuff like this.
- You like water.
More than trees.
Gosh, my father would love
this kind of place.
I just like seeing pretty things.
Nice.
(Screaming)
(Peekaboo)
Hey, what are you doing?
(They were so surprised that they
scream and walk in weird ways.)
- Why?
- What is it?
What is it?
It's a cute frog.
What was it?
- A frog.
- It's so big.
- It's a frog.
- It was so big.
No, it wasn't. It was a baby.
- I almost stepped on it. Saw it?
- It was a baby.
I didn't see it.
It was a baby.
It came here.
Something...
- It went between So Min's legs.
- passed by me, which surprised me.
I almost stepped on it.
Hey, your nickname is Frog.
You can't be afraid of frogs.
It was this big.
That's not big.
(People might think
they saw a venomous snake.)
I don't think we'll get wet.
Fortunately, we won't get wet.
Nice.
It's pretty.
"A ship to 100 million years ago?"
Did this exist
100 million years ago?
No. It means the river
was formed 100 million years ago.
- You mean the waterway?
- I guess so.
- Let's get on.
Let's board.
It's nice.
I guess this seat
is for the instructor.
I won't get seasick, right?
It's pretty.
No scary things, right?
It's nice.
How can the rocks look like that?
- Don't you agree?
- Right?
It looks like it's carved.
Let's look over there
and make a V sign.
Nature is so...
(Nature makes Jong Kook
sentimental like a girl.)
We're so unlucky.
Why do we have to go rafting
all of a sudden?
(As known as scaredy-cat quartet)
Four scaredy-cats are doing it.
- The best scaredy-cats.
- But...
Jae Suk looks quite brave
when he's with us.
He also shakes once it starts.
(A rafting challenge of the guys
who are equally cowardly)
Gosh, doing rafting here...
I've never done it in my life.
(A rubber boat will quickly pass
by the narrow stream.)
Why do I want to fart
when I'm nervous these days?
It's because you're old now.
It's cold as well.
Oh, gosh.
(The scaredy-cat quartet will never
pay to do this!)
How come we got to do this?
You should pull it. Or you'll die.
Haha, a rock or water plant
can go into the hole here.
That's not it. The boat can flip
over and you'll bump into the rock.
Your teeth will be gone.
Here's the instructor
who will explain rafting to you.
- How come...
- Hello.
- four cowards came here?
Hello.
- You should start rafting now.
- Okay.
- Before we begin,
- Yes.
- I'll teach you how to use...
- Okay.
foot loops.
- What? Foot loops?
- Yes.
Then we'll go down to the river
immediately and take the boat.
- Okay.
- For your information,
I don't know if you know it,
but we didn't volunteer to do this.
We picked something
and they made us do this.
- We don't actually...
- Please make it safe.
- enjoy rafting very much.
- I see.
There must be advanced,
intermediate, and beginner courses.
- It should be for beginners.
- Depending on the difficulty.
- We'd like a beginner course.
- A beginner course.
Our reactions will be big enough
even if it's a beginner course.
Four scaredy-cats have gathered.
Were you not going to do this...
if we had all stopped?
Yes.
- I see.
- Do you think it would've happened?
- I have no words to say.
- Okay. What should we do, sir?
Come here.
Which spot is scary?
- I'll sit in the back.
- Which one is the scariest spot?
It's more fun in the front.
- No, then...
- I'll sit in the back.
- No.
- Put your hand here.
- That's where you sit?
Put your foot into the foot loop
and twist your legs.
It might slip off.
It's going to be safe. Don't worry.
- I got it.
- Please take care of us.
Okay. Did you get it?
- Yes. We got it.
- Yes. We'll listen to you.
- Let's move to the river.
- Okay.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
Yes, sir.
- Yes.
- Why did I choose this?
Stand in two rows.
Okay.
We're such cowards. We think he'll
give us a fun ride if we behave.
"Yes, sir." We said it so nicely.
(Scaredy-cats who listen well
when they're scared)
It's cold as well.
Oh, gosh.
- The wind is also cold.
- Why is the stream strong there?
- All of a sudden.
- Oh, gosh.
Do we have to bring it down there?
Does it hurt?
(Laughing)
- He has a horrible look.
- But it's so...
- Because he's scared.
- I'm a little scared.
- Do you want to see your mom?
- I'll sit in the front.
Shall we go down?
- Stand in groups of two.
- Okay.
Yes. 1, 2.
- Do you see the handle?
- Yes.
- Here?
Hold the handle and put it up.
- It's heavy.
- Oh, my.
- One, two.
- Let's go in.
- My gosh.
- Please take good care of us.
- I've never done rafting.
Seriously, why am I rafting
all of a sudden?
Please push the boat.
Should we push it?
We got to do this
because we chose Go?
It seems fun though.
When will we ever get to do this?
Suk Jin, why do you...
- I'm assuring myself.
- It's because he's scared.
- That's why he talks to himself.
- Why are you talking to yourself?
- I'm assuring myself.
- It's because he's scared.
It looks very fun.
Honestly, as men,
we should enjoy this
more than the small boat.
Who will get on it first?
- Should I go first?
- Those sitting in the front first.
- Those sitting in the front first?
- Sit in the front.
- Please get on.
- Let me get on the boat.
(Jae Suk gets on the boat while
Seok Sam is hypnotizing himself.)
- Gosh, this is...
- I'm scared.
Which one is the front
and which one is the back?
- Should I go further?
- Towards the front.
- Here?
- More?
Like this. Yes.
- Like this. Yes. It's fine.
- Like this?
You look cool.
- Those who will row with us.
- We need them to go with us.
(The staff members got on as they
need a certain number of people.)
Gosh, I can't believe
I'm doing this.
I've never done this.
I can't believe I got to do this.
- Hey.
- It's done. Oh, my gosh.
- In the back, it's too...
- Be careful.
Are you wearing this?
- It's kind of cool though.
- It's...
How do I hold it? Like this?
Gosh.
- It's fun.
- Do you see the "T" here?
- Yes.
- Put your thumb on it...
- and hold it again.
- Like this?
Yes. And keep your arms the width
of your shoulders apart.
(Nervous)
I'll say "Both sides, front, one"
when I want to go forward.
When I say "one," make one long,
powerful stroke.
- Do you get it?
- Yes.
Let's practice. Let's go forward.
Both sides, front, one.
- One.
- Two.
(The boat is going forward
according to the command.)
- Two.
- This is fun.
- One.
- Two.
(They're done
with the rowing practice.)
All of a sudden...
- Stop.
- You should stop.
- Get it together.
You'll kill us all.
- Guys, let's enjoy it.
- Be careful.
Guys, we only live once.
Let's enjoy our past.
- What does it mean?
- Enjoy what?
I keep talking nonsense
because I'm scared.
Listen up.
If the boat flips over or you're
bounced off the boat,
put your head towards the upper part
of the river,
your legs towards the lower part
and spread your arms
like a scarecrow.
Keep your eyes on
the lower reaches...
- and let yourself be carried away.
- Got it.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
But we won't fall, right?
(Laughing)
We won't fall. Why would you...
Yes, sir. Do not worry.
- I'll do as you said.
- Why assume we're going to fall?
We didn't know we'd get to do this.
It's such an honor.
Why do you want to give
the instructor a good impression?
Let's go. Both sides, one.
- One.
- Two.
(Seok Sam's oar
barely touches the water.)
- One.
- Someone is not working hard.
- He's not doing it properly.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Don't just swing it in the air.
- Don't just...
touch the water.
Put your oar deeply into the water.
- Understood.
- When it comes to rafting,
teamwork is
the most important thing.
- Got it.
- If the boat doesn't move fast,
- it could flip over.
- He said we should move fast.
- I'll show you.
- We must move as one.
- Use your core muscles...
- Flex my core muscles?
and put your oar into the water.
You shouldn't swing it in the air.
- Got it.
- Put it into the water.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
- Keep that in mind to stay safe.
- Gosh. Look at him.
- Understood.
- Mister.
I told you not to just sweep
the surface halfheartedly...
- like this.
- I wasn't doing it halfheartedly.
As if he were scooping
some smoothie.
- I'm doing my best.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Stay alert. One.
- One.
- Two. One.
- Two.
- Oh, gosh.
- What was that?
(What was that?)
- There's a military base nearby.
- They must've fired a cannon.
- Oh, I see.
- I think it was a cannon.
- Gosh. What was that?
- Hey, did you just swear?
- Don't swear.
- I'm sorry.
- I was so scared.
- We're crashing into it.
Don't push. I said, don't push.
- They fired a cannon.
- Let's go. One.
The instructor ran out of
his patience. "I said, don't push."
- This is driving me nuts.
- Let's go.
- Here we go. One!
- One!
- Two!
- Louder!
- One!
- Two!
- No.
(They finally approach
the rafting course.)
- Hey, look over there.
- One.
- It's coming.
- It's coming!
Hey, it's coming.
- It runs so fast.
- Two.
- Should we keep rowing there?
- Yes. Keep rowing.
- Two.
- No. We shouldn't move that way.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
- Oh, no.
- I don't think we can do this.
(Rattling)
- Keep rowing.
- I don't think we can do this.
- Gosh. What do we do?
- We almost died.
(The swift current area continues.)
(The members continue groaning.)
- We have to keep rowing.
- Keep rowing.
- One!
- One.
- Two!
- Two.
- Don't panic.
- One. Two.
(The second swift current area
welcomes the scaredy-cats.)
- Look how fast it's running.
- My gosh.
- The water is running so fast.
- What should we do?
- Two! Keep rowing!
- We have to keep rowing.
- Be careful!
- My gosh!
- Gosh. Look at the whirlpool.
- My gosh.
- Two!
- One! Two!
- We can't do this!
- Please!
- Gosh!
- Oh, no! Please. This is so scary.
Please! Oh, no!
Please make it stop.
- It's too fast here!
- Gosh!
- Keep rowing.
- My gosh!
(Swaying)
- Keep rowing.
- My gosh!
- Suk Jin, sit up!
- Hey, look at Suk Jin.
- Be careful.
- Help Suk Jin!
- Gosh. I was so surprised.
- Oh, no. We'll fall.
(The big rapids won't even let them
pull themselves together.)
Let's move forward!
(The members' faces look ugly
as they row through rapids.)
Let's move forward!
My gosh!
- Keep rowing. One.
- There's a rock.
(The boat crushes into the rock.)
- That was scary.
- No!
- I said this would happen!
- Be careful.
My gosh. This is no joke.
- Sit up, everyone.
- Sit up straight.
- Jae Suk, sit up straight!
- Hey.
- Keep it together! This is real.
- I said this would happen!
- Hey, pull yourself together.
- This is no joke.
This is no joke.
- Think that we're...
- escaping a jungle river.
- Hey.
This is no joke.
Let's go!
(Team Stop's motorboat
starts moving.)
It's pretty.
This is so nice.
(They're enjoying the scenery
of the Hantan River relaxedly.)
We all look so relaxed.
I guess this is how relaxing it is
to ride a motorboat.
- This is nice, Ji Hyo.
- Indeed.
We can enjoy the scenery.
It's much better than I thought.
When I heard it was a motorboat,
I expected it
to move up and down a lot.
Ones that bounce.
You have such a wild imagination.
I'm talking about small boats,
you know.
We've been fooled so many times...
- I can't trust them.
- by the staff members.
It's beautiful.
I'll take some photos.
(Today, they can just relax
and enjoy themselves.)
Do motorboats run
in the morning too?
(Today, they can just relax
and enjoy themselves.)
By the way, sir,
if you swim in the river...
Are there any dangerous things
living in the river?
- It's a little scary, right?
- Yes.
- You don't know what's underneath.
- Exactly.
In movies, a monster appears
when people enjoy riding a boat.
- And the boat flips over.
- Yes. Usually, that's what happens.
I mean, if you put your hand
in the water just this much...
Oh, my. The water is so clear.
The monster would bite your arm
and drag you into the water.
(The other four members don't even
have time to imagine such a thing.)
It's so beautiful.
Look at the cracks in the rock.
Haha must be shivering with fear.
(That's obvious.)
He looked pale earlier.
There's a rock in front of us!
Left turn!
(The instructor won't
turn the boat.)
Left turn! Mister!
- Row.
- Mister!
- "Mister?"
- Gosh. Mister!
- We're about to hit the rock!
- Hey.
(The boat ended up colliding
with the rock.)
- Gosh. Mister!
- Be careful.
- He let it happen intentionally.
- Instructor.
I need to pee, sir.
Just go ahead and pee.
Mister!
- Gosh, seriously.
- Stop pulling pranks.
Hey, even my underwear is wet.
Did he do it intentionally?
I wear one pair a day.
One pair a day?
I'm sorry, sir.
Why didn't they tell us
to bring an extra pair of underwear?
- They told us.
- When did they tell you?
Why didn't they tell me?
- When you were on the plane.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Oh, boy.
- It's so scary.
- This is no joke.
- But...
- Sir, this is no joke.
- But isn't it thrilling and cool?
- It's scary.
- What's cool about this?
- We're enjoying our lives.
You were lying down here earlier.
You were lying around.
Don't you think it's cool?
- It's amazing that we can do this.
- Suk Jin.
Your pants are so thin
that I can see your underwear.
(The white see-through pants)
- That's the worst.
- It's okay.
- Are you wearing black underwear?
- He's right.
- Yes. How did you know?
- We can see them.
- He's wearing black underwear.
- At a spot like this...
Now, I see why people do this.
- It's kind of sexy, right?
- It's thrilling, right?
All right. Let's go.
- Let's go. One.
- One.
- Where are you going? Stop.
- Two.
- This is fun.
- Aren't we going?
- No. We won't go anywhere.
- Is it over?
No. There's something we should do.
Come on. Please don't do it again.
- Someone will fall out of the boat.
- We'll...
We'll play a game.
- Why should we play a game?
- Someone will fall into the water.
- The loser is chosen randomly.
- Really?
- That's the worst.
- Randomly.
- Hey, what's your name?
- Suk Jin.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be disrespectful.
- I'm sorry. My apology.
- The four of you...
- Put your oars in front.
- Okay.
- Here?
- Yes.
- What's going on?
- What are we going to do?
- Okay. Put it in there.
- Sir.
- Please go easy on us.
- Now...
I'm scared.
- Please give me your glasses.
- Pardon?
- Please give me your glasses. Yes.
- My glasses?
- Why do you need his glasses?
- Jae Suk, you too.
- Why do you need our glasses?
- There must be a reason.
- Can you hold their glasses?
- What is he trying to do?
- But our feet are secured.
- Now...
Take your feet out of the loops.
- No.
- Why should we?
- Take your feet out of the loops.
- Why suddenly...
- Please don't do that.
- Why are you being like this?
- What is wrong with you?
- Why are you acting like a thug?
- Sir, please.
- Come on.
Take your feet out now.
- We're not that kind of people.
- It's okay.
- Take your feet out...
- But the weather is...
- and face forward.
- It's quite chilly.
Face forward...
and sit cross-legged.
- Then we'll fall into the water.
- Don't do that.
- Sit cross-legged.
- We'll fall out of the boat.
- No, you won't.
- Come on.
- I mean...
- You won't if you get lucky.
Why should we dive into the water?
- Why are you making us do this?
- Face forward.
- You should do it while rafting.
- What's wrong with that man?
Face forward. Come on.
And sit cross-legged.
- I'm sitting cross-legged.
- Gosh.
Hey, are you guys enjoying this?
All of us?
Hold the life vest
of the person in front of you.
- Then we'll fall into the water.
- What?
We'll definitely
fall into the water.
- What kind of game is this?
- I'm scared of things like this.
The two in the front,
hold your life vests.
- Obviously, we'll fall.
- We'll fall into the water.
- Do you think we're stupid?
- We're not stupid.
- It's just a game.
Please do as I say.
- Face forward.
- Gosh, seriously.
- We have no choice.
- Okay.
- What should we do now?
- In this position,
lean back and forth.
- One, two.
- What is this?
One, two.
- One, two.
- What is this?
One, two.
(What kind of game
are they playing?)
Move faster. One, two.
- One, two.
(Pushing)
(They fall into the water.)
(Unlike what he said,
all of them fell into the water.)
(Their faces look ugly again.)
Why did you do that?
(It's an experience activity
at the trainees' level.)
Gosh! Mister!
Hey, you punk! I'm sorry.
My gosh.
Why did you do that?
Gosh. I can't believe you.
Hey, how could you?
Why would you do that?
- Why did you push us?
- Hey, how could you?
- My gosh.
- Gosh, I'm so cold!
The water is so cold. Darn.
(The water is so cold
that they can feel the autumn vibe.)
- This is so annoying.
- Gosh.
This is so fun.
(They're getting back on the boat.)
- Haha, help me.
- It was quite fun.
Pull me up.
- Okay.
- Wait! My butthole!
(The man in black underwear got it
stuck in the wrong area.)
(They're helping the members without
considering the body structure.)
Gosh. I'm so annoyed.
Gosh, it hurts.
(The members groan here and there.)
- Darn! Ouch. It hurts.
- It hurts, right?
- Gosh, seriously.
- What is this?
- You said we'd play a game.
- Mister.
Is this how you run your business?
- Let's go now.
- My gosh.
Hey, what's wrong? Be careful.
- Hey, how old are you?
- I'm old enough.
- Sir.
- Hold me.
Don't do such a thing.
That wasn't funny.
- Hey, guys.
- All right?
- Let's enjoy our lives!
- My gosh.
Isn't this fun?
(Then go into the water again.)
(He ran his mouth thoughtlessly
and fell into the water again.)
- Enjoy your life!
- He's enjoying it too much.
Are you all right?
- What did you say?
- Are you okay?
Do I look like I'm okay?
I'll pull you up.
(He's fluttering
while making a weird noise.)
Pull me up.
(Groaning)
How nice. So Min, I feel so relaxed.
- It's so beautiful.
- Indeed.
Hey, we made the right choice.
Wouldn't it be dangerous...
if their rafting boat came close
to ours while coming down?
- They're coming.
- My goodness.
Aren't they the other cast members?
My gosh.
They're not rowing properly.
It's a mess. Look at them.
They look tired.
Oh, dear.
- Is that a motorboat?
- Oh, there they are.
Are the others riding
that motorboat?
- I don't see them.
- They're coming.
- It's beautiful.
- Oh, there they are.
- I'm jealous.
- It's like a TV commercial.
- It must be so relaxing.
- They are enjoying the ride.
(People on the motorboat
are cheerful.)
- Jae Suk.
- You are working hard.
How is it?
- Hey.
- Splash water.
- Shall I do that?
- Yes.
- Bring the boat closer.
- Splash water.
- Let's go closer.
- Shall we go closer?
Bring the boat closer.
Are you having fun?
Hello.
- You are working hard.
- How is it?
(Get some water.)
It's cold.
(Despite the water,
Team Motorboat is happy.)
- It's cold.
- I am jealous.
I am jealous.
You worked hard.
- You worked hard.
- I got soaked.
Thank you for your hard work.
We fell into the water.
- Did you fall into the water?
- What?
- We fell into the water.
- Really?
- Yes.
- The instructor threw us in.
- Really?
- We fell into the water.
- He threw us into the water.
- Really?
- We got soaked.
- We got pushed into the water.
- Thank you.
Sir, I had so much fun.
- You complained earlier.
- I will visit with my son.
- I was joking earlier.
- Seriously.
- I don't get him.
- It's too late to say that.
- He has many rooms inside him.
- A fake life.
- Yes.
He leads a fake life.
It was an honor.
- Thank you.
- That's a lie.
Look at that.
(Look at him bring his hands
together.)
I hadn't brought
additional underwear,
but I survived.
We did pretty well.
- One underwear.
- You have a great track record.
Shall I choose Go this time?
Let's have a discussion
before we choose.
(What will be their choice
after choosing Stop?)
Gangmujeong?
- This place is so pretty.
- It's pretty.
It's nice.
What are you doing by yourself?
I was learning about the place.
What is this place, Jae Suk?
What is this place?
This is where King Sejong
oversaw Gangmu training.
King Sejong?
- Yes.
- King Sejang?
- It's Sejong, not Sejang.
- Sejong.
Gangmu training...
involved military training
and a hunt.
I thought "Mu" of Gangmu meant
something like this.
(So Min thought it was dancing.)
- Dancing?
- That was what I thought at first.
- But it meant something like this.
- Hey.
- In my opinion,
- Okay.
we practically received
a penalty already.
It seriously felt like a penalty.
Cooling down in this sweltering heat
isn't much of a penalty.
- We had a good time.
- Seriously.
I guess someone is hiding
behind the screen.
I think it's time for lunch.
For goodness' sake.
(Lunch is hidden
behind the screen on the pavilion.)
I had a nice meal earlier.
I haven't had anything
since morning.
- You must be starved.
- Didn't you eat gimbap?
- How about a sandwich?
- Gimbap?
I don't like gimbap
that contains mayonnaise.
I think mayonnaise is tasty.
- Where on earth is Suk Jin?
- Where is he?
- Is he taking a shower?
- Suk Jin.
What is Haha doing?
- There they come.
- I will tell them this.
Suk Jin, run so that you won't be
the last one!
Don't be the last one!
- Haha!
- Suk Jin can't run right now.
- Don't be the last one!
- He doesn't have the energy.
Suk Jin is running.
- Is that Suk Jin?
- Thank you.
- I think he will fall down.
- He runs with small strides.
He looks weak.
Hurry up!
(The younger man who is 44 years old
comes from behind.)
Run! Either one could win.
- There you go.
- Haha is fast.
- You are fast.
- Success.
Are you enjoying the Cheorwon trip?
- We are loving it.
- Yes.
How were the rafting experience
and motorboat ride?
- Those of us who only chose Go...
- It was so nice.
kept receiving
one penalty after another.
We are on a losing streak.
To be honest, you should have known
from the sound of Go.
- Struggles.
- The vibe of the word is...
- It has the vibe of a disaster.
- It has the vibe of going out...
- with momentum.
- A disaster.
At this point, it can't be helped.
Suk Jin has
about five personalities today.
- It was scary.
- I got scared earlier.
When we were on the boat...
When we pushed the boat and such,
he went, "What are you doing?
How old are you?"
- Really?
- When we were done,
we went, "We enjoyed ourselves
thanks to you."
- That's right. We saw him do this.
- We saw him do this.
- This, right?
- I felt bad.
- What's wrong with him?
- Suk Jin, your lips are blue.
- What?
- Where did your lips go?
- What? I never had them.
- Are you okay?
- By the way,
why do you look so haggard
when you haven't done much today?
- Why do you look so tired?
- I am tired.
Your hairstyle is a miss.
Really? This hairstyle is trendy.
- You had a different hairstyle.
- Your hair was blowing in the wind.
Isn't that Chakra's hairstyle?
You are right.
(She ended up resembling
an old idol group, not NewJeans.)
You can choose Go or Stop
for the next course.
- What should I choose this time?
- I will choose Go no matter what.
The mission for a sound hint is...
Trips are in the Order of Happiness.
At each course,
you got your photos taken.
- Yes.
(The photos captured
their happy memories.)
(Look over here.)
Let's go.
(The staff members took photos
at each course.)
(A photo of a relaxing moment)
(A photo of a difficult moment)
- All right.
- Let's go.
(They got numerous photos taken
without knowing what they were for.)
We picked each member's best photo
ahead of time.
- The best photo.
- When did they take my photos?
- Your facial expressions...
Throughout the trip.
AI analyzed the facial expressions
to measure the happiness index.
- Only the two members...
- I can't believe it.
with the highest scores
will receive the hint.
- It will be me.
- Please pick...
- a course...
- I win if my gums are showing.
you particularly enjoyed.
Course 1. Course 2.
- I liked Course 1.
- Rafting was okay.
- Rafting.
Those who rode the motorboat
instead of rafting...
shouldn't talk about rafting.
No one talked about rafting.
- Don't talk about it.
- Are you exhausted?
- Yes, I am exhausted.
- His arm is hanging loose.
- Lean on me.
- Let's see Haha's result first.
- Is it Se Chan's result?
- It's Haha's photo from rafting.
- It's Se Chan's photo.
- I am smiling from ear to ear.
- Is it Haha's photo?
- It's Haha's photo.
The analysis result.
(Haha managed a smile
on the rafting boat.)
The analysis result revealed...
that he is a middle-aged man
who is smiling sadly.
- Smiling sadly.
- He is a middle-aged man.
(A middle-aged man
who is smiling sadly)
A middle-aged man
who is smiling sadly.
- It's spot on.
- The index is 42.3 percent.
- Did you say 41.3 percent?
- It's 42.3 percent.
- It's spot on.
A middle-aged man
who is smiling sadly. It's perfect.
It isn't high.
- Why is it calling me middle-aged?
- Jong Kook, which one will it be?
I liked the first course.
- The first course?
- It was very...
- The atmosphere was nice.
- Carefree.
It was therapeutic.
You chose the monorail course.
Let's check Jong Kook's result.
I bet my result is mediocre too.
My eyes aren't visible, so...
- He looks sad.
- What? Why did you choose that?
(The analysis of Jong Kook's face)
(Everyone is smiling,
but one is daydreaming.)
- You grimaced.
- Why did you choose that?
- Yes.
"A middle-aged man's blank face?"
That's too much.
I laughed so many times.
That's a middle-aged man's
blank face.
The happiness index is 0.2 percent.
- Did you say 0.2 percent?
- Oh, no.
Jong Kook doesn't feel happy.
- What's wrong, Jong Kook?
- I laughed so many times.
The AI is precise.
He is a middle-aged man.
Se Chan comes next.
- I choose Course 2.
- Course 2.
- Yes.
- Choose rafting.
- Rafting.
Se Chan chose rafting.
- You fell into the water.
- You really fell into the water.
Did you take it
when I fell into the water?
Myung Jae.
A middle-aged man
who is angry, but happy.
- You are a middle-aged man too.
- The happiness index is 54 percent.
(A middle-aged man
who is angry, but happy)
(Happiness index: 54.2 percent)
(The sad middle-aged men
are jealous.)
- How nice.
- My gums are showing.
That's happiness.
- I enjoyed it too.
- Suk Jin, will you choose rafting?
- Of course.
- Okay. Rafting.
I can't choose the first one.
I didn't smile at all then.
I am torn.
Which one should I choose?
Look at his face.
- He is angry.
- Look at his face. He is angry.
It's the face of a middle-aged man
who is pretending to be happy.
(The face of a middle-aged man
who is pretending to be happy)
(He pretended to be happy.)
- The index is 9.8 percent.
- It's precise.
- Did you say 9.8 percent?
- Yes, 9.8 percent.
- Not bad.
- "Pretending to be happy."
- It's better than his.
- Yes.
- He leads a fake life.
- Mine was just above zero percent.
- Jae Suk, will you choose rafting?
- What should I choose?
I really enjoyed the observatory.
Jae Suk, you should choose rafting.
Rafting was a dynamic activity.
Going up to the observatory
wasn't bad. I enjoyed it.
You went up to it happily.
I will choose a photo that was taken
while going up.
I was happy then.
(He was with Suk Jin.)
- It's the worst.
(It's a photo
from a mischievous moment.)
The index is 0.5 percent.
The face of a 25-year-old man
who is pretending to be surprised.
- It's spot on.
- The index is 1.5 percent.
- A 25-year-old man?
- It's still higher than mine.
- For goodness' sake.
- His face was like this.
Mine was just above zero percent.
So Min, which course
will you choose?
- During the monorail course,
- The motorboat ride.
they teased me so much.
So I bet I grimaced.
That's happiness, So Min.
- Is that happiness?
- Of course.
Rafting. I mean the motorboat ride.
The motorboat ride?
- What's up with that face?
- She looks sad.
It's the face
of a female college student...
who is suppressing laughter.
- The index is 71.9 percent.
- My goodness.
(A female college student
who is suppressing laughter)
(A happy college student)
- A college student?
- It's the highest.
- It's high, Ji Hyo.
- I know.
- I guess I was happy.
- Unbelievable.
Isn't she more
of a mischievous college student?
- Unbelievable.
- The face of mischief.
- Ji Hyo, you... The motorboat ride.
- I will choose the motorboat ride.
Ji Hyo's face was that
of a recent university graduate...
who is suppressing laughter.
- A recent university graduate.
- The index is 71.1 percent.
(A recent university graduate
who is suppressing laughter)
- Our results are the highest.
- My goodness.
Our results are high.
- The index is 71.1 percent.
- A recent university graduate?
- Isn't she a middle-aged woman?
- She could be a senior manager.
Ji Hyo and So Min
will receive a hint.
- I should have chosen rafting.
- Let's share what we hear.
I am serious, So Min.
- No lies.
- I will choose a hint for Stop.
I will choose a hint for Go.
Go should be the better option
at this point.
- Now...
- I will choose Go.
- I will choose Go no matter what.
- Of course.
- I...
- I can't choose differently...
- at this point.
- Bracken.
Which hint will you listen to?
Will you listen to a hint for Go?
A hint for Go, please.
(Ji Hyo chooses a hint for Go.)
Where...
Do I put them on like this?
(Listening to the hint
for Go of Course 3)
(The familiar hissing sound?)
So Min, come and hear it.
So Min.
(It's So Min's turn
to listen to the hint.)
I listened to the hint for Go.
Stop.
I guess I look happy.
It's 71 percent.
She will choose Stop four times?
(Listening to the hint
for Stop of Course 3)
(A sound that makes her smile?)
- We did it.
- Yes.
We did.
You all heard the hint.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Was it a good thing?
- I had to walk.
- I'm not sure if it's good or bad.
Ji Hyo, give me a hint.
- I'll share it with So Min first.
- Okay.
Go, Jae Suk
- Go, Jae Suk
- What sound was that?
Look at them discuss the hint.
I guess it was ambiguous.
(Look at them discuss the hint.
I guess it was ambiguous.)
Now you will choose
either Go or Stop in turn.
Come and choose in turn.
(Go Jae Suk steps up.)
Gosh, he's going to choose Go.
(Go, Jae Suk!)
Go, Jae Suk
(Jae Suk chooses Go
4 times in a row.)
It's Go.
(Jae Suk chooses Go
4 times in a row.)
- I go no matter what.
- Next.
(Haha goes next.)
Haha, let's just...
- I'll choose Go.
- All the men will choose Go.
Be a man and go.
(Will all the rafting members
choose Go again?)
- That's right. He chose Go.
- Darn it.
Go!
I have no other choice now.
(It looks like they are all going
to choose Go this time.)
- Did you all choose Go?
- Will you choose Go?
Stop? What do I do?
(Stop? What do I do?)
Go.
- Will you go?
- I think I should.
Se Chan, choose Go. Okay.
I have no choice.
- Did you all choose Go?
- Yes.
- Even Se Chan?
Then should I choose Stop?
- Hey, you should choose Go.
- You kept choosing Stop, right?
- Yes.
- Then you should stop.
No. You can change it this time.
Change it.
I'll be the only one
who changes his choice, right?
Yes.
- I will...
- No.
- It's Jong Kook's turn.
- No. I should go first.
Gosh, I should...
(Is it time to change
his choice to Go?)
I'll stick to my choice.
(He doesn't change his choice
and sticks with Stop.)
Ji Hyo, what are you going to do?
(Now it's Ji Hyo and So Min
who heard the hint.)
I'll go next.
- Go.
- It's their choice that matters.
Right.
(What is Ji Hyo's choice
after choosing Stop 3 times?)
I'll...
(She chooses Stop
without showing it to others.)
What did she choose?
She tried to hide it.
Right. She can hide it.
There comes the rascal.
Rascal?
There's the rascal.
(What's Rascal Jeon's choice?)
So Min!
(They all made
the same choices as before.)
We got the same results again.
Four members chose Go.
- And three members chose Stop.
- Seriously?
You should've changed
your choice to Stop.
- For me...
- Seriously, make Go good.
I can't choose Stop.
Hey, I bet Stop is
a good thing again.
- Should I open Go first?
- My gosh.
You can open it.
Please.
(What's the fourth course for Go?)
(The stubborn Go lovers
finally seize the chance to win?)
(They earn a meal with tenacity.)
(And a beautiful tour course
filled with flowers.)
(Go Jae Suk's surprising trip
will be revealed next week.)
(And...)
(The members are locked in 7 rooms.)
(The greasy smell makes them
want to escape from the rooms.)
(They all must pass the test!)
(What's the highest mountain
in the world?)
(All the members...)
(didn't give the correct answer.)
(Is there a spy
who gives wrong answers?)
(Empty Head)
(Among the 7 Empty Heads,)
(there's only one betrayer.)
(One of the members is...)
(giving wrong answers on purpose.)
(Mr. Run,
How’s the Food Over There?)