(To celebrate our first shoot
in the New Year,)
(please come in the trendiest
outfit you think tomorrow.)
Hello.
When it comes to fashion,
you guys are no match for me.
I think I look amazing today.
You two should
stick together like that.
- Excuse me, ma'am.
- What?
- Stick with him.
- My gosh.
So Min, the suede...
- In the suede jacket,
- Hello.
- you look like a CEO.
- My goodness.
- Hello.
I think I look great today.
- I...
- I look good too.
Hey.
- You...
- Hey.
- He's really...
- Hey, what's with you?
- Do you know what the problem is?
- I'd like to buy some honey.
The problem is that
you didn't get rid of the price tag.
- The price tag is on.
- Don't take it off.
If you take it off,
I'll have to buy it.
You're so feeble-minded.
What? You're the lady
from the movie, "Snowpiercer."
No.
- It's you, right? "Snowpiercer."
- That's right.
You're Jenny, right?
The important thing is that
I can pull off an outfit like this.
If you go around looking like this,
the movie will be popular again.
- No.
- It's "Snowpiercer."
You look just like her.
- What's your name?
- What's that dog?
- The tail of the train.
- This dog?
- Its name is Seok Sam.
- Seok Sam.
- Hey, Seok Sam.
- It's pretty.
- It's Seok Sam.
- It's really pretty.
There's one disappointing thing
about Suk Jin's outfit.
You should wear these pants
without jeans underneath them.
Hey, you punk.
That's how
you're supposed to wear them.
This is disappointing.
You don't know fashion.
Did you just get a physical checkup?
What?
- He got a colonoscopy.
- A colonoscopy?
- On the back...
- An urological test on the front.
- And a colonoscopy on the back.
- It's also open on the back.
A colonoscopy on the back.
- Gosh, seriously...
- He just got...
a colonoscopy.
Suk Jin, you should
wear only the outer pants.
Right. Only the outer pants.
You can stay cool at home then.
- You look so tacky.
- No, I don't.
- Look at your hair.
- It's this year's new color trend.
Orange.
- Are you Michol or what?
- What are you talking about?
You're Dr. Octopus.
I don't look like Dr. Octopus.
That's right.
- From "Spider-Man."
- He's Tin Tin Five.
- Pyo In Bong.
- Move your head
Move it so I can see ahead
- Pyo In Bong.
- What's with you? Today...
Jong Kook is...
Imagine your boyfriend is a trainer.
This is how he's dressed up.
- Seriously, he is...
- He is wearing different color?
- The boyfriend look.
- He stands out.
He'd be the most
fashionable trainer.
This is called
the trainer boyfriend look.
- Seriously, you are...
- This is how you always look.
I saw Ji Seon sigh.
She must've prepared
some clothes for him.
I'm just glad
that he's not wearing shorts.
This hoodie is quite fashionable.
- What are you talking about?
- I guess it's cozy.
- I know what you mean.
- It's comfortable around here.
You know what I mean, right?
- It fits him well.
- It has lines here.
Hey.
- Ji Hyo, what's with you?
- She looks cute.
It's like
a cold medicine commercial.
Watch out for cold.
- A cold medicine commercial.
- Get me an abalone.
- My gosh.
- That's how she looks.
Ji Hyo reads
fashion magazines these days.
Is that true, Ji Hyo?
- I study fashion now.
- Actually,
- She studies fashion.
- she still looks good.
- It does look good on her.
- This is in style now.
- The bag is popular too.
- This one.
And we have someone
who's in the fashion business.
- That's not it.
- She runs a small store.
She sells imported clothes.
She imports clothes.
We can see ladies like her
in Itaewon.
There are a lot.
- In Itaewon...
- Now So Min looks...
pretty good in an outfit like this.
- She does.
- She's old enough.
- I look old, right?
- I mean, she's 37 now.
You look nice.
Since this is our first
shoot in the New Year,
I'd like you to talk
about your New Year's resolutions.
- This is our first shoot?
- Really?
I guess you all have
your New Year's resolutions.
And I heard one of Haha's
resolutions already came true.
- What is it?
- What?
- What is it? Are you pregnant?
- Your fourth child?
- Haha...
- What is it?
- I didn't do anything.
- Haha finally got the answer...
to the question that had been
bothering him for a long time.
- What is it?
- What's the question?
- What?
- What would it be?
- There's a video about it.
"How Do You Play?" or Running Man?
In 1, 2, and 3.
"How Do You Play?"
Oh, dear.
What?
(Feeling betrayed)
- Haha!
- Is this what you mean?
"How Do You Play?" or Running Man?
And you chose "How Do You Play?"
I can't believe this.
- Go away, you punk.
- Just go.
- I can explain.
- No.
- Let me explain.
- I don't like him anymore.
I can't believe this.
(Jong Kook raised doubts
about "The Man of Saturday.")
(After the suspicion was kindled,
Haha has been asked...)
(to choose between
Running Man and "How Do You Play?")
(And he failed
to answer every time.)
(The Man of Saturday
finally got his answer.)
- I don't like him anymore.
- I can explain.
- I hate him.
- Haha.
This is no joke.
- Seriously...
- I'm serious.
I recently went to Jeju Island
with my parents.
While I was driving,
my mother told me this.
"Since Haha started
'How Do You Play?'"...
"he doesn't seem happy
on Running Man."
- Seriously, she said that.
- Even she noticed it.
- She said that out of the blue.
- No.
I can't believe
you played this during the opening.
You're unbelievable.
This is the opening.
What am I supposed to do now?
- What's with you?
- Please.
Tell me.
Why did you say, "How Do You Play?"
I understand.
I've been doing this for 11 years,
but the show...
- It just started.
- It's new.
So I felt like...
it was my youngest daughter.
Then why do you look happy
on the show?
- You don't look happy here.
- Why is that?
Why do you try
so hard on the show...
- while you're not like that here?
- Why is that?
- That's important.
- That's just...
a misunderstanding.
You know what?
- That punk is serious about this.
- No.
- That's not true.
- Hey.
- Let's be honest.
- I...
You can feel it...
- while editing the show, right?
- He's immersed in it.
- He can feel it.
- That's not true.
- Not at all.
- Yes, it is. On "How Do You Play?"
- I got a herniated disk here.
- He looks very cheerful.
No. Don't get me wrong.
Hey! What's with your face?
- Hey, Haha...
- Jong Kook.
- I'm disappointed.
- You know what?
- I watched the show yesterday.
- I'm really disappointed.
- He's really...
- It's a new show.
He's proactive there.
Say something.
- He seems proactive there.
- That's not true.
- Thank you.
- He plays an active part.
- That's true.
- He's active.
(His Saturday colleague
pulls out right away.)
- That's because it's a new show.
- It just started.
You mean the show.
- He's pregnant too.
- Who?
Bo Pil. He's not?
- He's pregnant too.
- Who?
- Bo Pil.
- What?
- He's not?
I'm sorry.
Why would he get pregnant?
- What are you talking about?
- Is he pregnant?
Is he pregnant?
- Is Bo Pil pregnant?
- He says he's not.
Why would he get pregnant?
What are you talking about?
- What's happening?
- Who were you talking about?
- Who did you mean?
- Sorry. I couldn't hear it well.
Ji Hyo.
Take off your sunglasses.
- I'm sorry.
- What's wrong with you?
It was funny though. What was that?
- It was so sudden.
- Anyway,
Ji Hyo saved your life.
(Thanks to his friend from Mapo,
Haha got off the spot.)
My friend from Mapo.
It's just a joke.
No, I'm not joking.
I'm serious.
- Anyway, Jong Kook...
- Good luck, Haha.
- feels betrayed.
- Good luck.
- I do.
- Even your mom says that.
I'm very frustrated.
I'll call your mom
and clear up the misunderstanding.
My mom sounded serious.
She was serious.
While we were driving
on Jeju Island.
- That's right.
- My friends also talk about it.
That's why I didn't win
an award on SBS. Happy now?
They didn't give me anything
because I didn't do anything.
- Happy now?
- That's enough.
Enough is enough.
(He saves his life
by blaming himself.)
There's another video
that we received.
- What?
- One is not enough.
- Please play the second video.
- Haha?
- I hope it's not about me.
- What is it?
- Don't make it look like the truth.
- What would it be?
- What is this?
- Why? What are you doing?
- This is what I reported.
- What is this?
This is from Jae Suk.
(What is this?)
- What is this?
- Stop it.
- What is she doing?
- Don't play it.
- Stop it.
- I reported it.
What is she doing?
- Is it from Running Man?
- What is this?
- This is a scene from her drama.
- Her drama?
Please.
- What is this?
- What's with her face?
No.
- Where is this place?
- Turn off the cameras.
Is this "I Hear Your Voice?"
Are you tone-deaf?
- Hey.
- It's "Idol Drama Operation Team."
Turn off the cameras now!
Turn them off.
- Turn them off.
- What is this?
This is embarrassing.
- Hey.
- What is going on?
What's with his face?
(Feeling bitter)
What's that?
- Please turn it off.
- The last one...
Running Man is so unique.
- Who was that?
- What is she doing?
What was that?
This is what I was
talking about yesterday.
What was that?
- All right.
- What?
Let me see their faces again.
- What is it?
- Please play it one more time.
Did you see
the faces of the audience?
What's with their faces?
Is it supposed to be funny?
When was that?
(Please stop it.)
So Min.
What is this?
Is this "Comedy Big League" or what?
Is that "Comedy Big League?"
You reported it.
- I reported it.
- Are you tone-deaf?
The guy in the audience
is clenching his teeth.
- What's that, So Min?
- What's going on?
This is...
I made a cameo in a drama.
I played a singer
who's not so talented.
(Singing)
She did things like this.
What was that?
Guys, seriously... So Min...
- She's a treasure.
- She's done a lot of things.
- She's...
- She works really hard.
So Min does work hard.
- She's hardworking.
- So Min played...
- a character...
- She's supposed to be bad.
- who's not talented.
- The audience doesn't like her.
This video saved my life.
All right, everyone. You guys are
wearing trendy outfits today.
I think it will be hard...
for you to decide
who has better taste in fashion.
- So we will have a contest.
- A contest?
- Please.
- My gosh.
I don't want to be judged.
I just want us
to criticize each other.
We have four experts
who will evaluate your fashion.
- Okay.
- I'm in trouble.
Our youngest member So Min,
please open the curtains.
- So Min. You're the youngest.
- So Min.
- Okay.
- So this is what she does now.
So Min, hey
- Hey
- So Min, you should do this.
Use this hand. You should
open the curtains like this.
That's it. You should do that.
- She's really funny.
- I'm opening the curtains.
- What?
- I see.
(They see some silhouettes
behind the curtains.)
- There's a man.
- Four experts.
- Where's the man?
- It looks like...
- they are in the fashion business.
- There's a man.
I think the third one
is Kim Sook. Right?
- She must be Kim Sook.
- Is she Sook?
- Kim Sook.
- Number one is a slave hunter.
Number one is Hyuk.
Is it you, Hyuk?
- Hyuk.
- Please introduce yourselves.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
- I can hear her voice.
- Is it a man?
- It's a woman.
- She's a slave hunter.
The voice is disguised.
Number two, please say hello.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Who is she?
- Is she a comedienne?
Is she Jang Do Yeon?
- Jang Do Yeon.
- Number three.
Do Yeon's hair
doesn't look like that.
Hello.
I'm here to evaluate your fashion.
- She's Sook.
- Is that so?
- Number four, please.
- I have no idea.
Hello.
I'm the fiery fist of
the fashion industry, number four.
- The fiery fist?
- All of a sudden?
- In the fashion industry?
- We don't usually say that.
The fiery fist is quite slim.
- He's in the fashion business.
- He must be a model.
- I bet he's a model.
- He is well-proportioned.
- They look well-proportioned.
- Right. They're tall.
They look cool
with their legs crossed.
Did you see our outfits?
Yes, we did.
- Are you watching us?
- Yes.
We've been watching you
from the beginning.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Was there an outfit you liked?
Pick the best one.
Well...
(Judge number 4's evaluation)
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yes?
(Is the lady from "Snowpiercer"
the best dresser?)
Well...
He looks like...
a successful trot singer
from Hong Kong.
(A successful...)
(trot singer from Hong Kong)
- That's a perfect description.
- Hong Kong?
- He's...
- That's right.
He's really mean.
The four experts...
will evaluate each member's fashion.
- Please start with So Min.
- Okay.
Let me go first.
She matched different patterns well.
But she picked a jacket
of the wrong size.
It's an oversized jacket.
(She failed to pick the correct
size, which is the basics.)
I was going to say that.
- It's too long.
- So she looks ill-proportioned.
- Hey
- I know.
- And?
- First,
I think she prefers
the animal trend.
But she just looks like an animal.
She looks like a real animal.
(A real animal)
That was...
- That was too blunt.
- Exactly. It was blunt.
Many of those who work
in the fashion industry are blunt.
- True.
- We could...
We could criticize them
in the same way.
Right. Let's see what else they have
to say about us.
To be honest, I like So Min's style
more than the others'.
- See? She has an eye for it.
- She looks like a rich woman.
This is the first shoot...
- of the new year, right?
- Yes.
I think she picked the tiger pattern
to celebrate the Year of the Tiger.
- I guess she's right.
- Right.
- That's exactly my intention.
- There's one thing I don't like.
That she's wearing
such flashy clothes,
but her attitude doesn't suit
her outfit.
- Her attitude?
- Yes.
- She looks too shy.
- Attitude is important.
- Yes. It's important in fashion.
- Absolutely.
- So Min looks...
- Yes.
(Judge number 4's evaluation)
like the kindergarten director
in "Crayon Shin-chan"...
and Pikotaro who sang "PPAP."
She's somewhere between them.
- The kindergarten director?
- I know that character.
The one who always wears
a yellow jacket.
- Yes, that's the one.
- "PPAP."
(She aimed to be
a fashion leader, but...)
- "PPAP?"
- I know that singer.
- PPAP
- It's similar to their styles.
I know the character
from "Crayon Shin-chan."
- Judge number four...
- Me too.
- has a brutal way...
- It was a brutal criticism.
- Yes, it was a harsh evaluation.
- Yes.
- Judge number four.
- Indeed.
- Next up is Jae Suk.
- Okay.
He looks unexpectedly great
in his outfit.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
- He looks great in that outfit?
- I'm not sure how this might sound.
But he looks rather fake
than original, I would say.
(He looks fake.)
- I thought the same thing.
- That's so funny.
- That's so mean.
- His sneakers and everything.
- What's your problem?
- That's Jenny's fashion style.
- Gosh, seriously.
- I agree.
Looking at him from behind...
Hold on a second.
- She's taking a look at him.
- Is it because of his face?
What's wrong with my face?
- Don't criticize his face.
- Come on, ma'am.
- Just evaluate his fashion style.
- Looking at him from behind...
- That's why you're here.
- You see...
He looks okay overall
when I don't see his face.
- "He looks okay."
- That's cool.
- Oh, no.
I think he'd look better
if he showed his face in profile.
- He should show his profile?
- He should cover his face.
Gosh. Those judges are
absolutely ridiculous.
You're supposed to evaluate
our fashion styles, not our looks.
Why would she criticize my looks?
As for Jae Suk...
Just as I said earlier,
he looks like a successful
trot singer from Hong Kong.
- That's a perfect comparison.
- I'm telling you...
I'm dying to find out
who Judge number four is.
I'll say it in his face
when he comes out.
- That suits you though.
- So you became successful...
and bought Snowpiercer.
He used to be in the tail section.
- He's so mean.
- He got successful as a singer.
A trot singer from Hong Kong.
- He's the worst.
- Okay.
- A singer from Hong Kong.
- I'd rather...
- Next up is Seok Sam.
- I think...
- I think I look really stylish.
- Stand over here, everyone.
Well, as for Jeok Sin...
- "Jeok Sin?"
- That's the worst criticism.
- She said his name wrong.
- Jeon Sin, the king of criticisms.
- Her criticism has already begun.
- Please go on.
- Jeok Sin.
- I'm sorry.
He matched a black sweater
with manly leather clothes.
But too much emphasis has been
placed on his masculinity.
- Only that area catches eyes.
- "His masculinity."
She called it "masculinity."
- That area is cut out.
- Indeed.
- It doesn't symbolize masculinity.
- So he looks over the top.
- I think it should be closed.
- It shows his confidence.
She said you should close it.
- Close what?
- Just sew it up.
- Right. Sew it up.
- Close it.
- Right. That's too much.
- But I can't close it.
- It's over the top.
- But...
- In my opinion, Seob Sin...
- Suk Jin.
- I'm sorry.
- It's Suk Jin.
- It's neither Jeok Sin...
- His name is Ji Suk Jin.
- nor Seob Jin. It's Suk Jin.
- It's Suk Jin.
- "Seok" as in "rock."
- I guess Suk Jin...
- His name...
is not famous enough yet.
- He needs to be more famous.
- Exactly.
It seems as if he mixed everything
that was popular...
- among our dads' generation.
- "Our dads' generation?"
Oh, I see. "Our dads' generation."
- What does it mean?
- What our fathers liked.
- I don't think...
- His pants are too short.
- His pants are too short?
- Yes.
- That's because I have long legs.
- And what he's wearing over them...
What is that?
(What is that?)
- "What is that?"
Exactly what are you talking about?
- What are you referring to?
- I know what it is,
- but I don't like...
- You're talking about this, right?
I must say, they're all so candid.
Suk Jin looks like a second-hand
clothing store owner...
wearing all of the popular
fashion items that he'd seen...
- in fashion magazines.
- A second-hand clothing shop owner?
A second-hand clothing shop owner?
Why a second-hand clothing shop?
- Wearing the products in his store?
- To increase the sales.
- That's how he recommends them.
- Right.
- That makes sense.
- "I heard this was popular."
- It's simple.
- Next up is Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo looks cute.
- Right. She looks cute.
- She looks so cute.
- Ji Hyo looks really pretty today.
- She looks great in it.
I agree. Everything that Ji Hyo is
wearing now...
- is very trendy these days.
- Oh, you noticed them.
- Thank you. That's right.
- Especially her hat is so popular.
- Thank you.
- What are their standards?
Are you saying that fashion is
all about the face or what?
- I think Se Chan is right.
- That's right.
- Let's see what they say about me.
- Se Chan is right.
They evaluate the face,
not the fashion style.
- I too like Ji Ok's... Ji Hyo's...
- "Ji Ok?"
- She keeps saying our names wrong.
- "Ji Ok" as in "fiery pit?"
- I mean, Ji Hyo.
- My gosh.
- Go and wash your face.
- She keeps doing that.
She must be half-asleep.
What's with her pronunciation?
She called Suk Jin "Seob Jin."
It's very trendy, and you can see
her style...
- on runways very often.
- Really?
- You look so pretty, Ji Hyo.
- She's getting compliments.
Talk about her style, not her face.
- I think that the judges...
- What are your standards?
Why would you criticize...
Okay. Go ahead.
- Judge number four, go ahead.
- Okay.
- The feisty one.
- Let's see what he says.
There's this song.
(Pretty woman)
(He suddenly started singing
a love song.)
(What is going on?)
- What is his deal?
- What's wrong with him?
- Number four is just crazy.
- Hey, come out.
- He's just crazy. Who are you?
- Exactly.
- They all care about appearances.
- Judge number four...
Is he even an expert?
- Look how thin his wrist is.
- His fist looks so small.
- It's so thin.
- His punch would sting a little.
- Right. I'd get pricked and bleed.
- Okay. Let's hear them out.
Go ahead and criticize it all you want.
Number one, you're up.
As for Se Chan...
When it comes to his tops,
I think they're trendy and stylish.
Right.
- He dressed nicely.
- Although he dyed his hair orange,
- I think... It's not so bad.
- It's trendy these days.
- Oh, great.
- Really?
- It's not so bad?
- He looks great.
- I don't believe her.
- Exactly.
(Next up is
Judge number 2's evaluation.)
- His hair looks like Cheetos.
- Cheetos?
(His hair looks like Cheetos.)
- Cheetos.
- Hey.
My hair looks like Cheetos?
- She said it looked like Cheetos.
- That's a good comparison.
Hey, I like Cheetos.
- Cheetos? That's ridiculous.
- Cheetos.
- Cheetos?
- That's a great comparison.
Your fingertips turn that color...
- after eating those chips.
- Exactly.
Right. That's the exact color.
What about my clothes?
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
- Well...
- Who is this person? Let me think.
You look like a little boy
who's eight years old or younger.
And your mother is
a helicopter parent.
(The helicopter mom's son's style)
Who do you think you are?
How dare you talk about my mom?
- I can imagine the situation.
- Exactly.
- I can imagine it too.
- That was amazing.
- He's doing great.
- Who on earth is he?
- He's so observant.
- Who is Judge number four?
- There will be a talent show.
- He's so funny.
- Who is he?
- He's really good at this.
And your mother is
overly enthusiastic.
- My mom is overly enthusiastic?
- That's a good comparison.
- I can imagine the whole situation.
- Exactly.
- I can't wait to see his face.
- I've seen it.
- You can see it on social media.
- Indeed.
- Let's criticize them later.
- Let's do that.
- All right. My gosh.
- I've seen such kids before.
- Next up is Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook is up next.
Goodness, you.
Hey, put that water bottle down.
- This is a fashion item.
- That too?
- Of course. A water bottle...
- You're carrying it intentionally.
- Yes, I matched it to my outfit.
- Oh, I see.
Well... Right.
- Which camera should I look at?
- I have nothing to say.
Judge number four said that
he had nothing to say about him.
Well...
I can't evaluate his fashion style.
(They gave up on evaluating.)
- I knew it.
- Yes.
I wouldn't dress like that
even when I sleep.
Even when he sleeps?
He wouldn't dress like that
even when he sleeps.
I would never dress like that
even in bed.
- I can't believe him.
- He's amazing.
- I knew it.
- He has a nice body though.
(He has a nice body?)
- Is that so?
- Oh, I see.
- She doesn't sound very young.
- Do I have a nice body?
- I bet none of them is so young.
- I agree.
- They all use outdated expressions.
- True.
- I think they're done.
- Right.
- I'll go back in.
- That was quick.
Haha is up next. I wonder
how they'll evaluate his style.
- That was hilarious.
- Look how he's walking.
He's pretending to be younger.
He's 44.
- He's obsessed with being youthful.
- Absolutely.
He looks like Kanye West
from behind.
(She complimented how he looked
from behind.)
But once he turns around,
he looks like one of the minions
from "Despicable Me."
- One of the minions?
- Yes.
He looks completely different
from the front, don't you think?
- He looks great from behind.
- From Kanye West to a minion.
A minion from "Despicable Me?"
He looks incredibly stylish
from behind.
(He looks like a world-class
fashion leader from behind.)
- That's so funny.
- But he looks like a minion...
- from the front.
- My goodness.
(But he looks like an action figure
from the front.)
(To conclude, it's not
just about what you wear.)
I understand that he chose
oversized clothes intentionally.
He likes to wear oversized clothes.
But his pants make his legs
look too short.
He shouldn't have chosen
such long pants.
- My gosh.
- Who is he?
- His shoes have such thick soles.
- They're almost 10cm thick.
- Right.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
In foreign countries,
there are many fashion leaders
among homeless people.
That's all. I'll say no more.
- He's unbelievable.
- Who is he? I'm so curious.
- Who is he?
- Who on earth is he?
He practically called me a beggar.
Yes, that's right.
Come back in now.
I can't wait to find out
who they are. They're unbelievable.
- I'm upset.
- He would never dress like this?
Your fashion styles have been
evaluated...
- in detail.
- Yes.
Now, we'll reveal the four
fashion experts as you wish.
- Let's find out.
- Come out now.
- Number four, come on out.
- Who are you? Come out.
Number two, you said my hair looked
like Cheetos. Come on out.
- Come out now.
- I'll teach you a lesson.
- Number four, come out.
- My mom is a helicopter parent?
- That startled me.
- Oh, my.
- Oh, it was Woo Jae.
- Hello.
They sure are fashion experts.
- That startled me.
- Oh, my.
- Oh, it was Woo Jae.
- Hello.
I'm surprised.
(Running Fashion Show, Joo Woo Jae)
They all turned out to be
such amazing stars.
- Long time no see.
- Hi, Jae Suk.
- I can't complain to them.
- Hello.
- They all look so fabulous.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- They really are fashion experts.
- Hey, Woo Jae.
- It's been a while. Oh, hello.
- Hello.
- It's good to see you again.
- You look amazing.
Oh, my. They all look great.
Who said I looked like a minion?
(It was Irene.)
- Who called my hair Cheetos?
- It was her.
- Who said that?
- Who compared my hair to that?
I didn't know that Irene could be
so harsh.
- Their comments were so funny.
- As we expected,
- they have a lot of experience.
- True.
- It's hard to make such comments.
- It's not easy.
I'll introduce our guests
one after another.
First up is Lee Hyun Yi.
Hello, everyone. I'm Lee Hyun Yi.
I'm a fashion model.
- Is this your first time here?
- She looks gorgeous.
- Yes, this is my first time.
- Oh, really?
- Really?
- Yes.
- I think that's true.
- I've been enjoying the show...
- at home as a viewer until now.
- That's great.
Hyun Yi has been appearing
on many variety shows.
You've been very busy, right?
- Yes, I have.
- She seemed very enthusiastic.
- I'm busy shooting the shows,
- Yes.
but I'm also busy training
six times a week.
- Training for soccer?
- Yes.
- I spend most of my time training.
- I'm so jealous.
- I mean it.
- Join us...
- for training.
- I'm so jealous.
- They're like professional players.
- Indeed.
They've been training
as professional players do.
You see, Hyun Yi...
majored in economics
at Ewha Womans University.
- That was a long time ago.
- She's amazing.
- That's incredible.
- She has everything.
It was the only thing
I was good at...
- I wanted to major in economics.
- Economics?
- I majored in business, you know.
- Sorry?
- I majored in business.
- Right, he majored in business.
- Oh, right.
- I majored in business.
- It's similar to economics.
- What did you learn in college?
Like a business
that Huh Kyung Young runs?
(Could he have studied
to be like Huh Kyung Young?)
You're the one who makes calls
from his campaign team, right?
- I get a call from them every day.
- He's the one...
- who makes those calls.
- Oh, I see.
- I'm sure of it.
- Right?
No? I'm sorry.
- Huh Kyung Young?
I got a call from his campaign team
not long ago.
- Do you make those calls?
- No.
- "Hello."
- I got that call three times too.
- Do you...
- "Hello. I'm Huh Kyung Young."
Do you make those calls?
- No.
- No?
- No, I don't.
- Okay.
Hae Na is very famous...
in the fashion industry
because she is...
- shorter than most other models.
- That's true.
- Despite that, Hae Na is...
- Really?
- Is she very successful as a model?
- very successful in the industry.
- She has a well-proportioned body.
- Really?
- She's so stylish, you know.
- But she's very tall.
- Show us a few poses.
- True. I'm sure...
that I'm the shortest
among the active fashion models.
- Oh, I see.
- How tall are you?
- I'm 169cm tall.
- What?
- See?
- Aren't you taller than 170cm?
- She looks very tall.
- That's hard to believe.
So whenever I pose
with another model...
Let's say I'm posing with Hyun Yi.
I'd lie down or sit down right away.
(I'd lie down
or sit down right away.)
- I get it.
- Can you show us one pose?
- Let's say she's standing here.
- Okay.
- Then I'd bend my knees like this.
- Oh, I see.
- She has her own ways.
- You'd bend your knees?
Yes, to lower my body.
- You need to catch eyes...
- Haha does the same thing.
- Don't say that.
- He always...
- sits down in the front.
- That's true.
- He does that too. It makes sense.
- Right. He sits down in the front.
- I didn't realize that.
- I see that he had his own reasons.
He lowers his body every time.
- I can understand you.
- You do the same thing, Haha.
- That's very wise of you.
- He sits down right away.
- He had his own reasons.
- Now I see why he does that.
- He posed like that intentionally.
- Yes.
- I didn't know that.
- When I pose by myself,
I try to look as tall as possible.
I put one of my legs forward
and lean back a little.
- Leaning back? I see.
- Like this.
- I've seen models posing like this.
- Yes.
- Lean back a little?
- Like this.
- Irene is demonstrating it too.
- This pose makes your legs...
- look longer.
- It makes me look taller.
- Look at Ji Hyo.
- Why?
- Ji Hyo...
- Ji Hyo, what are you doing?
- What are you doing now?
- Are you a thug or a gangster?
(Are you a thug or a gangster?)
(She looks like a gangster forcing
people to buy cold medicine.)
- How do I look?
- Are you checking a property?
- As if she was checking a property.
- What is she doing?
- Checking a property to buy.
- Ji Hyo, are you a thug?
- One leg forward.
- She looks so funny.
- Next up is Irene.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
- Hello, everyone.
- She's been on our show before.
- Right.
- That's right.
- This isn't your first time here.
But it was a long time ago
when I just made my debut.
- Do you...
- I don't remember clearly...
- what I did on the show.
- Do you think...
you have changed since then?
- First, my Korean...
- She looks even younger now.
- I was younger back then.
- I said you looked younger...
- than you did back then.
- Really?
(The years have been kind to you.)
- The years have been kind to you.
- Thank you.
- First of all...
- Yes.
- I don't know. I think...
- Suk Jin.
- What's with that upset look?
- Exactly.
- He looked...
- He looked annoyed while saying it.
- It was a compliment. Then why...
- He was like this.
- "You look even younger now."
- It wasn't like that.
Why did you compliment her angrily?
- I wondered if it was a compliment.
- Why would you say it like that?
- You see,
- Why did you make an angry face?
had I said it too excitedly,
I would've seemed less sincere.
You're wrong.
You should exaggerate it.
"My, you look amazing."
"Well, you look good."
It's different.
- Did she live in a foreign country?
- Yes, she did.
- You didn't know that?
- You heard it when she first came.
- What's wrong with you?
- You didn't know that?
- I didn't know that.
- My gosh.
- She's from New York.
- What are you doing now?
- Irene.
- Yes?
You look young before.
What was that?
What are you doing
in those hideous pants?
The pants for colonoscopy.
Mister, go and get it done.
It's your turn.
- Come on. I'm a big fan of hers.
- Are you still under anesthesia?
- Next up is Joo Woo Jae.
- Welcome.
- Joo Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae is an MC...
- specializing in dating shows.
- That's right.
He's been hosting
a lot of dating shows.
Is it true that you and Se Chan went
on the same dating show?
- Yes, we did.
- Really?
Woo Jae and I appeared
on "Love Me Actually."
- Oh, it was "Love Me Actually?"
- Oh, really?
What was funny was...
that I was more popular with girls
than him back then.
(I was more popular than him
back then.)
- Se Chan was so popular.
- But why...
- Girls didn't seem to like him.
- Why...
They didn't like him at all.
- Why?
- I don't know.
Was he too blunt?
Didn't what you knew about dating
help you win their hearts?
He didn't get many votes.
- When I was cast for the show,
- Yes.
I was confident.
- I thought...
- Of course. I mean it was Se Chan.
Since I gave viewers tips
on dating...
- on my show every week,
- That's right.
and I have seen...
- so many couples,
- True.
- I thought it would be so easy.
- Right.
- "It'll be my absolute victory."
- And you must've checked...
- who else would be on the show.
- Of course.
That's right. I checked the list
and saw Se Chan's name there.
- But during the show,
- Yes.
I realized how charming he could be.
(During the show, I realized
how charming he could be.)
- He admitted his defeat?
- Why?
Don't you have dating skills?
He looked so handsome.
- Really?
- Oh, really?
Yes.
I find it hard to believe.
- On "Love Me Actually?"
- He looks happy.
Girls tend to pick someone
they feel comfortable around...
- when they're on a TV show.
- That's exactly my point.
- We hosted many shows like that.
- That's right.
That's why I said that Jae Suk was
my ideal type in an interview.
- Really?
- Yes.
You can find the article
on the internet.
"Song Hae Na's Ideal Type Is
Yoo Jae Suk."
- Really?
- Yes.
You look like a nice person. Okay.
She's socially savvy. Great.
It happens a lot...
- True.
- on matchmaking shows.
Many women choose someone else...
- They wouldn't pick whom they like.
- That's true.
- They would choose a different man.
- Woo Jae doesn't seem to agree.
I fell into a slump
for the first time in my life.
(I fell into a slump
for the first time in my life.)
Don't take it negatively.
- I hit rock bottom.
- He seemed so stressed out.
- You see,
- That was funny.
- Woo Jae has a lot of talents.
- I'm telling you the truth.
- Does he?
- He has a lot of talents.
- Yes. He's good at imitating...
- Really?
- Lee Soo Man,
- Me?
- Kim Jang Hoon,
- Of course.
Gong Yoo,
and so many other celebrities.
- Of course.
- You can imitate Kim Min Jong too?
- He looks like Min Jong.
- Yes, I can.
- I see the resemblance.
- By the way, Woo Jae...
It keeps bothering me.
Your shoulders are too rounded.
Right. You should fix it.
- Pull your shoulders back.
- Look at him.
- He's acting like a trainer.
- I couldn't...
Yoon Seok has a similar body to his.
(Yoon Seok has
a similar body to his.)
(The next Lee Yoon Seok)
- But...
- I can't ignore things like this.
- Come on, you guys.
- It bothers me.
He barely recovered his confidence
after "Love Me Actually."
- He may fall into a slump again.
- Not again.
- But it looks quite serious.
- Why would you talk about it?
I've been controlling my mind well
for the past few years.
- I see.
- But...
- Come on my show. I'll help you.
- Then...
Show us just one of them.
- A celebrity impression?
- Yes.
- He's really good at it.
- Well...
I think the best impression would be
Lee Seung Hwan.
Show us a little.
- You do have a similar voice.
- I'm excited.
- He's good at singing too.
- I think he'll do well.
(He started singing so suddenly.)
(Why did you leave me?)
- That was really good.
- That's all.
- He's amazing.
- My impressions are short.
- Imitate Min Jong this time.
- Sounds great.
- He's great. He never hesitates.
- He's really good at it.
- It was so good.
- You did well.
- He's good at it.
- I liked that.
(Now)
- That's it.
- Good job.
- He's really good at it.
- Imitate Kim Jang Hoon this time.
- That was good.
- Imitate Jang Hoon.
- Jang Hoon.
- He's good at it.
(1,000 times or 10,000 times)
That's good.
(You would come and go)
A kick.
(Jang Hoon's signature fly kick)
That's all...
- for the impression of Jang Hoon.
- That was so funny.
- That was impressive.
- Indeed.
- You did a great job.
- Yoon Seok...
- Yoon Seok is hilarious.
- How about Kim Dong Ryul?
- Kim Dong Ryul?
- Yes, I want to see his impression.
(He can imitate any singer
right away.)
- That was amazing.
- Good job.
- How about Yoon Seok?
- He's good at it.
- That was great.
- Indeed.
- How about Yoon Seok?
- He's amazing.
- Can you imitate him too?
- Yoon Seok?
Say his catchphrase too.
- That's good.
- "That's so mean."
- That was Lee Yoon Seok impression.
- Good job.
- "That's so mean."
- Great.
Let's give the four of them a hand.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Can you all step back a little?
- All right.
- That was hilarious.
There was a reason
for evaluating your fashion styles.
You can gain some additional points.
The seven of you will stand
where you are.
And the four guests will discuss...
deciding your rankings.
Starting from the worst dresser...
- Will they push us away?
- Yes.
- Starting from the worst dresser?
- That's terrifying.
- It's okay. Let's do this.
- Let's do this.
- It's okay.
- Please stand in front of them.
The higher you're ranked,
the more points you can get.
- It's okay.
- Since it's their decision,
- we should accept the result.
- Of course.
- We should accept it.
- Of course, we should.
- We should.
- Four of you, please discuss...
and push the person in last place first.
- Starting from the last place.
- This is so funny.
Please be fair and objective.
- He made no effort.
- I think...
we should choose Suk Jin.
- He should be in the last?
- His outfit is the worst.
- But that's too harsh.
- Decide based on our styles.
First, push the worst dresser
who came in seventh place.
- It's okay.
- Okay.
- I look cool from behind.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
He looks like Kanye West
from behind.
(They're discussing it seriously.)
Coming in seventh place would mean
you dressed awfully.
That person should never
talk about fashion again.
Now, please push the person
in seventh place.
- Can we push the person now?
- Push that person right away.
Push the person in seventh place.
Just push that person.
- Let's let Irene do it.
- Irene, go ahead.
It's okay. Don't hesitate
to push us.
We wouldn't mind.
- We won't be hurt.
- We would never be hurt.
(Who could be chosen
as the worst dresser?)
- I'm nervous.
- You can push me hard.
- Really?
- Okay.
(Suk Jin got eliminated first.)
- Are you serious?
- Really?
- Please move aside for now.
- My goodness.
- Please move aside.
- I'm glad I'm not in the last.
So this is what you do
on a variety show.
- Suk Jin is in seventh place.
- Suk Jin got eliminated.
Next, please push the person
in sixth place.
I have a feeling
that I'll be ranked high.
(Gym Jong Kook
is eliminated as well.)
- I'm good.
- You're out.
- Are you sure?
- It's all good.
- I...
- What he's wearing is better?
- At least I didn't come in last.
- Are you kidding me?
- It's understandable.
- Unbelievable.
Who's in fifth place then?
Go ahead.
- Nice.
- All right!
Seriously?
- It's true though.
- Right.
Are you kidding me?
Push the member in fourth place.
Take off your jacket halfway
like earlier.
But this is what
ties in the whole look.
- This isn't what I wanted.
- It's so true.
(Ms. Leopard Print came in 4th.)
It's So Min.
- Haha's too high up.
- I'm satisfied.
I agree with their choice.
- He looks different from behind.
- He looks so cool.
- From behind...
- That beggar?
- How can that beggar look cool?
- They're all professionals.
Ginger Boy is still up there.
We're down to the top three.
- Top 3?
- That alone makes me smile.
- Unbelievable.
- Top three?
- Are you kidding me?
- Let them see you from behind.
- On Running Man?
Things are too easy on Running Man.
It's down to those two.
Jong Kook's already annoyed.
- I can't look at Se Chan's legs.
- Did you hear him?
He's annoyed
when that's what he chose to wear?
It's not bad, right?
- Join me over here.
- They're professionals.
- No way.
- Come with me.
Third place is good enough.
(Ji Hyo is in 3rd place!)
- Seriously?
- I agree that you look good.
- I'm in third place, so...
- You sure are professionals.
- How does this make any sense?
- I'm in third place.
It makes no sense.
This is insane.
Are you sure about Se Chan though?
- This is insane.
- Tell me about it.
How does this make any sense?
How can that outfit be...
(The fashion terrorists
are outraged.)
This is crazy.
Let me explain though.
If he goes to
a fashion show overseas,
- he'll be photographed.
- Absolutely.
Irene, come on.
- He will be photographed.
- This is incredible.
- She's right.
- People will take his photo.
- I'm sure of it.
- No way.
He'll catch my eye for sure.
Don't you love
the color of his hair?
- Mr. Cheetos.
- Cheetos.
- I don't get it.
And now for the finals.
The finals.
- The finals?
- How is this even possible?
- I'm ashamed.
- How is this the finals?
We're the ones embarrassed.
- How can they be the finalists?
- This makes no sense.
- This is insane.
- I should buy these clothes.
Octopus Man is one of the finalists.
- Unbelievable.
- Octopus Man.
The one that gets pushed
will be in second place.
The one who remains
will be in first place.
Second place is good enough.
Then he's in first place?
The one who remains
will be crowned...
as the Fashion King.
The Fashion King. I love it.
When that's what they're wearing?
- They both look awful today.
- No way.
- They're professionals.
- Second place is good enough.
(The one who remains
will be the Fashion King.)
I look good from behind.
(Their pride hangs in the balance.)
(Who will be crowned as
the Fashion King?)
Let's do this.
- Haha won.
- Okay.
(Haha is the Fashion King!)
You guys are professionals!
They were serious about this.
- I mean...
- Right?
You're the real deal.
How about a photo?
I can't believe it.
- How does this make sense?
- Look at him.
He's really happy about this.
In 2, 3.
(He takes a selfie not caring about
what the others think.)
Seriously.
How does this make any sense?
This is a huge honor.
This is insane.
From behind...
- It works globally.
- They're professionals.
- They know what's trending.
- His style...
- works globally.
- Absolutely.
He'll be photographed a lot...
- out on the street.
- Exactly.
You will be given points
depending on your ranking.
- Okay.
- Nice.
Today's race is all about
earning points...
and using that
to make yourself taller.
- It's the Key Point Race.
- Key Point Race?
Since height means everything,
you will be sorted into teams
according to your height.
Tall, average, and short.
To make things fair,
Woo Jae will either be on
Team Average or Team Short.
- Do I get to choose?
- Yes.
All right.
Here is Team Tall.
Lee Hyun Yi.
- Right.
- Of course.
Hyun Yi's tall, so...
Joining her will be Irene.
Irene's tall as well.
Also on that team is Jae Suk.
How is he on Team Tall?
I'm 178cm.
And Jong Kook.
- So we're on one team.
- I see.
- Jong Kook and I are teammates.
- Nice.
- Let's do this.
- That's Team Tall.
I can't believe we're the tall ones.
- But...
- If you think about it,
- we're not exactly that tall.
- I know.
- Next up is Team Average.
- Team Average.
Suk Jin.
So Min.
And also Se Chan.
- Is it just the 3 of us?
- Is it us 3?
Yes, you're Team Average.
Aren't we the weaker team, then?
Here is Team Short.
Haha, Ji Hyo, and Hae Na.
- And Hae Na too.
- Right.
- So that's how it is.
- Last but not least,
Woo Jae will choose
the team he'd like to be on.
Since he'll be 60 soon...
What do you mean I'm almost 60?
- You're right.
- We should respect our elders.
- He'll soon turn 60.
- Still...
You're right.
I can tell that he's fond of me.
He'll need someone
to make up for his lack of energy.
You shine among us.
- He was born in 1986 as well.
- Just like us.
- The year of the tiger.
- That's right!
You can be his children for the day.
- Got it.
- Of course.
Let me now explain
the rules to today's race.
- I'm sure we have advantages too.
- Only they are a team of three.
Right.
You will increase your height
by winning in games.
The team with...
the highest average
on the touchpad will win.
(Reach higher
by increasing your height.)
You will find a wall
when all the games have ended.
- Where you manage to touch...
- Really?
Here's how you can grow taller.
You will earn coins
after playing today's games.
With them, you will be able
to purchase blocks.
So that's how it'll be.
You will be able to reach higher
if you have more blocks.
The number of members
receiving the penalty...
will depend on
how well you do as a team.
The winning team will win a prize
and earn immunity.
The shortest member
of the team in second place...
will receive the penalty.
The two shortest members
of the team in last place...
will also receive the penalty.
There's a way for you all
to increase your height...
which could lead you
to have immunity.
With the coins you earn,
you can either spend it
to get the team ahead...
or spend it
to increase your own height.
That's all we need.
- Let's not be selfish.
- They will lose for sure.
I can either buy blocks
for the team...
- or spend it for myself.
- Let's not be selfish.
- They will play dirty.
- It could get dangerous for them.
Buying shoe lifts
will hurt your team,
but you'll save yourself
if your team loses.
Buying blocks for the team
will get your team ahead.
You will be given
a moment to make your purchases...
every time we wrap up a game.
After four games,
your purchased items
will be revealed.
The three best-dressed members
will receive 3 coins, 2 coins,
and one coin respectively.
For the best-dressed members?
He gets three coins.
For looking fashionable.
This is super annoying.
Our team already has two!
- Nice.
- It was super important.
You'll gather after changing
into your team sweaters.
- All right.
- Okay!
(Who will win today's race?)
See you later!
- Let's go.
- Off we go.
(They gather to chat
in their team sweaters.)
Really?
(Looking around)
Where's Suk Jin?
Exactly. But it's only once a week.
Who's taking so long?
(His mouth twitches
as he teases Suk Jin.)
Are you kidding me?
At your age,
you should be setting an example!
Guys.
Oh, you're here.
- Who said that?
- How polite.
Suk Jin, you're here.
Wasn't someone talking about me?
- No?
- Of course not.
- No way.
- It wasn't the case.
Suk Jin, you're here.
- How polite of him.
- Hey.
Never forget your manners.
- Manners. Of course.
- Se Chan.
- Always be polite.
- Well-mannered.
- Hey, there.
- I will always bow.
You make living worthwhile.
Gather around, everyone.
How tall are you?
I'm around 187 and 188cm.
- Really?
- You're really tall.
Aren't you 190cm?
- Are you good at basketball?
- Basketball?
I'm terrible at it.
I love to be on my back.
It's annoying, you know.
People ask them that all the time.
Exactly. People ask me that too.
- "Do you play basketball?"
- Right.
You'd think that Yoon Seok
is good at basketball too. He isn't.
- Hyun Yi, do you play basketball?
- Are you good at it?
I'm terrible at it.
- Basketball...
- Aren't you good at volleyball?
- That would be her.
- I used to play volleyball.
- Yes, of course.
- She was on a team.
- Really?
- Hae Na, what about you?
- Me?
- Drinking alcohol.
- She's a heavy drinker.
- I can hold my liquor well.
- It's true.
- She's a heavy drinker.
It's a talent in its own right.
She loves to drink.
(At that moment...)
- It's a talent in its own right.
- And Hae Na...
I heard that as well.
- What are you up to?
- He...
- What's that?
- What are you doing?
What is it?
(Why is he wearing goggles?)
- Hold on.
- Check him out.
- This is too much.
- What are you wearing?
I have my reasons.
- Which is what?
- I'm not trying to be funny.
You're like...
- That's not the case.
- Are you an attention-seeker?
- What's going on?
- You see,
two days ago,
I received
vision correction surgery.
Like LASEK?
No, I had lens inserted.
So that's why.
I couldn't risk
my eyes receiving a blow.
- Of course.
- Then...
you should've stayed home.
(Hyun Yi chimes in.)
The procedure was done two days ago.
- Of course.
- So why...
He's here to get out of his slump.
- It could get worse though.
- It was done two days ago,
- so why bother...
- She is funny.
- Woo Jae...
- You're doing well today though.
Do you know what gave me the chills?
Yoon Seok wears goggles
when he works out.
Really?
The surgery must've taken
a toll on him.
"You're so thoughtful."
- When he plays games.
- "You're so thoughtful."
- He's good.
- Woo Jae...
Woo Jae is quite good
with variety shows.
- It's of high quality.
- He's good.
- High quality?
- He gets along with anything.
All right. Please slate for us.
- Hey, you didn't do it?
- Hey. So Min.
(The slate by the youngest member
of Running Man)
- Do it even if you're not told.
- Why didn't you do it?
- I'll slate now. In 1, 2, 3.
- What do you mean?
- Slate!
- What are you going to do?
You have to say it politely.
Say, "I'm going to slate."
- Don't say that. Say...
- I'm going to slate.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Are you upset?
- No, I'm not.
- You seem upset.
- Slate like this. Not like this.
- You should slate like this.
- Okay!
- Do it like this.
- So Min.
- That's how they tease people here.
You should be snappy.
- Okay.
- You're the youngest, you know.
- Stand over here now. Here.
All right. In this mission,
you have to hold out...
through all humiliations
with your determination.
It's called I'm Holding Out.
- It sounds hard.
- A man and a woman...
will pair up.
A couple from each team
will play the mission.
For two minutes,
we'll count the time each couple
is on the buoy.
The couple that holds out
the longest wins.
It's simple, right?
- It sounds fun.
- We must go up there.
- How do we go up there?
- The time we hold out on the buoy?
The two of us should be up there
for you to count, right?
- Correct.
- Got it.
- A man and a woman?
- That's right.
But there are three men
on this team,
- Can't two men play?
- so Suk Jin will play woman.
He'll be a woman?
- I'll do it.
- He should do it. He's a bit...
- But Suk Jin is...
- I'm really strong.
- You are?
- I'm too strong to play woman.
Woo Jae is quite competitive
unlike how he seems.
- He is.
- He's quite competitive.
What's creepy is that
Yoon Seok is also very competitive.
I'm glad he's competitive.
- "You're so thoughtful."
Please pick players
who will play in Round One.
- Come over here.
- It's okay as long as...
- our feet don't touch the ground?
- You should quickly dominate.
- So Min, use your feet, and...
- I can go up like this.
(Woo Jae's long legs seem useful.)
That was great.
Your thighs seem strong.
The thing is,
they'll grab your legs.
They won't let you go up there
like that.
(Wrestling is most important
in this mission.)
- Right. We must go up together.
- So Min and Woo Jae...
- should play first.
- Okay. Sounds great.
- The two of you should play.
- You two should play.
- I'll play with Seok Soon.
- You and I will go second.
- You should watch Ji Hyo play.
- All right.
Who is officially stronger
between you two?
- Irene's arms are stronger.
- They are?
- Is that so?
- She's the goalie.
- My arms... Okay.
- Then...
- I should play with Irene.
- Okay, I'll play with you.
- Hey...
- Jong Kook is going second?
Jong Kook is going second?
Hey, let us play first.
(Urgent)
We'll play first.
- No, we'll play first.
- No.
- We'll go first.
- Jong Kook is going second?
Then Woo Jae should play later.
You should play against Jong Kook.
- You're the fiery fist, aren't you?
- Right, since we're...
- on the same level.
- That's right.
Then we should go first.
- You can show your power then.
- Okay, I'll play later.
- I'll wait for the rival match.
- But you two are really strong.
Players for Round One,
please stand here.
You can start
once we stop the music.
- All right.
- So Min and Woo Jae,
please come over here.
- Me? Okay.
- Okay.
- He looks good with So Min.
- They're in trouble.
- So Min looks good with him.
- So Min, he looks good with you.
- You go well...
- I mean it.
- With me?
- with comedians. He's Yoon Seok.
- Yoon Seok.
- How many times...
do I have to impersonate him today?
- "You're so thoughtful."
- Did you see...
- So Min's face just now?
- Why?
When we told her she looks good
with Woo Jae,
she went, "With me?"
("With me?")
Why are you acting shy again?
No, it's...
Do we look good together?
This is when she made it
really obvious.
It was when she found out
that Woo Jae was coming.
When we paused the shoot
to get changed,
she went to Woo Jae and said,
"Hey, we're the same age."
("Hey, we're the same age.")
(Trying to build a bond
in a cheesy way)
Jae Suk, you heard that?
- For me...
- I'm not the type...
who can easily talk casually
to strangers.
But she directly asked me
to speak casually.
So Min is also not the type
to speak casually right away.
But what if So Min
just ends up liking Se Chan?
- Then Woo Jae...
- Woo Jae will have to...
- will experience another slump.
- Is this "Love Me Actually?"
- No, it's not.
- It's not.
Woo Jae, this is Running Man.
You should focus.
- You remind me of that show.
- So Min and Se Chan...
have something going on.
- Right. I know that they do.
- Yes.
Focus, Woo Jae.
We'll play the music for Round One.
You can start as soon as
the music stops.
There's going to be wrestling.
We go up...
- once the music stops?
- Yes, when it stops.
Then what do we do
while the music plays?
(The first song is "Dynamite" by BTS.)
(The geezers' dance moves
that we wish ARMY wouldn't see)
Ji Hyo is the strong one.
- Yes, Ji Hyo is strong.
- She's quite strong.
Ji Hyo is...
(The ace with 12 years of experience
relaxedly enjoys the dance.)
(The match starts.)
- Hey, Irene!
- Haha just hit Ji Hyo.
(Haha and Jae Suk quickly
occupied the buoy.)
(Long-legged Irene falls off.)
Irene! Don't come up
from there. It's dangerous.
(It only counts
if the two of them are on the buoy.)
Come up, Se Chan!
- Hold on, Suk Jin.
- Push Ji Hyo off!
Don't push me!
(Irene managed to come up.)
Irene, come here.
(A defender who specializes
in weaklings)
(Hold me!)
(Screaming)
- Hurry.
- Hold me!
- Irene.
- No. Hurry.
Hold me!
Go up again.
(She attacks ruthlessly
with her high-pitched screaming.)
(Studying in advance)
Hey, she's trying to come up.
Who is this?
Is it Irene?
I thought it was Ji Hyo.
(The two middle-aged men
go head-to-head.)
- I thought it was Ji Hyo.
- Jae Suk!
Okay. Well done.
(Suk Jin ends up falling off.)
(All members of Team Average
are wiped.)
- Hurry up. It's okay.
- Go up again.
- It's okay. Go up.
- Push them, Irene!
- Go up again.
- Ji Hyo, push them!
- Go up again, Suk Jin!
(Among the pro players
with 12 years of experience,)
For how long do we have to hold out?
(Irene became an iron gatekeeper.)
Over here! Okay.
(Hitting)
(The invisible hand intrudes.)
It's over. You can't go up there.
- Push them.
The male couple is too merciless.
Se Chan.
(The male couple from Team Average
is playing shamefully.)
Se Chan, come up here!
What are you, a spy?
- Irene!
- Hey, Se Chan!
Ten more seconds!
- Go up again.
- Irene is no joke.
It's over anyway.
(Round 1 ends.)
I did well.
- Irene.
- Irene never let go of her place.
I did well.
(The orange boy and the old man
are dead tired.)
You did it, Irene.
(Irene has a strong grip as
she was a volleyball player once.)
All right.
Wow, Irene was no joke.
She's a tough one indeed.
Everyone, we have the results
of Round One.
Round 1's 1st place...
goes to the team that held out
for 1 minute and 6 seconds.
It's Jae Suk and Irene.
(Team Tall wins 1st place
with 1 minute and 6 seconds.)
You won?
I knew it.
- That's amazing.
- Great job.
- What did you do?
- Second place...
goes to Haha and Ji Hyo
who held out for 56 seconds.
- Good. Second place is good too.
- We're in second place.
- Well done.
- It was impossible to go up.
Third place goes to
Se Chan and Suk Jin...
- who held out for 18 seconds.
- Only 18 seconds?
- Gosh, Yangsebari.
- Hae Na.
- Yes?
- Let's go.
I'm coming.
I don't think we can win.
Jong Kook...
We'll combine the scores,
so you can turn the tables.
- Because of Jong Kook.
- This is...
- I don't think we can win.
- We need to work together.
Players for Round Two,
please gather.
- Okay.
- He's really strong.
This is a rival match.
Hey, Jong Kook...
We should work together.
- All right.
- He'll kill you all.
- We'll turn on the music now.
- I know.
Can I even go up here?
- Music, cue.
- You should be able to.
(The music for Round 2 plays.)
(The song for Round 2
is "Gotta Go" by Chungha.)
All right.
Let's go.
(Too bad it's already midnight)
Oh, that means midnight?
- Stop. Hyun Yi, what's that?
- That doesn't seem right.
Something seems off.
Something seems off about her dance.
That doesn't seem right.
Something is off.
What are you doing, Hyun Yi?
(Her body roll seems somewhat off.)
- Something is off.
- Something is...
What are you doing, Hyun Yi?
Her dance is off.
(The cheesy girl
has taken over the stage.)
That's it. That's the dance.
What are you doing, Hae Na?
(Hyun Yi has taken over
the dance floor in the meantime.)
I'll join you.
Gosh, Hyun Yi is...
- Look at Hae Na.
- She's just...
Her dance is off.
- Why are their dances so weird?
- How they're such bad dancers?
(It's impossible to understand
the way they move their bodies.)
- Hae Na, come up to the center.
- The models' dances are weird.
(Woo Jae is only thinking
of dominating Jong Kook.)
So Min, you must come down now.
We'll start now.
- I have to go down?
- Go around.
You must win.
- Go up there.
- I just came down.
I just came down.
(Jong Kook came up first.)
- Help me.
- It's over. Hyun Yi went up.
(So Min is focused on
attacking Hae Na.)
She already went up.
Go up there!
Go up, Woo Jae!
Go up!
(The rivals are finally
taking on each other.)
Are you going to lift me?
(Hugging)
(After trying a few times,
he suddenly hugs Jong Kook.)
- Be careful! I might go blind.
- Go up there.
(Woo Jae tries to attack them
with empty threats.)
- Be careful.
- Push Woo Jae off.
- Hey.
- Woo Jae.
Push Woo Jae off.
(The grasshopper
is hanging by a thread.)
I might go blind!
- Woo Jae!
- Stay still.
(So Min hasn't come up
while Woo Jae threatens them.)
We should go up.
What is he, a rock?
Stay still. You can just stay still.
- You should...
- Hey!
- You should go up.
- So Min, you should go up.
- Go up there, So Min!
- You need to go up.
(Team Tall has pushed everyone off.)
- You must go up.
- Go up there, So Min.
(Team Short barely manages
to join Team Tall.)
- Just stay still.
- Go up there!
- Go up there.
- I'm really going up this time.
- Here I go!
- Look at Woo Jae.
- Go up to the buoy!
What is Woo Jae doing?
- Yes, Hyun Yi and you should...
- Go up there.
Here I go!
Go up there, Woo Jae!
I'm really going this time.
Yes, Hyun Yi and you should...
(He lightly runs as though he's
going to face Jong Kook head-on.)
- He's coming up.
- Just stay still like that.
(Woo Jae jumps up to the part
where Jong Kook isn't present.)
(Hitting)
- That's it.
- Woo Jae...
Here I go.
- Here I go. I'm serious.
- Woo Jae is like a paper doll.
I'm really going this time.
- Hey.
- A paper doll.
(The paper doll
is jumping around again.)
- He's a paper doll.
- Totally.
Woo Jae. Where did he go?
("Navillera")
- Hey.
- He is a funny guy.
(Overcoming embarrassment
with an outdated skit)
- Hey.
- He is a funny guy.
Great one, Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae.
- I got a call.
- Good one.
- Woo Jae, it's not too late.
Woo Jae is hilarious.
- Hey.
- What's with that team?
- That team...
- We're the worst.
Woo Jae...
Hey, Woo Jae!
You're so sloppy.
(Woo Jae's rival wins
an overwhelming victory.)
All right.
- What was that?
- Woo Jae.
- That was a good fight.
- I thought you were a paper doll.
- What were you doing?
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
He's only competitive.
It was intimidating, wasn't it?
This guy... I didn't know
where he'd pop up.
- We're in last place.
- I thought...
- Woo Jae was a kite.
- All right.
- You were just flying around.
- All right, got it.
I think we didn't even earn
two seconds.
- I couldn't go up, not even once.
- Well done.
- We did really well.
- Jong Kook...
- and Hyun Yi.
- We lost, but we fought well.
Your record is
1 minute and 58 seconds.
They didn't come down at all.
- Except for two seconds?
- Yes. I mean...
Next is...
Haha and Hae Na. Your record
is 1 minute and 15 seconds.
(Team Short's record isn't bad.)
- All right.
- What about us?
- Next is...
- I bet it's similar to theirs.
Woo Jae and So Min.
- Right.
Your record is
rounded up to two seconds.
- Pardon?
- You rounded up?
- That was terrible.
- So it was less than two seconds.
They couldn't go up there together.
How did...
So the team in first place...
is Team Tall.
- All right!
- We did it.
- They must have a lot of coins.
- Three coins each.
- Okay.
The team in second place
is Team Short.
If you think about it...
- Here you go, Irene.
- Thank you.
Here, Hyun Yi.
Thank you.
- Thank you! This is nice.
- We have so many coins.
Good job.
All right, now. Combining the points
and the points you earned earlier,
you will take turns
to enter the voting booth...
and purchase either
a block or a shoe lift.
Buying shoe lifts
will hurt your team,
but you'll save yourself
if your team loses.
But buying blocks for the team
will get your team ahead.
The number of members
receiving the penalty...
will depend on
how well you do as a team.
The winning team will win a prize
and earn immunity.
The shortest member
of the team in second place...
will receive the penalty.
The two shortest members
of the team in last place...
will also receive the penalty.
We must buy it no matter what.
- We should think of the team first.
- We must buy it. Of course.
The result of the vote will be
revealed only toward the end,
so feel free to choose
whatever you want.
We won't reveal it right away.
We must buy blocks.
- We must buy blocks.
- Of course.
- We don't even need to...
- say this many times.
- Of course, we should get blocks.
Of course. It's a given.
- We can just trust each other.
- Since we're already tall.
- I won't talk about it anymore.
- Okay.
I'll get a block too.
We must be at a disadvantage
to think of betraying each other.
- You're right.
- We have it good right now.
- Let's go.
- Hyun Yi, you can go first.
- Me? Okay.
(Hyun Yi of Team Tall
goes to vote first.)
How do I get in here?
So Min! You should be careful!
- Do I just put it in here?
- We'll be in first place.
(They need to put in the coin they
earned in each box...)
(to purchase either a block
or a shoe lift.)
(Team Tall promised each other
to buy a block just 30 seconds ago.)
We must buy blocks.
We should think of the team first.
I'll get a block too.
How thick is the shoe lift?
(What will the first voter,
Hyun Yi, choose?)
(She purchases a block.)
Then how much is a block?
(She buys blocks in a row
while thinking of her teammates.)
(She spends the last coin
on a shoe lift.)
(Lee Hyun Yi of Team Tall,
2 blocks, 1 shoe lift)
- You spent it all, right?
- I bought blocks.
- Right?
- It'd be meaningless otherwise.
- I know. It'd be meaningless.
- We all have the same height.
(She indifferently increased
her height by 1cm.)
- Can I put all of them in?
- Yes, you can.
I can?
Then I'll use two, and...
(Will Irene keep the promise
she made with her teammates?)
Okay.
(Irene of Team Tall,
1 block, 1 shoe lift)
(Irene also bought a shoe lift
to increase her height by 1cm.)
- I'm going to get blocks.
- Shoe lifts are useless.
- I'm going to get blocks only.
- You should think of the team.
We will win. We can just win it.
You're tall.
Goodness. We don't have to
buy shoe lifts just yet.
We should invest in blocks.
Where is it?
This is for a block.
(He buys 2 blocks
as he confidently said.)
Will the other members
pay all their coins for blocks?
(Will the other members
pay all their coins for blocks?)
For your information,
(The members of Team Tall
have similar heights.)
(Then shoe lifts
will come in handy.)
(Tapping)
(He could feel the coins
the others spent on shoe lifts.)
We can just win first place
as a team.
I'll get a shoe lift.
(Jong Kook purchased a shoe lift.)
(Jong Kook got a shoe lift!)
I'll insert one for a block.
Do we have plenty of blocks?
(He purchases a shoe lift
as expected.)
There's quite a lot in here too.
(Every member of Team Tall
betrayed each other.)
(He spends his last coin
on a shoe lift as well.)
(Yoo Jae Suk of Team Tall,
1 block, 2 shoe lifts)
(It's Team Short's turn.)
(Hae Na was contemplating
her loyalty to Haha and Ji Hyo.)
Hae Na, don't you use your head!
No, I didn't!
(Haha...)
(uses all his coins on shoe lifts
without thinking twice.)
- See you later.
- Okay.
Don't make a confusing face.
Haha, seriously... I...
- You know how it's like, right?
- You know me.
- Ji Hyo has changed a lot.
- She twists games a lot.
- She twists them a lot.
- No, I don't.
Is that so?
(She purchases shoe lifts
right away.)
(Ms. Song has been betraying
everyone recently.)
(She uses her coins
to buy 2 shoe lifts.)
(Song Ji Hyo of Team Short,
2 shoe lifts)
So Min!
If we all choose to vote for
the team, we'll win first place.
I can't get the penalty today.
Okay. You can't
get the penalty, right?
(Team Average is after an immunity
by purchasing blocks.)
Hello.
I don't even need to say it
out loud. I'm getting shoe lifts.
I should make myself
taller first, and...
So Min! They said you'd need to...
change your underwear
for today's penalty.
I already bought it.
Penalties these days...
are so harsh,
so I need my team to win.
(Ji Suk Jin of Team Average,
1 shoe lift)
So this is how good it feels
to do something nice.
This is only our first round.
We don't need to buy shoe lifts.
- Not yet.
- You're right.
Woo Jae! Think of the team.
How many times must I tell you?
- You're tall.
- I...
can afford it.
(He purchases a shoe lift.)
I think my team
will come in last place.
As long as it's not me.
I won't see them ever again anyway.
This is the lift?
(Everyone of Team Average
chose to buy shoe lifts.)
(Se Chan got 3 shoe lifts.)
All right.
Your first choice is over.
Let's move to the second floor
for the next mission.
Let's go.
Are we going to keep
playing this game?
No, we won't. Come on, Woo Jae.
I was confident to do well
in the next round.
We change games.
- You must've been worried.
- No, I was sad, that's why.
That's why I asked.
(Fortunately, the paper doll
won't have to flap around anymore.)
- So Min.
- Yes?
This is so troublesome.
Let me explain it to you.
When everyone is gone...
Look at the cameraman and ask...
if you can slate. When he says yes,
that's when you slate.
- You got it, right?
- Can I slate now?
Look at the cameraman
and check if everyone is gone.
- Okay.
- Look. You need his permission.
- Do I hit it vertically?
- Yes. Tell him you'll slate.
I'm going to slite.
It's "slate," not "slite."
(The path of becoming the youngest
is long and tough.)
Let's do it.
- I'm going to slate.
- Yes, leave your hands like that.
One, two.
Gosh! It should be one, two, three.
Then move out.
I'll slate.
One, two, three.
That's it! Good job.
I'll teach you again.
I need to teach you well.
(After the youngest's slate,
they move to the next spot.)
Wow, what is this place?
This place is nice too.
That's understandable.
It feels odd.
- Why?
- So Min.
Because she's sitting next
to me and Woo Jae?
So Min must be really happy
with her team today.
I thought So Min...
What's wrong with you, So Min?
It's so fascinating.
I don't get why you're so happy...
because they're not
doing anything for you.
- But you are...
- She doesn't need all that.
So Min doesn't mind it.
I was wondering
why she seemed so happy.
So Min doesn't mind that at all.
As long as she's satisfied,
- she's all good.
- She's just happy.
Why don't you guys fight over me?
- Over you?
- Yes.
You want them to fight over you?
Try to steal my heart.
Woo Jae doesn't seem
interested at all.
- Rather than that...
- Why would you want us to fight?
- "Rather than that?"
- It's something I'm bad at.
You mean stealing a woman's heart?
You can do it.
What was that?
What are you doing?
She said he could do it.
- Woo Jae...
- I was watching the show,
and there was a comment
I could totally relate to.
- Which one is it?
- It's what you said.
- You called her cheesy.
(You called her cheesy.)
You said you've never seen
anyone like this.
- There are two people.
- Exactly.
There are two people I say that to.
Her being cheesy is her charm.
- It is.
- It suits her.
The thing is, So Min likes him
not because of his looks...
- but because of his wit.
- That's right.
- I like guys who are humorous.
And he's really funny.
- Woo Jae is indeed cool,
- He's a good talker.
but it's not like
he's amazingly cool.
He's not that cool.
- But he's really charming.
- He's not that cool.
I wasn't known for my looks...
among the models.
- Then were you known for your wit?
- But...
- you're the best-looking one here.
- That's true.
- Well, that's...
- Right?
- I won't deny that.
- You're the best-looking one.
- He won't deny it?
- He said he wouldn't deny it.
You know how we have
many guests, right?
But I'm not that envious
of your looks.
(I'm not that envious
of your looks.)
You're not that cool.
We have a lot of guests,
- but you're not that cool.
- When Woo Jae...
When Woo Jae walks by,
it doesn't turn my head.
You're not that handsome.
- You know it yourself.
- I'm not envious at all.
- Your looks...
- It's not because of your looks.
When you first drew the curtains,
I just went,
"He's wearing a designer label."
- That's all.
- "Nice jacket."
- I went, "Nice jacket."
- "It's Gucci."
- That's all.
Isn't there something going on
with you and Sae Ho?
You guys have something going on?
- With who?
- What do you mean?
- Irene and Sae Ho?
- There's nothing? I thought...
But we're really close.
- She's the type Sae Ho likes.
- So we hang out too.
- Really?
- For real?
- We ate together too.
- She's the type he really likes.
- Why?
- Did you two eat alone?
No, I wouldn't do that.
- Then was Chang Hee there?
- Don't get me wrong!
(Adamant)
No. It's not like that.
- Are you offended?
- It's not like that.
- We have many mutuals.
- What do you mean?
- Mutual friends.
- We have many mutual friends.
I thought she said "Musical."
I heard it
as "Village Survival, the Eight,"
- the show.
- "Village Survival, the Eight."
It's not every day
that we meet people...
- in the fashion industry.
- They rarely visit variety shows.
Is Woo Jae popular among models?
I am not sure.
(I am not sure.)
- She said it with seriousness.
- Today,
Woo Jae is getting attacked a lot.
- I see that Hae Na can't lie.
- Isn't he popular?
- He isn't someone...
- Seriously.
who gets talked about much.
My goodness.
He isn't popular
in the fashion industry.
- He is popular in other industries.
- That's the worse.
- Hey.
- Seriously.
- It's like that.
- You are an intellectual.
- They can't rate themselves.
- I said it as it is.
An economy major sure is different.
Do junior models talk about
Woo Jae and go,
"He is pretty nice?"
He doesn't get mentioned much.
I see.
Who gets mentioned?
The male model
who gets mentioned a lot...
is Nam Joo Hyuk.
- I see. Joo Hyuk.
- You know who he is.
I am jealous of him.
Another one is Jang Ki Yong.
- Jang Ki Yong.
- He is popular these days.
When they mentioned Jang Ki Yong,
I realized what it's like.
- Nam Joo Hyuk too.
- Seriously.
Fortunately, I am unbothered...
because I know
that they are on another level.
It's not like...
such words hurt my feelings.
- He is confident.
- I see.
In the modeling industry, he is...
- the only one who works that way.
- No one else is like him.
He is the only one.
- He works steadily.
- His boyfriend-like photos...
- are famous.
- He is witty.
- He is charming.
- You know,
- there is that.
- The boyfriend-like photos.
His boyfriend-like photos
are famous.
What are those?
- The boyfriend-like photos.
- Someone's actual boyfriend.
He dresses like
someone's actual boyfriend.
- The boyfriend look.
- Yes.
- Are those what he is famous for?
- It means...
that he looks like a non-celebrity.
Hyun Yi.
- Stop it.
- Hyun Yi.
- We were talking among ourselves.
- All of us could hear you.
- Do you know what Hyun Yi said?
I went, "Woo Jae is famous
for his boyfriend-like photos."
She went, "It means..."
"that he looks like someone
you would meet in real life."
- I see. She has a point.
- He isn't like Jang Ki Yong.
- Someone you could seduce.
- That's right.
Someone you would see
around universities.
- That's right.
- Like an actual boyfriend.
So people think,
"If I make up my mind,"
- "I might be able to seduce him."
- That's right.
All right.
Fine. Good.
With my charms,
I target a niche market.
- That's right.
- Of course.
- Do you accept it then?
- I'm so happy about it.
- It's a good thing.
- He said he is happy.
- Are you happy?
- During an interview...
For goodness' sake.
I am sorry,
but why are you showing teeth?
(I am sorry,
but why are you showing teeth?)
(He gets annoyed
upon seeing Jae Suk's teeth.)
His mouth was closed, but...
His teeth are always showing.
That's how it is.
- You are being sensitive.
- Really?
You are being sensitive.
- I...
- You are being sensitive.
- Woo Jae, you are being sensitive.
- Hey.
You must have sneered at him.
- Jae Suk's teeth...
- Why did you sneer at him?
are always showing.
His mouth was closed,
but one tooth was clearly visible.
- Hey.
- That's how it is.
- He is being sensitive.
- Woo Jae, you are being sensitive.
That happens
when he is feeling good.
- Yes.
- That's right.
This time,
we will play a game
so many viewers requested.
What is it?
It's the Yang Se Chan Game.
That game.
- We haven't played it in a while.
- I know.
- It's a fun game.
- It's named after me.
Your identity is on your forehead.
(It involves guessing the identity
of the person on the hat.)
(Wrong and funny answers
made the game popular.)
(Sharp questions are needed
to guess the person's identity!)
There will be four rounds.
We came up with a list of matches.
In Round One, Jae Suk,
Woo Jae, and Haha will go.
It's a war between the stars.
My team will win.
- I will show you.
- Woo Jae.
Let's go.
Let's win.
If the game
doesn't involve using my body...
You are good at it, right?
I rule.
(Haha's keyword is Kim Yeon Koung.)
What is he going to do?
- Jae Suk's identity is hard.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Is mine easy?
- It's easy.
Everyone's identity is easy.
But it will be hard to explain.
- You checked everyone's identity.
- I will get it right quickly.
It's funny.
I won't be funny in this round.
- I will get it right quickly.
- Okay.
Show us your skills.
- Okay. I will show you.
- Watch.
Which question...
- should I ask?
- It can be confusing for newbies.
- You need to be experienced.
- Don't be flustered.
Don't be flustered, Woo Jae.
Just don't be flustered.
- Hey.
- Let's hear your first question.
Both of them are clumsy.
- We don't need time to think.
- They are clumsy.
Let's begin right away.
Is this person...
from the past or present?
He is pretending to be sharp.
(He gets caught
trying to play a detective.)
Is this person
from the past or present?
That person was born in the past
and is living in the present.
- That person is alive.
- What?
That person is alive.
- Is this person alive?
- Yes.
- Really? Okay.
- That's right.
- Okay.
Then this person must be old.
- Can I ask a question?
- Yes.
"This person must be old."
Is this person a man or a woman?
(Joo Woo Jae, Donald Trump)
That's sharp.
(Well...)
Come on.
(You guys are too much.)
That's just wrong.
- It's hard to say.
- What?
- What's the matter?
Don't you know the answer?
- Come on.
- Don't do that.
- What's the matter?
- It's hard to say.
- Don't you know the answer?
- You are too much.
- Hold on.
Listen.
It was a sudden question.
- Give him the answer.
- It takes time to answer.
- I can't believe it.
- That person is...
- I can't believe them.
- Why are you hesitating?
It's a person.
- We can tell him this much.
- Yes.
- A man.
- That's right.
That's right.
- Okay.
- It's basic information.
- I heard that he is a man.
- Yes.
Is this person a man or a woman?
(Haha, Kim Yeon Koung)
(Well...)
Unbelievable.
- Do you know?
- They are too much.
Come on.
- It's the first question.
- Okay.
- Let's answer truthfully.
- Tell me this much.
- Tell him this much.
- She is...
- a woman.
- A woman?
- I see. She must be a woman.
- Okay.
Let me ask you this right away.
What does this person wear?
Hold on. You should have asked
about the person's sex.
Casual clothes.
My goodness.
- Casual clothes?
- Yes. Casual clothes.
- Yes.
- You asked a stupid question.
- I think...
this person often wears
formal clothes.
This person wears
casual clothes too.
This person's fashion style
is cosmopolitan.
- Cosmopolitan?
- Yes.
It's also nomadic.
- Nomadic?
- Yes.
I am sorry, but you should ask
a definite question.
You should narrow things down.
- For goodness' sake.
- You need answers...
that narrow things down.
Your question wasn't very helpful.
- Are you a player?
- No.
- I am a meddler.
- I see.
That's the person's style.
Is that so? Okay.
- Casual clothes.
- Yes.
- He is pretending to be sharp.
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
- He is pretending to be sharp.
Is this person Korean?
(Joo Woo Jae, Donald Trump)
(Pondering)
- That's so funny.
- Don't you know?
- Why are you hesitating?
- This is...
- an essential step.
- It's so funny.
- I need to take a breath first.
- It's an essential step.
- You are doing so well.
- Do you really have to think?
- It's an essential step.
You are being professional.
- Is this person Korean?
- Do you really have to think?
It's the global era,
so nationalities aren't important.
(Even his teammate is incredulous.)
I agree.
It's like that these days.
Isn't it a childish question?
We are the world.
- In any case...
- "A childish question."
"We are the world."
If you want to know...
Just tell him.
He isn't Korean.
(Okay.)
I will ask my question.
Is this person Korean?
My goodness.
It's unclear, right?
- Really?
- Right now,
- she isn't in Korea.
- Is it unclear?
- That's right.
- She isn't in Korea.
Is she a Korean national?
She isn't in Korea right now.
That's not what I asked.
Is she a Korean national?
Didn't you hear me?
She isn't in Korea.
I didn't ask you if she is in Korea.
Is she a Korean national?
- Is she?
- She isn't in Korea.
(They endlessly say,
"She isn't in Korea.")
- Woo Jae.
- I said the same thing.
I didn't ask you...
- if she is in Korea.
- Okay.
Is she a Korean national?
- You are in Korea, right?
- Yes.
She isn't in Korea.
That's not what I asked.
I am Korean.
- It's the same thing.
- I am Korean.
- I know that.
- What's your nationality?
- What? I am Korean.
- How about you? How about her?
- I am Korean.
- We are in Korea.
- That's right.
- She isn't in Korea.
- Is this allowed?
- It's the fact.
- She is a global person.
- So she is Korean. All right.
- Okay.
- A Korean woman.
- We can give him that much.
I will ask a question.
What is...
this person's job?
- It's really hard to say.
- I know.
That question wasn't very sharp.
Be quiet!
Why did you sit behind me?
- What?
- Seriously.
Irene, stop him.
For goodness' sake.
Why is he so bad
at asking questions?
Job.
This person is a hero.
- This person is a hero. It's true.
- A hero.
This person is a hero.
That was a good answer.
I know.
I will say this.
"Along with the Gods."
"Along with the Gods?"
- A hero.
- "Along with the Gods."
That's cool.
- That's...
- "Along with the Gods."
- That's true.
- I figured it out.
- Really?
- Who is it?
- I figured it out.
That can't be right.
I figured it out.
Let me answer.
(Let me answer.)
(Person of the present day,
casual and formal clothes, hero)
(What will be Jae Suk's answer?)
Robert Downey Jr.
(Robert Downey Jr.)
(He guessed the person
to be Robert Downey Jr.)
How did he get that?
- How did you get that?
- How did he get that?
- Robert Downey Jr.
- How?
- How did you get that?
Robert Downey Jr.
He is our hero.
- That's incorrect.
- Really?
- You aren't even close.
- Jae Suk.
- A hero in the widest sense.
- Really?
Haha calls everyone a hero.
- Can I ask a question?
- Go ahead.
- Woo Jae, let's go.
- How many characters?
What do you mean?
Well...
- It depends on how you count.
How many characters are in the name?
It's hard to tell.
I think the name has
5, 6, or 7 characters.
- I think it has over 20 characters.
- That's right.
- You could say that.
- Yes.
You need to judge well, Woo Jae.
That's right.
I will get things started
in earnest now.
I will ask a sharp question
about this person.
Does this person appear on TV?
Hae Na is quite startled.
This person must appear on TV.
- This person...
- I asked the right question.
This person appears on TV.
- Is that the case?
- This person appears on TV.
This person appears on TV.
This person must be
a TV personality.
(Chuckling)
We are at a disadvantage
because he is the master of games.
(We are at a disadvantage.)
- I think he is close to the answer.
- A TV personality.
Hold on.
Who was that person?
- I can't remember the name.
- Who?
Can't you remember the name?
Didn't this person win a big award?
- Can't you remember the name?
- No.
Hold on.
- Can't you?
- Hold on.
- You know this person, right?
- I know this person.
- But you can't remember the name.
- It's on the tip of my tongue.
You know the person,
but you can't remember the name.
Jae Suk figured it out.
- You can't remember the name.
- Jae Suk figured it out.
He figured it out quickly.
- You know, right?
- My teacher.
- You know.
- "My teacher."
What's this person's job?
- Now, he is taking a break.
- He is jobless.
- That's right.
- Now, he is jobless.
He isn't working.
- That could be a hint.
- Let me answer.
(Let me answer!)
- A genius would get it right.
- Donald Trump.
- How did you know?
(Woo Jae is correct.)
(Woo Jae got the answer
by asking 4 questions.)
- You are a genius.
- I am good at using my brain.
(The paper doll
finally showed his strength.)
- That was incredible.
- You are a genius.
He is a genius.
He did an amazing job.
That was incredible.
- That was incredible.
- You should answer like that.
Woo Jae is so annoying.
He is smart and sexy.
Does the second place get something?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
So this person is a Korean woman
who isn't in Korea.
Haha, ask a question.
The only thing he knows is
that she is a Korean woman.
- This person...
- Ask a sharp question.
- Right now...
- What does this person wear?
(Haha, Kim Yeon Koung)
(Haha asks a sharp question
about what she wears.)
What does she wear for her job?
She wears something sporty.
(She wears something sporty.)
You gave that information.
- You gave that information.
- That's good information.
I am impressed.
(Haha gained crucial information.)
- Is it that person?
- Sporty.
(Will he be able to figure it out?)
Let me answer.
I really know the answer.
Kim Yeon Koung.
(Kim Yeon Koung is correct.)
- Sporty.
"Sporty" was crucial information.
My goodness.
Sporty.
"Sporty" was crucial information.
It's too bad
that you couldn't remember the name.
I...
(Na Kyung Eun)
She is a hero. She really is.
- How was I supposed to get this?
- She is a hero.
- I said, "Along with the Gods."
- I mean...
- All moms are heroes.
- That's right.
(Woo Jae took 1st place
and Haha took 2nd place.)
For goodness' sake.
- Thus, Jae Suk took third place.
- It was Kyung Eun.
All right.
In Round Two, Irene
So Min, and Haha will go.
- Okay.
- You will go again.
- It's a good one.
- Woo Jae was really good.
I know.
- I am curious.
- How will they get it right?
- The first place...
- Is mine hard?
- I think it's too hard.
- You can do well.
She will never get it right.
Seriously.
- I think it will be hard...
- I will guess without looking.
- for So Min.
- Will it be hard for me?
She might not know who it is.
What?
(Jong Kook hasn't looked
at Irene's keyword, Kim Jong Kook.)
I will guess without looking.
It will be hard for So Min.
I will give you
straightforward answers.
Irene, do well.
Okay.
- You can do it.
- Ask a question.
Is this person from the present day?
Of course.
That's right.
- All right.
- They are cool about it.
- That's good.
- Give each other some hints.
- That's right.
That's right.
Is this person a man or a woman?
That's a good question.
For goodness' sake.
- A man.
- All right.
- Let's speed things up.
- Is he definitely a man?
- He is definitely a man.
- Okay.
Is this person a man or a woman?
(Haha, Spider-Man)
(Well...)
(The sound of cheaters)
Come on.
- It's the first question.
- He is a man.
- Is this person a man?
- Yes. He is a man.
He is a man. Okay.
Is this person a man or a woman?
- A man.
- A man?
- Yes.
- He is a man.
A man from the present day.
- I like that this round is quick.
- A man from the present day.
Is this person Korean?
(So Min, Elon Musk)
- No.
- No?
She said no.
No?
- And that's the correct answer.
- I got confused for a second.
- That's impossible.
- Haha, answer the question.
- Look at Irene.
She said he isn't Korean.
- Is he Korean?
- She said he isn't Korean.
- Why would you be confused?
He is trying to confuse you.
I just realized it now.
I am not confused.
What's this person's job?
His job?
He studies.
He studies?
- That's right.
- He studies.
- What's this person's job?
- I like how speedy this round is.
- A civil worker.
- A civil worker?
- It's true too.
- That's right.
- It's true.
- He is a civil worker.
He must be someone from the past.
What's this person's main job?
- That's a good job.
- The main job.
- What does he do?
The main job.
He does many things.
He has a variety of jobs.
- Right?
- The main job.
He runs a business.
For goodness' sake.
- But...
- It's true.
- That's what I know of him.
- For goodness' sake.
- "That's what I know of him."
- That's what I know of him.
- Same here.
In that case...
(It's So Min's turn
to ask a question.)
I will ask a basic question.
Is this person alive?
(So Min, Elon Musk)
- No. Is he alive?
- He is alive.
Why did you say no?
(He tried to give her
false information.)
(Why did you say no?)
- He is alive.
- What is your problem?
- Is he alive?
- He is alive.
- I am glad to hear that.
- Haha is too much.
He is alive.
- You play dirty.
- He is alive.
Is this character a person?
Just now...
- A character?
(Haha suddenly used the word,
"Character.")
Yes, he is.
- A person?
- Yes.
- That's right.
- A person?
- Yes, he is.
- He is a person.
- Okay.
- That's right.
- Irene.
(Does Haha have a hunch?)
Do you know this person?
- Of course.
- I am really...
- All of us know him.
- Is this person here?
- What?
- You already asked...
- Here?
- You already asked a question.
(Irene's question
makes everyone flustered.)
(Is Kim Jong Kook here?)
Is this person here?
- What?
- Well...
Hey. Come on.
Why aren't you telling her?
- Seriously.
- Tell her.
Why aren't you telling her?
- Why aren't you telling her?
- I think I know the answer.
- Here.
Is this person here?
- I think I know the answer.
- He isn't here.
He isn't here.
- I think I know the answer.
- He isn't here.
- That's right.
- Here?
He isn't here.
(They avoid the crisis by saying
that he isn't at the table.)
He might be outside of the table.
- I think I know the answer.
- Irene.
(Is it me?)
(Yes!)
Irene.
- You are close.
That was a sharp question.
I figured it out
without looking at the answer.
- You are close.
- Didn't you look at the answer?
- I didn't look.
- Irene, they are flustered.
- I got it right. Yes.
- Did you get it right?
- Job.
- You made them flustered.
Tell me about this person's job.
- You asked them if he is here.
- Tell me about this person's job.
- Job?
He runs a business.
What business?
Seriously.
- He runs a business.
- He is an entrepreneur.
- An entrepreneur?
- That's it.
- An entrepreneur.
- A foreigner.
He is an entrepreneur.
- Irene, you need to get it right.
- Okay.
Is this person Korean?
Does he have a Korean ID card?
- No, he doesn't.
He must be something like Pengsoo.
(Haha figured out
that it's a character.)
A man.
- Irene.
- I will ask a question.
The last question.
Which color...
(Irene, Kim Jong Kook)
is this person wearing?
- What?
- This person...
- Hey.
(Irene seems to know
that this person is here.)
(This person...)
Answer the question.
(Team Tall is close to the answer.)
- Answer the question.
He is wearing black.
No. His favorite color is brown.
- He is wearing black.
- I didn't ask about that.
- Which color is he wearing now?
- They don't know that.
- He is wearing black.
- Black, I think.
- Black.
- Yes.
- It's black.
It's black.
Black.
He is wearing black.
(Black?)
(Irene checks the colors.)
He is wearing black.
Let me answer.
Kim Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook is correct.)
I knew it!
(They failed to hide the answer.)
- I thought it was you at first.
- Irene.
Okay.
Irene, how did you?
- What?
- How did you know?
I asked them if he is here.
- She looked at my pants.
- I asked them if he is here.
I realized it when I saw his pants.
- You are sharp.
- Can I ask a question first?
- Yes.
Make things certain.
Did this person make money by...
- She knows.
Did this person develop
an electric car?
(So Min, Elon Musk)
Hold on. Let's hear his answer.
(He is in trouble.)
(Not even a cheater
can dodge this bullet.)
- Did he develop an electric car?
- Are you talking about Tesla?
(That's exactly
what she is talking about.)
Let me answer.
- Elon Musk.
- Okay.
(Elon Musk is correct.)
- I got it right.
- You are second place.
I could have done better.
They said this person isn't Korean.
In Round Three, Jong Kook,
Se Chan, and Hae Na will go.
Okay.
- I'm honored to go against Se Chan.
- Okay.
I'm honored.
- I can win.
- This is the Yang Se Chan Game.
I'm honored.
Show us what you can do.
It will be fun.
We have to win this time.
But I just can't explain...
- the opponents' words.
- This is going to be okay.
(Jong Kook's word:
General MacArthur)
This is hard.
- Do you know those people?
- It won't be half bad.
- What?
- Do you know them?
Do you know those people?
- What?
- Do you know them?
I'm not sure about one person.
The one on Hae Na's head?
Yes. The one on Hae Na's head.
- Are you confused?
- That's good.
- All right.
- I haven't done this for a while.
I did some research on this game.
- You did? Like what?
- I'll ask sharp questions.
- Do you have a plan?
- Yes.
- Hae Na.
- All right.
Hae Na goes first.
What is this person good at?
- My gosh.
- What is the person good at?
(The first question
hits the bull's eye.)
- That's sharp.
- She's good.
Hae Na is clever.
(You answer first.)
- My gosh.
- You answer first.
He doesn't know.
You answer first.
He doesn't seem to know this person.
- Go ahead.
- He doesn't know.
Is he good at cooking?
(Is he good at cooking?)
Well...
He invented something.
That's a big clue.
My gosh.
Why would you say that?
- Why?
- Did you want to look smart?
- I can't believe this.
- That's it.
- I mean...
- That was sharp.
- Hey.
- That's what it is.
Did you want to look smart?
- I know, right?
Hey, how could you...
- You shouldn't say that.
- You can't give...
such a direct hint.
I just don't know much.
That's all I know.
Right.
I think he drinks a lot.
- Hey.
- What?
I think he drinks a lot.
- Excuse me.
- What?
- Are you making guesses?
- No. It's true.
- Are you serious?
- Yes. He drinks a lot.
(He remembered a scene
from the movie, "Forbidden Dream.")
He invented something,
and he drinks a lot?
- Does he?
Tell me about his age.
How old is he?
- That's sharp.
- His age?
He is older than you, Se Chan.
He's older than me.
I'd say he's a grandpa.
- That's a big clue.
- He's old.
A grandpa?
You guys are
being generous. Hang on.
All right. Is the person...
older than me or younger than me?
- What?
- His age.
Older than you.
- He is?
- Yes.
Why are you hesitating?
(Why are you hesitating?)
- He hesitated.
- Wait.
I was thinking of his photo.
You answered
her question right away.
It's not like that. I was thinking
of the photo I saw.
- When I saw it...
- Does he look younger than me?
I think he's about his age.
I guess you two are
of a similar age.
- I see. That's possible.
- A similar age.
I think so.
My turn?
- Well...
- Hae Na, you ask good questions.
- Really?
- She asks sharp questions.
You're sharp. You're almost there.
What did he invent?
(Hae Na, Jang Yeong Sil)
- This is new.
- This is it.
- My gosh.
- She's really good.
(It's a point-blank question
with no way out.)
- Go ahead.
- I'll just say what I know.
It might be a big hint.
Okay. It will make you look cool.
It's a battle with yourself.
He made a map.
(He made a map.)
(Did he make a map?)
(He gave a wrong hint
without knowing.)
- He made a map?
- Is that a big hint?
Is that right?
- I don't think it's correct.
- Hey, get out.
(Embarrassed)
- It's hilarious.
- It's done.
- Now...
- That's all I know.
- That's it.
- Jong Kook, that's what I know.
- It's done.
- It can't be helped.
- All right.
It's done.
- Isn't that correct?
- No.
- Okay.
- That's what he thinks.
- That's good though. Well done.
- All right.
- It's my turn.
- Okay.
- Ask a sharp question.
- Ask the question you prepared.
- I did my research.
- This is Yang Se Chan Game.
Everyone is flustered
by this question.
What is his job?
(Se Chan, Oh Il Nam)
(It turns out the research
wasn't so profound.)
We don't know.
- What?
- We don't know his job.
Why not?
Because we don't.
No. I think I know.
He's unemployed.
- Right.
- He is jobless?
- He's jobless.
- Is he?
- Yes, he is.
- This is getting tricky.
There are a lot of jobless people.
- A grandpa?
- Yes.
A jobless grandpa?
But I think he is a global star.
What?
A global star?
- She told you everything.
- Se Chan, this is the easiest one.
- This is the easiest one.
- You can answer it now.
- You're almost there.
- You should know it by now.
Think carefully.
It's not a lie.
Right?
I get it. Okay.
- My gosh.
- I told you the truth.
- I get it now.
- Se Chan knows it.
Se Chan knows the answer.
- Se Chan, give your answer.
- I get it.
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
(Let me answer.)
McDonald's Grandpa.
(Incorrect)
(He's completely wrong.)
- Hey.
- No?
- McDonald's doesn't have a grandpa.
- There's no McDonald's Grandpa.
McDonald's doesn't have a grandpa.
There's no grandpa.
- Oh, right. It's KFC.
- It has a clown.
Isn't that the grandpa?
(Next week!)
(Se Chan keeps
giving away big hints.)
(Do you like her?)
(And Round 4 continues.)
(He makes 10,000 dollars a month
wearing jeogori?)
It's obvious.
(Is he more handsome than me?)
(The worst question ever
for Yang Se Chan Game)
- He's more handsome.
- It's over.
(They have no one to trust.)
(The only thing they can
turn to is the shoe lift.)
- Irene. We have no choice.
- I know.
(They fight for 1cm...)
(having hand-to-hand combat.)
(They have
an intense cat-and-mouth game.)
(Yesterday's enemy...)
(is today's friend.)
(Yesterday's friend...)
(is today's enemy.)
(Get rid of everything
that stunts your growth.)
(They show real teamwork or just fake it.)
(Who will be at the top?)
(And...)
(To celebrate 2022,
the Year of the Black Tiger,)
(five tigers are coming.)
(The Myth of Dangun
in the Year of the Black Tiger)