- Hello.
- Come here, Ji Hyo.
Look at Ji Hyo's fashion today.
What's with Ji Hyo?
It looks like an awards ceremony.
Oh, right. Haha...
Ji Hyo looks chic today, right?
You look pretty. It's so cool.
When something like this happens,
it means she got...
- a new stylist or something.
- She looks amazing.
- She did.
- I knew it.
Right. She got a new stylist.
- Really?
- She did.
- She wants to show something.
- Right.
- Why did you get a new stylist?
- He's so sharp.
Her stylist would want
to make her presence felt.
- Exactly. It's a performance.
- "This is what I can do."
So Min is all dressed up today.
- NewJeans.
- Right.
- Is someone coming today?
- We need to point that out.
You look pretty.
It's strange. She's too dressed up.
Right. What's with her?
Why is she dressed up?
- She must have a reason.
- No.
We have to point this out.
This is connected to the previous story.
- Let me tell you what it is.
- What is it?
What's going on?
- This is about So Min's spy.
- So Min's spy?
(So Min's spy?)
- Is she...
- Is it caught?
- Did you catch the spy?
- That's right.
- Not yet.
- It's not caught yet.
She also knew about
Seok Jin Versus Seok Jin.
She did.
(A question about So Min's spy
has been continuously raised.)
(It was first suggested 6 months ago
at the Credit Card Payment Race.)
- Who is it?
- "We'll dress as slaves tomorrow."
(All the information about venues,
concepts, and PPL has been leaked.)
(She even knew about Jin of BTS,
which was top secret.)
(Who's So Min's spy
who leaked all the information?)
She didn't seem surprised
when the door was open.
This is what's important.
Since So Min knows a lot
about the shoot,
she can prepare an outfit
that's perfect...
for the concept of the day.
- She even knows about the penalty.
- That's right.
This is getting too big.
- We must cut this vicious link.
- We have to.
(It's time to catch the spy.)
Everyone. That's why...
I've been trying
to detect the spy...
who's been helping So Min.
It's not one of our producers.
- Because...
- Really?
We've been talking about it
for quite a long time.
So they wouldn't have been able
to keep giving her the information.
Then is it one of our writers?
- I don't think it is...
- No.
- one of our writers.
- It can't be one of our cameramen.
Now...
- That's Chan Hee!
- Is it Chan Hee?
- It might be Chan Hee.
- Kang Chan Hee.
- It's not Kang Chan Hee.
- Gang Gam Chan Hee.
- The spy is you, Gang Gam Chan Hee.
- Gang Gam Chan Hee?
Let me tell you
why it's not Chan Hee.
Chan Hee got surgery
for his cervical disk,
so he couldn't come to work
for three months.
- But she still knew stuff.
- So Min kept getting information.
So Chan Hee is excluded
from the list of suspects.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- Then who is it?
- Who would it be?
- Soon, So Min's spy...
- Spy.
- will be caught.
- Good.
We will start the project soon.
(The spy-catching
project is coming soon.)
- That sounds so thrilling.
- Good.
- We will catch the spy.
- That's right.
This is so funny.
- Catch the spy.
- And the one who's...
most indifferent to this
looks like the spy now.
- The spy is Song Ji Hyo.
- It's you!
- It's not Ji Hyo.
- Bang!
- It can't be Ji Hyo.
- She has nothing to do with this.
So is So Min dressed up like this
because she knows about today?
- That's right.
- I guess someone's coming.
But today...
- We are having guests today.
- I see.
- What's with her?
- Gosh, Jeon So Min.
What's going on?
All right.
We will bring in the guests...
- who will join today's race.
- My goodness.
(So Min already knows
about today's guests.)
- I got goose bumps.
- She knew it.
I just know
that we have guests today.
What kind of guests are they,
So Min?
They're coming from there.
- This way.
- Hey, Sang Hun.
- Hello.
- Hey.
(Actor Jeong Sang Hun)
(And more guests show up after him.)
- That's Oh Tae Sik.
- This is amazing.
Tae Sik.
(Actor Kim Rae Won,
Actor Park Byung Eun)
(An actor with charismatic looks
and a charming voice)
(Park Byung Eun, the icon
of a fatal villain)
(Jeong Sang Hun shows his top-tier
performance in a comic role.)
(Kim Rae Won, the actor
who lives up to his name)
(And he's the protagonist
of the legendary film, "Sunflower.")
(Oh Tae Sik is back.)
- Hello.
- I'm a big fan.
- Oh Tae Sik is back.
- Did you really have to take...
- everything from me like that?
- Oh Tae Sik is back!
I love him.
- My gosh.
- Actually,
- Se Chan loves the movie.
- I do.
I'm a big fan of Oh Tae Sik.
- Oh Tae Sik.
- That's true.
Oh Tae Sik is back!
- I'm so excited.
- He's still...
- He's still Oh Tae Sik.
- To me, he's Oh Tae Sik.
Se Chan uses the name
when he books a restaurant.
- I always use the name.
- Right.
- That's true.
- I'm serious.
- You live as Oh Tae Sik.
- I do.
- You should show him, Se Chan.
- Oh Tae Sik.
"Who did that?"
"Byung Jin, you wait outside."
You just sound like a fool.
Isn't he just a fool?
No, this is what he did.
- Hey.
- "Byung Jin, you wait outside."
"I can't believe this."
"Byung Jin, you wait outside."
"Did you really have to..."
All right.
We have three guests today.
- Let's meet them one by one.
- This is so nice.
All right. Byung Eun, please say hi
to our viewers.
Hello. I'm Actor Park Byung Eun.
Nice to meet you.
"The Fishermen and the City."
He's from
Is he on
"The Fishermen and the City?"
That's his latest work.
- He's a close friend of Tae Hyun.
- Right.
And In Sung.
- He's also close to Sang Yeob.
- Right.
And we have Kang Rae Won here.
It's Kim Rae Won.
- My goodness.
- Jae Seok!
- I'm so sorry.
- What did you just do?
- Who is Kang Rae Won?
- There's a man named Kang Rae Won.
I guess he was thinking
about Kang Won Rae.
- I'm so sorry.
- I know...
- it's been a long time, but...
- Hey.
How could you call him Kang Rae Won?
- Rae Won, it's been a long time.
- Kang Rae Won?
- Hello, I'm Jegal Byung Eun.
- He was confused.
- Just stay quiet.
- I can't believe this.
Why would you say Jegal Byung Eun?
- Don't make things worse.
- Okay.
- All right. We have Kim Rae Won.
- Namkoong Rae Won.
- I apologize again.
- It's all right.
Hello, I'm Kim Rae Won.
Nice to meet you.
(Tae Sik has
an attractive low voice.)
It sounds like he's in a cave.
He's got an amazing voice.
- Well...
- He was on other variety shows.
I had the movie press conference
a few days ago.
- But I see more cameras here.
- Of course, you do.
We have many cameras
to intimidate our guests.
- Some of them are fake.
- We have fake cameras.
- There are fifty cameras.
- Some of the cameras are fake.
They are fake cameras.
Some of them are fake.
We don't want people
to look down on us.
- I'm very shy with strangers.
- That's understandable.
So I don't know what to do now.
- There's a drone flying around.
- Right.
- That's fake.
- It's a fake drone.
And half of the production crew
is fake.
It's their hobby.
- Okay.
- To intimidate you.
And we have Sang Hun here.
- Hello.
- Sang Hun!
(The next guest is Jeong Sang Hun,
lamb skewers and beer.)
- How are you?
- Shut it.
(Shut it.)
- Stop talking.
- "Stop talking."
"Stop talking."
- Otherwise, you'll lose your teeth.
- My teeth.
You'll lose all your teeth.
I'm back with
a new movie, "Decibel."
I'm Jeong Sang Hun.
Sang Hun.
The three of them
recently did a movie together.
- It's called "Decibel."
- "Decibel."
Our movie is about a bomb
that has been set in the city.
The bomb goes off if it reaches...
- a certain decibel.
- It goes off.
- It's about sound.
- That sounds interesting.
- It sounds fun.
- Right.
Rae Won, tell us more
about your new movie.
Byung Eun pretty much said
everything that needs to be said.
You can talk about something else.
- Hey, what's wrong with you?
- Don't cut in.
- Leave him alone.
- What's with you?
Why would you treat
a top star like that?
Rae Won.
I'm not the one who brought it up.
Byung Eun, what's wrong?
- What were you looking at?
- The color of his pants...
What about them?
They look good with his shoes.
Do you like them or what?
(Do you like them or what?)
- Why are you being like this?
- Why are you trying to fight?
- Move over.
- Why are you doing this?
- Am I not supposed to like them?
- What was that?
- Calm down.
- Why is he being like this?
- Byung Eun, calm down.
- He's older than you think.
- They are kind of similar.
- My gosh.
He looks so weak.
- He's a fighter today.
- I'm just feeling good.
Why? What makes you happy?
- That's because of this guy.
- Who?
- "This guy?"
- Is he your friend?
- Do you not know his name?
- Don't you know my name?
- Are you two friends?
- Of course, I do.
- What's his name?
He asked me
about his name in a whisper.
That's not true.
She's joking.
You know she likes to play jokes.
- So what's my name?
- What's his name?
Can I call you Sung Ho?
- Sung Ho?
- Sung Ho.
- What's his last name?
"Can I call you Sung Ho?"
- I'm sorry.
- My gosh.
- What's Sung Ho's last name?
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about this.
- What's his last name?
- His last name.
- Kim.
- That's enough.
It's not easy
to pretend not to know.
I'm just trying to be funny.
This is hard.
- So what's my last name?
- What is it?
What is my last name?
My last name!
- Kim...
- Kim?
- Kim.
Darn it!
(He finishes the SNL-style skit.)
The skit was funny. That was fun.
- I like the skit.
- "Kim?"
- He's Kim Sung Ho.
- Kim Sung Ho.
- I'm Kim Sung Ho.
I'm Kim Sung Ho starting today.
- I'm Lee Sung Ho.
- No, you're not Lee Sung Ho.
- What is it then?
Just let it slide.
- Let's move on.
- "Let's move on."
"Let's move on."
- All right.
- You know he's old.
- Let's move on.
- Just say you don't know it.
- All three of them are hurt.
- Right.
What are we doing today?
Before we start today's race,
you should choose your teams first.
- Really?
- There will be three teams.
- Okay.
The captains are Jae Seok, Seok Jin,
and So Min.
What? Jeon So Min?
(Yu Jae Seok, Jee Seok Jin,
and Jeon So Min are captains.)
- Me? Am I a captain? Why?
- Why?
Is So Min a captain?
Are we starting
the spy project today?
- Why is that?
- You were on "The Age of Shadows."
(Is the spy project
beginning today?)
- Why is that?
- You were on "The Age of Shadows."
- No, it was "Assassination."
- It was "Assassination."
Come on, Seok Jin. What's with you?
Will you stop that?
Seok Jin, please.
- It's "Assassination."
- It can be confusing.
Just because
it's a two-syllable word?
- It can be confusing.
- Like "Ditto?"
The secrets behind the captains
will be revealed later.
The three captains will stand here.
And the rest of the members...
- will choose a captain they want.
- Okay. Come here.
If you join my team,
you can be the captain.
- Really?
- I'll do the same thing.
- You can be the captain.
- What about you, Jae Seok?
I'll be the captain.
Is that what you're doing?
- Okay.
- Rae Won.
- It's done.
- Is it done?
- So we have three teams now.
- Yes.
Today's race is...
Pass the Bomb: You're the Bomb.
Currently, there are
two secret bomb designers.
(Two of the members are
the secret bomb designers.)
- Two of us?
- There are two.
The captains are
not the bomb designers.
- Captains are not the designers.
- That's right.
Not the captains?
- No. Not the captains.
- We're not the designers.
The captains who are out
of the list of suspects...
- were chosen by the bomb designers.
- What?
The bomb designers chose
these three captains.
- Really?
- I see.
- They were chosen?
- Why?
So there are two designers.
The two designers are supposed
to be on different teams.
If they succeed, all their
team members except for them will...
- get the water bomb penalty.
- All of them?
And the designers and the team
without a designer...
will win the prize.
If the race ends with
the designers on the same team,
the designers and their captain
will get the penalty together.
So the designers
should be separated.
Right. They have to be
on different teams to win.
So are we going
to change our team members?
- You can change your team members.
- Okay.
But only the winning team gets...
a chance to change team members
and hints after each mission.
Are we playing this game
because of our movie, "Decibel?"
- Yes. It's about bombs.
- My gosh.
I like the decibel of his voice.
- It sounds so nice.
- It sounds perfect.
- The bomb will never go off.
- Right.
- It sounds like a cave.
All right. We will start the race
after you get changed.
- Okay.
- I like the sunshine.
It's so warm.
You're good at golf.
- Not really.
- Right.
- He's really good.
- In the waiting room...
- I heard Rae Won was good at golf.
- He's amazing.
- That's true.
- He's brilliant.
I heard Rae Won was very athletic.
And I heard Byung Eun was funny.
(The first mission for athletic
Rae Won and funny Byung Eun)
Let's go.
Here's the first mission.
It's called
Dating Expert or Dating Bomb.
There will be
questionnaires about dating,
and you should guess the answers
ranked 1st, 3rd, and 5th.
The 1st, 3rd, and 5th.
This is what I'm good at.
This is my thing.
(Laughing)
I'm...
- Why are you laughing at me?
- No, it's not like that.
The team who gives
the most correct answers...
will get hints and a chance
to change the team members.
- Okay.
- We need to figure out...
whether our team has
a bomb designer or not.
- So we have to win.
- We have to win no matter what.
Some of us will give wrong answers
on purpose.
Those who talk nonsense
are likely to be the designers.
So Min is good
when it comes to dating.
- That's her thing.
- Right.
Do you have many dating experiences?
I do.
He just likes fishing.
- Fishing?
He dated fish.
What about you, Rae Won?
I like fishing too.
- You just like fishing.
- Rock sea bream.
What about you, Sang Hun?
- He's a master.
- I'm married.
As far as I know, you didn't date
many women before you got married.
You didn't date many women.
- Me?
- Yes.
- That's not true.
- No?
I bet he was popular.
Sang Hun is...
- My gosh.
- That's not true?
- Sang Hun was very popular.
- I bet he was.
- He must've been popular.
- I know that.
Sang Hun, were you popular?
- Jae Seok.
- Do I have to say it?
I was really popular.
He dated a girl I knew.
Really?
Are you crazy?
Why would you say that here?
I'm serious.
Why did you bring that up?
- Do you want me to talk about you?
- I'm just...
- I can talk about you.
- Go ahead and say it.
- Do you want me to talk about you?
- I'm just...
- I can talk about you.
- Go ahead and say it.
- Just say it.
- I can do that.
Here's the first question.
Please bring in the board.
"The man you'd never
introduce to your sister."
- Isn't this obvious?
- It's obvious.
- A man who's busy and flirty.
- A womanizer.
A guy who rarely answers his phone.
- Someone who's hard to reach.
- Exactly.
A guy with many female friends.
Let's talk about it one by one.
Byung Eun, who wouldn't you
introduce to your sister?
A man
who overcommits to his hobbies...
- That's you.
- Yes.
- Fishing?
- I was talking about myself.
- He was talking about himself.
- Fishing and golf.
- But he's right about that.
- Yes.
- It's important.
- A man who's too into his hobby.
- If you're obsessed with it...
- But there's a good thing about it.
Although he's into his hobby,
he'd be interested in nothing else.
- Since it's been brought up...
- I agree with him.
- I agree with Byung Eun.
- Yes.
I mean, you're too passionate
about working out.
- True. But that's my only hobby.
- But it's healthy, and he's frugal.
- I don't drink or spend much money.
- Wherever you go,
you need time to work out
even when you're with others.
- He only needs 2 or 3 hours.
- You can give him only 2 hours.
- Exactly.
- He needs five hours...
including his commute.
- No, three hours is enough.
- Don't deny it!
Three hours is enough.
Oh, great. This is it.
- They're finally going to break up.
- That's good.
They're breaking up.
Three hours is enough.
(Will the friends of the century
break up just like this?)
- Jae Seok, you have a point.
- Right. I see now.
- Yes, you're right.
- No.
- Jong Kook, you're right.
- You have a point too.
I see that you have a point as well.
- Sometimes I play soccer too.
- That's annoying.
- Right.
- Then I spend 5 or 6 hours.
- We need to break them up.
- He can go with his girlfriend.
Let's break them up.
What about you, Rae Won?
(What is Rae Won's opinion?)
- A man who lies often.
- Right.
- I agree.
- Small lies.
- Small lies are bad.
- I agree.
Rae Won,
do you often tell small lies?
- I don't think...
- That was unexpected.
- I tell lies.
- You think you don't, but you do.
- He got caught.
- Everyone lies once in a while.
Get the bottom of it.
I think I never tell lies, but...
What was the last lie you told?
- I never lie.
- At the opening earlier...
"I never lie."
- Earlier...
- You can pull this off, Jae Seok.
He's trying to squeeze it out.
- Jae Seok, you've got this!
- Go, Jae Seok!
- Since Rae Won is here,
- I'll be hard on him.
- Yes, be hard on him.
I'll be hard on him.
- I don't get to see him often.
- True.
- We shouldn't go easy on him.
- That's right.
- Squeeze it all out.
- You're right.
- We should be hard on him.
- Absolutely.
- It's our job.
- That's right.
He's squeezing it out.
Did you lie or not
at the opening earlier?
- I might have.
- See?
He's honest.
- He's honest.
- Could he be the designer?
A lot of children are watching this.
Is Santa Claus real or not?
(What will Rae Won,
who can't lie, say?)
He's real.
(Santa Claus is real.)
- You're lying.
- Rae Won.
You're a liar.
- But he's real.
- I can't believe him.
- He tells so many small lies.
- He's real.
- I see that he tells small lies.
- He just wants to receive a gift.
He does tell small lies.
I would never
set my little sister up with him.
This is hilarious.
What about you, Sang Hun?
Among us?
The bad guy type.
- Oh, I see.
- But they're attractive.
- Women are attracted to bad guys.
- I think...
But you wouldn't want to set him up
with your younger sister.
- I hate it when a man...
- A bad guy.
calls himself a bad guy...
- to justify his unkindness.
- Exactly.
A bad guy comes across as blunt...
because he's not good at
expressing things.
- Aren't you that kind of person?
- What do you mean?
- You feel too shy to show emotions.
- Yes, I do.
I feel too shy
to express my affection.
- You're quite blunt.
- Yes, I am.
- You want to be a bad guy, right?
- Exactly.
But someone like Jae Seok
can't be a bad guy.
- That's right.
- Right.
- They have to be kind to date.
- A bad guy...
- A bad guy should be handsome.
- Or else, no one would date them.
- That's right.
- Hey, Sang Hun.
- "A bad guy should be handsome?"
- That's true.
- Why are you getting worked up?
- Right.
- I mean, you crossed the line.
- You can never be a bad guy.
- You're good-looking.
- No one here except for Rae Won...
- can be a bad guy.
- To be honest,
- I'm the bad guy type.
- Rae Won can.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- You're simply a bad person.
- A bad person.
- I'm quite blunt.
- Byung Eun?
- How is your dating style?
- I'm the type that calls her often.
- He must be nice to his girlfriend.
- Oh, he's a sweet guy.
- He'd be a good boyfriend.
- Byung Eun?
- I'd give her the fish I caught.
The fish he caught?
I'm not lying.
- That's nice.
- He gives away the fish he caught.
- That's great.
- He's so pure-hearted.
It's because those who like fishing
feel happy when they give...
- others the fish they've caught...
- They like giving away fish.
- and seeing them enjoy the fish.
- Right.
- Oh, that makes you happy.
- Yes, I really feel happy.
Byung Eun made it sound
like a heartwarming story.
- Why?
- Was that a lie?
Going fishing so often itself
makes him a bad guy.
- I know this because I fish too.
- I see.
Women don't like it, right?
My ex-girlfriend said this
a long time ago.
"Must I be jealous of a fish?"
Oh, right.
- I heard something like that too.
- That's how they feel.
- "Must I be jealous of a dumbbell?"
- That's exactly my point.
"Must I be jealous of a dumbbell?"
- "Must I be jealous of an octopus?"
- Because they like it too much?
- Yes, that's what happens.
- I understand.
Then what about you, Ji Hyo?
- I hate the opposite.
- Okay.
A man
who's obsessed with being kind.
- A man who's kind to everyone.
- Excessive kindness?
- A man who's kind to everyone?
- A man who's... Yes.
A man who's so kind to everyone
that people get the wrong idea.
- He'd give others the wrong idea.
- I see.
Personally, I would never
set my sister up with...
- What type of man?
- a handsome man.
- Why?
- They are more likely to cheat.
- Jong Kook.
- Come on. That's not true.
- It's true.
Jong Kook, ugly guys cheat
despite their ugly faces.
Hey, that's mean.
- They're the worst.
- That's out of line.
You've crossed the line.
- Why are you getting upset?
- Why would you say such a thing?
That's why I want to set Se Chan up
with my nieces.
His face is just good enough.
(He has a just good enough face
according to Jong Kook.)
- It's perfect.
- So it's because he's ugly.
- Check the 2nd and 4th places now.
- The 2nd and 4th places?
What... I'm sure what we've said
is on the list.
- Of course.
- I'm sure of it.
Then let's check the second place.
Here we go.
(A man who makes
physical contact naturally)
"A man
who makes physical contact..."
- Right. That wasn't brought up.
- I agree.
- Next up is the fourth place.
- Let's find out.
- The fourth place.
- Oh, we got that one right.
- It's on the list.
- Aren't you surprised?
- But working out is not a problem.
- Right.
Then we have to guess
the 1st, 3rd, and 5th places.
I wouldn't like a man
who likes luxury goods.
- A man who likes fashion.
- Right.
A man who likes to dress up.
- Right. It must be on the list.
- I think it's on the list.
A man who loves himself too much.
- Say, "Let me answer."
- Let me answer!
- And you'll get to answer.
- Oh, gosh.
- Let me answer!
- Let me answer.
- A man who loves himself too much.
- Isn't that our team's answer?
- That's our answer.
- No, it's not. I said it first.
- That's our team's answer.
- So Min came up with that answer.
- He got the chance to answer first.
- How could you?
- Exactly.
- She talked about luxury goods.
- My answer is a man with self-love.
- It's different. Tell them.
- It's not the same.
It's different. Rae Won, tell them.
You can say your answer
after he says his. All right?
(He settled the situation
with his low-pitched voice.)
- He turns out to be a good liar.
- Good job.
- He speaks so calmly.
- Also...
- He's calm and has a good voice.
- He's scary as he speaks so calmly.
- He has such a great voice.
- Okay.
- All right.
- A man with self-love, right?
Yes, a man with self-love.
A man with too much self-love.
- It's not on the list.
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
A man who's too interested in
improving his appearance.
- Isn't that the same as self-love?
- That's good.
A man who likes to dress up
is ranked third.
- I told you so.
- I knew it.
Rae Won, we can guess
the one ranked first.
- Rae Won, try to guess the answer.
- I see the words "luxury goods."
- I got it right.
- It should be you.
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
- A man who likes to drink.
- A man who drinks often.
A man who drinks often?
- No, a man who likes to drink.
- Let me answer!
- A man who likes to drink.
- Let me drink!
He drinks often
because he likes to drink.
A man who likes to drink...
- Let me answer.
- Give me a chance for a change.
- Right.
- A violent jerk.
- What?
- That's not even worth mentioning.
- That's too obvious.
- A man who gets aggressive...
- when drunk.
- A jerk with nasty drinking habits.
- Let me answer!
- I bet it's on the list.
- You can't say several answers.
- A man with nasty drinking habits.
- A man with bad drinking habits.
- It must be on the list.
It's ranked first.
- That was amazing.
- It's the same as our answer.
- Really?
- No way.
- But...
- It's the same as our answer.
- He said several answers.
- That's what we meant.
- They said several answers.
- He said more than one answer.
- How many answers did he say?
- I did a good job, right?
- He said more than 1 answer.
- He said 5 answers.
A man who gets aggressive
when drunk.
Can we guess
the one ranked fifth now?
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
- A man who never answers his phone.
- Oh, right.
- It must be on the list.
- A man who's hard to get a hold of.
- Maybe it didn't make the list.
- It's one of the other answers.
- Let me answer.
- A man who's close to his mother?
A mama's boy.
- Yes. I bet it's the one.
- Right.
- It didn't make the list.
- Let me answer.
- I'll give you a hint.
- It was mentioned earlier.
- I see.
- Let me answer.
- When? Did we mention it?
- Sang Hun, go ahead.
- Something like physical contact.
- A friend of mine.
- Maybe.
- What?
- It didn't make the list.
- Oh. That's a shame.
- That's funny. "A friend of mine."
Let me answer!
- Let me answer.
- She said we had mentioned it.
A jerk who stays in touch
with his ex-girlfriend.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
Stop it.
- Jong Kook mentioned it.
- Jong Kook did?
- What did I say?
- Jong Kook, it was your idea.
- Try to remember.
- What did I say?
- Try to remember what you said.
- Is it regarding working out?
- But it's already on the list.
- What did I say?
Try to remember what you said.
(Thinking hard)
- Let me answer.
- What is it?
- You talked about a handsome man.
- Oh, right.
- A handsome man.
Really?
- I remembered what he said.
- Hey.
- A handsome man.
- Is it really on the list?
I would never set my sister up
with a handsome man.
- A handsome man was the answer?
- Right. You shouldn't.
- Such men are more likely to cheat.
- They're more likely to cheat.
- I agree because none of the men...
- A perfect man. Right.
they wanted to set me up with...
- was handsome.
- Right.
- One of the other answers is...
- Yes.
a man who doesn't get nervous
even when he sees a pretty woman.
- Why?
- I don't understand.
It means that he pretends
he's not interested in her.
- Because he's sly?
- Maybe he's not interested in her.
Women hate it
when a man shows his interest too.
- But...
- They hate it if we're interested.
- We shouldn't hide our feelings.
- Then what should we do?
- Is there a halfway point?
- What should we do?
You shouldn't compliment
the beautiful woman...
- to the point...
- Yes.
that it offends your girlfriend.
- Right.
- Of course.
- But you can share your opinion.
- You must be tactful.
- Should we?
- It'd be weird if you hide it.
Oh, my. Can you be that confident?
- That's bold.
- What I'm saying is...
that you shouldn't react
whenever you see a pretty girl.
"My gosh. How gorgeous."
- "Beautiful."
- "Honey."
- "Look at her. She's gorgeous."
- See?
- "She's incredibly beautiful."
- You shouldn't react like that.
- That's not good.
But when your girlfriend asks you
for your opinion...
- What would you say?
- "Well, I think..."
"that she's stylish.
She has a great fashion sense."
- "How about I dress like that?"
- I don't think that's a good idea.
- What?
- "How about I dress like that?"
- "I don't think it suits you."
- That's not a good idea.
"Why? You said she looked pretty."
"Yes, but it suits her, not you."
"Are you saying I'm ugly?"
- "No. You have your own style."
- "Are you saying I'm ugly?"
- He's in trouble.
- "You said that it was pretty."
- He messed up.
- Exactly.
- He fell into a hole.
- I shouldn't react that way.
"Since you like her style,
I want to try it."
- "I love you just as you are."
- Just tell her that she's prettier.
"Why would you copy her style?"
- "You never said I was pretty."
- Tell her that she's pretty.
- Say, "You're prettier than her."
- But...
- She's upset.
- Just tell her...
- "I can't..."
- He can't get it sorted out.
- "I can't say you're prettier..."
- He can't deal with the situation.
"I can't say
you're prettier than her."
Jae Seok isn't good at improvising
in a situation like that.
I believe that you should be honest.
But don't go overboard.
- Let's move on to the next survey.
- Okay.
What's this?
"When you want some alone time..."
- What to say to go home on a date?
- I see.
- Can we start right away?
- Let me answer.
- Let's begin right away.
- We're ready.
- If we talk about this topic...
- We'll begin right away.
- I'd say that I'm not feeling well.
- Faking it?
- "I'm not feeling well."
- Pretending to be sick.
- Lying that you're feeling unwell.
- "I'm not feeling well."
- In a worse case,
- "I'm sick."
- you can say it two days before.
- To make it sound convincing.
- Two days before the date, say,
- To make her believe you.
- "I think I'm having a cold."
- Right.
- What's funny is...
- "I'm sick."
- that you start feeling unwell.
- "I'm not feeling well."
- You actually start feeling unwell.
- "I'm not feeling well. I'm sick."
- "I'm sick?"
- It's ranked second.
- Oh, good.
(I'm not feeling well.
I think I need to rest.)
- Oh, the 2nd place?
- The 2nd place? What a shame.
(They get a point when they guess
the 1st, 3rd, or 5th place.)
- Let him answer.
- Let me answer.
"Something came up at home.
My parents need me home."
A memorial service.
- "My parents need me home?"
- I agree with Jae Seok.
"Something came up at home."
- It's ranked second.
- But... Okay.
- It's ranked third.
- My gosh.
- Which one?
- A memorial service?
- Is it on the list?
- A memorial service.
"Something came up at home."
"Something came up at home?"
I think he has said that
as an excuse before.
- Have you ever told that lie?
- He can't tell a lie.
- I have never done that before.
- I see.
I... No.
- You can even put on an act.
- We didn't get a point.
Your mother asks you to pick up
something on your way home.
You say, "Right now?"
- He's acting.
- You start putting on an act.
- "Yes. I see."
- "What did you say?"
"What?"
- I can tell he's acting.
- "What's wrong?
- You're suspicious.
- You got caught.
Your acting went on for too long.
- "Right now?"
- She suddenly says, "Hello?"
"Yes. Got it. Okay."
(The phone call ended.)
- "What's the matter?"
- "What is it?"
He can't make eye contact
with her...
- because he's not a good liar.
- "I should go now."
- "Why? Is something going on?"
- "Where are you going?"
- He's chuckling.
- Why are you chuckling?
- He can't tell a lie.
- He failed.
He got caught.
- By the way,
- "Where should you go?"
- "Where are you going?"
- why is it always So Min...
who plays my girlfriend?
- She was so natural and serious.
- Prosecutor Jeon.
- You can't get out of it.
- You got flustered, right?
- I mean...
- As if you were trapped in a maze.
- No.
I'd be worried first.
"Is everything okay?"
- I know, but...
- "Is everything okay?"
- She says she'd be worried first.
- Her eyes...
She doesn't look like she's worried.
It's as if she were saying,
"Look at you trying to fool me."
She's like an investigator.
She looks like an investigator.
Prosecutor Jeon.
Let me answer.
I've said this before.
"You don't look well.
Why don't you go home?"
(Suggesting she should go home)
Oh, right. Yes.
"You don't look well."
Is it on the list?
"You should go home now."
- It's ranked fourth.
- Oh, really?
- It really is on the list.
- How come we got...
- the 2nd and 4th right?
- I'm surprised.
It's on the list.
- But we didn't get a point.
- "You look tired. Why don't you..."
- "go home now?"
- What a way to fool your lover.
- That's unbelievable.
- "You look tired."
- "You don't look well."
- My goodness.
"You have dark circles
under your eyes."
When she's feeling so energetic.
She couldn't feel better.
She even got a massage
before meeting him.
- Let me answer. "Let's go..."
- Seok Jin...
- Why?
- He got it right.
- He's very active right now.
- I don't even remember...
- the previous topic.
- He's very active.
It's so funny...
I can't even remember
the previous topic.
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
Say you'll take her for a drive
and go to her house naturally.
Driving her home?
While driving...
- Drop her off at her house.
- "We're in front of your house."
- "Go on in."
- He's so good at acting.
"How about we have canned coffee?"
- Just like salmons.
- Yes.
Just like salmons.
- Naturally... Yes.
- Opening the car door for her.
If I were his girlfriend,
I would be so disappointed.
He said he'd take me for a drive
and drove me home.
- But...
- "Why are we heading to my house?"
(Correct)
- Is it on the list?
- Really?
- It's ranked fifth.
For real?
- It's on the list.
- Really?
Is it really on the list?
- Do some people really do that?
- For real?
I didn't expect that.
"I didn't realize we were walking
to your house. Go home safely."
Seok Jin is amazing.
- That was unexpected.
- Great job.
- Seok Jin...
- That's unbelievable.
Seok Jin is like an expert
when it comes to this topic.
- He got three answers right.
- Seok Sam is a pro.
- Exactly.
- I have experience.
He's on a roll.
- I saw the one where Seok Jin...
- I'm surprised.
- Which episode?
- The one where he was...
excited because his family members
were on an overseas trip.
(In Episode 621)
(When the news about
his wife's trip was shared,)
(the devoted husband's true face
was revealed.)
- Oh, you saw it?
- Yes.
(Rae Won saw the legendary scene.)
- I was reminded of that scene.
- Because of that...
His wife saw that
and decided not to go on a trip.
- She canceled the trip.
- Because she was so upset.
- Because she was upset.
- And Seok Jin was disappointed.
He was disappointed.
I wonder what's ranked first?
We only have the first place left.
Could it be something like this?
"Something urgent came up."
Right.
Let me answer.
"Something urgent came up."
- "My supervisor called me over."
- That's the one.
- "Something came up."
- Right. I knew it.
(The answer is
"Something urgent came up.")
"Something urgent came up."
- "Something came up at home?"
- It's different.
It was "My parents are coming
to my house."
- We got that one right.
- Exactly.
- You did a good job.
- Indeed.
- It's simple.
- Yes.
Something just came up.
I'll read another example for you.
"I need to go and meet someone
to sell something."
- Really?
- That must be disappointing.
- Times have changed.
- Indeed.
- It's a good idea.
- I think it's a great idea.
I tagged along with my ex-boyfriend
when he went to meet a buyer.
(I tagged along
with my ex-boyfriend.)
- He must've felt smothered.
- Hey.
- It's like being locked up.
Couldn't you just let him breathe?
You should've let him go alone.
So Min is so hilarious.
- "When do you hate your friend..."
- "Who's in a relationship?"
- It makes you upset.
- When they kiss in front of me.
Who would do that?
- In a barbecue restaurant.
- Hey!
- Hey.
- No one would do that.
- I have...
- After eating a vegetable wrap.
And Cheongyang chili.
A friend who puts one leg
over her boyfriend's lap.
- That'd be really annoying.
- It's annoying.
And she touches his ear like this.
"My boyfriend...
I'll tell you something about him."
- Who is she dating?
- Rae Won.
As a result, Team So Min won.
- Yes!
- All right.
(Team So Min won.)
Gosh, So Min.
The captain of the winning team...
will be informed
if there's a designer on her team...
- and get to change a team member.
- Okay.
- If not, change a member.
- You can decide...
- whether to change a member.
- No, I shouldn't.
If So Min changes a member,
it's likely that he's a designer.
- No. Whatever they tell her,
- No. You don't know that.
- Exactly. Right.
- it'll affect her decision.
They'll tell her
if our team has a designer.
(She's telling So Min
if there's a designer on her team.)
Why are there two designers?
So Min, tell us later.
Having four members isn't
an advantage, right?
- We'll all survive if we stay.
- The probability will rise.
Won't you change a member?
(What could be
Captain Jeon's decision?)
Regardless of the hint,
I want to change the atmosphere.
- The whole team.
- Really?
Her team must have a designer.
That's why she made that decision.
I'm not a designer. Trust me.
Win another round to see if there's
still a designer on the team.
Send Byung Eun to another team
no matter what. I'm not a designer.
- Why should she send me away?
- It might be true. Haha...
- He's suspicious.
- Haha might be telling the truth.
He must be one of the designers.
(What could So Min's decision be?)
- Trust me. It's not me.
- I'll replace Haha.
- Hey, you fool.
- Oh, it's Haha.
- Goodness, you fool.
- I will...
- replace Haha.
- With whom?
- Well...
- He must be one of the designers.
(Whom will she recruit?)
- You're making a mistake.
- I hope she won't send Haha here.
- So Min is so foolish. So Min.
- That's right.
You're sending me away
because you heard we had a designer.
- Oh, her team has a designer.
- That's not the case.
- There's a designer on that team.
- If you think about it,
even if there are no designers
on your team,
you can choose to change a member
just to cause confusion.
- Is it up to the team captain?
- That's right.
But So Min wouldn't pull a trick
like that.
- What kind of game will we play?
- Okay.
- That's an important tip.
- It's not a difficult game.
You don't have to be smart
to win this game.
- Then I won't be a bad choice.
- Then...
What makes you think
So Min is not smart?
- Exactly. That's offensive.
- Why...
- I mean, So Min...
- It makes me upset too.
- Why do you think that So Min...
- You guys,
- I'm not offended at all.
- But...
- I'm not offended.
- I mean...
- We feel offended.
- Are you biased against us?
- I want Sang Hun on my team.
- That's so funny.
- I'll replace Haha with Sang Hun.
- You want me to go?
- Okay.
- Okay. Then the team members...
will be changed as she said.
Let's move to the next place.
- Let's go.
- Yes, that's right.
Keep a close eye on him.
- Whom? Okay.
- Haha. Keep a close eye on him.
He's suspicious.
He must be one of the designers.
(They'll move to another place
for the next mission.)
You'll play the drawing game you like.
It's Air Picasso.
- Air Picasso?
- We're good at drawing.
Each team will play the game
at a time.
The first player has to draw
a given keyword in the air.
Another player watches
the first player's drawing,
draws it on a sketchbook,
and guess the keyword.
- It's so difficult.
- The remaining player...
has to guess the keyword...
based on the drawings in the air
and on the sketchbook.
The other teams...
can also guess the keyword
based on the drawing in the air.
You get two points if you guessed
what your team members draw.
You get one point if it's a question
for another team.
- Got it.
- What a fun new game.
Each team will get three minutes...
to draw in the air
and guess the answer.
The two teams that finish
first and second...
- will receive the benefits.
- Got it.
Can other teams
also guess the answer?
Yes, but only from the drawing
that is drawn in the air.
- Okay.
- Of course.
- Jeonsobari's team will go first.
- Team So Min is up first.
Ready...
(Byung Eun will be drawing
in the air.)
- And go.
- Let's observe.
(The first word)
Byung Eun is hilarious.
It's three-dimensional.
I doubt they drew it correctly.
- He just drew a star.
- What is that?
A circle. A black hole!
Byung Eun is hilarious.
It's three-dimensional.
(Copying Byung Eun's movement)
- He just drew a star.
- What is that?
A circle. A black hole!
Why are you drawing
a three-dimensional object?
It's three-dimensional.
I doubt they drew it correctly.
- He just drew a star.
- What is that?
(Yang Ssaebssaeb
tries to intercept.)
Why are you drawing
a three-dimensional object?
A black hole!
- Let me answer.
- I don't get it.
A helicopter.
- I think that's right.
- That's the one.
(Helicopter is the right answer.)
- How?
- How did you know that?
You scored one point.
- Nice!
- How did you know that?
I lost track of my own drawing.
Byung Eun, you should be
looking over here.
I'm the one
you should be drawing for.
- You?
- Yes.
- Our team.
- You're part of their team.
Byung Eun complimented me
on a job well done.
- Byung Eun.
- But he did do a good job.
- He's not on your team.
- You shouldn't be helping him.
- We're on a different team?
- We need to win this.
He asked if they were on
different teams.
Check the color of your jacket.
- Let's switch.
- Let's trade places.
- Swap places.
- Let's change it up.
Sang Hun, draw well.
- Sang Hun, draw well.
- Draw well.
Hold on a second.
I'll keep it simple.
- How can we guess this?
- He'll keep it simple.
(Bidet)
- All right.
- He's quite good at drawing.
Here we go. Watch closely.
I'll draw it as is,
starting up here.
Sure. Go ahead.
Okay.
- And inside...
- Okay.
A flower pot!
- I see.
- And then...
Watch this.
This one is three-dimensional.
What's that?
- A fountain.
I'll do it once again.
Let me answer.
Let me answer. It's a bidet.
A bidet?
(Hesitant)
- A bidet?
- I think that's right.
- A bidet.
- I think that's the one.
(Bidet is correct.)
- He drew the toilet.
- Yes, the toilet.
(That was close.)
- Why weren't you participating?
- I didn't know the answer.
It was a bidet.
(A swing)
This is a simple one.
- We're at zero points.
- It's a simple one.
- It's really simple.
- We'll guess correctly for you.
- Just follow the lines.
- We're at an advantage.
- Sang Hun, show us instead.
- Right.
- Let us see it.
- Show us instead.
It goes down.
Down and across.
It came back.
- What is this?
- It goes down.
(A swing)
Down and across.
It came back.
(She has the outline of a swing.)
- What is that?
- I don't get it at all.
It came back?
It came back.
- What is that?
- I don't get it at all.
It came back?
- Let me answer!
- What is that?
(Swinging)
(The 3D swing moves back and forth.)
Let me answer. A seesaw!
- I meant a swing.
- A swing.
Let me answer. A seesaw!
(He was late.)
- Okay!
- Good job.
- I said "swing."
- Our team said it.
- She didn't say, "Let me answer."
- She did.
- I said that.
- She said it.
- "Let me answer. A swing."
- That's right.
I said all of it.
Look at him talk.
You said "seesaw" first.
- I know, but...
- Ji Hyo was faster.
- She said the right answer.
- We agree that you won.
- "Got it."
- She said it first.
Our team wasn't able
to score any points.
- What do we do?
- Team So Min, your time is up.
- And you scored zero points.
- Okay!
We can guess the answers later on.
- Are we up next?
- Yes.
- We'll guess theirs instead.
- Rae Won, you should draw.
(Team Jae Seok is up next.)
- That left me suspicious.
- It doesn't give you an advantage.
I now have my doubts.
Byung Eun, why weren't
you saying anything?
I said "zebra" earlier,
but someone beat me to it.
Jeonsobari, move.
- What were you even drawing?
- Byung Eun's gaze...
- You weren't enthusiastic.
- That's not true.
You didn't say anything
after claiming to know the answer.
That's not true.
- We'll guess theirs correctly.
- But...
- I don't think the drawing helps.
- We'll guess theirs instead.
- I'll give it a shot.
- Go ahead.
Are you ready?
(The first word)
Look into his eyes.
- His eyes?
- Hold on.
He's taking a while.
- It must be tricky.
- Yes, tricky to draw.
No, that's not the case.
I'll just draw the outline
since it's an easy one.
(He begins to draw in the air.)
- Waves?
- Let me answer.
(He begins to draw in the air.)
Let me answer. Diving.
(Incorrect)
Now, watch this.
Here's the outline of the object.
Is it up top?
- Two dots.
- What's that?
(He's drawing a power strip!)
Two dots. An excavator?
(A mess)
- Two dots.
- What's that?
That...
- An excavator?
- Let me answer.
A truck.
- Let me answer. An excavator.
- A tank.
(Incorrect)
- What is this?
- Let me answer. An excavator.
- This is a hard one.
- I'll draw it again.
- From here...
- Is it a tough one?
Is it hard to guess?
Watch closely from here.
Here's the outline.
(Calmly)
- You sound like a top tutor.
- You're very kind.
Here we go.
There are different kinds of these.
I'll draw it once more.
(Chapter 1: The Fundamentals
of a Power Strip)
Doesn't he seem
like a science teacher?
- You get the shape, right?
- Yes.
It's like this.
There's a circle...
Another circle...
Let me change the order of things.
From this to...
Is he allowed to talk like this?
- Can't I?
- Hold on.
- You shouldn't talk.
- Seriously.
- He has a nice voice though.
- I was enjoying his voice.
- Let me answer. A button.
- Doesn't he have a nice voice?
(Incorrect)
A line and then another line.
I'll make this bigger.
- Right.
- What is that?
Two dots.
Let me answer!
Electrical outlet!
- I think that's it.
- What?
- Let me answer.
- Let me answer. A power strip.
- Nice!
Okay, good.
Electrical outlet, no.
A power strip.
- How was that a power strip?
- That was it.
Hold on a second.
How can one guess that?
- Show us your drawing.
- Here's your power strip.
- It's true.
- You draw it.
- It's similar.
- Why couldn't you tell?
You did quite well.
It wasn't an easy one.
A power strip
isn't that distinguishable.
- It doesn't pop into your head.
- Okay.
Here we go.
- What's that?
- Okay.
- Let me answer.
- Let me answer. A snowman.
- Let me answer. A bottle gourd.
(Incorrect)
It's similar.
It's similar?
Are you kidding me?
- He can't say that.
- So what?
- Let me answer.
Olaf.
Let me answer. Hoppangman.
- What?
- Are you kidding me?
- Let me give you a hint.
- A hint?
You're supposed to be
giving us hints anyway.
From my perspective...
- I know what it is.
- Right here.
That's Korea.
- Let me answer.
(It's on Jeju Island.)
That's Korea. Jeju Island.
- Let me answer!
- I know.
- Jeju Island.
- No.
- Let me answer.
Let me answer. I know what it is.
- A hareubang.
- Okay.
- A dol hareubang.
(The witty Team Seok Jin
guessed correctly again.)
Something native to Jeju Island.
So that's what it was.
- I see.
- We should switch places.
- Take my seat instead.
- What?
- But he was the best.
- Keep Rae Won up there.
- It wasn't an easy one.
- It wasn't.
A power strip and a hareubang.
- That was a tough one.
- I didn't get it at all.
I have to ask this.
Are you both designers?
No, I'm not it.
I'm not a designer.
I'm just bad at this game.
Aren't they both designers?
Good job, guys.
- A hareubang was tough to draw.
- We scored a lot of points.
We did score a lot of points.
Okay, watch closely.
(Millstone)
It has to be flat.
- That's three-dimensional.
- Keep it flat, will you?
- It's three-dimensional.
- It's supposed to be a drawing.
- Draw it in front of you.
- Got it.
Then...
(Millstone)
Why did it have to be him
of all people?
- Poke.
- He makes it hard for us to focus.
- What?
- I can't concentrate.
(Will this be enough
to know that it's a millstone?)
- He's terrible at drawing.
- I can't concentrate.
- Can you take it from the top?
- Here we go.
It's a flat drawing.
- A flat drawing?
- Yes.
(A flat drawing of a millstone)
Let me answer.
- Let me answer.
- I bet he knows what it is.
Is it a millstone?
- Let me answer.
- It's our turn.
Okay, nice.
Nicely done with the millstone.
- Good.
- I see.
Why on earth would you
draw it that way?
(Thanks to Rae Won,
Team Jae Seok scores 2 points.)
Are you a genius?
- It was a millstone.
- I can't believe it.
There wasn't a handle.
That was him sticking the handle in.
It's time for the next team.
- Okay.
- Okay, you guys did well.
(Lastly, Team Seok Jin is up.)
Nicely done.
- Good job.
- He was the best.
- Ready, set, go.
- Okay.
(Haha will draw for Team Seok Jin.)
- I'll copy his exact moves.
- Yes, do so.
- Go ahead.
- And...
- Right.
- Good.
- Okay?
- Yes, okay.
(Why is Se Chan turning the page
after drawing?)
He's quite good at drawing.
What could that be?
It seems complicated.
(Haha passionately draws.)
He's quite good at drawing.
What could that be?
It seems complicated.
(But Se Chan doesn't copy
Haha's drawings.)
- Right.
- Okay.
- He's signaling them with his leg.
- That's not it.
- That's cheating!
- What's wrong?
- What?
- You're wrong.
(Here we go!)
- He's signaling them with his leg.
- That's not it.
(So Min suspects foul play.)
- You're wrong.
- Get over here.
- You...
- He's signaling them.
- He was signaling them.
- You have it wrong.
Let me see that.
(Before Team Seok Jin
went up as the drawing team.)
Draw whatever you want
and then make a fist.
- Got it.
- That's when we get serious.
- I'll shift my legs.
- Okay, got it.
- Sure.
- Maybe you can suddenly stand up.
(And like that,
they came up with a signal.)
- Come here.
- He's giving them a sign.
- You can't do it.
- Just do it.
- Do it.
- Wait a minute.
- Look.
- This is not right.
I know it.
They got this, this, and this move.
No.
You can't do that.
How can you give a sign with feet?
My goodness.
My gosh.
(A guard to prevent cheating)
- It's okay.
- Block it, Jae Seok.
I blocked it.
(He blocked the cheating zone.)
He's doing it with his eyes.
- Do it.
- Yes. That's it.
- Yes.
(It means
he's going to pretend to draw.)
That's it. Number two. Yes.
- Yes.
- Number two.
Is that move for number two?
Hurry up.
- You can start.
- Yes.
Okay. That one.
And that one.
(He's going to draw for real now!)
- Number 20.
- We got 2.
- Okay.
- That's right.
- I know.
- I know. A stove.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- There you go.
- A stove.
- Yes.
- It's a crushing victory.
- After doing that...
We got this.
I think we don't have a spy.
- We won.
- We're first place.
We don't have a spy here.
- We got the final result.
- Okay. We're in second place.
- We're in 2nd place.
- Team Seok Jin is in 1st place.
- Okay.
With 11 points.
Just see if we got one or not.
- Team Jae Seok is in second place.
- Okay.
- With eight points.
- First place and second place only.
Team So Min is in 3rd place
with 1 point.
Okay.
- I'll give the first place a hint.
- Yes.
(The leader of the 1st-place team
checks the hint.)
Without being caught.
(Your team has a designer.)
(One of the three is a designer.)
(Is Haha who was sent
by So Min earlier the designer?)
Decide if you're going to switch
team members or stay as it is.
- I...
- Seok Sam will send one.
I should send one member at least.
- Right?
- What?
- Is there a designer?
- Do we have one?
- That's why I'm sending one.
That's why I'm sending a member.
It's him.
I said I'm not.
I'm really not the one.
His drawing was weird.
I'm just bad at it.
But I got the stove right.
(Who is the designer
hiding among the three?)
- I'm not the one.
- Seok Jin.
It's Jong Kook.
- But...
- Jong Kook?
Is it Jong Kook?
- It could be Jong Kook.
- They...
I guess they have a designer.
Look at their eyes.
Seok Jin, please tell us.
- It's a glove.
- A glove.
Sung Hun.
- Yes.
- "Sung Hun?"
- "Sung Hun."
- It's "Sang Hun."
- Sang Hun.
- That's so rude.
- Jeong Sang Hun.
- I'm sorry.
Come here, Sang Hun.
Back to the original members?
- No, right? Or who are you...
- Me and...
(Either Jong Kook, Haha, or Se Chan
will go to Team So Min.)
You two play rock, paper, scissors.
- Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
(Win)
Which one will you send?
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- Are you going to switch like this?
- Yes.
- Switching with Sang Hun?
- The person who won.
(Sang Hun from Team So Min,
Jong Kook from Team Seok Jin)
- Why would he switch like this?
- Are you the designer?
No, I'm not.
Didn't you see how hard I worked?
- You were released.
- I did it like crazy.
- It doesn't make sense.
Is it me?
I sent the one who won.
(Jae Seok, the leader of
the 2nd-place team checks the hint.)
(Your team...)
Jae Seok, are you going to switch
members or stay as it is?
But you can't switch with the member
of the first-place team.
- I can't?
- You can only switch with them.
(He can bring
either Jong Kook or Byung Eun.)
(What will Jae Seok choose?)
- I...
- I'm really not the one.
I'll keep the status quo.
- You chose to stay.
- For now.
(Jae Seok will keep
the team members as it is.)
I'll try with them one more time.
Really?
(Is there no designer
in Jae Seok's team?)
(His strategy might be switching
team members at the end.)
Okay. Eat with your team members
and move on to the next mission.
(They will move on to the final race
with new team members.)
- Come on.
- But it is confusing.
This is the final race where you
can get a hint about the designer.
Why do they separate everyone?
Individually?
Are we doing it separately?
Bombs for each member are hidden
in the training center.
We should find them.
When the designer turns on the switch,
the bomb is activated.
When the time runs out,
the bomb will explode immediately.
Which eliminates
the owner of the bomb.
There are wires in six colors.
One of them defuses the bomb.
One of them sets the bomb off.
Four of them reduce
the remaining time.
If you have a good instinct,
you can just cut the wire.
But you can get a hint about
the defusion wire by taking off...
the name tag of other teams.
- If you want a hint.
- I see.
I should cut it,
following my instinct.
If your name tag is torn off,
the remaining time...
will be reduced by ten minutes.
So I shouldn't let them
take mine off.
And I should sneak around
to find the bomb as well.
For your information,
only the designer can cut someone else's.
You can cut your own wire, but only
the designer can cut someone else's.
These designer punks.
(Glaring)
No.
Before the designer activates
the bomb and cuts the wire,
take off as many name tags as you
can to get hints to your advantage.
I should meet someone and take off
their name tag to get a hint.
Then I should find my bomb
and cut the wire based on the hint.
The race is over when seven people
or more are eliminated.
The rank of the team is decided
by the number of remaining members.
Only the 1st and 2nd-place teams
can switch members.
We could be eliminated
in ten minutes.
(The final race will give them
the last chance to switch members.)
Okay. I got it.
Are you suspicious of anyone?
Haha.
If So Min had sent Haha,
there must've been a reason.
I should be suspicious of him first.
Seok Jin and I aren't the one.
It's either Se Chan or Jong Kook.
Why are you suspicious of Se Chan?
Se Chan is too ugly.
"It's me, you jerk."
Why do I like the line so much?
(The suspect with a protruding mouth
is into playing Oh Tae Sik.)
We got Name Tag Elimination
and I want a 1-on-1 with Tae Sik.
I will fight against Tae Sik.
"Tae Sik, you must be sad."
I'm going to take off his name tag
from his back.
I'll make you even sadder.
(While Tae Sik's number 1 fan
is into the role play...)
Byung Eun.
(Rae Won is suspicious
of Byung Eun.)
I think Byung Eun is the designer.
Byung Eun.
(Rae Won, Jong Kook, and So Min
are suspicious of Byung Eun.)
It just feels like it.
Now...
(What is Byung Eun, the one
suspected the most, thinking?)
I feel like Jae Seok is suspected.
Or Seok Jin.
I think it's the two.
(He's serious by himself.)
Okay. For taking off name tags...
How do you do it?
- Sorry?
- You can get a hint.
The race will begin.
Is it starting?
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
- The race begins.
- Okay.
Oh Tae Sik is back.
You have no idea
where the bombs are, right?
(They start searching for bombs
individually for now.)
Would they have put a bomb here?
No, right?
What does the bomb look like?
(While everyone is focused
on finding bombs,)
What would it look like?
(the designer starts to work.)
(The bombs are activated.)
(Secretly turning on the power
of the bombs)
(Some of the bombs
already started counting!)
Gosh.
Is it here?
It's locked.
(They're still looking for the bombs
separately in the meantime.)
It's a fake.
The safe.
We don't need to compete against
each other. You're not the one.
- I'm not.
- I know you're not.
- They're making us compete.
- I got it.
So that we will be eliminated
quickly.
- Jae Seok. Watch your behind.
- Hey.
I'm sorry.
(Jae Seok, watch your behind!)
I'm sorry. It's because it's been
a very long time.
You can't do it.
Without realizing,
I keep thinking
that I should take it off.
Rae Won, come here.
Hold on.
(Rae Won joins them.)
- You punk.
- Okay.
- Come here.
- Let's not do this.
- Let's negotiate.
- We don't have to do this.
- Now, it's like...
- Let's have each other at our back.
- Wait.
I did it without realizing it.
- What?
- I'm sorry. I apologize.
- Let's go this way.
- You go that way.
- You can't do it.
- I'm sorry.
You're making a big mistake.
- You're on our team. Come here.
- Come here.
Come here. Se Chan, come here.
- Oh Tae Sik!
(He finally meets up
with Oh Tae Sik.)
Oh Tae Sik, you are back.
Oh Tae Sik, you must be sad.
- There are three of us.
- What are you going to do?
- Now...
- You had better watch out.
I will hold Rae Won.
Seok Jin.
Hold on.
- Hold on.
- Be careful.
- There is something behind you.
This is the beginning of the race.
Don't be ridiculous.
You sent me away.
- Seok Jin, hurry up and come here.
- Come here.
- It's 4 to 3.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Wait.
- Why?
- Grab them.
- Why are you getting involved?
- Come here.
- For goodness' sake.
Hey. Hold on.
Let me ask you this.
Why did you send me away?
No one worked harder than me.
- It's true. I regret my decision.
- Seriously.
It's strange.
Hey. Hold on.
All right.
I will stay out of this fight.
- Same here.
- I will stay out of this fight too.
- Let's fight some other time.
- That's right.
Let's fight some other time.
- Let's fight some other time.
- I can't believe them.
(One man was watching the fight.)
- I don't understand.
- I think you are it.
- What? Me?
- Yes.
- Why?
- You seem like a designer.
You haven't seen my bomb, have you?
No, I haven't.
I am searching for them.
- It's okay. I am your teammate.
- Really?
Why do I get so startled?
It's not like I committed a crime.
Did I commit a crime?
- For goodness' sake.
- Byung Eun.
You really look like
you would be bad at fighting.
Do something about your outfit.
I haven't fought once in my life.
People are rough.
They are rough indeed.
On Running Man,
people get incredibly rough
during the Name Tag Elimination.
I need to find my bomb.
(Jae Seok looks for his bomb.)
For goodness' sake.
(What?)
(He finds his bomb
that hasn't been triggered yet!)
(It's a special bomb
that has been made safely.)
One of these wires...
(The designers haven't turned on
Jae Seok's bomb yet.)
defuses the bomb.
Yes. One of the six wires
will do that.
(There is only one "defuse" wire.)
Okay.
I shouldn't do anything rash.
(Jae Seok leaves
after checking the location.)
At least I know
the location of my bomb.
So things don't happen...
until the designers
turn on the bomb.
What? I found it.
(Did Sang Hun find something?)
It's Ji Hyo's.
I found Ji Hyo's bomb.
My goodness. I found Ji Hyo's bomb.
Ji Hyo.
(He hurriedly leaves the bomb.)
Then I will take off name tags.
I don't know where my bomb is.
- I will find it.
- I need to find it.
I know where your bomb is.
- Where is it?
- It's a secret.
I will give you ten dollars.
If you tell me where mine is...
- Look for mine.
- I will look for yours.
I know exactly where yours is.
(Se Chan leaves after saying
some meaningful words.)
(Jae Seok searches
every nook and cranny.)
What? Ji Hyo's bomb is here.
(He finds Ji Hyo's bomb.)
What? The timer is going.
(The timer is going!)
(When Sang Hun saw her bomb,
the timer hadn't been started.)
- I need to find it.
- I know...
(Se Chan said he knows
the location of Ji Hyo's bomb.)
(Is one of them a designer
who started Ji Hyo's bomb?)
Ji Hyo's bomb is here.
Then I should tell Ji Hyo, right?
Ji Hyo.
(Jae Seok decides to tell Ji Hyo.)
(He checks up on his bomb
while searching for Ji Hyo.)
The timer is going.
(Jae Seok's bomb
has been started as well.)
The timer is going.
Someone turned on the timer.
(His bomb got turned on
just a moment ago.)
We need to catch the designers.
(He searches the premises
since the designer must be nearby.)
How much time is left on my bomb?
Gosh, you startled me.
(Byung Eun comes out of the room
Jae Seok's bomb is in.)
- Hello.
- What are you doing here?
Hello, Jae Seok.
- Your bomb is here.
- That's right.
- I was surprised.
- But...
- What?
why were you...
You just found my bomb.
Everyone is searching
for his or her bomb.
- That was what you were doing.
- Yes.
(Suspicious)
What is it?
- It's nothing.
- You looked at me strangely.
Who are the designers?
- What?
- The designers...
- You aren't a designer, are you?
- No, I am not.
(Very suspicious)
- Are you certain?
- I am not a designer.
- I know who it is.
- Who is it?
Sang Hun.
Really?
(Why is Byung Eun certain
that Sang Hun is a designer?)
- Sang Hun?
- Yes.
I think so. I am 90 percent sure.
I have time,
so I will look around some more.
Where is mine?
- Haven't you found yours yet?
- No.
- Hey, Sang Hun.
- Jae Seok.
People say you are a designer.
- That's nonsense.
- People say you are a designer.
I am not. I swear I am not.
- Where are you going?
- I am not.
(Sang Hun says he isn't a designer
and leaves suddenly.)
- You aren't?
- I swear I am not.
If you aren't a designer,
why are you leaving the area?
- Where are you going?
- I swear I am not.
(Flustered)
I don't understand.
Where are you going?
(He left when he became suspected.
Is Sang Hun a designer?)
Hey.
You got your name tag removed
once, right?
Your bomb got turned on.
Where is my bomb?
- What?
- Are you a designer?
I can remove
the name tags now, right?
Byung Eun, come here.
(He chases after Byung Eun
right away.)
Why would you remove my name tag?
I need a hint.
- Really? Did you see my bomb?
- Should I stop?
- Yes.
- Where?
I might stop.
Byung Eun went to my university.
Let me remove your name tag once.
Go ahead.
(What?)
(Byung Eun suddenly let him remove
his name tag.)
I removed your name tag.
What happens now?
Rae Won, you will receive a hint
since you removed a name tag.
- Okay.
- My goodness.
Is my bomb turned on?
Did you turn it on?
- No. It was turned on.
- Really?
Someone must have turned it on.
(Rae Won receives a hint
on his "defuse" wire.)
Among the wires,
(Rae Won receives a hint
on his "defuse" wire.)
the "defuse" wire isn't green.
Okay. Maybe I should write it down.
If I get lucky...
and cut off the "defuse" wire of my bomb,
I will live forever.
Okay. I should find my bomb.
I will cut it off no matter what.
We haven't done this in a while,
so it's fun.
I am excited.
(The short man is excited
about the bomb race.)
I will cut it off no matter what.
I am lucky today.
I made many correct guesses today.
(He believes in his luck
and looks for his bomb.)
What? Hey. This is incredible.
(He finds a bomb.)
This is incredible.
Someone cut off my wire.
(Haha's bomb
already has the white wire cut off.)
Who did it?
(Haha's bomb
already has the white wire cut off.)
(A designer cut off a "reduce" wire,
so 10 minutes have been deducted.)
(Designers walk among them.)
Where did I see it?
Hey, Oh Tae Sik.
You had better be careful.
(They keep taking action.)
If I cut off the right wire
in four tries, I will live forever.
Just avoid the "out" wire.
Okay. Let's go. I will go ahead.
I will cut the green wire first.
(1 "defuse" wire, 1 "out" wire,
and 3 "reduce" wires remain.)
No, the blue one.
Here I go.
One.
(What could the blue line be?)
Two. Please.
Three.
One, two, three. Okay.
(He cut it.)
Three. Okay.
Oh, no!
(10 minutes got deducted.)
(He cut a "reduce" wire
and deducted 10 minutes.)
(Sighing)
I will cut another one.
I am confident. The yellow one.
(One of the four is
the "defuse" wire.)
Here I go.
One... No. The green one.
One, two, three.
(What will happen this time?)
(Another 10 minutes got deducted.)
Come on!
(He lost 20 minutes in a moment.)
No!
(Haha doesn't have much time left
since he failed twice in a row.)
I should remove someone's name tag.
(Haha doesn't have much time left
since he failed twice in a row.)
I will be able to guess if I remove
one more person's name tag.
(Rae Won already received 2 hints
by removing name tags.)
Is there an easy target?
I will go up to the second floor.
(The 2nd floor)
Where is my bomb?
(He is the only one
who hasn't found his bomb yet.)
I need to see it.
Gosh.
(He found an easy target.)
Where is my bomb?
(A sudden attack)
(My goodness!)
(Falling down)
- Are you okay?
- I am okay.
Gosh, you are quick.
(He threw his body
and took off Seok Jin's name tag.)
- Gosh.
- Seok Jin, you lose ten minutes...
for getting your name tag
ripped off.
Did I lose ten minutes?
Is my timer going?
My timer must be going.
I have to hurry up and find it.
For goodness' sake. Rae Won got me.
Maybe I will die
without seeing my bomb.
Did your bomb get turned on?
Well... Jong Kook.
- Did your bomb get turned on?
- Not yet.
- What are you doing?
- I think it got turned on.
I will tell you where yours is.
- Where is it?
- Then don't rip off my name tag.
Your bomb got turned on, right?
I haven't even found my bomb yet.
- I...
- So you don't know.
I got my name tag ripped off
by four people.
- Really?
- I will tell you where yours is.
Seok Jin. You don't have a chance.
(The name tag hunt begins.)
At this rate...
For goodness' sake.
Hold on.
I will run out of time
and die at this rate.
Without seeing my bomb...
Without seeing my bomb, I will die.
Hold on. I don't think
I have much time left.
I need to receive a hint.
Give me a hint.
(Jong Kook receives a hint
after a successful hunt.)
Hint!
Gosh.
I will die without seeing my bomb.
I need to see my bomb
to cut off a wire or something.
(He hurriedly looks for his bomb.)
Now...
Now, I have no choice...
What? It's here!
(At that moment)
Now, I have no choice...
What? It's here!
(He finally finds his bomb.)
(Only 15 minutes remain
on the timer!)
Fifteen minutes remain.
Gosh, what should I do? Hold on.
It will be late if my name tag
gets ripped off once more.
If my name tag
gets ripped off once more...
(Should I cut off a wire or not?)
I should take off
someone's name tag.
Hold on.
No.
I have...
two chances.
Even if I fail once...
If I avoid the "out" wire...
(Solemn)
(He becomes serious
as if it's a real bomb.)
The blue wire.
(He has 14 minutes left.)
Which color should I choose? Yellow?
White?
(If he avoids the "out" wire,
he has two chances.)
White.
(After deliberation,
Seok Jin chooses the white wire.)
(What's the white wire?)
(He cuts it!)
(It exploded.)
(The wire he cut off
detonated the bomb.)
Was the white one...
Was the white one the "out" wire?
It was a 1 in 6 chance.
This is unbelievable.
(He got eliminated
with a 1 in 6 chance.)
I had 2 chances
even if I chose a "reduce" wire.
(He is unbelievably unlucky.)
This is unbelievable.
You are out.
I am so unlucky.
Gosh.
This won't do.
I am too hot in these clothes.
(I am too hot in these clothes.)
I don't have time for this. Hold on.
I need to rip off
someone's name tag.
- I will leave it here.
- What are you doing here?
- Aren't you scared of me?
- It's not like that.
Don't rip off my name tag.
I have ten minutes left.
- Please let go of me.
- Why do you have ten minutes left?
Jong Kook, we were good together.
What? I don't care about that.
This is a team competition.
- Hold on.
- I called your name,
- but you kept your distance.
- No, I didn't.
You totally did that.
- Hold on.
- I know you did that.
If you do this,
I will have ten minutes left.
You said earlier
that you have ten minutes left now.
- Your timer hasn't started yet.
- Did you rip it off?
- Se Chan, hurry up and come here.
- What is it?
- Se Chan.
- Behind you.
- His timer hasn't started yet,
so it would be meaningless
to rip off his name tag.
- Really? It hasn't started yet?
- No.
- It would be meaningless.
- Really?
- My timer hasn't started yet.
- I know...
- It would be meaningless.
- Really?
- My timer hasn't started yet.
- I know that it has started.
- Haha, you lost ten minutes.
- Okay.
(Haha lost 10 minutes.)
- Put this on my back.
- Be careful.
- Doesn't that mean...
- Is your timer going?
I have eight minutes left?
You have five minutes left.
Five minutes?
Hold on.
I have five minutes left.
I am done for
if I cut the wrong wire, right?
I have five minutes left,
so I need to cut a wire.
- Three wires have been cut off.
- My guess is the black one.
The black one?
- The black one?
- Yes. The black one.
I am certain it's the black one.
(What will Haha's choice be?)
For goodness' sake.
I will cut off the black one.
I believe in you, Sang Hun.
One, two,
three.
(Will he be able to survive
miraculously?)
(Haha's bomb explodes.)
What?
The black one was the "out" wire.
Which one was the "defuse" wire?
(Team Seok Jin is at a disadvantage
since Haha got eliminated.)
Gosh.
Hold on.
(Sang Hun comes to see his bomb.)
Okay.
Hold on.
(However,)
(one wire is cut.)
Did my bomb explode already?
Look at this. I almost died.
(A designer came secretly
and cut a wire.)
Hold on.
(Despite the suspicion,
Sang Hun isn't a designer!)
There is a favorite color of mine.
(He decides to cut a wire.)
Yellow.
One, two, three.
Two, three.
Ten minutes have been deducted.
Gosh.
(10 minutes have been deducted.)
All right.
I have 24 minutes left.
No one knows that my bomb is here.
Only one person knows.
(Who is the designer
who cut Sang Hun's wire?)
(Is either Byung Eun or Se Chan
a designer?)
Jae Seok, when I took off...
Byung Eun's name tag
for a hint earlier.
he let me do it
without any resistance.
Isn't Byung Eun suspicious?
I have been suspecting him.
- Byung Eun.
- From the start. Earlier,
when we had the drawing game,
he did it very half-heartedly.
(Please scold him.)
when we had the drawing game,
he did it very half-heartedly.
(He tattles in an honest way.)
You are good at tattling.
- Really?
- Your tone...
- Your tone is very trustworthy.
- Okay.
(Ji Hyo is looking
for her teammates.)
Will you rip off my name tag again?
No.
Don't lie.
I only have 35 minutes left.
- How many minutes?
- I only have 35 minutes left.
Byung Eun.
No.
- No.
- Byung Eun, rip off her name tag.
Come on.
- Please excuse me.
- No!
I am sorry.
All right. Let go of me.
- Let's have a 1-on-1 fight.
- A 1-on-1 fight.
(She asks for a face-off.)
- I don't think I have a chance.
- Let's have a 1-on-1 fight.
- Your eyes look scary.
- Don't help him.
(Ji Hyo has a chance against him.)
Hold on. My goodness.
- Don't kick him.
- Don't hit me.
- My goodness.
- Byung Eun.
Come on, Byung Eun.
- Hold on. Excuse me.
- Hey, rip off her name tag.
Hey.
Jong Kook, Jae Seok is coming.
(So Min joins them
with Jae Seok chasing after her.)
- Jae Seok is coming.
- Jae Seok.
- Hey.
- Jae Seok is coming.
- Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok entered a tiger's den.)
- Hey.
Jong Kook is here.
You should have told me
that Jong Kook was here.
(Jae Seok)
(Jae Seok lost 10 minutes.)
For goodness' sake. Hey.
You did it.
You ripped off her name tag.
- You did it.
- For goodness' sake.
- Jae Seok.
- Jong Kook was next to you guys.
- Didn't you see me?
- No.
I was looking at you.
- For goodness' sake.
- This is...
I didn't see you
since your clothes were dark.
- No way.
- That was the worst.
- I couldn't rip it off again.
- All right, Jong Kook.
We are in trouble.
- We got taken out.
- That shouldn't happen again.
- I shouldn't have chased after her.
- There are people.
- No.
It's a strategy.
(Team Se Chan is hiding
in order to get Jong Kook.)
It would become
too exhausted and sweaty...
- if I challenge Jong Kook, right?
- You should do it.
Give it a go.
You should do it.
- Do you want to remove my name tag?
- A 1-on-1 fight?
- No.
Just in case...
- I might remove your name tag.
- Yes.
- Both of us have a chance.
(Glancing over)
Bring it on.
- It's a 1-on-1 fight.
- Bring it on.
All right.
(They get caught.)
Jong Kook, there are people
behind you.
- Hey!
- Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, there are... Stop it.
- I said, "Bring it on."
- I knew something was off.
- Come on.
- I felt like there were people.
- Let's go out.
This is wrong.
- Hey.
- Come here.
Hey.
Jae Seok, come here.
Don't do it.
Come on.
(So Min)
(So Min lost 10 minutes.)
(At that moment)
- Get him.
- Good.
(Jong Kook goes for a face-off.)
I got him. Rip off his name tag.
- Rip off his name tag.
- Jae Seok, come here.
- Hurry up.
- Rip off his name tag.
- Jae Seok.
- My clothes came off.
- I ripped it off.
- Hey.
I ripped it off.
(Jong Kook's name tag
gets ripped off!)
(Jong Kook lost 10 minutes too.)
Stay put!
(Byung Eun lies down.)
Come on.
(Byung Eun lost 10 minutes.)
Jong Kook's name tag got ripped off.
(Things turned chaotic
in an instant.)
Did it satisfy you...
to rip off my name tag like that?
(Did it satisfy you
to rip off my name tag like that?)
(Jae Seok, Rae Won, Ji Hyo, So Min,)
(Byung Eun, Jong Kook,
Sang Hun, Se Chan)
Oh Tae Sik.
I don't know what to say to that.
(So Min checks the time
on her bomb.)
I have 27 minutes left.
Shall I cut a wire?
(She tries cutting a wire
right away.)
Hold on.
(Despite having no hints,
the tiger moth doesn't hesitate.)
Green is my favorite color,
so I will cut the green wire.
(She chooses her favorite color.)
(So Min)
(10 minutes have been deducted.)
I will cut another one.
This is the last chance.
I don't have much time left.
(She has about 16 minutes left.)
(Cutting the "defuse" wire
is a 1 in 5 chance.)
The yellow one.
(She chooses the yellow one.)
The bomb has been defused.
(The bomb has been defused.)
No way.
No way. I am invincible.
I am invincible.
(So Min survived.)
- I need to make a decisive move.
- Right.
- Have you seen mine?
- Yes.
(Sang Hun is going to end the game.)
A minute.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
(The "defuse" wire is not red.)
Yellow.
("Defuse" wire)
If it's not red, then it's black.
I think it's black.
Black.
Am I right?
I'll trust my luck.
One, two, three.
(Sang Hun's bomb blew up.)
Oh, my goodness.
(Jeong Sang Hun)
(He cut the "reduce" wire.
Sang Hun is out.)
I'll blow up my own and suicide.
It'll be funny.
(He's the only one left in the team.
He decides to blow himself up?)
Let's end the game.
- Se Chan.
- Yes.
Your "defuse" wire is...
not blue.
(The "defuse" wire is not blue.)
I choose red.
Red.
(He contemplates and chooses red.)
("Defuse" wire)
Wait.
(What's the red wire Se Chan chose?)
(It blew up.)
Why did you choose that wire
of all lines?
(Everyone in Team Seok Jin is out.)
Am I out?
That's so lame.
(Se Chan's acting weird.
Is he the designer?)
(Seok Jin, Sang Hun,
Se Chan, and Haha are out.)
Se Chan, let's go.
- Did you die too?
- It was hilarious.
Did your bomb blow up too?
It blew up in front of me.
How many times did you try
before it blew up?
- How many times?
- Two.
I had two left.
I had three left.
We can show that off here.
- "How many did you cut?" "Two."
- That ranks us.
He blew it up at once.
Amazing.
At once.
I think I'm the bottom here.
- Life is all about one shot.
- Yes.
(They all blew up their own bombs.)
That's hilarious.
Let's just cut it.
If I'm out, that's too bad.
(Ji Hyo in Team Jae Seok is
moving to end the game.)
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Ji Hyo has no hint
or any broken wire.)
It's black.
Black...
Do I cut it?
(Lucky Ji Hyo chooses black
without contemplation.)
(Ji Hyo's bomb blew up.)
I'm out.
(Ji Hyo is out.)
I must not curse.
(Now, it's 2 versus 3.
It's advantageous for Team So Min.)
No.
I can't go because of Jong Kook.
You can catch him.
Catch him and rip off his name tag.
Byung Eun can't run.
Byung Eun. It's too dangerous.
- I'm stuck.
- Just catch him.
- No.
- We first...
- Why not?
- No.
It's our job.
- Right. We have no choice.
- Sit down.
- No.
- It's "Sunflower."
- "Sunflower."
- No.
- It's "Sunflower."
Sit down first.
- We need to rip his name tag off.
- There's no place to jump.
You should rip it off.
Okay. I have no other choice.
- Jong Kook.
- Come here.
Jong Kook. No.
- No.
- Wait.
No.
(Will Oh Tae Sik be able to
get away?)
- No.
- Be careful.
Wait.
No.
(Kim Rae Won)
You lost ten minutes.
(Rae Won loses 10 minutes.)
- Let's go.
- Go, "Decibel."
(The power is shifting.)
- What are you doing here?
- I'm...
I don't have much time left.
What are you doing here? Come here.
- Wait.
- Byung Eun.
Wait.
What were you doing here?
- What were you doing here?
- Isn't that cheating?
Let's go.
Follow me.
- I'll go up.
- So Min. Come here.
- I'm okay.
- Hey...
You shouldn't go around alone.
It's too dangerous.
I'm...
- What?
- I'm...
Okay.
(So Min is invincible
after deactivating her bomb.)
I don't have much time left.
It's either one.
I have to end it.
It's not black or red or blue.
It's either yellow or white.
(At that moment,
Byung Eun heads to his bomb.)
(He also doesn't
have much time left.)
("Defuse" wire)
Then...
(Only 3 wires remain.)
(Going for a 30 percent chance)
(Another person stands
before the bomb.)
I'm going for white.
White.
(Someone's bomb blew up.)
I cut the "out" wire.
Now... Are you out?
- Yes.
- How?
(Byung Eun is out.)
I thought you were the designer.
- I cut the wire.
- Did your bomb blow up?
It blew up.
(Byung Eun's bomb blew up?)
(Park Byung Eun)
(Byung Eun cut the "out" wire.)
(He might not be the designer.)
White.
The bomb is deactivated.
Okay!
(The bomb is deactivated.)
I'm immortal, right?
Yes.
I'm immortal.
Let me go cut it.
(Rae Won is off to end the game...)
(after hearing Jae Seok
deactivated his bomb.)
I got three hints.
(He has 20 minutes left.)
Should I cut it?
(He tries to deactivate it.)
(Rae Won got 3 hints
from ripping off name tags.)
Green.
Blue.
(If he cuts the "defuse" wire,
he wins.)
Black.
(So far, 6 people are out.)
(With 1 more person out,
the race ends.)
(If Rae Won is out,
Team So Min wins.)
Yellow it is.
(If Rae Won deactivates it,
Team Jae Seok wins.)
What do I do?
(This will determine the result.)
One, two, three.
(What's the result?)
It blew up.
(Rae Won is out.)
Why did I have to choose that?
- Good.
- Nice.
Is it over now?
The race is over.
With seven people out in total,
the winner is Team So Min
with only one person out.
Who's out?
- Byung Eun.
- Me.
My goodness.
I mean...
When did you get eliminated?
How did you get eliminated?
Did you cut the wire?
- Yes.
- I see.
Seriously.
He was out?
Does that mean
he's not the designer?
Second place goes to Team Jae Seok.
(Team Jae Seok places 2nd.)
We all cut the bomb and blew it up.
- We all blew it up.
- Third place goes to...
Team Seok Jin where everyone is out.
- We love fireworks.
- We love to cut wires.
Did you all major in engineering?
- Yes.
- In just one go.
- We go crazy when we see wires.
We can't wait to cut it.
First place can change two people.
Second place can change one person.
(Team So Min can change 2 people.
Team Jae Seok can change 1 person.)
- We have a strong suspect.
- So Min?
(Strong suspect)
Isn't the answer obvious?
- The answer is obvious.
- Yes.
What's there to think?
Isn't it strange that he's out?
Maybe it was his strategy.
You don't know
if the spy is here or not.
I don't know.
I'm sending both of them.
(She'll change all her members.)
- Me too?
- You're not even ridiculous.
Me?
You're not even ridiculous.
- I know.
- Me?
I chased you like crazy,
and you're letting me go?
I think I should
let both of them go.
I want to let both of them go.
- Oh, you're the captain.
- I'm the captain.
- That's so cool.
- But I...
But I eliminated
so many people here.
Jong Kook.
All your efforts went to waste.
- No, wait...
- Me?
(He's about to get discarded
after making her win.)
I'll send Jong Kook back
to his original team.
- Why?
- Am I going back?
- I'll bring Haha.
Thank you.
Why are you letting me go?
- If I send them both...
- Don't make eye contact.
(With Jong Kook)
- They both...
- Why did you take Haha?
- Because it's clear it's not me.
- I'll also let Byung Eun go.
- To where?
(Who will she bring
instead of Byung Eun?)
How about him?
Choose someone
who isn't the designer for sure.
- I think it's not Ji Hyo for sure.
- That's right.
- Bring someone who isn't.
- I'll trade him with Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo?
- You may trade them.
- It's not Ji Hyo?
- I think she isn't.
Byung Eun.
You're back to Team Jae Seok.
Like this.
Haha could be the designer.
- Never.
- That's possible.
But Haha said...
- Wait.
- Don't say that.
Jae Seok. Now you can trade...
someone from the bottom team.
(Who will he send
and who will he bring?)
You're the captain.
- Right.
- Can he keep the team?
- Yes.
- Jae Seok.
I have no idea who it is.
- Me too.
- I have no idea.
I think you should let Byung Eun go.
(Rae Won suggests him
to let Byung Eun go.)
Byung Eun did act weird.
- Isn't it Rae Won?
- I don't think it's Rae Won.
- No.
- It could be Rae Won.
- He's very good at this.
But I think...
He keeps a poker face.
They're both nervous.
It's not him
based on the hint I got.
- What did the hint say?
- It's not whom?
My second hint said...
there was no designer in my team.
(Jae Seok received a hint
after the mission.)
(Your team doesn't have a designer.)
(At the time, Ji Hyo and Rae Won
were in Team Jae Seok.)
I had Ji Hyo and Rae Won.
- That means...
- It makes sense.
Exactly.
It's obvious now.
What's there to think?
If there wasn't one,
send Byung Eun to the other team.
You can't bring Ji Hyo back anyway.
- I'm not sure about whom to bring.
- Me?
From this team?
- It can't be the captain.
- No.
Jong Kook... I have no idea.
Jong Kook?
(Jong Kook's face says
he shouldn't bring Se Chan.)
Jong Kook? I have no idea.
Jong Kook? Is it Jong Kook?
I thought it was Jong Kook,
but now I think it's Haha.
- I swear I'm not a designer.
- I hope you're not.
- I think it's Jong Kook.
- I pick Se Chan.
- Okay!
- Who's going?
- Byung Eun.
- Se Chan?
- Go.
- I swear.
- I knew it.
- You're not a designer, are you?
- You know me.
I'm not a designer. Thank you.
- Are you done choosing your team?
- Yes.
- The teams are fixed now.
- It's not you, right?
Today's penalty is the last bomb
installed by the bomb designers.
It's the water bomb.
Each team should stand
under the bomb.
- Each team?
- Gosh, this is really...
In teams?
My goodness.
- Jae Seok.
- This is so nerve-wracking.
- Gosh.
- You should gather around.
Okay.
- You're not a designer, are you?
- No, I'm not.
If the two designers are
on different teams,
- the citizens in those teams...
- The designers don't get splashed.
- will get the water bomb.
- Two designers.
If the two designers are
on the same team,
all the team members
will get the water bomb.
- One.
- I'm so nervous.
- Two.
- My gosh.
Three.
(Only Team Seok Jin gets splashed.)
- Darn it.
- I told you.
Today's bomb designers were
Kim Jong Kook and Park Byung Eun.
It's them.
(Today's bomb designers,
Kim Jong Kook, Park Byung Eun!)
(The 2 bomb designers
sneaked into Running Man.)
(And they installed
the members' bombs in advance.)
(They turned on the bombs secretly
at the beginning of the race.)
(They avoided
everyone's eyes like that.)
(And the designers
activated the bombs.)
You two...
are the bomb designers
who sneaked into Running Man.
You should be on different teams...
at the end of the race
hiding your identities.
If you end up on the same team,
you will lose and get the penalty.
We should be on different teams.
After each mission,
only the captains of each team...
will get a hint about the designers
and a chance to switch members.
You should stop the captains
from getting a hint...
and make the other team members
look suspicious.
I see.
(Byung Eun was
not competitive at all.)
(When he gave the right answer...)
(Lukewarm)
(When the other team
gave the right answer,)
(he seemed very excited.)
(He stayed calm even when he had
his name tag ripped off.)
(When Jae Seok almost caught him,)
(he escaped the crisis
by framing Sang Hun.)
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook took
the opposite strategy.)
(He tried his best for the missions
to avoid any suspicion.)
(However...)
(Jong Kook and Byung Eun were
put on the same team.)
(They didn't expect this to happen.)
How did that happen?
I tried my best to avoid suspicion.
And I was hoping to be switched
at the last minute.
Things were going just as I planned.
So Min, listen to me. Now...
we are on the same team.
Let's say... What if...
the two of us are the designers?
Then what should you do to survive?
There's nothing you can do
in this situation.
Then you have to tell me the truth.
So I'm telling you now.
- She should understand it by now.
- Are you two the designers?
No way. That's highly unlikely.
The chances are so slim.
Do you want to survive?
You should win
first place in the mission.
Then you can send us
to another team.
That way, you can survive
and we can survive too.
(With So Min on their side,
they started a joint strategy.)
(They cut the wires of the other members
to shorten their lives.)
Okay.
(They removed their name tags
whenever they got the chance.)
(That's how they won
1st place in the mission.)
(And So Min sent them
to other teams.)
(While the designers were happy...)
(There was no designer on my team.)
(The designers forgot
about Jae Seok's hint.)
(With Jae Seok's choice,)
(the 2 designers
got together again.)
(Their plans went down the drain
because of Jae Seok.)
It was them.
- Jae Seok chose it.
- This is unbelievable.
- I knew you weren't the designer.
- I'm sorry, Haha.
I wasn't the designer.
Team Jae Seok and Team So Min
avoided the designers...
- The water is warm.
- with their hawk eyes.
- So they get the prize.
- Yes!
(Team So Min and Team Jae Seok
get the prize.)
- Please bring in the prize.
- It's been a long time.
The prize is crabs.
It's soy sauce marinated crabs.
- Soy sauce marinated crabs?
- Yes.
This is nice.
- Thank you.
- This is it for today.
- Yes!
- Thank you.
- We had a lot of fun.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)