(To finish the 4-week-long
Whatever Penalty Project,)
(a special race in Gangwon Province
was prepared.)
(However...)
(The weather suddenly became worse.)
(I'm afraid we will have to postpone
the shoot in Gangwon Province.)
(Can we find another place?)
(Okay!)
(And we will need a new theme.)
(The production crew's
group chat room is busy.)
It's raining a lot.
Is it raining hard?
Gosh, it's raining heavily.
Are we going somewhere?
- The theme is traveling.
- Where are we going?
This way.
- Can we just go in there?
- Please come in.
- Hello.
My gosh.
Let's go.
(A familiar voice welcomes them.)
Hello.
- What's going on?
- If you really want us
- This is Haha's song.
- Make some noise
Make some noise!
- This is Haha's new song.
- Haha.
So this is the song.
- This is it.
- I like the song.
Hello.
We are going underground again.
I see.
I just hit like on your video.
But I did it
without listening to the song.
- So...
- I didn't expect you to hear it.
So I didn't know it was your song.
- I was like, "What is this?"
- "Maniac."
Right.
What? Did you call him a maniac?
That's the title.
- No.
- She just called you a maniac.
- Why?
- That's the title.
- The title is "Maniac."
- Is that what you meant?
What's with you, So Min?
Why are you wearing sunglasses?
I heard today's theme was traveling.
That's why I'm dressed like this.
- You two should go together.
- You two will get a penalty.
- This is about traveling.
- What's going on?
You don't look like
you're going on a trip.
- That's not it.
- I'm just dressed casually.
We were going to have
the last penalty race...
in Cheorwon, Gangwon Province today.
- I know.
- That's right.
- This is too bad.
- Too bad.
But we had to cancel it
due to the typhoon.
- I see.
- The typhoon is scary.
I hope there will be
no damage caused by the typhoon.
I heard it would be powerful.
- I hope nothing will happen.
- Please. It should veer off us.
- It should.
- We were disappointed,
so we rented a restaurant that
serves dishes of Gangwon Province.
You know Suk Jin is...
- from Gangwon Province.
- I'm from Gangwon Province.
- Suk Jin is?
- Jeongseon.
- I'm from Jeongseon.
- He went to Jeongseon...
- on Running Man the other day.
- He's from Jeongseon.
But none of the local residents
recognized him.
"Everyone! I'm Ji Suk Jin,
the son of Jeongseon!"
- "What?"
- They had no idea.
He's the son...
(About 9 years ago,
he had the shoot in Jeongseon.)
(Did you know
Suk Jin was from Jeongseon?)
(We didn't know.)
I'm still the son of Jeongseon.
Suk Jin, what kind of dish
is famous in Jeongseon?
Jeongseon is famous...
- Rice with thistle?
- Right. Rice with thistle.
- Look... Is that right?
- Thistle?
- It tastes good.
- Is it famous in Jeongseon?
Rice with thistle is good.
Suk Jin likes beef tripe.
Who likes beef tripe?
Suk Jin, you like lamb.
- I do like lamb.
- He likes lamb.
- I like lamb.
- Suk Jin likes lamb.
- Lamb.
But he couldn't eat lamb
when he went to Mongolia.
- It had a strong flavor.
- He only ate cup noodles.
- It was quite strong.
- You know what?
Suk Jin doesn't even know himself.
- He's just fake.
- I really like lamb.
- He lives a fake life.
- He's still learning about himself.
He's getting to know about him.
That's so funny.
All right. Please have a seat first.
- Okay.
- And enjoy the food.
All right. Thank you.
My gosh. This is a sumptuous feast.
This is buckwheat crepe.
- What is this?
- This is ongsimi.
- It looks delicious.
- Look at this bossam.
And this is makguksu.
- Let's eat.
- Enjoy.
This is so good.
(Yoom)
- It's delicious.
- It is.
- I love it.
- It's so tasty.
The bossam is really good.
It melts in my mouth.
- This makguksu...
- Try the ongsimi.
- Potato ongsimi.
- By the way...
- Let me tell you something funny.
- What?
I asked our writer to give me...
- our mission bag.
- Our bag?
Yes. I asked, "Can I get my bag?"
And she said, "Okay.
You'll get it once you go in there."
- Where?
- So...
I thought we'd get something here.
- Can I get my bag?
- You'll get it once you go in.
- Please come in.
- Se Chan.
- She just pushed you in.
- She just said that.
- Just to send you in.
- She meant, "Just go in."
She didn't want to say much.
"All right. Just go in."
That means, "Stop talking
nonsense and just go in."
- She's unbelievable.
- That's adorable.
You fell for that.
- She's unbelievable.
- She works hard.
On Saturday...
Jong Kook suddenly called me
the previous day.
(Jong Kook suddenly called me
the previous day.)
"Jae Suk!
What are you doing tomorrow?"
"Can you come over
for my YouTube channel?"
"We can just talk
for about an hour."
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin joined
Jong Kook's channel as guests.)
We filmed
for about an hour and a half,
- You cast them?
- but we got three episodes.
- Really?
- Did you do the shoot?
I did.
If you have three episodes,
you should give me one.
- Suk Jin, stay out of this.
- That could be a way.
Suk Jin, you didn't do much though.
I promised Jong Kook
that I'd join his channel.
- That's right.
- You can't do this.
You called me
and asked me to join you.
That's because you weren't doing
anything at home when I called you.
So I asked, "Do you want to go to
Jong Kook's place and do nothing?"
Suk Jin was invited
as a special MC.
- That's right.
- Yes.
(He was invited as a special MC
at the last moment.)
Ji Hyo, what did you do yesterday?
I was at home yesterday.
Doing nothing?
I slept.
Ji Hyo, why do you always
stick at home doing nothing?
(Ji Hyo, why do you always
stick at home doing nothing?)
What are you talking about?
Don't be like that, Ji Hyo.
- She's not like you though.
- Why would you say that?
Be confident and go out more.
The world is your oyster.
Do you think life is short?
- It's not like I can't go out.
- What? Life...
(Do you think life is short?)
- It's not like I can't go out.
- What? Life...
- "Do you think life is short?"
- What is he saying?
- Life is...
- I'm startled. What does that mean?
"Do you think life is short?"
(He can't even tell
what's right and what's wrong.)
Do you think life is long?
- What is he saying?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- By the way...
- You should go out.
Why were you at home doing nothing
when you knew all that?
You always stay home.
I'm old enough to stay home.
Something good will
happen to Suk Jin soon.
- Suk Jin.
- Hey.
- Stop talking.
- Is that true?
- Suk Jin has good news.
- Will you stop it?
- I mean,
his wife is...
going on a trip to the States.
(His wife is going on a trip
to the States.)
Play the music!
(Waving his hand to deny it)
He's really excited now.
- I told him.
- That's not true.
(It means a lot
to the devoted husband, Mr. Ji.)
That's not true. No.
- He's really excited.
- No, I'm not.
- What are you going to do?
- What?
What's your plan?
I'll just stay home.
I have nothing to do.
- Then you should come to my place.
- Why?
To babysit Na Eun.
(Come and babysit Na Eun.)
- I have no place to go.
- Once you arrive, she will come...
running to you saying, "Grandpa!"
She will come running to you...
saying, "Grandpa!"
"Grandpa!"
As soon as you arrive...
- Why grandpa?
- Na Eun likes grandpas.
She's so adorable.
Because grandpas
often give her pocket money.
- Hey.
- That's why she likes them.
- "Grandpa!"
- My gosh.
- You should wear hanbok then.
- Grandpa.
Congratulations, Suk Jin.
- Congratulations.
- What do you mean?
I'm really worried.
How would I hold out for a month...
(How would I
hold out for a month...)
Why are you laughing?
Suk Jin.
(Laughing hard)
- He's so happy.
- Why are you laughing?
No. I'm really worried.
Why do you guys just assume...
that a husband will be happy...
when a wife goes on a trip?
(Laughing)
(He can't hold back his laughter.)
Why are you laughing?
(He can't hold it in.)
Why are you so happy?
Suk Jin.
Don't be like that.
I've never seen him so happy before.
(I've never seen him
so happy before.)
That's just an outdated thought.
- That's outdated.
- I know.
This is hilarious.
We have a penalty for Suk Jin.
(We have a penalty for Suk Jin.)
Send him to the States
to meet his wife.
(A special penalty for Suk Jin)
- No, that's not true.
- Sounds good.
Suk Jin,
it will be a nice surprise.
- No.
- It can be a surprise for her.
She will be so happy.
It's not like I can go
to the States only for 3 or 4 days.
Then you should talk to Hyung In...
You'll just go see her face
and come back.
- Just see her face.
- If you want to go,
- I can give you two weeks.
- What?
I'll let you take two weeks off.
You can take two weeks off.
- Hey, don't do that.
- Bring a camera with you.
He gets 2 weeks off out of 4 weeks.
- That's very generous.
- Hyung In.
She wants him to be gone
for two weeks.
I have to come every week.
So we will do the shoot without him?
(They all are serious
when teasing Suk Jin.)
That's not true.
My wife would get the wrong idea.
- She might take it the wrong way.
- Right. She might misunderstand it.
Su Jung, you might fall for that.
This is hilarious.
The typhoon... Seriously...
So what are we going
to do with the penalty?
It will be decided today, right?
Yes, today.
We're in trouble.
It will be decided today.
- Will two people get the penalty?
- Yes.
Today, in this episode,
we will decide on
the one with the most stickers,
and the one with the fewest stickers
will be exempted from the penalty.
- Exempted?
- Exempted right away?
Exempted from the penalty?
Hang on. What's the current score?
- We have 4 and 4...
- I'm losing my appetite now.
It's not easy to win
first place on Running Man.
Suk Jin has three.
- Do I have three stickers?
- Jong Kook has...
- One.
- I have one.
- Only 1 sticker?
- And Haha has 4.
We will get more anyway.
It's 0, 1, 3, and 4 stickers.
Se Chan and I have four stickers?
Guys, you know what?
Jae Suk has none,
so we should give him more stickers.
I don't have to
tell you this, right?
- Yes.
- Sure.
- The one to get more stickers.
- Right.
- He has zero stickers.
- That doesn't sound right.
Jae Suk has none.
That doesn't make sense.
We have to give him
all the stickers.
We should give him all. Everyone.
- Can you believe Jae Suk has none?
- No.
- That's unbelievable.
- Let's give him all the stickers.
- I'm nervous today.
- That just doesn't sound right.
Jae Suk and Jong Kook
look intimate today.
But I...
This is why I'm feeling reassured.
This isn't what I intended,
but I did Jong Kook
a favor last week.
Gladly.
(I did Jong Kook
a favor last week. Gladly.)
- Jong Kook!
- My gosh.
Is this what you intended?
(He joined Jong Kook's channel
at a time like this.)
So they formed an alliance.
I went there...
and did a lot of interesting things.
- It was really fun.
- I know.
I hate it
when these two work together.
- Did you enjoy your food?
- Yes.
We had to cancel the race
we prepared due to the typhoon.
Instead, we prepared
We Want to Go to Gangwon Race today.
- I really want to go to Gangwon.
- I want to go.
Can't you say it better?
That's just lame.
- "We Want to Go to Gangwon."
We Want to Go to Gangwon.
We will have
We Want to Go to Gangwon Race.
- Well done.
- We can't go to Gangwon,
but we will have missions
that will remind you of the place.
When you think of Gangwon,
the first thing that comes
to your mind is potato.
Today, you will get potatoes
instead of R-coins.
- They are real potatoes.
- They are delicious.
After each mission, the winning team
will get 13 potatoes...
and the losing team
will get ten potatoes.
With the potatoes you earn
from each mission,
you will have the final mission.
And you will get penalty stickers
depending on the results.
So please try to get
as many potatoes as possible.
There will be two teams
for today's race.
Haha and Se Chan with
the most stickers will be captains.
(Team Yang Se Chan and Team Haha)
Haha, Jong Kook, Ji Hyo,
and So Min will be a team.
(Team Haha: Jong Kook,
Ji Hyo, and So Min)
And Se Chan, Jae Suk,
and Suk Jin will be a team.
Really?
- Why is that?
- Each team has...
- seven penalty stickers in total.
- I see. Okay.
Let's begin the first mission then.
- Okay.
- Show us.
- This is about a penalty.
Please take a seat with your team.
I think I'm on a stronger team.
- That's not true.
- Don't you think so?
- It's a weak team because of you.
- Right.
You make your team weak.
The team that has you
has to be weak.
(Her rival provokes her.)
What's with him?
You know what, So Min?
The team that has you is weak.
And the team that has Suk Jin
is the weakest.
I think Suk Jin is
taking his own course.
Suk Jin,
if you provoke So Min like that...
- She will give you stickers.
- She will choose you.
Don't do anything silly today.
Here's the first mission...
where you can experience
a trip to Gangwon indirectly.
It's called How Have You Been.
(Mission 1: How Have You Been)
- How have you been?
- What was that?
- How have you been? She's good.
- You sound better now.
You'll hear a sentence
spoken in Gangwon dialect...
- and guess what it means.
- I can do that.
- He's from Jeongseon.
- I'm from Jeongseon.
But he doesn't know anything.
I moved when I was three,
so I don't know much.
You should say "Let me answer"
before giving your answer.
And the team who gives
more correct answers wins the game.
Okay.
- Here's the first question.
- Okay.
Please play the question.
- I should catch the nuance.
- It's really difficult.
- Jae Suk.
Don't you think
you're being too yangyang?
(Don't you think
you're being too yangyang?)
- Yangyang?
- Let me answer.
Jae Suk, don't you think
you're being too frivolous?
- Hey.
- I think that's correct.
- Aren't you being too frivolous?
- That sounds about right.
Being yangyang.
Let me answer. Jae Suk,
aren't you being too nagging?
Let me answer.
Jae Suk.
- Aren't you being too nosy?
- That must be it.
- I think that's it.
- No?
Jae Suk, aren't you
being too mischievous?
That's the same thing.
Frivolous and mischievous.
Jae Suk.
Is it about his mouth? Isn't
your mouth protruding too much?
- No, that's not it.
- Jae Suk.
Ji Hyo, you do it.
- I'll give you the second sentence.
- Okay.
- Please.
- You'll hear it together.
- At the same time.
- Okay.
Jae Suk thinks he's popular.
(Jae Suk thinks he's popular.
I hate it when he's being yangyang.)
- Let me answer.
- He said that first.
- That means he's bragging.
Okay.
- He puts on airs.
- Jong Kook.
- He brags.
- I thought the same thing.
I knew it. I was going to say boast.
- That means he puts on airs.
- This is difficult.
- I'll give you the next question.
- Okay.
Haha.
Where's your jabakseoi?
(Haha. Where's your jabakseoi?)
Let me answer. Where are your wits?
Jabakseoi?
- Jabakseoi?
- What's jabakseoi?
- I'd like to hear it again.
- Okay.
- Haha...
Haha.
(Haha. Where's your jabakseoi?)
Where's your jabakseoi?
- "Where is it?"
- Jabakseoi.
Jabakseoi.
- I guess it's manners.
- Manners.
Your brain?
- "Where are your manners?"
- Give it a try.
It must be your brain.
- "Where are your manners?"
- Give it a try.
- Brain?
- Manners.
- Brain.
Your brain.
- Isn't it like a calf?
- No.
- Is it height?
- "Where's your height?"
- That can't be it.
- Where's your brain?
Where's your brain?
Your head... Your brain.
It's the brain.
Where's your jabakseoi?
Go ahead and try it.
Can I try?
- It can't be brain.
- No.
Why would they say such a thing
even in Gangwon dialect?
Your brain...
Let me answer.
Where are your manners?
- Let me answer.
- I think that's correct.
Where is your hair?
- No.
- That must be it.
That's correct!
- I was going to say that.
- My gosh.
- Gosh, So Min.
- I was going to say that.
(So Min heard Se Chan carefully
when he talked about the brain.)
Hair.
- See? I told you.
- I was going to say that.
I was going to say it.
- I said hair.
- Is it hair?
That's what I thought.
- We gave them a hint.
- Is that jabakseoi?
- This is jabakseoi.
- That means hair.
Jabak.
- Jabak?
- All right.
- I'll give you the next question.
- Okay.
So Min got it right.
Give us the question.
- Hurry and give us.
- That's the North Korean dialect.
- That's North Korean.
- Since Se Chan is...
siksbari...
(Since Se Chan is siksbari...)
Since Se Chan is siksbari,
I thought he was jinsengi.
- What was that? Who?
- "Sisbari" is "jinsengi?"
- "Sisbari?"
- What is "sisbari?"
- Was she talking about me?
- "Sisbari..."
Can we hear it one more time?
Since Se Chan is siksbari,
I thought he was jinsengi.
- Is this the Korean language?
- Let me answer.
Since Se Chan rarely showers,
I thought he was dirty.
(That could also be
a correct answer.)
Isn't that a correct answer?
I think it is.
- It should be the correct answer.
- "Since Se Chan rarely showers..."
I'm dirty.
Since Se Chan rarely showers,
- I thought he was dirty.
- "I thought he was dirty."
- I rarely shower.
- Is it incorrect?
- What does "siksbari" mean?
- "I thought he was jinsengi."
Let me answer.
Se Chan...
has a face of a beast.
- "Jingsengi" sounds similar to it.
- That's right.
- "I thought he was jinsengi."
- Let us hear it just one more time.
Since Se Chan is siksbari,
people used to think
that he was jinsengi.
- "Since Se Chan is siksbari..."
- "Siksbari..."
- Does it mean "clumsy?"
- "To make mistakes often?"
- Oh, right.
- Yes.
- You go ahead. Let him answer.
- Let me answer.
Since Se Chan made mistakes often,
I thought he was a beast.
- Let me answer.
- I'll tell you...
what "jinsengi" means.
- Please tell us.
- "Jinsengi" means...
- "stupid."
- Oh, I see. It means "stupid."
Since Se Chan is siksbari,
people used to think...
- that he was stupid.
- "Siksbari?"
- Hey, were you...
- Were you born at six months?
- "Siksbari?"
- Let me answer. Since Se Chan...
- Could it mean "empty head?"
was born at six months, he's stupid.
- "Empty head?"
- Gosh.
- Let me answer.
- Isn't that what "siksbari" means?
Since Se Chan always makes mistakes,
- I think that's correct.
- Since he always makes mistakes,
- No, I don't think so.
- he's stupid.
"Siksbari" is an action
that Se Chan does often.
What do you do often?
Something that I do often?
- And it makes him look stupid?
- She said she thought I was stupid.
- She thought he was stupid.
- Because he does it too often...
- Let me answer.
- Se Chan! I think it means "klutz."
- Se Chan!
- I think it means "klutz."
- She must know the answer.
- Since Se Chan...
- He was fast. We have a chance.
- It's our turn. They had a chance.
- We have a chance.
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
Since Se Chan is a klutz,
- No, that's not it.
- I thought he was stupid.
Since Se Chan is a klutz,
- No, that's not it.
- I thought he was stupid.
Let me answer.
Since Se Chan laughs all the time,
I thought he was stupid.
- Oh, right.
- That must be correct.
(So Min got two questions right
in a row.)
Yes, that's correct.
- You did a great job.
- Okay.
- I had no idea.
- Oh, my.
- A person who laughs easily?
- Like "silso" as in "laugh?"
- Since he laughs easily...
I must say, she speaks
Gangwon dialect perfectly.
- Did you understand what she said?
- Yes. I mean...
- "Siksbari."
- Here's your next question.
You have to block gunggei obudengi.
- What?
- You have to block gunggei...
obudengi.
Block what? Fart?
- No.
- To block something "obudengi?"
- "Obudengi?"
- Let me answer.
- To block something "obudengi?"
- "Obudengi?"
- Let me answer.
- No.
(Level One:
You have to block gunggei obudengi.)
You have to block the anus
with a cork.
- Of course, it's incorrect.
- Right.
- I think it's correct.
- I agree.
It's something like that.
To stop farting.
No, that's not what it means.
- "Obudengi."
- Let me answer.
- I know the first word.
- Block farts thoroughly.
- No, it doesn't mean "farts."
That's not correct.
What was the word? "Obudengi?"
- Let me answer. Block the butt...
- Block it with fish cakes.
Fish cakes? You thought
"obdengi" means "oden," didn't you?
Fish cakes? What kind of fish cakes?
- Fish cakes...
- S brand's fish cakes.
- Block it firmly.
- With fish cakes.
- Firmly.
- Block it with fish cakes.
You have to block gunggei obudengi
to prevent water leaks.
(Level Two: You have to block
gunggei obudengi...)
(to prevent water leaks.)
Let me answer. You have to block
a hole thoroughly...
- to prevent water leaks.
- To prevent water leaks.
- That must be correct.
- It's very close to the answer.
It's the correct answer.
- Block a hole...
- Firmly?
- Thoroughly?
- I already tried "thoroughly."
- Block a hole...
- Properly?
- Like this.
- Properly.
- tightly.
Like this. Wrap around it like this.
- Like this.
- Or...
- wrap around it twice.
- Properly.
It's so close to the meaning,
but you have to say the exact word.
Let me answer.
Block a hole...
Let's say there's a hole here,
Hyung In, okay?
So it should fit the hole perfectly.
You know what I'm saying, right?
- Turn off the water properly?
- Watch this carefully.
- So this hole...
- Let me answer.
- Block a hole...
- Here's an example of "obudengi."
- Okay.
- "Obudengi."
All I can think of is "fairly."
Se Chan read all the books
in the library obudengi,
- but he's still an empty head.
- Let me answer.
Completely.
("Obudengi" means "completely.")
- That must be correct.
- Completely.
- Block a hole completely.
(Correct)
The answer is "completely."
- The answer is "completely."
- Right.
- Completely.
- "Obudengi."
- Right.
(Team Se Chan got a question right
for the 1st time after 4 questions.)
- It was a difficult question.
- It was so difficult.
- It was really difficult.
- "Obudengi."
- He's the son of Jeongseon.
- It was difficult.
Hey, empty that completely.
Hey, you should block it completely.
- You should block it completely.
- Record completely everything.
Every cameraman should do so.
You should all record
completely everything.
I'm sorry, but are you an idiot?
- Are you?
- No, he's an idiot, not me.
I'm not an idiot.
- He's an idiot, not me.
- Obudengi.
- He's wearing a stupid hat.
- I'll give you the next question.
I ko when Suk Jin eolbun.
"Ko?"
- "Eolbun?"
- "Eolbun..."
- Does it mean "to shake the legs?"
- "I ko when Suk Jin eolbun."
- "Eolbun" must mean...
- Let me answer.
I think it means
"to shake the legs."
I hate it
when Suk Jin acts arrogant.
(Could it be the correct answer?)
- Oh.
- I think it's correct.
(Jong Kook got it right
at the first attempt.)
Right? That's what it means, right?
- Did you live in Gangwon Province?
- No.
- How did you know that?
- I didn't.
I guessed based on the nuance.
- "Eolbun..."
- Right.
- "I ko when Suk Jin eolbun."
- I just...
Yes. That's how it sounded to me.
- I guessed "ko" meant "to hate."
- I'm impressed.
- How did he know?
- How did you get it right?
- It just sounded like that.
- We lost.
- It's a complete defeat.
- Really?
- You have no more questions?
- We do have more questions.
Then shall we try
just one more question?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Then let's...
- This is fun.
- Give us 5 points.
- Right. Give us 5 points.
- Or four points.
- Four points.
- That's ridiculous.
- We'll be tied.
Then our efforts will
go down the drain.
- They all do so on a variety show.
- Just four points.
- But this is too much.
- Come on.
- I would understand...
- Listen to me.
if the score was 5 to 3.
If we get four points,
the two teams will be tied.
- Then we'll have the final match.
- Come on.
Suk Jin,
I hate it when you do that.
(The smart frog used the expression
she learned right away.)
Then slap one another in the face.
That's ridiculous.
(Slapping)
(They do so right away.)
(They build teamwork
by massaging one another's cheeks.)
That's funny. Okay.
That's enough. You can stop it.
- It was good enough, right?
- Yes. That was good enough.
- Okay.
- Let's do as you suggested.
We slapped one another.
So we're good now, right?
You should at least do that
to get another chance.
- Of course, we'd do it right away.
- That was funny.
- You'll get four points this time.
- Yes.
- We're so nice.
- That's too much.
- Let's make it two points.
- Let's do that next time.
- We slapped one another.
- Let's make it three points.
- Four points.
- Or else, it'll be pointless.
- Okay. Let's do that.
- I'll give you the question.
- Yes.
Suk Jin has a lot of gichaengi.
- Let me answer. Laziness.
- Let me answer.
- Suk Jin has...
- Suk Jin coughs a lot.
- Let me answer. I know this.
- I said, laziness.
- Go ahead.
Suk Jin has a lot of earwax.
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
(Correct)
- We won.
- I knew what the word means.
- It means "earwax."
- They call it gichaengi.
- What was it called?
- Gichaengi.
- Doesn't it mean "laziness?"
- I thought it meant "laziness."
- I could guess the meaning too.
- My grandma uses the word.
(So Min who used to be called
an underdog surprised everyone.)
They made questions
based on the facts.
People might think it's true.
The viewers might think
that it's true.
(Seok Sam may have a lot of earwax,
but he doesn't get angry easily.)
They say,
"Right will prevail in the end."
- You won after all.
- That's right.
- Had we won...
- Right.
- They would've been upset.
- That's right.
- The mission ended.
- They would've gone wild.
- I'm relieved.
- It's 7 to 6. Team Haha wins.
- Okay!
- Oh, boy.
Team Haha will receive 13 potatoes.
Team Se Chan, the losing team, will
receive ten potatoes.
Ten potatoes?
They got three more potatoes.
- Only three more potatoes.
- That's not bad.
- We should win the next game.
- Right.
- It's not bad.
- It's not a big difference.
- Then let's move on.
- Okay.
- We'll stay here?
- Yes, we'll stay here.
- That's great.
- Good.
Before we begin,
please go to the kitchen
and bring one item you want.
- Bring an item here?
- Just one?
Yes, one for each.
(They'll choose an item without
knowing what game they'll play.)
- One for each?
- I like this.
- What do you think of this?
- That's nice.
Right?
- We'll pick one more item.
- Should I choose a clay pot?
Jae Suk, wouldn't tongs be helpful?
- What should we choose?
- Tongs?
- A tool.
- Okay. Let's take them.
We can pick one more item.
Let's take a ladle with these.
With those?
Jae Suk, can we choose
an alcoholic drink?
- What?
- Shall we take something wide too?
- Something wide?
- An alcoholic drink?
(Haha picked an alcoholic drink
as Ji Hyo said.)
- Is it allowed?
- Yes.
This is it.
(Will the drink bottle be helpful
in the next game?)
Suk Jin, what about this?
- That?
- It's really big.
Jae Suk took two small items.
- Did he? Okay.
- Yes.
Let's take a big item too
just in case.
Then I'll pick this item.
- What is it?
- I picked this.
- It's pretty.
- It's a kettle.
- This is what I chose.
- I picked this kettle.
Did you bring an alcoholic drink?
- Did you?
- Yes, I did.
An alcoholic drink?
- What about this?
- I already picked it.
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo is fiddling
with something in the corner.)
Ma'am, can I use this
and give you back? What is this?
I'll give you back later.
- I can throw it very far.
- Yes.
- Oh, my. What's that?
- What is it?
- What's that?
- She wants to use it.
- She wants to use this?
- My gosh.
She picked that?
- This box?
- Yes.
- What's in it?
- What's in the box?
We received it as a gift.
She wants to borrow it.
- You received it as a gift?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Ji Hyo...
Yes. You can borrow it.
It's quite heavy.
She picked pears.
So Min picked a similar item...
No, I was wrong.
Oh, no. We picked the same item.
(I picked a kettle too.)
- Come on. Don't do that.
- It's okay.
- But the size is different.
- Why?
(She suddenly acts cute.)
What was that, So Min?
"Why?"
I'll explain the rules to you now.
At the 2018 Winter Olympics
that was held in Gangwon Province,
(Curling, the hottest event at
the Pyeongchang 2018 Winter Olympics)
- curling was very popular.
- Oh, curling?
So we prepared this mission.
It's The Kitchen Curling.
- Curling?
- We picked the right items.
- With this ladle...
- We brought this too.
Oh, boy.
- How can we play curling with this?
- Exactly.
- You'll use the items you brought.
- Okay.
The members of each team will
take turns.
The closer to the center
of the target your item stops,
the higher your score gets.
(They should get their items
to hit the center of the target.)
- He picked a good item.
- That's the best.
After everyone's attempt,
we'll tally the scores...
of the spots
where your items stopped.
- Got it.
- Right.
- Please bring the curling court.
- It doesn't fit, right?
The box full of pears...
That's really good.
- It can cover more than one ring.
- Right.
- We can just make space here.
- Yes.
Hey, this is too big...
I knew you knew that.
What could my score be
if it covers the whole area?
(The target is too small compared
to Suk Jin's large basket.)
I'll be at a disadvantage.
- What do you mean?
- Where should it stop?
It's very wide.
I'm not sure if it's good or bad.
(Haha practices throwing
his makgeolli bottle.)
- You picked a good item.
- It's easy to throw, right?
I think it's good.
(Haha picked it because he likes
alcohol, and he got lucky.)
It's really good.
The two team captains will play
rock-paper-scissors.
The winner will decide
whether to go first or not.
- Okay.
- Come here.
- You should win.
- Isn't it better not to go first?
- I think...
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay. They will go first.
- He won. That's better.
- You want them to go first?
- Yes.
Who is the first player
on your team?
- Okay.
- So Min will go first.
- Must I use only mine?
- I can beat her.
- You can only use yours.
- I see.
- Can I use only the lid?
- Yes, you can.
- Really?
- But we can't throw it...
- We're not allowed to throw it.
- That's correct.
- You must slide it.
- We can only slide it.
Curling.
(So Min, Team Haha,
Stone: Kettle lid)
(The cautious shooting stance)
- Roll it.
- Just roll it.
- It will be funnier.
- Right, it'll be funnier.
(She slid it!)
- Nice!
- Nice! Great job!
(It didn't reach the target.)
She didn't say, "Start."
- I didn't say, "Start."
- She didn't say, "Start."
- Here you go again.
- That doesn't count.
- Gosh, seriously.
- You know she didn't say it.
- That's not fair.
- But she didn't say, "Start."
- Okay. Here we go.
- Gosh.
- Start.
- Seriously.
- Hey, don't forget to say, "Start."
- Didn't you say, "Start?"
- Start.
- She stepped on the line too.
Why is it brown?
Gosh, So Min.
Hey, you shouldn't do it like that.
- So Min.
- What do you mean by that?
- How should she do it then?
- Okay!
(It fell out of the court.)
- He said she wasn't doing it right.
- You said it.
- You did a great job.
- How should she do it?
- When you slide it...
- This one counts. Please leave it.
- Let's move on.
- Next, please.
That's much better.
- We must do it inside the line?
- I should've used that.
- It's okay if your hand crosses it.
- I won't say, "Start."
- I'll practice once.
- Then... For example...
We can let our hands cross the line.
- Oh, our hands are okay?
- Yes.
- But not your body.
- Okay.
Okay!
- Nice.
- Okay!
(It stopped inside the house.)
- He didn't say, "Start."
- He said it.
- Did he?
- He said, "Start."
- It's your turn.
- Okay.
- Next.
- Who's next?
- Haha?
- Just push it.
- I'll go next.
(I got away with it.)
- Oh, that...
- We're all serious about this game.
You should make sure
it moves in the right direction.
- But this bottle...
- It doesn't move straight.
- Hey.
- Why don't you just have a drink?
Roll it gently and make it stop
right next to the lid.
- If I roll it gently, it swerves.
- Does it stop?
- Oh, it swerves?
- It doesn't move straight.
You should think about
how it would swerve.
Think of the lie before sliding it.
- "Lie?"
- Think that you're playing golf.
- Curve it slightly.
- Roll it gently.
- Oh, no. You rolled it hard.
- Oh, boy.
(Will it turn out
as the makgeolli man planned?)
- Please stop in the house.
- You rolled it too hard.
- Right.
- Hey, it didn't curve a lot.
- It didn't.
- It barely swerved.
- It almost rolled straight.
- What a shame.
- It barely swerved.
- Move, kiddo
- Here I go
- See? I knew it.
- Move, kiddo
- He's at an advantage.
Which one of these should I use?
Here we go, let's do this
(The beggar singer
suddenly got excited.)
Use this one. It'll be funnier.
- Which one?
- This one.
I can do that.
- Use the ladle.
- He has two attempts anyway.
- I am Gung Ye
(It's hard to see
why he's so excited.)
- Then I'll go with this one.
- Go with the ladle.
- Yes. Go with the ladle.
- I can do this.
- It will be funny.
You're stepping on the line.
- He's stepping on the line.
- Is this okay?
- Yes, your hand can cross the line.
- This is okay, right?
- This is okay.
- Just don't step on the line.
(Will it reach the center
without hitting Se Chan's stone?)
- Nice... Gosh.
- Okay.
Gosh. That was close.
What was that?
Okay. I know how fast it should be.
- What a shame.
- I figured out the speed.
It must be very light.
A gourd scoop is light.
(He slid it!)
My gosh. Hey!
(Taken aback)
- We won
- Why did it stop there?
Wait. I didn't say, "Start."
- I didn't say, "Start."
- Come on.
- You can't try again.
- But I didn't say, "Start."
- Next.
- Why didn't it go farther?
- Seok Sam, you're up next.
- Did all of you try?
- No, it's your turn.
- Me?
- I slid it as hard as Jae Suk did.
- Okay. Here we go.
- Get ready.
- Start.
Wait. Oh, you have two chances.
- Yes, you have 4 members.
- We picked 4 items.
I think I can make it
stop inside the house.
- I can do this.
- Make it hit the center.
(Jong Kook, Se Chan)
- It's inside the house!
- Okay!
Eight points!
Make it hit the center.
(It landed in the house
without touching the gourd scoop.)
(Good shot, beggar singer.)
- Ji Hyo, just push it hard.
- Next!
- Push them all out.
- Push it hard.
Could she pull it off?
- Put it on the floor.
- Could she push them out?
- Push it hard.
- Put it down on the floor.
- Don't throw it, but slide it.
- No. Further than that.
- Further.
- Grab the knot.
- And slide it hard.
- Further.
- It's impossible.
- Ji Hyo, you can go further.
- Could she pull it off?
- You can go further than that.
- Say, "Start."
- Further.
- Hey, stop.
- Oh, no.
- Ji Hyo, I think...
- You shouldn't start from there.
- Don't forget to say, "Start."
- I think...
- That's right. Slide it.
- you should run toward the line...
and slide it like this.
- That's throwing.
- Right?
We're playing curling.
- You shouldn't throw it in curling.
- Come here.
(Refuting)
That's what they do in curling.
Run from there.
That's throwing.
- That's not allowed.
- Slide it hard.
Say, "Start."
- Start.
- She said it.
- Let's go.
Be careful.
- Good. Oh, boy.
- Oh, dear.
(The box pushed the gourd scoop!)
(Will she turn the game around?)
- Oh, gosh.
- Okay.
(It ended up pushing Team Se Chan's
tongs to the ten-point spot!)
(What a shame.)
Thank you
- Did I fail?
- Ten points!
We got ten points thanks to her.
- They pushed our tongs.
- We got ten points
The score is 15 to 6.
Team Se Chan wins.
- Okay.
- Let them win this time.
- Thank you.
We'll begin the second round now.
- Yes.
- Bring one item you like...
from the kitchen
as you did in the first round.
- Should we pick something else?
- You can use it if you want.
Are we going to play curling again?
You'll play a different game.
We'll play a different game.
It could be jegichagi.
I'll pick something flat this time.
Shall I take this?
- I'll take something like this.
- You should.
- Shall I take this?
- Yes.
- It's easy to roll.
- Okay.
Then I'll take a cup.
It must be different from curling.
- I'll find something round.
- I have a feeling...
that it'll be very different
from curling.
- We won't have to roll it.
- That's correct.
- My gosh.
- Gosh.
I'm back with an item.
Let's have some fun.
Let's do this.
(A restaurant partition)
Hey, this is...
Let's have a blast.
We won!
I picked a good one.
Seeing that the staff members are
laughing,
- this will make people laugh.
- We don't know the game we'll play.
I brought this partition.
Okay! That's good.
I brought this. I didn't know
what game we'll play, but...
Okay.
I made my choice.
- I wonder what game we'll play.
- It's cool.
- You all brought an item, right?
- Yes.
(So everyone selected an item.)
We brought items.
The game you'll play this time...
Please bring it now.
I guess
we won't play curling this time.
What is it?
We won't play table tennis, right?
No way.
- We won't play table tennis, right?
- I don't think so.
If I had to play table tennis
with this...
- Hey, we'll play table tennis.
- Right.
- Gosh, we'll play table tennis.
- No way.
- This is driving me nuts.
- Gosh.
No wonder I had a bad feeling.
How will Ji Hyo play table tennis
with a spoon?
- It really is table tennis.
- I brought the perfect item.
Gosh, this is crazy.
- I picked a good one.
- I can't believe this.
This is good
for playing table tennis.
(Except for Ji Hyo, everyone
on Team Haha made good choices.)
Gosh, this is crazy.
It'll be hard to play table tennis
with both of them.
- Yours is the best.
- Right. Mine is the best.
Gangwon Province has become...
the mecca of table tennis.
- Really?
- That's why we prepared this game.
It's a 2-on-2 table tennis game.
- Okay!
- A 2-on-2 game.
- Okay.
- We watched...
the 1988 Summer Olympics
when we were kids.
The 1st team to win 21 points wins.
And you can change players once
whenever you want.
- Whenever we want? Okay.
- Got it.
(The 1st team to win 21 points wins.
They can change players once.)
But we don't have to change players,
right?
- On our team...
- You must change players once.
We have a referee on our team.
There's no referee there.
You're all players.
They should be divided
into two pairs.
- As soon as the game begins,
- No.
- let's switch...
- You and I can...
- right after winning one point.
- play alone.
- No. They must play as well.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- That's not what I'm saying.
- We must change players once.
- We'll let them just stand still.
- My gosh.
No, I'll play the game.
I heard that it was okay
for them not to hit a ball.
- You're right. But I think...
- I'll hit a ball too.
- we should let them play first...
- Yes.
and as soon as the game begins,
we'll replace them.
Why?
Or else, we'll have to give up
and lose some points.
So Min, I think
they have no expectations for you.
So Min.
If you were on our team,
we'd treat you as our star player.
- Of course.
- Obviously.
Why let yourself
get treated that way?
When you're as good as you are.
- Should I give them the stickers?
- So Min,
- that's not it.
- Of course.
This is a team game.
Don't you know the phrase,
"There's no I in team?"
I know, but you...
- Ji Hyo, I'm sorry.
- I'm curious though.
Why do you like table tennis?
(Why do you like table tennis?)
Tell me why you like table tennis.
Why?
I just like playing games
with you, that's all.
Oh, I see.
- How about a practice round?
- Sounds good.
- Just a second.
- Don't you have the ball?
Are you here to install that?
- Are you a handyman?
- Just a second.
- He's a handyman.
- How about this?
Lift it up like so.
You're covering up the space though.
- You need to hold it up.
- Like this?
Yes, hold it up. It's just as funny.
Haha, you're in my space.
Nice.
- It blocks everything.
- It can block anything.
You only need to let it hover.
- Isn't it heavy?
- It is.
This is perfect though.
- That...
- This is perfect though.
(Spinning)
(Drop)
- Are you supposed to be a magician?
- What's wrong?
Nice, right?
- Isn't this allowed?
- We can utilize what we have.
- Wait.
- Why is this not allowed?
It's like he's grabbing the ball.
Why is this not allowed?
- How many times did it bounce?
- I'll let it bounce once.
That's a cup.
- It was funny but...
- Don't be so harsh.
- How many times did it bounce?
- I'll let it bounce once.
(Meanwhile, So Min practices.)
- No, not like that.
- It was funny but...
Bounce it off the center.
No, aim it upward.
Hold on. Don't show your annoyance.
No, that wasn't the case.
- So Min, it's okay.
- I wasn't annoyed.
Don't show your annoyance.
- That really wasn't it.
- Seriously.
So Min, aim it upward.
- Yes, upward.
- Not downward.
Let me demonstrate.
- Can you pass me the ball?
- Yes, upward.
- I'll demonstrate.
- Upward.
- Just focus on receiving the ball.
- Let me demonstrate.
Here and...
- Like that.
- Aim it upward.
- I know, Haha.
- Not downward.
I know, darn it!
Downward, So Min.
Give it a try.
- Push it upward.
- In 2, 3.
- Not like that!
- Nice.
- It didn't bounce high enough.
- She can't seem to do it.
- Let's do this, then.
- It didn't bounce high enough.
- I'll try again.
- Upward.
- Yes!
- That's right.
- That's it.
- That was great.
- That's how you do it. Let's go.
- Okay.
You and Jong Kook will go first.
- All right.
- Maybe like this.
- This will see who gets to serve.
- Do it.
- Who gets to serve.
- And go.
- Nice.
- This is how you do it!
- I...
- Upward.
- She...
- Take this...
- and do this.
- Actually,
- the box isn't hard enough.
- Aim at So Min.
- Send the ball her way.
- You get it, right?
- Okay!
- It's still our serve.
- Push it hard.
- The game begins.
They get to serve first.
Whoever scores 21 points wins.
- Okay.
- We've won.
(Team Haha scores the first point.)
- Okay.
- We've won.
- We won.
- That's 1 to 0.
I knew it didn't count.
- We get to serve.
- I knew it didn't count.
- That game was already over.
- I'll move out of the way.
- Who's serving?
- Okay.
(Team Se Chan versus Team Haha)
- That game was already over.
- I'll move out of the way.
- Yes!
- Okay.
- Get a grip on yourself.
- Darn it.
(Sliding in)
Okay, that's 2 to 0.
What's with you?
- Okay.
- That's 3 to 0.
- I'm exhausted.
- It's 2 to 1.
We won that point.
- Oh, we didn't.
- It's 2 to 1.
This is blocking my view.
- But...
- Seriously?
Set it down and rest, then.
- It's too heavy.
- Gosh.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Do you know what's funny?
So Min's determined
to do well today.
- She's in my space.
- You're doing great.
(The serve is aimed at So Min.)
- Okay.
- I get it now.
- Can we switch places?
- Can't one ask for a rally?
- Hold it like this.
- I blame my position.
- It's better to hold the handle.
- It's 2 to 2.
- The score is at 2 to 2.
(Deep breaths)
The score is at 2 to 2.
- Okay.
- Nice.
(Partition Boy manages to score.)
- It's 3 to 2.
- But that...
Should this be allowed?
(The next round)
It's too small.
Why don't you receive the ball?
- Me?
- It's 4 to 3.
I can't though.
(Partition Boy works out alone.)
- Gosh.
- Nice!
- Good.
- Okay.
I have gotten the hang of it.
- Jae Suk, wait.
- Move!
- Just a second.
- Move it!
Let me rest a little.
Okay, nice one.
Okay!
(It bounces twice.)
- Okay!
- It's 6 to 4.
- So Min, please.
- Did you have to hit my racket?
- Jong Kook, come on.
Let me hit the ball, will you?
- All right.
- Let her receive it.
- Alternate serves.
- You get to serve now.
- I see.
- Do you want to serve?
- So Min, go ahead.
- Let's receive this.
(So Min is given an opportunity.)
- Look at So Min.
- Do I hit it immediately...
- after throwing it?
- No.
- Do I hit it immediately after?
It should bounce once here and here.
- What...
- Like this.
- I knew it.
- Hold on.
I get that you're enthusiastic,
but watch this.
It should bounce once here first.
Like this, So Min.
Right. You can do this, So Min.
- Haven't you been watching?
- You can do this.
Do I bounce it once and then hit it?
- Yes.
- No, not like that.
- Bounce it off the racket first.
- I see.
- Then, bounce it here and here.
- Okay.
She can do it the easy way.
- That's it.
- Nicely done.
- Nice!
- That's how you do it.
- Keep doing that.
- That's how it goes.
It isn't easy to receive the ball.
Do just that.
- Bounce it here.
- Is she serving?
- Okay.
- Gosh.
(She immediately misses her serve.)
(His patience has run out.)
And that brings us to...
It's too late.
- We're switching players.
- No way!
- Ji Hyo.
- Give it here.
- Us too?
- Yes, let's switch players.
- You and me.
- I'll get some rest.
The cup was a terrible choice.
It's annoying, isn't it?
- We can switch once more.
- No, you can't.
Both players can only
be switched once.
Then play a little longer.
- Ji Hyo, come on.
- A while longer?
We need to run off with the game.
As much surface as possible.
Okay, like that.
- That board...
- I know.
(He's wrapping his hand with tape.)
They're up to something.
- They're up to something.
- Just a second.
We're only using what we have.
- We're making a racket.
- Yes, we're making a racket.
- What on earth are they doing?
- Wait.
- Good.
- Hold on.
Let's do this.
- This is what we had.
- We...
Where's your cup?
- We have two.
- Yes, two.
This is what he brought,
and this is the only way to use it.
(Jae Suk's satisfied.)
All right.
Is that a loofah?
Is that what it is?
- Is it from Italy?
- It's a table tennis racket!
- Is it a loofah from Italy?
- No, a table tennis racket.
- I'll hold it this way.
- Is that better?
- Show them.
- Send it So Min's way.
- Go ahead.
Make it go wide. Nice.
- Okay!
- I...
Go, So Min!
Nice. Okay!
(Alone, So Min
loses them ten points.)
Nice, So Min.
- You're the best.
- You don't have to hit anything.
You're the best on their team.
- So Min, this will be easier.
- It's 11 to 10.
I only ask because I'm curious.
Is it wrong
to stop her from playing...
when she's this poor at it?
Is it wrong
to stop her from playing...
when she's this poor at it?
I only ask because I'm curious.
I ask the viewers
because I'm curious.
- When she's this poor at it...
- When this is the case...
- She's your best player.
- It's like this.
So Min's opinion matters.
You want to play, don't you?
Yes.
(The player wants to compete.)
- Then she should.
- Go ahead.
Who's at fault? Her or us?
You'll agree to this too, right?
- She should get to play.
- If you were me...
She should get to play.
- But...
- Hold on a second.
I have something to complain about.
I don't get to hit the ball
that I know I can send over.
The previous one was easy enough.
- How so?
- How was that hard?
- It was doable.
- What are you talking about?
- That was the easiest kind.
- But...
- It was an easy one.
- It was impossible.
What's more frustrating is that
we're the only ones annoyed.
- The viewers aren't.
- Keep at it, then.
You may not be annoyed, but I am.
This is so unfair.
- Let's keep playing.
- Okay.
- It's 11 to 9.
- Go ahead.
- It's 11 to 10.
Get ready.
Nice.
How was that hard to hit?
(So Min makes another mistake.)
I stood here doing nothing
on purpose.
I purposely stood by doing nothing.
How was that hard to hit?
- So Min, was it a difficult one?
- It's not that.
You looked like you were going
to hit it but you didn't.
- What are you talking about?
- It alarmed me.
I stood still and only observed.
You aren't annoyed, are you?
But we are.
Don't make us the bad guys, okay?
- It's driving us crazy.
- How was that not easy?
- You don't receive penalties.
- So Min's opinion matters.
Do you want to play this game?
- I do.
- Exactly!
Tell me why
you want to play this game.
- Who are you to want this?
- It's settled, then.
Our team will lose.
- "Who are you to want this?"
- Why did you step aside...
when you always
hit the ball yourself?
- Earlier...
- You wanted to hit the ball!
You wanted to hit an easy one
that came your way.
Are we going to play or not?
That team is in shambles!
- Let's play some table tennis.
- Go ahead.
- Let's switch.
- Yes, let's switch.
- Switch.
- Let's switch.
Hold on a second.
- Aim for Ji Hyo with the spoon.
- Okay.
Let her suffer with her spoon.
- Get ready with your spoon.
- He hid himself.
- He concealed himself.
Look at that.
The prankster is at it again.
He concealed himself.
- So it begins.
- You can't tell when he'll serve.
- Prankster Jae Suk.
- Whatever.
- The prankster strikes.
- Is it time?
- Just get on with it.
- He has surfaced.
(A sneak attack)
- That's it.
- Nice!
- I knew it.
- That was close.
- The ball went out.
- Nice.
I sliced it at too much of an angle.
The ball went out.
All right.
(Haha's first offensive strike)
Nice.
Okay!
- Okay.
- Let's calm down.
- Have confidence.
- Got it.
- What's the score?
- It's 13 to 14.
A shadow casts over their faces.
(Haha serves again.)
- Gosh.
- Okay!
- A shadow casts over their faces.
Check out their faces.
(He's no longer smiling.)
All right.
(Haha is on a roll,
and he serves again.)
- Nice.
- There you go.
(Haha makes up
for the points So Min lost.)
- Good.
- Nicely done.
- What's the score?
- It's 19 to 18.
We only have two points to go.
- Just 2 more points.
- That's 2 to go.
- That's too bad.
- It was a good move.
(They're in the end game now.)
You should receive it.
(Mr. Mole misses.)
- It landed here.
- It's 19 to 19.
- Gosh, 19 to 19.
It's a close match
although it's nothing great.
They sent it over.
(The ball heads Ji Hyo's way.)
(Please!)
(During practice, Ji Hyo
showed off her table tennis skills.)
(Will she do the same
under pressure?)
It's nothing great.
- They sent it over.
- Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
- Yes.
(She failed to touch it.)
(Current scores,
Team Se Chan: 20, Team Haha: 18)
- One point.
- We scored one point.
- They said it's deuce.
- It's too hard.
It's hard.
- Just end it at once.
- Just one more point.
(Team Se Chan has to score
1 point to finish the game.)
(Team Haha needs to score
2 times in a row.)
- You should receive it.
- End it with the serve.
Nice.
End it with the serve.
(At that moment,)
(Haha's sudden smash)
(Who will win this game?)
- Yes!
(They won!)
It was close.
- Come on.
- Good job.
Based on the final score,
Team Se Chan won.
- Okay.
- It's okay. We can win next time.
- We can win next time.
Thank you very much.
Team Se Chan that won
gets 13 potatoes.
Team Haha that lost
gets 10 potatoes.
- It's the same.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Move to the next mission place.
- Let's go.
- Move.
(They're singing in messy harmony
in the car.)
(Immersed)
It's a harmony match.
Sing in harmony.
- It's not filmed.
- He's a loser.
- He keeps bullying me.
- We should do well when they fail.
- It's not love
You're singing my notes again.
- Our encounter
- You should switch with Jong Kook.
- Earlier, you said...
- Do you want to sing high?
- It's not
- You should sing in harmony.
- Okay.
(The tone-deaf member
butts in out of nowhere.)
(He's the typical guy who is excited
by himself and keeps the mic.)
Is he singing the right one,
Jong Kook?
- Time is tinged with light
- Next to a singer...
Why are you guys singing
with a singer between you?
- They did well.
- But who is a singer?
- My friend.
- How come he's a singer?
- "How come he's a singer?"
- What is he then?
- He's a gym trainer.
- What are you talking about?
I'm a full-time singer.
- That's your part-time job.
- A former singer?
Didn't you go to karaoke?
- How did you know?
- Where?
She kept wanting to sing in harmony.
- I went to karaoke.
- You went to karaoke recently.
- The day before yesterday.
- I knew it.
(Jae Suk found out.)
I know you well.
How did you know?
There's no reason for you
to want to sing in harmony suddenly.
- Right. She sang it somewhere.
- You sang it somewhere.
- Who did you sing with?
She sang this song 100 percent.
Didn't you sing this song?
She must've sung it
with a guy younger than her.
Hey. What's wrong, So Min?
She sang it 100 percent.
I guess you have a guy.
- Say it here in Running Man.
- No. I sang with my friend.
Don't jump to conclusions.
- Right.
- I didn't jump to conclusions.
- Just let her be.
- A crush.
- No.
What do you mean I jumped
to conclusions? That's what I want.
- So just let her be.
- Don't even want anything for her.
- Why not?
- Don't care about her love life.
- Right. Don't go deep.
- Stay still.
- For both So Min and Ji Hyo.
- Right. Don't be curious.
- Don't care about her love life.
- Right.
I don't have one.
I don't have one,
but you guys are interrupting.
I really don't have one.
But someone might be interested,
- but can't approach because of you.
- It's possible.
- It's really possible.
- We don't do it on purpose,
but we're always filming
and close to So Min.
The same goes for Ji Hyo. So...
they might think,
"If I meet So Min,"
- "I should get to know..."
- Right.
"with the other guys around her."
It can be burdensome.
- You can't date her secretly.
- You can't.
And we can say our opinions.
- We can say opinions at least.
- Yes, we can.
It means sketchy guys...
- shouldn't come.
- No.
- No is a no.
- That's true. That's cool,
- They're cool brothers.
but I could just
want a casual relationship.
- No.
- You can't.
- We're not easy ones.
- Hey.
You should focus
on variety shows now.
- Of course.
- About holding hands,
- you should do it after 100 days.
- Right. You can't do it.
Kiss her after a year, you punk!
I don't know who you are,
- You can never do that.
- but if you have bad intentions,
you're dead.
- He's like a dad of a daughter.
- If you...
Don't have your eye on her.
I won't sit still.
Haha should be around
when we kiss though.
- With a plastic bag on his head.
- I will be with you.
- I'm invisible.
- He's invisible.
- He has to be with us.
- It's a promise.
And I'll be in the group chat too.
But I'll act like I'm not there.
I won't send emojis.
He's not there.
- We can tell at a glance.
- And...
- You can use a stethoscope.
- Stop.
I said enough. I haven't seen anyone
for five years.
- I can tell at a glance.
- Stop.
Just get off.
And if there's a girl
interested in Jong Kook...
You get off too. Shut your mouth.
- That's so random.
- You get off too. Shut your mouth.
- Who are you talking to?
- Is he talking to me?
- No.
- Who is he talking to?
- Is he talking to me?
Were you talking to someone
interested in me?
Yes.
Considering the timing,
he was talking to me.
- Someone interested in me.
- No, it's not you.
- Was it not me?
- The timing was...
- Considering the timing, it's me.
- The timing was off.
- He pointed his fingers.
- He said it was not you.
- Of course not.
It was a coincidence
that I was talking and you...
- spoke at the same time.
- Let me continue.
- Okay.
- If you're interested in him...
Did you not hear me, you punk?
If you heard me, close your mouth.
- Is it me?
- No.
- No, it's not.
- It's someone else.
- It's the timing.
- It's a misunderstanding.
- Coincidentally, the timing is off.
- It's the timing.
- It's someone else.
- When I speak, you speak too.
- No. He was continuing.
- It's the timing.
Anyway, this is funny.
We've become a family.
- That's so random.
- Hey.
We've become a family.
(Bursting into laughter)
- What's wrong with him?
Hey, you should be good
to your family before saying it.
- We've become a family.
- Just be good to your family.
- So we meddle in...
- Don't say we're a family.
our sisters' love life.
Have we become a family?
- When did we become a family?
- Without realizing,
we've become a family.
So we want So Min and Ji Hyo...
- to meet nice guys.
- That sounded so fake just now.
- He said we've become a family.
- What?
- Wasn't it unnatural?
- I'll chase you...
if you treat her badly.
- You're lying.
- But...
- Let's play games.
- Yes, let's do it.
- It was neat.
(Sighing)
You trash.
He meant it.
(The eldest brother said
a heart-warming word to them.)
That was good.
- He keeps trying to give a lecture.
- Right.
(They're like family
to Seok Sam now.)
Suk Jin, you get off first.
Me first? Okay.
(Suk Jin got off first by himself.)
The potatoes the team earned...
- are divided now.
- Okay.
In the end, Team Se Chan lost.
Team Haha got 13 potatoes
and the losing team got 10.
It's a close game.
I think we should have
a plot twist today.
If you get there later,
you'll carry out the final mission
using the potatoes.
And you will get penalty stickers
through the mission.
I guess the last game
is quite long as well.
When you arrive there,
you will get off one by one...
to choose a briefcase
with different numbers of potatoes.
Are there real potatoes in it?
The potatoes the team earned
are divided now.
It has a different number
of potatoes. We don't know how many.
You can choose randomly.
- One out of these three?
- Yes.
- I can't shake it, can I?
- No, you can't.
(Pick 1 out of 3 randomly.)
(He should pick the one with
13 potatoes to have an advantage.)
(Team Se Chan's potatoes:
13, 10, 10)
Check the inside.
Should I?
(Suk Jin was surprised
when he saw the inside.)
- Should I leave it? Take it?
- You may take it.
The potatoes the team earned
were divided.
- They were?
- It's random.
(Team Se Chan's potatoes:
13, 10, 10)
Pick and check before you go.
(Jae Suk checked it as well.)
Yes, I checked it.
(It's Se Chan's turn
and there's one briefcase left.)
This isn't bad.
Where should I go?
(Who picked the one with 13 potatoes
among the members of Team Se Chan?)
How many did you get?
They told us not to say it.
I got 48.
We got 30 in total.
How can you get over 40?
- I'm just saying.
- I got nothing.
I think one has much more potatoes
than the others. I got too little.
How many did we get in total?
- Was it 30-something?
- It was 33.
I think one has much more potatoes
than the others. I got too little.
- Right.
- This has almost nothing.
(They start baiting each other.)
- You got none of what?
- Potatoes.
I also got a little.
(While they're saying random things
to confuse others,)
(Team Haha starts picking randomly
among 36 potatoes.)
Oh, my goodness.
(Team Haha's potatoes: 10, 10, 8, 8)
Is this a lot?
(Ji Hyo made her choice as well.)
The penalty this time is...
I hate that I should come out
that day rather than the penalty.
- Me too.
- You should spare a day.
- That's intense.
- That's what makes you crazy.
- That's the biggest penalty.
- This penalty is intense.
But...
Aren't we getting the penalty
during the shoot?
The ones who don't get
the penalty...
won't have an extra shoot next week.
(The ones who don't get
the penalty...)
(won't have
an extra shoot next week.)
(Only those who get the penalty
will have an extra shoot.)
It's the last day
of the Chuseok holidays.
- Only two people will shoot?
- Then the rest can enjoy...
a longer break.
That's right.
We shouldn't get this.
- We really shouldn't.
- It's the worst.
Then only two members
will do the shoot?
Gosh, that's crazy.
- What do we do?
- I'll support you with two.
What do we do?
Only two members will do the shoot.
- I'm going to use the restroom.
- Only two members...
Isn't it so cute
that he's taking it with him?
Seeing how he's taking it with him,
it must have many potatoes.
- He must have a lot.
- There must be a lot.
He's taking the briefcase with him?
- Why did he have to take it?
- We wouldn't bother to open it.
Gosh, it's sad...
that I had to take the briefcase
with me...
- to the restroom.
- Why did you take it?
- It's sad.
- There must be many potatoes.
No, there isn't.
- If not, he wouldn't have taken it.
- You wouldn't bother to take it.
- Want to hear something funny?
- What is it?
After you guys left one by one,
Ji Hyo and I were the only ones
in the car.
Then suddenly Ji Hyo called me.
She said this while lying down.
"Do you find me uncomfortable?"
All of a sudden...
(Do you find me uncomfortable?)
We've known each other for 11 years.
It wasn't like she came up
to me to ask it.
She was just sprawling
on the seat and asked me.
What do you suppose
she meant by this?
(Only Haha and Ji Hyo
were left on the bus.)
Do you find me uncomfortable?
- What?
- Do you find me uncomfortable?
You? Why would I?
- No.
Why did you ask that?
It suddenly occurred to me.
You're a nutjob.
Why did you ask that?
Are you a nutjob?
- I just asked out of nowhere.
- What was that about?
- "Are you a nutjob?"
- But why?
I was really scared.
That's what made you
uncomfortable, right?
So I asked her why.
Why did you ask me that?
I just wanted to ask
all of a sudden.
Were you possessed?
Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin.)
I find you uncomfortable.
They've been friends
for over 30 years.
Hasn't it been over 30 years?
- Yes, it's been 30 years.
- You still find him uncomfortable?
- Yes, I do.
- I see.
- It can't be helped, then.
- Here's the last mission.
You must make good use
of the potatoes...
so you wouldn't get
more penalty stickers.
The mission is called
How to Make Use of Potatoes.
Gosh, you can stop
with the dialect, Hyung In.
- It's cute, Hyung In.
- It's cute.
I can't stand it anymore.
The number of potatoes
that each member has...
won't be revealed.
But we'll reveal the total number
of potatoes each team has.
Team Haha acquired a total
of 36 potatoes.
- What?
- They have 36 potatoes.
Team Se Chan has 33 potatoes.
- We're only three potatoes away.
- Thirty-three?
Based on the total number
of potatoes,
you can guess if the number
of potatoes in your briefcase...
- is high or low.
- How many do we have in total?
Thirty-six.
In this mission,
you'll submit as many potatoes
as you want individually.
The team that submits
more potatoes wins.
- We need to submit them?
- The fact that you are...
- giving us such a mission...
- Come on.
Let's stop with it already.
The winning team
won't get any penalty stickers.
The losing team will get
as many penalty stickers...
- each round has.
- Let's submit them all.
For the first round,
you'll get one sticker.
For the 2nd and 3rd round,
you'll get 2 stickers each.
You're not uncomfortable with me,
right?
So we'll carry out three rounds
in the same way.
The member with the least amount
of potatoes within the team...
will take all the accumulated
penalty stickers of the team.
- The penalty stickers?
- Yes.
They'll be given to the member
with the least amount?
Then we won't try to submit
our own potatoes.
- Then no one will submit them.
- We'll avoid submitting them.
But we won't get the stickers
if we win, right?
- If you win, you won't get any.
- Let's just submit them all.
- Promise me.
- Yes, let's all submit.
- Of course.
- We win if we submit them all.
We have 36 potatoes,
and they have 33.
I'll have to get the penalty anyway.
- Seriously. I'm getting it anyway.
- That's true.
- Why?
- Yes, you must submit them all.
I have four stickers,
so we must win.
There's one thing
to consider, though.
One of you will be confirmed
to get the penalty.
One with the most number
of stickers.
The one who has the least amount
will be exempted completely,
like I announced earlier.
For instance, if Jae Suk...
tries hard not to earn any stickers,
then he'll be exempted
even from the random choice.
- He'll be exempted.
- He won't get it?
So if he doesn't have
any stickers...
But the odds are against me.
It's hard to not get any stickers.
It's whether you put yourself
or your team first.
That's what the show
always makes us think.
It's a dilemma. That's what you were
going to say, right?
Now, you can discuss
for about ten minutes.
Then you'll go one by one
to submit your potatoes.
You can come up with strategies.
Let's submit all of our potatoes
in all three rounds.
- But...
- Let's submit everything.
- And?
- Let's submit 11 in each round.
(Seok Sam suggests submitting
11 potatoes in each round.)
The 1st round
has 1 sticker at stake,
and the remaining 2 rounds
have 2 stickers each, right?
- So for the first round...
- Let's divide it into three.
Let's just think of taking
the sticker from the first round.
Then let's do this. Don't submit
any potatoes for the first round.
For the second round...
Let's not submit any potatoes
for the first round.
They might come up
with the same plan.
- Then...
- Should we just submit one each?
They might not submit anything
in the first round.
But if we just submit one,
and one of us doesn't submit any,
we'll have a conflict.
So let's just not submit any.
You might have to take the sticker.
Right.
So for this mission...
- I must submit them.
- You must submit them.
- I must definitely submit them.
There's no need to even discuss it.
We must submit them.
- Otherwise, you'll be a fool.
- That's right.
- You must think of winning.
- Of course.
It's not like you're taking
the potatoes until the end.
- They'll be used here only.
- That's exactly what I mean.
- All right. Let's do it.
- Let's use them up.
But what's that look in your eyes?
So we won't submit any
for the first round.
- Don't submit for the first one.
- Okay.
The thing is, they might actually
not submit a lot.
Then let's not submit any
for the first round.
Let's just beat them
in the 2nd and 3rd rounds.
I think we can still win if we
don't submit any in the first one.
I know. Let's just gather
about five.
- Or...
- One each?
I'll submit two.
You guys submit one each.
I'm serious.
Please trust me just this once.
- I'll submit everything.
- You'll submit three?
- I swear.
- Then I'll submit three.
I'll bet my everything.
Haha, don't you betray us.
Hey, I have no place else to go.
- Do you find me uncomfortable?
- I'm on the edge of a cliff.
I don't find you uncomfortable!
Why would I?
I've known you for 11 years.
Just keep this in mind. Haha...
has the highest chance
not to submit any...
because he has the most number
of stickers.
Don't be swayed by that.
They have a higher chance
of not submitting any.
Think about it. Jae Suk doesn't
even need to play for his team...
because he doesn't have
any stickers.
Even if his team loses,
as long as he has many new
potatoes, he won't get any stickers.
- What new potatoes?
- What do you mean?
- New potatoes?
- Haha.
- It's just potatoes.
- Potatoes.
- Hey. Listen.
- What new potatoes?
Are you a new potato PR ambassador?
- You saw how flustered I was, no?
- New potatoes?
Was I flustered?
Do you find me uncomfortable?
New potatoes.
Not many people use that expression.
But newly harvested potatoes
are good.
Are you a farmer?
- So let's just win the first round.
- Right.
- Right, let's do that.
- Follow my hunch.
- Let's do that.
- Let's go with my plan.
- I'm really desperate here.
- Sounds good.
Se Chan will go first.
- Team Se Chan will go first.
- Go, Se Chan.
Since we're submitting 1 each,
the total must be 3.
- That's right.
- Right?
- Guys.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Brothers.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
- I trust you as the youngest.
- Se Chan. In 1, 2, 3.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go! Go!
- Let's go!
- Here come the new potatoes.
- Okay, go!
- Hey, we...
- New potatoes?
- Go!
- They're just regular potatoes.
Guys, I'm going to submit
just as we discussed.
- Of course.
- I have nothing to lose now.
- Me too.
- Just follow our plan. Okay?
Let's go.
If the total number matches
the one we promised, I will cry...
- because I'll be so touched.
- Don't worry.
I have a question.
Let's say I submit one.
Then the remaining potatoes
I have...
will be minus
the ones I submitted, right?
(Sighing)
This is driving me crazy.
I have no other options anyway.
(They agreed to make the total 3
by submitting 1 each.)
I'll submit one for now.
We decided to forget about
the first round...
and go all-in
in the 2nd and 3rd rounds.
It can't be helped.
I'm submitting one...
since we made a promise.
(Se Chan kept his word
by submitting 1 potato.)
(Next is Seok Sam.)
I'm contemplating.
The three of us made a firm promise.
(Rambling on)
(Suk Jin contemplated for a while.)
(Will he submit one
just as he promised?)
(He returns confidently.)
Seok Sam, you're back.
- Jae Suk, it's your turn.
- Okay.
- You're on your way back, right?
- You're back.
I am. Why do you look so down?
You won't tell me
how many they submitted, right?
(Obviously not.)
(Contemplating)
It looks like you didn't submit any.
Maybe I'm the only one who did.
I don't think Jae Suk
will submit any either.
Jae Suk won't submit any,
but he'll just stand there
pretending to be contemplating.
I'm certain of it.
- He came back pretty fast.
- He's back so soon.
You don't need to take much time.
Just do as you promised.
- Right?
- Yes.
(Jae Suk returned
faster than they thought.)
You don't even have to contemplate.
We'll submit
just like we discussed, right?
- Team Haha, it's your turn.
- Okay.
- Haha can go first.
- I'll be back really fast.
- Come back as soon as you leave.
Okay.
(Haha promised to submit
2 potatoes alone.)
I love you guys!
Okay!
That makes him suspicious.
No, I think he'll submit
as he promised.
Seeing how he went so far,
he'll submit them.
(Haha has been going overboard.)
(What will be his choice?)
(He submitted 2 potatoes.)
(Haha submitted 2 potatoes
just as he promised.)
(When they were choosing
the briefcase,)
(Haha chose one with 8 potatoes
out of 36.)
(He was happy to choose a briefcase
with the least amount of potatoes.)
(He gladly submitted
2 potatoes out of 8.)
Next!
- Wow! Should I go next?
- Jong Kook, you're next.
Okay. I'll be back soon too.
You don't even have to think much.
- Did you really submit them?
- I did. I swear.
But that wasn't enough time
to open and close the briefcase.
But that wasn't enough time...
(He came back this fast?)
- No, I submitted them for real.
- You're such a good actor.
But that was almost like...
- You came back so fast?
- So Min, you'll be the only one.
Just as I promised. All right.
I'll submit one.
(He doesn't even think twice
and submits 1 just as he promised.)
- I swear. He came back fast too.
- Ji Hyo, you're next.
- I swear I submitted them.
- No.
- I swear.
- It looks like you didn't even...
put down the briefcase.
So Min, don't be embarrassed later
when you watch this episode.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors,
and the loser...
How can they come back so fast?
(Ji Hyo comes out all suspicious.)
Maybe they didn't submit any.
(Ji Hyo and So Min
are done submitting as well.)
Okay.
Are you done?
- I think they are done.
- They are done.
(Submission is complete
for Round 1.)
- Let's see.
- Yes.
- The result of Round One is out.
- Okay.
- A penalty sticker is on the line.
- That's right.
Team Haha submitted...
a total...
(The total number of potatoes
Team Haha submitted)
I will submit 2, so submit 1 each.
(Team Haha agreed to submit
a total of 5 potatoes.)
Team Haha submitted a total...
- of two potatoes.
- Hey.
- This is too much.
- A total of two potatoes.
- Hey.
- This is too much.
- You punk.
- Whose fault is this?
- You promised to submit potatoes.
- They are fighting.
- Haha.
- Hey.
- I submitted potatoes.
- Haha.
- You promised to submit potatoes.
- For goodness' sake.
- Haha.
- This lousy team...
- Why didn't you keep your word?
- I got fooled.
- We decided to submit one each.
- I knew this would happen.
- We won.
- We submitted one each.
Did you submit potatoes
as you promised or not?
(A physical fight is
about to break out.)
- Only I submitted potatoes.
- We won.
- Listen.
Had you submitted potatoes
as you promised,
- I will give you my entire fortune.
- Okay.
- Make sure you do that.
- I can't believe it.
- It's a promise.
You didn't submit a potato.
Didn't you submit a potato,
Jong Kook?
- I will give you my entire fortune.
- Haha, you are the one...
who didn't submit any potatoes.
Hey,
- I will bet my entire family.
- Then the number should be greater.
(Will he bet his family?)
- Will he bet his family?
- Jong Kook.
- Haha.
- I submitted potatoes.
- Hold on.
- Haha.
Doesn't that mean
the count is wrong?
- Well...
- Is the total two?
- No way.
- It can't be two.
Count again.
- It makes no sense.
- Seriously.
I bet my entire fortune,
and he bet his family.
I bet my family.
It makes no sense.
- Count again.
- I bet my entire fortune,
- and he bet his family.
- I swear I submitted potatoes.
- We are checking.
- Check.
- Check. I misunderstood then.
- We bet our fortune and family.
- I am sorry.
- I can bet my entire fortune too.
- Hold on.
Isn't it that team's total?
I think that team submitted two.
- We should have at least...
- Outside,
- the staff counted wrong.
- I knew it.
- Hey.
- I can't believe you counted wrong.
- I am sorry, Haha. I love you.
- It's okay.
You get it now, right?
Yes.
Okay. I am sorry.
- I submitted potatoes for real.
- We bet our fortune and family.
I bet my family.
- I was startled.
(What's the real total
for Team Haha?)
How could you count wrong
when there were only two potatoes?
- All right.
- Team Haha's total is four.
- That makes more sense.
- Come on, So Min.
Team Haha's total is four.
- That makes more sense.
- Come on, So Min.
So Min didn't submit any.
- It isn't me. I did submit one.
- She betrayed us.
- I really submitted one.
- So Min didn't submit any.
- She didn't submit any.
- No.
- I really submitted one.
- What will you bet?
- Me? I will bet my mom and dad.
- I will bet my mom and dad.
- Ji Hyo, bet your dog.
(So Min acts like
she is victimized.)
- Let me see your fingers.
- It's Ji Hyo. Look at her face.
- Ji Hyo didn't submit any.
- I can bet my entire fortune.
- Maybe the count is wrong again.
- Let me see your fingers.
- I can bet my entire fortune.
- Your toes must be crossed.
(Either JI Hyo or So Min is lying.)
- You...
- My toes aren't crossed.
- That would be impossible.
- Maybe you counted wrong again.
Are you certain?
- Now comes Team Se Chan's total.
- Our team.
- Let's see.
- We submitted two each.
- Team Se Chan submitted a total...
of one potato.
- What?
- Excuse me?
A total of one potato.
- What?
- Excuse me?
- Hey.
(They fail to stifle
their laughter.)
Who is it?
- We won.
- I can't believe you guys.
- Hey.
- Seriously.
- Come here.
- Is it really one?
- Hey.
I think I should submit one potato.
I will bring more potatoes
in the following rounds.
(No more potatoes were submitted.)
- Come here.
- One?
- Don't be like that.
- Hey. One?
- One?
- For goodness' sake.
- I can't believe them.
- One?
- Hey.
- You should have submitted one.
- Seriously.
- Don't you trust us?
For goodness' sake.
I trusted you guys. Listen.
Suk Jin, I...
- Hey.
- We talked about this.
You shouldn't be like that.
- Only I submitted a potato.
- Are you certain?
- Team Se Chan lost...
- Can you bet your wife?
and acquired one penalty sticker.
Round Two will begin now.
Please discuss among yourselves
for ten minutes.
I won't submit any potatoes then.
Two penalty stickers are on the line
for the next round.
This many potatoes...
are more than enough
to surpass that team.
- We used too many potatoes.
- We used too many of them.
- I told you so.
Now, we can't ask people
to submit potatoes. Think about it.
We have to play individually.
We need to submit potatoes now.
Come here.
Come here, Se Chan.
- I won't submit any.
- Suk Jin, come here.
I won't submit any.
- I won't submit any.
- Listen.
- We need to win in the next rounds.
- I won't submit any.
We have to submit potatoes now.
- We have to do it.
Listen to me.
You know that I submitted
a potato, right?
You didn't submit any potatoes.
- It's true. Come on.
- I submitted a potato.
- It's time to tell the truth.
- Suk Jin.
- You should be honest.
Let's have a cheer.
(Let's have a cheer.)
(He suddenly suggests a cheer.)
- Let's have a cheer.
- Let's do that.
Se Chan, let's have a cheer.
- One, two, three.
- Let's go.
- Good.
- This is the beginning.
- What was that?
- Let's start anew.
- To be honest, I didn't submit any.
- You didn't either.
- I didn't submit any.
You submitted a potato.
- Se Chan, let's start anew.
- You submitted a potato.
- I submitted a potato.
- Let's go.
Let me tell you this.
If you don't submit potatoes...
in the next rounds,
- we will lose.
- It will be game over.
We will lose.
We will get
all five penalty stickers.
- We can't let that happen.
- No.
We can't let that happen.
Tell us later
why you didn't submit any.
I submitted a potato.
- Tell us later.
- I submitted a potato.
- You are embarrassed, right?
- You can bet your mom and dad.
- Yes.
(Yes.)
What will you say to your mom later?
- Why are you teary-eyed?
- Will you live separately?
You feel bad, right?
Apologize to your mom and dad.
(When it was her turn
to submit potatoes,)
(she only pretended
to open the briefcase.)
(Only So Min didn't submit
any potatoes.)
You feel bad, right?
Apologize to your mom and dad.
- Apologize to your mom and dad.
- Apologize to them.
Go to the Jimmy Jib
or your camera and apologize.
- We forgive you. Go and apologize.
- Do it.
I did submit a potato.
Did everyone keep the promise?
- She didn't.
- I did.
- I totally did.
- You did, right?
Only So Min didn't.
So Min, what are you going to do?
This is why we treat her this way.
You belong to our team.
Seriously.
Listen.
Although we didn't keep the promise,
we just made up.
- We just laughed it off.
It's nothing big.
We just laughed it off.
- I mean...
- Come on out and apologize.
They keep telling me to bet things.
Who does that?
Hurry up and tell them to stop.
- Apologize to them.
- Seriously.
- My mom and dad would understand.
- This is a variety show.
"My mom and dad would understand."
(They demand collateral
over a potato.)
Let's submit three each.
I don't think they will submit many.
If Jong Kook submits 3,
their total will be 6.
Because that team has Jong Kook...
If we submit three each,
- we will win.
- Really?
Okay. I will listen to you.
- Then we will go all in.
- Nine potatoes.
We need to win the next round.
Potatoes will be meaningless
if we lose.
- We need to win the next round.
- I do want to win, but...
If we submit four each,
- it won't be a problem.
- Okay.
- Four each.
- This time, submit potatoes.
- Please.
- Okay.
- Let's win.
- I can't believe them.
- We will submit potatoes.
- They are looking at me like cats.
- We will submit potatoes this time.
- Of course.
I am sorry, but what's the point...
of having a meeting?
We are tight.
- It's our strategy.
- We are tight.
- Only a fool would submit potatoes.
- Why?
- Why are you having a meeting?
- Only a fool would submit potatoes.
- Why?
- Why would you say that?
- We will win.
- Why would you submit potatoes?
- We will win two rounds.
- What are you saying?
- Jae Suk wouldn't submit any.
- Of course he would. We must win.
- Of course I would.
- What are you saying?
- Submit potatoes no matter what.
(The cats are pretty determined.)
Hear me out.
I have a strategy.
This time,
let's not submit any potatoes.
- We won a round.
- Yes.
- Let's go all in for Round Three.
- Let's do that.
- That's a good idea.
- Yes.
We should do that.
- We can win then.
- We should do that.
- Let's do that.
- I believe in you guys.
I think they will submit potatoes.
I think so.
We will focus on the last round.
I hope that team submits
a lot of potatoes in this round.
Two rounds remain,
- so we have to win.
- Okay.
- In the next round,
- That's right.
- they might not submit potatoes.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
- Let's bring our hands together.
I can't believe them.
- Come here.
- Jae Suk.
- We aren't fools.
- Hey.
We got this.
One, two, three.
- Let's go.
(Cheers for the team.)
- Jae Suk.
- Jong Kook, please go first.
Okay.
- Haha.
- Okay.
- This is our strategy.
I got it.
(Team Haha agreed
to submit 0 potatoes.)
(What kind of a result
will their strategy bring?)
(The first member, Jong Kook)
(He submits 0 potatoes.)
(Team Haha finishes submitting.)
All right.
- I am stressed out.
- Yes.
- Seriously.
- That was simple.
Of course. I changed a lot.
- Suk Jin, you are up.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- How many potatoes?
- Is this enough?
- Yes.
(Team Se Chan's plan
is to submit 9 potatoes.)
My conscience and rationality...
keep fighting.
(The match of the century,
conscience versus rationality)
Rationally,
I know exactly how to win.
But my conscience...
(Suk Jin has
a fierce inner battle.)
But...
What should I do?
(Should he submit 3 potatoes
as he promised or not?)
My conscience and rationality
keep fighting.
I should submit some potatoes.
We might win.
In any case...
(Suk Jin makes up his mind
after much deliberation.)
I am torn.
We do need to win.
I think Se Chan is submitting
one potato at a time...
because he has a lot of potatoes.
There is no way
Suk Jin submitted three potatoes.
(He thinks Suk Jin doesn't have
many potatoes.)
(Briefcase selection)
(Team Se Chan's potatoes:
10, 10, 13)
(Jae Suk received 10 potatoes.)
I checked.
(That means either one of them
received 13 potatoes.)
(Se Chan is the last one to go.)
(How many potatoes
did Se Chan submit?)
He came back quickly.
- Let's see.
- Round Two has ended.
I will reveal...
- Team Se Chan's total first.
- I bet the number is high.
- What should the total number be?
- Nine.
- What should it be?
- Yes.
Team Se Chan submitted a total...
of one potato.
For goodness' sake.
(Team Se Chan's total is
one potato.)
- They are too much.
- Hey.
- One potato.
- For goodness' sake.
(The number is much lower
than they expected.)
This is too much.
- I can't believe them.
- Hey.
I can't believe them.
(Who submitted 1 potato?)
(He took back all potatoes.)
(Se Chan put on a show
and locked up his briefcase!)
(Jae Suk thought there was someone
with more potatoes.)
My conscience and rationality
keep fighting.
(Suk Jin's conscience
and rationality had a big match.)
One potato.
I should submit some potatoes.
We might win.
(Thus, he submitted one potato
for his conscience.)
- I can't believe them.
- Hey.
(The team spirit is in the gutter.)
- Come here.
- For goodness' sake.
- They are too much.
- One?
- Hey.
- What's wrong with you guys?
- Didn't you submit any?
- You should have submitted three.
- I submitted one potato.
- I did that.
- For goodness' sake.
- Didn't you submit any potatoes?
- Unbelievable.
- And...
- All right.
Team Haha submitted
a total of zero potatoes.
- We won.
Team Haha submitted
a total of zero potatoes.
(Did they win with 1 potato?)
- We won.
(The miracle of one potato)
We won with one potato.
We did it.
Someone submitted one potato.
(Team Se Chan won
with fewer potatoes than expected.)
Someone submitted one potato.
I wonder who submitted one potato.
- Who did it?
- I am sure Se Chan did.
Do I have a lot of potatoes?
(Briefcase selection)
I have ten.
What's the highest number
of potatoes?
- Jong Kook doesn't have a lot.
- It seems that way.
(Team Haha's potatoes: 8, 8, 10, 10)
(10 potatoes)
I have eight.
(8 potatoes)
Please discuss among yourselves
for the last round.
- Someone submitted a potato.
- We won.
(At this rate, Haha will receive
a penalty sticker.)
- I submitted a potato.
- We did it.
- You didn't submit any.
- We still won.
Good.
We have a chance.
They submitted zero potatoes.
- I submitted a potato.
- Please discuss among yourselves...
for the last round.
- They don't have potatoes to spare.
- Suk Jin.
I can't believe we won.
- Someone submitted a potato.
- I think...
we should submit two potatoes each.
Sit down.
(One had 13 potatoes
and the other had 10 potatoes.)
You should think about winning,
not keeping your potatoes.
You won thanks to me.
You submitted 1 potato
when we agreed on 3.
I knew you would submit
zero potatoes.
You have a point.
You have a lot of potatoes, right?
- I don't have many left.
- Be honest.
- Why don't you have many left?
- I have less than ten.
- Don't lie.
- I looked into it.
- Really?
Someone took 13 potatoes.
The others took ten potatoes each.
(Did Se Chan take 13 potatoes?)
- Are you certain?
- Yes.
Do you have ten potatoes now?
Tell me what the strategy is.
Submit two potatoes this time.
Why?
You and I should submit one each.
Ten potatoes each.
We need to submit
as many potatoes as possible.
We have different numbers
of potatoes.
- Leave some potatoes and...
- Submit all but two potatoes.
(Laughing)
We had this talk earlier,
but only one potato was submitted.
Didn't we have
the same type of discussion earlier?
But we didn't get
more than one potato.
This is ridiculous.
It's a bit funny.
Let's submit potatoes this time.
I will submit potatoes
since receiving a penalty sticker...
- is meaningless.
- Let's all submit potatoes.
(The three cats have
the same type of discussion.)
What should we do now?
Here is what I think, Jong Kook.
This time, I think that team
will either submit zero potatoes...
- or one potato.
- Right.
A member who received many potatoes
should submit one.
(Jong Kook suggests
submitting one potato.)
- Okay.
- Okay?
- In that case...
- It goes without saying.
Instead of submitting one potato,
let's do this.
I see.
I would be grateful if you do that.
- Submit two potatoes? Okay.
- Yes.
She must have many potatoes.
I only have a few.
I will do it for the team.
That team will try to keep
their potatoes.
- So Ji Hyo will submit this many.
- Yes.
- Thank you. You are so cool.
- I will do it for the team.
Ji Hyo is... My goodness.
Ji Hyo.
You are insanely cool.
Although I only have a few potatoes,
- I will do it for the team.
- Then I will submit a potato too.
We should win this round.
Can you submit one potato?
(So Min, can you submit one potato?)
Do it to restore our faith in you.
- Okay.
- Promise us.
- Okay. I will really do it.
- For real.
Then you will submit this many,
and Ji Hyo will submit this many.
- All right.
- How about you?
I submitted potatoes earlier.
That's right.
This balances things out.
- Team Se Chan's Jae Suk is up.
- Okay.
- Decide before you go.
- Listen to me.
- Then Jae Suk should take it.
Submit all but one.
- Okay, I got it.
- Got it? Really?
- Let's go.
- You know,
- We will go all in.
here is what I think.
The team that submits
three potatoes will win.
(He gives up.)
Three potatoes.
Suit yourself.
I think the number is less
than that.
We will go all in.
The team that submits
one potato will win.
(Jae Suk could be exempt
from the penalty...)
(since he has 0 penalty stickers.)
(Jae Suk)
(Will he go all in for the team
or submit 0 potatoes for himself?)
We agreed to submit 3 each
and I submitted 1 in a naive way.
Suk Jin is up next.
- Submit all but one.
- As for Suk Jin...
Why did you make a fist?
(Laughing)
(Chuckling)
After having a lengthy discussion,
we will have one potato.
I am so impressed
that no one became sullen.
- No one became sullen.
- We understand each other.
We understand each other.
We let things go.
- We let things go.
- "I am sure he had his reasons."
- It happens on a show.
(Again, he must choose
between conscience and rationality.)
Since I submitted a potato earlier,
they won't submit any.
I don't even feel
a prick of conscience anymore.
We won the last round thanks to me.
I did more than enough.
All right.
(How many potatoes
did Suk Jin submit?)
Had So Min joined this team...
(Suk Jin returns with seriousness.)
Suk Jin, let me see your eyes.
Let me see the truth in your eyes.
How many did you submit?
(Eye contact of the truth)
- Okay.
- Did you submit potatoes?
- Of course.
- Just submit all of them.
My briefcase is empty.
- You can't boil them at home.
- They will be a burden.
(Rolling)
Why did you do that?
Hey.
You said you submitted all.
Why are potatoes rolling around?
(The sound of guilty conscience)
Seriously.
You said you submitted all.
Why are potatoes rolling around?
(The man with guilty conscience
collects potatoes.)
It's hot in here.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
The 1st and 2nd rounds
left me with many scars.
(Team Se Chan finishes
submitting potatoes.)
So Min, please go first.
Hey.
So Min, don't get swayed.
- Okay.
- Follow the strategy.
- I will do that.
- Do what you promised...
- and we will win.
- Okay.
(All members of Team Haha
finish submitting potatoes.)
There is someone
who has more potatoes, right?
- If we are lucky,
- I am sure everyone was torn.
- we will win again.
- We could take a win.
With how many potatoes?
With how many potatoes will we win?
Tasty potatoes.
(He gives a strange answer.)
You should give me a number.
You are good at mathematics.
- It will be a tasty win.
- Tasty?
Yes. It will be a tasty win.
You finished submitting potatoes.
- Okay. It's time.
- It's time. Let's go.
I will reveal the totals
for Round Three.
- In this round, Team Haha...
- Okay.
- submitted a total of...
- There should be four.
Did they submit four?
Four potatoes.
So Min submitted a potato.
(Ji Hyo submitted 2,
So Min and Jong Kook submitted 1.)
- So Min submitted a potato.
- I didn't think she would.
- Did you submit one each?
- Team Se Chan submitted...
- I told you to submit one.
- Okay.
a total...
(They agreed to submit all
except for 1 potato.)
- A total...
- I bet we won.
A total...
of zero potatoes.
(A total of 0 potatoes)
Team Se Chan lost
and acquired two penalty stickers.
- I knew it.
- Three and two.
You played all three rounds.
Team Haha got
two penalty stickers...
and Team Se Chan got
three penalty stickers.
Three? We have two.
(Which members will get
the stickers?)
Jae Suk should take some stickers.
Jae Suk won't get a penalty.
Team Haha, check
the remaining number of potatoes.
The one with the fewest potatoes
will take two stickers.
- Is it me?
- Let's count.
I have eight potatoes.
I have six potatoes.
I have nine potatoes.
I have five potatoes.
- Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo has the fewest.
- You had ten potatoes too.
(Ji Hyo)
- You know,
- You are cool.
Ji Hyo did all the work.
Team Se Chan has
three penalty stickers.
Three, right?
- Suk Jin...
- Jae Suk.
I have ten potatoes.
Two, four, six...
(How many potatoes
does Suk Jin have?)
- All right.
- You got quite a lot.
- I bet he does.
- He had a lot.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
(Either Se Chan or Suk Jin
will receive the penalty.)
(How many potatoes
does Suk Jin have?)
It's him who took 13 potatoes.
I have 12.
Two, four, six, eight, and ten.
- It's him who took 13 potatoes.
- Two, four, six, eight, and ten.
He got nine.
- How many?
- I have nine.
(Se Chan 9, Jae Suk 10,
Suk Jin 12)
- That was so close.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
He has zero stickers.
- My goodness.
- This is unbelievable.
He didn't get any stickers.
So the four-week-long
penalty race is over.
Will Se Chan get the penalty?
Yang Se Chan got seven stickers,
so he will get the penalty.
Oh, no. Se Chan.
- And?
- Jae Suk with no sticker...
- is exempted from the penalty.
- This is ridiculous.
- Darn it.
- I can't believe this.
How is this possible?
So he's exempted?
- We're in trouble.
- I should've picked 13 potatoes.
We should've given him
one sticker last week.
Who will watch Running Man?
He should get the penalty.
We will decide the penalty and
the member to get it next week.
I will announce
the proposed penalties then.
What matters is
what the proposed penalties are.
So Jae Suk is exempted
from the penalty, right?
I'm exempted.
(Panning for gold
at a stream in Gangwon)
(Riding a sky-glider in the sky)
(Upgraded water jump)
(A bike that runs in the sky)
(The final list will be complete
with the viewers' opinions.)
(We will wait for your opinions
about the penalty.)
Please open number one first.
Let me open it.
What are the sky bridge
and flying swing?
You should go to Yeosu...
- Yeosu?
- to get this penalty.
- Yes. You'll go high up.
And you will cross a bridge
in the air with a rope.
- I know what it is.
- It's like the L tower.
How would we go
all the way to Yeosu?
(Sky bridge and flying swing)
And you will see
the flying swing up there.
The two members will ride
the swing together.
My gosh. I can't do that.
(Sky bridge and flying swing)
(How would we go
all the way to Yeosu?)
And it's the last day
of the long holiday season.
- The traffic...
- On your way back...
- It will be terrible.
- It will be tough.
Gosh, I can't do this.
- What's next?
- I just can't.
This is crazy.
- This is not right.
- Don't be ridiculous.
(Cleaning the windows
of the SBS building?)
Hey, I like this one.
- This isn't right.
- I like this.
- It will end soon.
- It's our viewers' idea.
Do we go down on a machine?
Yes, you will be hanging
outside the window.
- How? With a rope?
- Don't be absurd.
They have a machine, right?
You might die. It's really scary.
- We did it before.
- Seriously.
- This is better.
- We tried it before.
(You might die. It's really scary.)
(This is better.)
- I think...
- This is the best one.
- This is the best one among these.
- That's better.
- I can't do this.
- But this one is...
You just say that
because you're not doing it.
- I think this one is...
- That's better.
This is the best thing to do
on the last day of the holidays.
You just need to go to Mok-dong.
Next.
Gosh, Jeju Island.
How would we go to Jeju Island?
- It takes a long time.
- I'd go to Jeju Island.
- I like this one though.
- This is better.
You will be a diver
and catch abalone and octopus.
- I like this one.
- I want to go to Jeju Island.
- This is good.
- Then you go.
- Me?
- You should go.
- No.
- All right then.
The penalty and the member
to get it will be decided next week.
- Okay.
- My goodness.
(Next week)
(There are 7 penalties.)
(And one spot is left.)
(The madman has nothing to lose.)
(And the rest of them
don't want to join him.)
(They will be deciding
the member to get the penalty!)
(Who's the unfortunate member
who will share pain with Se Chan?)
(I'll see you two there.)
(And a few days later...)
(Se Chan drives a convertible car
with someone.)
(I can go anywhere
if I have some romance.)
(He also enjoys
all sorts of delicacies...)
(and a luxurious yacht trip.)
To the penalty!
(Are you here to have fun?)
(Laughing)
(This is getting strange.)
(What's all this?)
(I'm sure
the other members can't do this.)
This is no joke.
(My goodness.
I'm getting motion-sick.)
Oh, no!
(Going crazy)
(The member to get the strange
penalty will be revealed next week.)
(Anyway, The Penalty Goes To...)