(The center of the global economy,
Wall Street)
(On the outskirts of Wall Street,)
(there's RM Investment
and Securities for Koreans.)
(Running Stock
Investment Club is here.)
Okay.
Let's go.
- This is nice.
- It's a perfect day to invest.
- My gosh.
- My goodness.
- Hey, Michael.
- Hi.
- Michael.
- Long time no see.
- Hi.
- Do you even know who he is?
- Are you from Hong Kong?
- Yes.
- Hi.
- It's been a while, Michael.
(Welcome to RM
Investment and Securities)
(This place is...)
- You said it would go up.
- You were sure of it.
You told me it would go up.
(Great sums of money change
hands in the blink of an eye.)
(Watch the global economy closely
with your every nerve bristled up.)
Use your phone.
This is why we have a phone.
Hello?
I'm sorry, sir.
Yes.
I'm sure it will soar next month.
Okay. Bye.
- Hi.
- Long time no see.
It's been so long.
I haven't seen him for a while.
Hey, James.
Hi.
(Chris and Sam, not James)
- This is like Wall Street.
- Long time no see.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- You working out?
- Yes.
- Good.
Hey, this is John.
I know him. Nice to meet you.
- They're all very annoying.
- Nice to meet you.
My name is So Min.
- Sorry?
- So Min.
Alex.
- Alex?
- My name is Young Ji.
- Young Ji?
- Yes, Young Ji.
- I see.
- All right. Investors.
- Yes.
Has it begun?
We're finally here.
We're here. It was a long flight.
After a long flight,
you finally arrived.
Flying in economy was darn hard.
- Finally, we are...
- It was darn hard.
Come on. Speak more elegantly.
- Just say you're very tired.
Now that
all the global losers are here...
(The global small investors arrived
safely.)
Are you a cowboy?
- You punk.
- No.
- He's dressed as Tae Jin Ah.
He rode all the way here on a horse.
He was very fast.
I'm an investor from Texas.
- He's like a tourist in Disneyland.
- From Texas.
- You know him, right?
- I'm sorry, but...
He's a stock market tycoon.
Mr. Lim Ha Ryong is here.
(Mr. Ji Ha Ryong)
- No, you're wrong.
- Come on, Mr. Tae Jin Ah.
- He's Waiter Song Ji Hyo.
- You look different in that hat.
- Gosh. What's this?
- Waiter Song Ji Hyo?
- He's Waiter Song Ji Hyo.
- Waiter Song!
- Don't be ridiculous.
- He has a name tag.
- Why am I a waiter?
- You're Waiter Song Ji Hyo.
- This is New York fashion style.
- Hey, I'd like to pick up my purse.
I'm going home now.
Where's my purse?
- Can I get a beer, please?
- Excuse me.
Are you
from a funeral service company?
- I'm Sandra.
- Okay. Sandra?
- Yes. I'm Sandra.
- Sandra?
You see, whenever we have
an episode related to economics,
you guys wear glasses.
And I don't like it.
- It makes me look intelligent.
- I understand that, but...
You guys wear glasses whenever it's
about studying or economics.
- How about this?
- It makes us look smart.
What do think about having a pen
in the chest pocket?
Isn't this the worst?
He's right.
All of you are wearing glasses.
Do you just dress like a thug...
regardless of the theme
of an episode?
- Exactly. He's dressed like a thug.
- How dare you call me a thug?
I'm not dressed like a thug.
- Sae Ho looks nice.
- Indeed.
- Is he on "You Quiz on the Block?"
- "You quiz?"
- You quiz?
- Step by step
"You quiz?"
- My fashion style? You quiz?
- Are you a used car dealer?
- I do everything that's productive.
- I see.
- Yes, ask me anything.
- Do you sell used cars too?
- I know someone in that field.
- He looks like a used car dealer.
- He's hilarious.
- You will start investing now...
- with seed money of 500 dollars.
- We'll get 500 dollars?
- Good, 500,000 dollars?
- Let's get this started.
We'll use Korean won.
- We have 500,000 dollars.
- It's worth 500 dollars.
I'll just think
that I have 500,000 dollars.
Invest the given money in stocks
for nine years...
from 2014 to 2022
to grow your assets.
Those are perfect years.
- Do you know much about stocks?
- Of course, I do.
We'll reveal the stock prices
of ten American companies.
Just as we did last time,
these are real companies,
and the stock prices are
based on real records.
- Okay.
- This is...
- You see...
- My heart is pounding already.
The only company I know is Tesla.
Also, although we won't tell you
the names of the ten companies.
But you all know
at least eight of them.
- Really?
- Are they that famous?
- They must be famous companies.
- They're good at this.
You have to predict the prices...
based on the social
and cultural issues in the year.
That's the key point.
Twenty minutes in the real world
equals one year in the simulation.
- Got it.
- You have to buy information...
and make investments
within 20 minutes.
When the bell rings,
we'll reveal the prices.
- Right. I remember that.
- Got it.
- It was thrilling.
- Yes.
Also, we'll give you the points...
- you earned last week.
- Okay.
Last time, we had a mission
once every three years, right?
- Yes. That's good.
- This time, there'll be no mission.
So you need to use
your points wisely.
- That's simple.
- You'll use it for ten years.
- That's right.
- I like that.
- I'll announce your points.
- Okay.
Jong Kook placed first...
- with 24 points.
- Really?
So Min and Jae Suk were tied
for second place.
- Okay.
- No way.
And Se Chan placed last
with eight points.
- How many points do I have?
- Eight points.
- What?
- I feel bad for Se Chan.
There are
three information exchange offices...
in the hallway over there.
You can visit any of them
to get information.
- I see.
- Good.
You can get level 1 information
with 1 point,
level 2 information with 3 points,
and level 3 information
with 7 points.
- Level three information?
- Seven points?
The level one information
provides...
(The content
of the level one information is...)
a piece of information
from that year written in English.
(Information from the year
written in English)
- Written in English?
- How are we...
- One-point information has...
- In English?
a news headline about the company
written in English.
- It sounds like a good deal.
- That's right.
Although it doesn't tell you
whether it will go up or down,
- it gives you a hint.
- A news headline?
Next, three-point information has...
the same news headline
written in Korean.
- Oh, three-point information?
- Yes.
And seven-point information has...
the same information
written in Korean, and tells you...
Information on the price?
- if the price will go up or down.
- Really?
- Okay.
- That's the best one, obviously.
- I'll buy it and invest all I have.
- But...
it doesn't tell you how much
the price will go up or down.
- I understand.
- It only tells us if it'll go up.
Whether the price will
go up or down.
As soon as we reveal
the stock prices of 2014...
and the time in the calendar starts
to pass, you may begin.
- Okay.
- Got it.
Kim Yoona from South Korea won
a silver medal.
- And shoot!
- Shoot!
Goal!
Pope Francis's visit to Korea...
The fear of Ebola, the fatal virus,
has spread across the world...
For the fourth time, ISIS...
The protests in Hong Kong...
- are heating up every day.
- They're continuing the protest,
occupying the central area.
We'll announce the stock prices now.
Reveal the companies
and the stock prices.
(Stock Market of 2014,
A IT: 28 dollars, B IT 33 dollars,)
(C Automobiles: 11 dollars,
D Automobiles: 50 dollars,)
(E Biotechnology: 15 dollars,
F Biotechnology: 82.5 dollars,)
(G Fashion: 33 dollars,
H Sports: 33 dollars,)
(I Media: 49.5 dollars,
J Airlines: 28 dollars)
(Stock Market of 2014)
I think I know all these companies.
- The IT companies...
- Are the prices...
- converted to Korean won?
- Yes.
- I don't know any of them.
- I'll just have to follow my guts.
- I have no idea.
- You know all of these companies.
- That's the whole point.
- But I have no idea.
- If you know...
- The IT companies...
- We hid the names intentionally.
- Of course.
You can guess the companies
easily with the information on them.
- Those are the actual prices.
- Yes.
- Do you remember the prices?
- Yes, of course.
Is F Biotechnology Ferrari?
No, that letter has nothing to do
with the company name.
It's not the initial
of the company name.
- J Airlines must be Boeing.
- Is Tesla on the list?
Tesla is the only company I know.
Tesla is on the list.
- Is it?
- Really?
- I think it is.
- I Media.
- Tesla shares weren't expensive.
- Was it worth nine dollars...
- It wasn't so expensive, right?
- No, it wasn't.
I'll invest in the company in 2017.
- I'll invest everything I have.
- Really?
- In 2017,
- You'll invest everything?
I'll invest in C Automobiles
or D Automobiles.
- You mean, Tesla?
- Yes, Tesla. Back then...
Which one is Tesla? C or D?
I think it's C.
It must be C. It almost failed once.
- It could be C.
- For example...
(They will start making investments
for a year.)
Let's go.
Hold on. I think
I should get some information first.
We can go to get information now,
right?
- Do we have 20 minutes?
- Can we go to get information now?
You have 20 minutes.
Time is passing.
- I'll go and get some information.
- You should spend it wisely.
- Everyone is getting busy.
- I'll be right back.
So Min, stop walking like a model
because you're dressed like that.
Come on. It's strange.
(She walks around the office,
immersed in her character.)
What did you say?
- Okay. Let's go.
- She's walking arrogantly.
(The small investors are going to
the information exchange offices.)
- Which office gives which level?
- We're here.
I can decide in there? I see. Okay.
I'm going in now.
(Surprised)
- They're foreigners.
- Foreigners?
What is this?
Why are they foreigners?
Se Chan.
Hi.
- What's going on?
- I was surprised too.
This is not right.
Why are they all foreigners?
- Are they all foreigners?
- Sorry. See you.
(The arrogant investor said goodbye
hastily as well.)
- This is bad.
- Did you get information, So Min?
No, they're all foreigners.
- Why are they all foreigners?
- They're all foreigners.
Where is Information Exchange?
Why are they foreigners?
I don't speak English.
Why did they bring foreigners?
- Do we have to speak English?
- Yes.
(Haha took up his courage to enter.)
- Hi.
- Hello. Welcome.
- Have a seat.
- Yes. Long time, no see.
- Long time, no see.
- Yes.
Tom?
- Alex.
- Alex? Yes.
Just kidding.
- How have you been?
- What?
- Well... Just...
Well... All... The same day...
- Investments doing good?
- Sorry?
Investments doing okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
- Okay.
(The Wall Street trader tries to
figure out what he means.)
How can I help you?
(Level 1 and 2: Simple information,
Level 3: Specific information)
C...
C Car.
It's 1 point
for the level 1 information, right?
I'll use one point.
Do you want level one?
Yes, C Automobiles.
(An article about the company
in English will be revealed.)
Your first hint.
"C Automobiles manufacturer
announced that it would recall..."
"their vehicles having been..."
"complained for
faulty-devices issue."
- "Issue?" I see.
- Yes, a problem.
(C Automobiles announced a recall
due to a faulty-devices issue.)
- "Recall?"
- "Recall."
Call again.
Yes, that's right.
Isn't it a good thing?
Very good?
I don't know.
(You have to interpret the hint
on your own.)
"Having been complained..."
Right. "Complained."
(He found a familiar word.)
Too much complaining.
Oh, I see. Okay.
The people in high positions
decided to recall the product.
And people made complaints.
- Okay. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Good luck. All right.
- Thanks for the good hint.
Thank you. See you.
- Hi.
- Yes, please do.
This is my office.
My name is Sandra Jeon.
- Sandra Jeon?
- Yes.
That's funny. My name is John.
- John?
- Yes.
- We have the same name?
- John and Jeon.
- Yes.
(It's good to see you, my friend.)
I'd like to get the level three
information on C Automobiles.
- Seven points, right?
- Seven points will be deducted.
- Yes.
- This will be a tough one, right?
So you're...
Oh, this is a Korean one.
Can you read it?
No, I can't speak Korean.
- "Jadongcha."
- "C Automobiles..."
"announced that it would recall..."
Oh, okay. I don't know.
- It's too fast.
- Difficult?
"Jangchi."
But this question is for you.
It's not for me.
Oh, sorry.
He's speaking too fast.
"Vehicles having been complained
for faulty-devices issue."
"Thanks to C Automobiles' proactive
approach, the stock price rises."
(Level three information
on C Automobiles)
(The stock price
of C Automobiles goes up?)
So the price goes up.
Due to a flaw in the mechanism?
"Having been complained..."
Right. "Complained."
They recalled their vehicles,
and there were complaints.
(Level three information
on C Automobiles)
(The stock price
of C Automobiles goes up!)
- You are handsome.
- Thank you. You are very pretty.
- Thank you so much.
- Yes.
Passing compliments.
- I want to check it.
- You punk.
- You're disappointing me.
- I'm serious.
(She walks back full of confidence.)
Just tell me the item.
- C Automobiles.
- Tell me what you saw.
(Jeon So Min's account balance)
I'll spend 500 dollars
on C Automobiles.
(She puts all her money on
C Automobiles with the information.)
- Hello.
- What?
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
- Hi. What is your name?
What's your name?
- David.
- David?
- Yes, David.
- Suddenly, David?
- Oh, I see.
My name is Robin.
Robin Williams?
- Yes. Of course.
- Robin Williams?
- Yes. Same.
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
- Good. He's dead.
Oh, I didn't know.
- Are you sure?
- I'm a fan of his.
- Are you a fan? Me too.
- Yes. I'm sad.
Me too. He was amazing.
- An amazing comedian.
- Amazing.
Are you amazing too?
Maybe...
In the stock market? Amazing.
- Really? Me too.
- Yes.
- You too?
- Are you an expert?
- Yes. I'm professional.
Really.
- Why are you laughing?
- He speaks Korean.
Why are you laughing?
(Flustered)
I want E Biotechnology.
E Biotechnology. Level One.
- I'll have Level One Information.
- Okay.
- "E Biotechnology..."
- Yes.
"published its Earning Surprise."
(E Biotechnology
published its Earning Surprise.)
Earning Surprise?
- Please... One more.
- Thank you.
Here you go. "E Biotechnology
published its Earning Surprise."
"Published."
Published? Public?
"Its Earning Surprise."
Earning Surprise is...
bad news, right?
- It could be bad news.
- Bad news. Earning Surprise.
- I feel it. It's like "Wow!."
- It's like "Wow!"
- Yes.
- Earning Surprise.
Yes. So it's good or bad.
Published. What does publish mean?
(Impressed)
Are you making fun of me?
Published.
- Nice to meet you.
- Step into my office.
- Michael?
- Jordan.
- Jordan?
- Michael Jordan. John.
- Jordan? I see.
- Jeon.
- Se Chan.
- Se Chan?
Yes. I'm Yang Se Chan.
- Okay.
- My boyfriend.
She's a friend.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Give me good information.
Okay. I will give you
the best information.
Yes. And...
- IT.
- IT? Which IT?
- A.
- A IT? Can we do that?
Is A IT good?
A IT? They are all good.
- No good?
- They are all good.
The good?
Let me read it out loud for you.
"A IT announced that
they would newly provide..."
"the streaming TV service."
TV service?
- Yes. Would you like to read it?
- Yes.
There you go.
They started a new service?
"This IT company started
a TV service."
Good. Nice information?
Nice information?
Do you like TV services?
TV services? Yes.
Then it's nice to you.
"Nice to you?"
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes. Nice to meet you too.
(Suddenly he's glad to meet him.)
- TV service, man.
- TV service.
- Netflix?
- Maybe. I mean...
- Maybe?
- I just don't know.
Amazon?
(Surprised)
Graph. Hey.
- The graph of A IT...
- Yes?
The graph goes up or down?
Well, I don't have a graph.
So I don't know. If it's up or down.
I can't tell you.
- Hey. Jordan.
- Yes.
Is your condition up or down?
- Me?
- Yes.
I'm all over the place.
I can't decide if I'm up or down.
Gosh, this is so hard. Okay.
Jae Suk, I didn't speak
a word of English.
(Stock Market of 2014)
- I think B IT is...
- This is a fraud.
I bet there will be
a dramatic turnaround.
I should get the information
about B IT.
Secret information.
Oh, my goodness.
"Oh, my goodness?"
- What was that?
- Get out.
- What? Oh, my goodness?
- What was that?
- Get out.
"Decided to..."
They decided... "To partner."
"With Google, the leading company."
I see. "Leading."
(The hint about B IT has
some words that sound promising.)
- Okay.
- Winning.
- You are handsome and smart.
- No.
(Is this information
a favorable factor?)
And a rich man.
Okay.
(Jae Suk goes into the next room.)
- Hi. Welcome.
- Yes.
What would you like to know?
- What kind of information?
- B IT.
- B IT? Okay.
- Yes.
What level would you like?
Seven.
- Seven coins.
- Seven. Okay.
Yes.
(B IT partnered with G company,
the leading US portal site...)
(for exposure to search engines
and had their stock price increase.)
- Is it good information?
- Good. So...
- Amazing?
- Yes, amazing.
- Are you happy?
- Yes.
- I'm very happy.
- That's good.
Okay, Robin. See you.
- Nice to meet you.
- All right.
I need to hide this.
(Yoo Jae Suk's account balance)
I'll invest in B IT.
(He invests
half of his money in B IT.)
I should be a man about this.
I'll go all-in on B IT.
- This is nerve-wracking.
- I'll invest all in B IT.
I bet H Sports is Under Armour.
- John, long time no see.
- Hey. Come on in.
- Yes. We're here.
- Yes.
I'm interested in sports.
- Okay.
- H.
Yes, there's a space...
"H Sports to Model Stephen Curry."
I see. Okay.
(It's good news that they signed
a contract with Stephen Curry.)
- So good.
- You know about sports?
It's done.
Curry?
"To Model Stephen Curry."
(Jong Kook gets
the same information.)
My goodness.
(Now they know
what H Sports exactly is.)
(And there's someone eavesdropping.)
(The investor from Texas)
Yes!
Okay.
Okay. Got it.
(Yoo Jae Suk's account balance)
I'll put half of my money
into H Sports.
(He invests half of his money
in H Sports.)
Yes. Sell them all.
Half in B IT.
And the other half in H Sports.
(Jong Kook buys the same stocks.)
(And there's someone
who's eavesdropping on him.)
First, 33 dollars...
B IT...
and the rest on H Sports.
- It's right there.
- I'll go get some information.
- You can't do that.
- Okay.
Hi.
- Hello. Welcome.
- My name is Se Chan.
Se Chan, nice to meet you.
- What's your name?
- My name is Robin.
- Romance?
- Yes.
- Wow, Romance? Sounds good.
- So romantic.
- Good?
- Yes.
Give me information.
What kind of information
would you like?
- J.
- J company?
(J Airlines entered the
registry of S and P 500 Index.)
"Entered the registry
of S and P 500 Index."
Five hundred?
"S and P 500."
(J Airlines entered the
registry of S and P 500 Index.)
- What do you think?
- Index?
Yes. Do you understand?
Index. S and P. Five hundred?
S and P.
- Five hundred.
- Entered.
- Angel?
Enter?
I don't know what it means.
- I don't understand any word.
- Entered.
(The black thing is letters,
and the white thing is paper.)
Index...
Five hundred. Index.
- Jong Kook.
- This isn't good?
Jong Kook, what does index mean?
What is index?
An index is the thing you use
instead of a gas stove.
That's an induction heater.
That's not it.
- Tell me what it is.
- Index?
- That's kitchen furniture.
- What's an index?
- Index is like a gas stove.
- It's kitchen furniture.
You know what it is.
What is an index?
"The registry of S and P 500 Index."
(Investor Ha got the same hint.)
- In 2015.
- What's S and P?
Anyway, is it good news?
Maybe.
I'll buy ten stocks of H Sports.
(He follows his hunch
and invests in H Sports.)
Then I'll invest
the rest in J Airlines.
- Let's go.
- J Airlines.
(Se Chan invests all his money
in J Airlines...)
(with faith in the index.)
It looks really nice.
You're not supposed to see this.
- No?
- You shouldn't look at mine.
- Sae Ho, you can't see this.
- I didn't see it. I'm already done.
- You won't see it, will you?
- I'm finished too.
- Get lost.
- Where did you invest?
- Get lost?
- I... Are you done?
- Yes.
- I invested in three companies.
- Three companies?
- Are you done?
- Can I say it?
- Which information did you get?
- What information did you get?
- Is it okay to tell him?
- Just tell me one thing.
- I can't.
- Only one thing.
- I'm not supposed to say it.
So Min, did you
make your investment?
- So Min is over there.
- So Min is there.
I'm sorry.
I just talked to So Min.
- Gosh, this is hard.
- Are you done?
- It's chilly in here.
- It will be announced now.
Let's do this, Ha Dong Hoon.
Let's go.
Gosh, I'm nervous.
I want to make it big.
We will make it big.
Please.
Gosh, this is really...
This isn't a good time
to invest in automobile companies.
- Automobile companies will be...
- I think...
- in 2017...
- you should get on my good side.
- Why?
- I know exactly...
how the stock prices of Tesla go.
- You do?
- Yes.
Then invest your own money
and be rich.
I'll do that.
Don't ask me for advice.
I won't.
I can't wait to watch
the match between you two.
- He's just...
- He's totally...
Our salaries are totally different
on Wall Street.
Is that so?
- My bonus...
- Do you work on Wall Street?
I do work on Wall Street.
He's just at his in-laws' house.
Don't be ridiculous.
- Last year...
- Honestly, I'm not sure.
- It's the 28th.
(The stock price of 2015
will soon be revealed.)
My heart is thumping.
- Here we go.
- White snow falls
(Which stocks will bring joy
to the investors?)
Make me happy just this once.
(Which stocks will bring joy
to the investors?)
- Here we go.
- Let's go!
- B IT.
All right.
Gosh, I just got the chills.
I doubt there will be
a big difference.
(Invested half in H Sports
and half in B IT)
- Guess who it's endorsing.
- Come on.
- Just this once.
- Let's go.
Let me be in the money.
- B IT.
- Come on.
(Haha and Se Chan invested
most of their money in J Airlines.)
Here are the stock prices for 2015!
(The stock prices are revealed.)
Plus 67 percent!
(Stock Market of 2015)
(B IT, H Sports, J Airlines)
(J Airlines: plus 100 percent)
No way!
I might just die!
Kill me already. This is crazy.
(H Sports, B IT: plus 67 percent)
Plus 67 percent.
- Plus 67 percent!
- Nice.
(H Sports, B IT: plus 67 percent)
Sae Ho, bring it in.
- No way.
- I might just die!
- Plus 67 percent.
- Kill me already. This is crazy.
What's with J Airlines?
(Haha and Se Chan
won big with J Airlines.)
- J Airlines
- No way.
- Gosh.
- I can't believe it.
Plus 100 percent.
Hey, excuse me.
- S and P.
- Okay.
Five hundred Index.
I love you, Robin!
Yes, come on.
Robin, I love you!
(Robin, make some noise!)
- S and P 500.
- You made my day.
- Very good.
- Yes.
Good. Yaman.
Boombastic!
Mine is only at a plus 20 percent.
(The others are bitter
even though they saw profit.)
I didn't earn a lot.
Only a 20 percent profit.
Darn it.
(Hur Young Ji's account balance:
685 dollars)
- H Sports is at plus 67 percent.
- Right.
- Is that all you bought?
- That and B IT.
- Good.
- This is all in?
Yes, I invested everything in them.
Jae Suk and I made
the same investment.
- Everything in B IT?
- Yes.
We made the exact same investment.
- What about you?
- But...
(Yoo Jae Suk's account balance:
830 dollars)
It sure is a joy.
How much do I currently have?
You're at plus 67 percent.
Plus 67 percent must put me...
near a million dollars.
Did you say 50? I meant 70.
- Amateurs!
- It is now...
- the year 2015.
- Guys, move over.
Let's do this.
What are your predictions
for H Sports this year?
- Let me see.
- You see...
Has a new year begun?
- Yes, just now.
- Already?
I didn't expect the IT company
to see that big of a dip.
- How much are you at?
- Hi.
- Is that iced Americano?
Yes, it is. If you want some coffee,
there is coffee over there.
Is there a coffee station?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Help yourself.
Stop striking up conversations
with those passing by.
You can't even probably end one.
How much is the coffee?
This one?
- If you want...
- Coffee price is going up.
Is it free?
Do you want to invest in coffee?
Free? The best coffee?
Thank you.
(Giggling)
Don't strike up conversations
if you can't end them properly.
Thank you.
(There's a newfound confidence
in Se Chan's English.)
Thank you.
Hello and welcome back.
Well, my friend...
- Is he good?
- Yes.
Your information made me a rich guy.
- Oh, yes.
- Yes, thank you.
- My information is so good.
- Thank you.
A IT, please.
- A IT?
- Yes.
Thank you. "A IT..."
"announced the releasement
of wireless earphones."
Earphones?
What is "release?"
(No way!)
(I know which company this is!)
Thank you.
Earphones. Gosh, A IT.
- Earphones.
- Do you love me?
Yes. How about a kiss?
- No? Okay.
- Dangerous.
Thank you. A IT.
A IT must be Apple.
Okay, thank you.
Earphones will be released.
Wireless earphones.
I will invest everything in A IT.
(He sold his J Airlines' stocks
to buy A IT's stocks.)
The bean sprouts. The phones.
A IT is Apple.
Please make sure
my investments are kept hidden.
I'm selling information!
- Here.
- The bottom three went up.
H, I, and J.
I learned new information,
so if you share what you know...
- Sure.
- It'll be perfect for us.
In 2017... It was in English,
but this single word
is a game changer.
- Here.
- But...
Haha, I'll make you rich.
- Suk Jin, you don't want in?
- No.
- Okay.
- What is it?
- What should I buy?
- Buy B IT's stocks.
- What?
- B IT.
- Are you sure?
B IT is Apple.
How do you know that B IT is Apple?
What listening device
did they release?
Wireless earphones?
Is that A IT or B IT?
B IT.
- B IT?
- Yes.
Wait. When did he pass away?
- Who?
- Its founder.
- That isn't important.
- Steve Jobs.
Just invest in it. Whatever.
- Young Ji.
- Did you go all-in?
Yes.
A diversified portfolio
is what we should build,
but we all have
a long way to go today.
We need to take risks,
fatten our wallets,
and then build
a diversified portfolio.
I would've believed you
had you not been talkative.
You talk too much.
That's why I don't believe you.
Darn it. Should I trust him?
B IT...
Hey, for the price of two points,
I'll share the information I have.
What do you mean?
I need these for myself.
How about one point?
This time around...
You can trust me.
So Min, for the price of one point,
I'll share my information.
Okay, thank you.
So Min, come this way.
Se Chan, me too.
- I want in.
- Okay.
Here you go. C Automobiles is Tesla.
Since that's the case,
you should go all-in.
- Isn't it too early?
- No, in 2015...
- Trust me.
- From what I know...
- I heard about C Automobiles and...
- You heard it too, right?
- It was parting ways with England.
- Right.
(So Min received information
on C Automobiles.)
(Level one information
on C Automobiles)
(What's this?)
(Young Ji received
the same information.)
Is Brexit a place?
(At the time, they didn't know
what Brexit was.)
- It was parting ways with England.
- Right.
- Brexit...
- You heard it in English.
- No, wait.
- You heard wrong.
It means that
they signed a contract.
- No, wait.
- You heard wrong.
(It's favorable news.)
- It was bad for the company.
- No, it was good.
The States and England
parting ways...
No, it's favorable news.
They now own an exclusive contract.
Trust me!
- It's good news.
- I heard it in English,
(Favorable news?)
I'll invest everything
in C Automobiles.
(So Min ends up
falling for Se Chan's lies.)
Se Chan, did you go all-in?
Yes. It's good news.
Really?
It saw a dip in stock price, right?
It'll need time to recover from it.
No way!
The fact that it was
published in the news says it all.
You'll see a result
the very next day.
This is driving me crazy.
(Se Chan manages to fool
So Min and now Young Ji.)
I'll invest everything I have
in C Automobiles.
(And just like that,
Se Chan fools three people.)
(I Media: plus 44 percent)
I Media saw a sizable rise as well.
- Level 1 information on I Media.
- Level 1.
"Rumor has it that Disney,"
"a major media
entertainment company,"
"is taking over I Media."
(Level 1 information on I Media)
- This is I Media, right?
- Yes.
Gosh. "Rumor has it that..."
- "Rumor has it that..."
- My gosh.
(Level one information on I Media)
My gosh.
What does that mean?
(He responds like an Angeleno.)
There you go. Good.
Yes, M and A.
- M and A?
- Disney!
"A major media
entertainment company..."
"is taking over I Media."
- An M and A.
- That's right.
So Disney took over this company.
Yes! Okay, thank you.
(He also thinks
that it's good news.)
- Very good.
- Goodness.
(They both received information
on I Media.)
I can guess which companies
are which now.
I've been on a roll up until now.
Is it time to go big?
(Kim Jong Kook's account balance)
I'll invest everything I have
in I Media.
- I Media?
- Yes, I'm going all-in.
The winner is the one
who laughs at the very end.
I'll invest everything I have
in I Media.
- I Media?
- Yes.
It's December, so please hurry.
Let's go!
I just hope
I got it right once again.
Just so you know,
what I heard was huge.
What is it?
- Did you go for I Media?
- Yes.
- I Media?
- Yes, I Media.
- I went all-in.
- I Media?
- I Media.
- Really?
Just so you know,
(There's good news for I Media?)
- I Media.
- Yes?
I'm going all-in.
- Will you sell what you have?
- Yes, everything.
- That's right.
- What is Suk Jin up to?
You can't make an investment
after hearing that.
That's not fair.
- Once you make a purchase...
- This shouldn't be allowed.
What is he up to?
He made a purchase
after hearing us talk.
We shouldn't have said anything.
How is this allowed?
You only have yourselves to blame.
- I never coerced you to speak.
- But...
Should I drag him out of here?
You should watch what you say.
- Seriously?
- You shouldn't be so talkative.
- Unbelievable.
- How is it my fault?
To be able to hear isn't a crime.
- Was this your plan all along?
- Having ear holes is not a crime.
It's just that I might make
some other holes in your body.
You should blame
yourselves for talking.
It was his plan
to wait for someone to talk.
I could've done the same, you know.
- I could've done that too.
- The bell hasn't rung yet.
- Unbelievable.
- No way.
I have a feeling that
one will hit rock bottom.
- All right.
- Here we go.
Let's do this.
Come on!
(Jong Kook, Jae Suk, and Suk Jin
invested everything in I Media.)
(Se Chan invested everything
in A IT.)
(And they received false information
from Se Chan.)
- Come on.
- Show us.
- Please let me be lucky.
- Open.
(Stock Market of 2016,
B IT: minus 60 percent)
(C Automobiles: minus 17 percent,
I Media: plus 23 percent)
Open!
Yang Se Chan, that jerk.
(B IT: minus 60 percent)
- What happened?
- Hey.
- Gosh, seriously!
(The victims were completely
fooled by Se Chan's lie.)
What happened?
- You. Come here.
- What happened?
Take a look at that yourself!
(A IT: plus 11 percent)
I Media.
- We're the sole winners here.
- I Media.
(Jong Kook and Jae Suk
made profits through I Media.)
Gosh, Ji Seok Sam. My gosh.
Thank you.
(Suk Jin made profits thanks to
the last-minute cheating.)
It's so annoying!
Se Chan! This is so annoying!
Why are you blaming me?
(What is this?)
(Cho Sae Ho's account balance:
726 dollars)
(Haha's account balance:
418 dollars)
(He lost half of his money
because of Sae Ho's false info.)
It's your fault
for becoming clouded...
after hearing information
from someone else.
Why are you blaming me?
- You. Come here.
- My information was correct.
- My English...
- I'm going to kill you.
- My English is bad.
- So annoying!
Se Chan! This is so annoying!
How much did you invest?
I went all-in!
- It's not looking bad. Just wait.
- What do you mean?
That old fox.
- Why that...
- I'm not going to trust him again.
- Did you invest in I Media?
- Yes.
- Did you invest all your money?
- I went all-in on I Media.
- Gosh.
- Why?
(Suk Jin survived by picking up
information from others.)
- You're so sly.
- What about you?
You should figure out
whether my information...
is true or not.
I'm going to kill that jerk.
Ji Hyo, I went all-in
because I believed in Se Chan.
- Gosh, Se Chan!
- Se Chan.
Everyone is crying here.
(Everyone is crying here.)
Everyone is crying.
- You can't trust anyone...
- How can you trust...
- a sly guy like him?
- in Wall Street.
- How can you trust anyone?
- You lost your money too?
Otherwise, Suk Jin would have...
- Look! A homeless.
- She's...
She's gone broke.
(So Min ended up on the streets.)
Please be more strict.
What Suk Jin did
is considered cheating.
The bell hadn't rung then.
- Look here.
- Listen.
We thought we were wrapping up.
You can't change it last minute.
- There's no such rule.
- You stole the info from us.
I went all-in because they said
I Media would flourish.
- My gosh.
- This is incredible.
I made some money thanks to you.
- This is driving me crazy.
- I can't believe this can happen.
- It's 2016.
Hey, if investing in stocks
was that easy,
everyone would be rich.
This is why you can't sleep
when you invest in stocks.
- You are seriously...
- The economy was bad in 2016.
You told me info on B IT,
but you invested in A IT.
I'm going to kill you.
You're such a jerk.
You're a jerk. You...
You should end up in jail.
Follow me.
(Cho Sae Ho's account balance:
726 dollars)
(He lost his money when he didn't
even get false information.)
(He's bruised along
with his account balance.)
I don't know.
I lost maybe about half.
(He lost all the money he made
by investing in H Sports.)
I'm sorry to hear that.
It's okay.
I think the automobile industry
will flourish soon.
- But that's...
- No, it's too soon.
- Is it C or D?
- It's too soon.
- Everyone is...
- You have no idea.
dying to find out
which one is Tesla.
Jae Suk! Darn you.
"Darn you?"
(They're desperate to find
the initial for Tesla.)
Se Chan.
You told me C Automobiles is Tesla.
I'm not sure yet.
- Gosh, you!
- I'm not sure.
So Tesla is...
I know hot tips on Tesla.
From 2017...
I'll give you the info
if you come to me.
Can you be quiet?
Why would I be here
if I were to keep quiet?
I'll give you information on Tesla
from 2017 if you give me a coin.
- B IT.
- All right. B IT.
(Desperate Haha purchases
Level 1 info on B IT.)
- Level One for now.
- Level One? All right.
It's 2017. Newly inaugurated...
President Trump is active
on B IT's SNS.
(Level 1 info on B IT)
- Is that a good thing?
- I don't know.
Just tell me that much.
- I can't.
- Come on.
- Come on!
- I can't.
Is it good or bad?
(Asking for insider info
by bribing him with R coin)
Is Trump?
All right. So Running News 2017.
Newly inaugurated President Trump
is active on B IT's SNS.
- My gosh. Yes.
- Yes!
- Trump?
- Trump.
- Donald Trump?
Active on...
SNS.
- Yes.
- B IT?
- On B IT?
- On B IT.
- Wow, oh, my gosh.
- Yes.
- It's good news!
- This is...
- I don't know if it's good news.
- It's good news!
It could be good news.
This is crazy.
I got some crazy info.
(Information Exchange)
I figured out which company B IT is.
B IT.
It's Twitter.
(Suk Jin induced it
from the hint, "Trump's SNS.")
You're going all-in? Do you want me
to help just one last time?
- Go away!
- No, it'll be the last time.
- I'm serious.
- Go away! Don't mess with me.
Do you want to go all-in
on this company with me?
Let me help you.
I feel bad for you,
so let me give you help.
- No, thanks. I...
- Come here.
- I'll show you investing in it.
- No, I...
I will live my life...
- What's wrong with him?
- Mister, what's wrong?
Mister, what's wrong with you?
He bumped himself into the bench
while trying to help me.
- He bumped himself into it?
- He did.
Isn't he so funny?
He's dying to show off,
so he's all over the place.
- He's acting up, isn't he?
- He's going all over the place...
offering information.
He insists on sharing
the info he knows.
- I'm so embarrassed.
- Earlier,
he was saying...
that he'd share information
if we gave a coin to him.
(Suk Jin acted up and bluffed
that he knows info on Tesla.)
That's how stocks are like.
You never know what will happen
with stocks.
But I'll help you out this time.
Come here.
No one is following him.
Young Ji.
You can invest in the company
I invest in.
- Then show me.
- I'm seriously...
I need to see you investing in it.
- I'll start my investment.
- Okay.
- Don't tell anyone about it.
- Come here.
- Okay.
I'll go all-in on B IT.
For real?
Don't tell anyone.
I'm helping you out one last time.
(Suk Jin actually went
all-in on B IT.)
- Come.
- Really?
In return,
you should spread a rumor
that B IT won't do well.
- Okay.
- Hurry. All right?
Yes, I got it.
I'll sell all of them
and go all-in on B IT.
I'm going all-in on B IT.
Which one do you think is Tesla?
- C Automobiles or D Automobiles?
- Others are waiting.
(Other investors are still trying to
figure out which company is Tesla.)
- Right?
- C Automobiles.
- Level 2. Yes.
- Level 2?
(Ji Hyo purchases Level 2
information on C Automobiles.)
C Automobiles appoints a new CEO...
who transformed a large furniture
company into a global company.
He transformed
a large furniture company...
into a global company?
What does it mean?
C Automobiles...
Is it Tesla?
- No?
- I don't know.
- Please.
(It's vague information to confirm
C Automobiles as Tesla.)
I'll divide my investment...
into C and D Automobiles.
- You'll divide it? Are you sure?
- Yes.
They might
suddenly invest differently.
Is C Automobile doing well?
How do you know that?
(The hacker overheard
another piece of information.)
Is it Tesla?
I got the information.
What level?
Level Three?
- How well is it doing?
- Sorry?
- Well, that's...
(Suk Jin was tempted
by Ji Hyo's false information.)
- Okay?
- Oh, that's why you're rich.
- Yes.
- Yes, that's why you're rich.
C Automobiles.
(C Automobiles)
- You ready? Take a look.
- Yes. Thank you.
(Is the information Ji Hyo received
a good one or a bad one?)
(C Automobiles
appoints a new CEO...)
(who transformed a large furniture
company into a global company.)
(However, as he has no experience
in managing automobile companies,)
(the investors are withdrawing
their investment.)
(Their stock price falls.)
That's a lot of information.
Suk Jin, I have a question.
Suk Jin.
Did Tesla...
acquire any other companies?
Did they expand their business?
They have several businesses.
They're exploring Mars too.
What about it?
- Sorry?
- Why did you ask?
I just saw a piece of information
on it.
So is Tesla C or D Automobiles?
What is it? Is it C or D?
- So from the start, we should've...
- I think it's C Automobiles.
- You think it's C Automobiles?
- Yes.
From what I saw, it's C Automobiles.
- You think it's C Automobiles?
- Yes. It's C Automobiles.
Then its price will increase a lot
in 2017.
Then it must be C Automobiles.
(Se Chan encourages him to
invest in C Automobiles...)
(even though he knows
that its price will drop.)
I'll sell...
half of B IT's stocks.
(Ji Suk Jin's account balance)
And I'll invest in C Automobiles.
- All of it?
- Yes.
(Suk Jin ends up falling for it.)
I'll invest in D Automobiles.
(Se Chan goes all-in on D
Automobiles after fooling Suk Jin.)
I'll go all-in on D Automobiles.
- D Automobiles?
- Yes.
Gosh, I can't tell this time.
No, I'll invest
in one of the automobile companies.
I'll invest in B IT
and D Automobiles.
(He invests in B IT and
D Automobiles based on his hunches.)
E Biotechnology, please.
- E?
- E Biotechnology?
Running News 2017.
Trump wins
the Presidential Election.
Here you go!
(Level 1 info on E Biotechnology)
What do I do?
(Trump won the election?)
Trump...
- Are you happy?
- Yes.
(Sae Ho is sure that it's good news
after seeing the word, "win.")
- Are you happy?
- Yes.
- Oh, you know?
- Okay.
- I don't know, but...
I'm not sure. "Win?"
I'll buy 35 stocks...
of E Biotechnology.
Which one are you going to sell?
I'll sell everything else.
Will H Sports be a jackpot?
(Haha is still not over H Sports.)
- I'll go all-in on H Sports.
- H Sports?
(Haha's account balance)
I'm broke now.
I don't know how this will go.
Ji Hyo.
G Fashion.
Hold on.
(Get lost!)
How dare he try to con me.
Why would you act so cheap
in Wall Street?
That's the year Trump
became the president of the US.
(Yoo Jae Suk's account balance)
I'll invest in I Media.
(He invests in I Media again
based on what he knows.)
It's December, so please wrap up.
(December 21, 2016)
We're almost there!
- We're almost there.
- It's hot.
- A new year will dawn.
- The New Year's Bell will ring.
- Let's see!
- Since their prices dropped...
Isn't it about time they go up?
(Suk Jin invested in C Automobiles,
thinking it's Tesla.)
- Merry Christmas!
- Happy New Year!
- Feliz Navidad
Let's go!
Feliz Navidad
(The stock market in 2016
was down overall.)
(How will the stock market
be like in 2017?)
- It's the new year!
- Happy New Year!
- Make some noise!
- It's the new year!
The US stock market of 2017...
is open!
- E Biotechnology!
- I Media!
(Stock Market of 2017)
(E Biotechnology: plus 400 percent,
I Media: plus 100 percent)
(I Media: plus 100 percent)
- E Biotechnology!
- I Media went up by 100 percent?
- I Media!
- How did it go up by 100 percent?
(C Automobiles: minus 10 percent,
D Automoblies: plus 50 percent)
It's open!
(E Biotechnology Sae Ho invested in
went up by 400 percent.)
(E Biotechnology!)
(Dealer Cho hit the jackpot!)
I Media!
(Wailing)
F Biotechnology
went up by 400 percent?
E Biotechnology
(Cho Sae Ho's account balance:
3,500 dollars)
Four hundred percent?
- How did this happen?
- You made it?
- You punk!
- Is it a good thing or a bad thing?
- He...
- It's a jackpot!
He told me that E Biotechnology's
price would drop.
Did you buy it or not?
You lost your money again.
Gosh, E Biotechnology...
(Haha's account balance:
225 dollars)
Is this for real? I have no info
on biotechnology at all.
You bought E Biotechnology.
Fifty percent isn't bad.
(Yang Se Chan's account balance:
1,518 dollars)
It's not bad.
C Automobiles' price dropped!
(Ji Suk Jin's account balance:
1,216.8 dollars)
Why did you lie to me?
I didn't. It was doing well.
Check out the amount of money
you earned in 2017,
and we'll begin a mission
where you can earn some points.
I told you!
- This is amazing!
- There is...
There's a beggar here.
- I should buy C Automobiles'.
- So Bal.
I told you to invest in I Media.
Everyone, you don't have to be
disappointed just yet.
The US stock market's boom
is just starting.
That's right. It's just starting.
The percentage of increase
will be much bigger from now.
- Of course.
- What we earned was chicken feed.
- These two over here...
- Did they go bankrupt?
- They're almost bankrupt.
- What happened?
What? You jerk!
- I'm sorry.
- Why...
- You're so mean.
- Please keep your manners.
- I really want to punch him now.
- It's infuriating, isn't it?
- I really trusted him.
- I really did too.
- He has no conscience at all.
- He's going to...
I thought he'd have a conscience,
at least.
Goodness.
We'll reveal the ranking of 2017.
Bring in the chart.
(Current Asset Ranking)
- Jae Suk.
- How did the bottom three...
end up there?
Young Ji, So Min, and Haha.
(The three gullible ones
are at the bottom.)
- Right.
- Whose information did you get?
- What happened to Seok Sam?
- Where is he?
- You were so...
- You bluffed so much.
- But he's...
- He bluffed so much, but...
Compared to how much he bluffed...
- His ranking is...
- He's in fifth place.
- What on earth...
- I'm in third place.
It hasn't even begun yet.
It's your last chance
to earn additional points.
It's a mission to train
to stay composed...
when you impulsively
want to buy or sell stocks.
It's called You Insulted Me.
You Insulted Me?
We'll pick a member,
and the rest of you should come up
with a sentence...
that will infuriate them
on the board.
All right.
The one who upset the selected
member the most gets three points.
The next 2 will get 2 points each.
You'll be understanding
even if it upsets you, right?
I can't assure that.
Jong Kook is the type...
who loses his temper sometimes.
It can be anything,
whether it be a nickname or such.
- We can even write a letter?
- It doesn't matter.
We can write a letter.
The first member is Jong Kook.
All right. I don't mind them
unless they're facts.
There are a few things...
- I can think of.
- Of course.
I don't mind unless they're facts.
Let me tell you this in advance.
I don't care unless they're facts.
I won't even look at it.
- You won't even look at it?
- Of course.
But I wrote a fact.
- Sure. That's only your opinion.
- You should add another one.
This is a fact. Wait. Let me add...
Jong Kook, you don't get upset
with things like this, right?
Of course not.
Tell him not to hit us.
- Of course not.
Those who want to go first,
go ahead.
- Should I go first?
- Sure.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes.
I can tell
what they're going to say.
You're horrible in soccer.
You know you're
a terrible soccer player, right?
Quit it. If you didn't have money,
they wouldn't let you join.
(If you didn't have money,
they wouldn't let you join.)
All right. I'll go next.
- Say it right away.
- I knew he'd say that.
So it doesn't affect me.
Do you actually like soccer?
- Doesn't it upset you?
- Not at all.
- Why?
- I knew they'd talk about soccer.
Why would you like soccer?
(His face is hardening.)
- Let me reveal mine too.
- They're all talking about soccer.
- It's about soccer, isn't it?
- You're a princess, aren't you?
You're worse than me in soccer.
(Princess Jong Kook
tries to stay composed.)
It doesn't affect me at all.
He's the worst celebrity
soccer player.
That's fine. It's quite funny.
- It's hilarious.
- Is it?
- The worst celebrity soccer player.
- It's hilarious.
Mine is really boring, to be honest.
- I saw it, and it's really boring.
- It's okay. Go ahead.
- Go ahead. Let's hear it.
- Go ahead.
Jong Kook, open your eyes.
Can you even see me?
That's intense.
It's quite offending.
- Is it?
- Yes, it is.
It's no fun but offending?
- That is...
- It's offending?
- His comment is offending?
- He was upset with ours.
He was upset with ours.
But that's a fact.
I'm sure he was upset
with our comments.
- Not at all.
- Pick them in the order...
- of the most offending ones.
- Of course.
- I'll say mine.
- It's Young Ji.
Jong Kook, you smell like
a chicken farm.
(I smell like a chicken farm?)
- She's good.
- That's a good one.
You're good.
- It's so offensive.
- She's the best at it.
That was a good one.
- Jong Kook.
- Good job.
He must've had
so much chicken breast.
- Young Ji.
- Young Ji, good one.
He smells like chicken?
- Young Ji is good.
- Like the smell of eggs.
She knows how to offend people.
It's not a fact.
Pick a member
who was most offensive.
That will be Young Ji.
Young Ji's was most offensive.
- What about second place?
- Second place...
You should skip the comments
on soccer.
The worst soccer player.
- The worst celebrity soccer player.
- No, not that one.
They wouldn't let you join
if you had no money.
Not at all. That was the worst one.
- You look upset.
- No, it didn't affect me at all.
But they'll really
not let you join...
- if you have no money.
- That's not true at all.
- You see? You're a princess, right?
- No, I'm not.
- Do you like soccer?
- That's not true.
- Why?
- But it's true.
It's true that you're bad at soccer.
- No. That's not true.
- I'm serious.
He's never seen me
play soccer properly.
- You sound upset already.
- No, not at all.
- You're a horrible soccer player.
- Not at all.
- I saw it last time.
- I'm fine because I know I'm good.
- No, I'm good at it.
- You play soccer like this.
- Like this.
- I'm good at it.
- You shot it to the wrong place.
- That's not true.
No, I shot it properly.
- You seem very upset.
- No, I'm right.
No. Not at all.
You should earn a lot
if you want to play soccer.
I already have plenty of money.
- I'm earning a lot already.
- You should earn a lot.
- He's so annoying.
- You should earn a lot...
- if you want to play soccer.
- I already have plenty of money.
You should pick second places now.
- He wouldn't look this way.
- Let me see.
- He wouldn't look at us.
- Hey.
- He's upset. He's clearly upset.
- I'm totally fine.
- You're clearly upset.
- Not at all.
If they were a pro, like
Lee Young Pyo, I'd be hurt.
- But they don't know soccer.
- But you're crossing your legs.
- He's very upset.
- Not at all.
- Yes, you are upset.
- We can feel it.
It's clear that you're upset.
I need to pick 2 members
for 2nd place, right?
I hate that comment.
"Open your eyes."
- You win second place.
- Me?
- Also...
- What do you mean?
- This is...
- He got mad because of us.
- I know.
Aren't you going to give points
to Young Ji's comment?
- I gave her 1st place.
- He gave her 1st place.
- She's in first place.
- He did? Okay.
- He's the worst.
- He gave her first place...
as soon as he started.
- As soon as he started.
- Oh, I see.
(He must've been confused
because of the chicken farm smell.)
I was so startled.
Next is Se Chan.
- It's my turn?
- Yes.
I'll be fine with them.
We need to focus on the points
that would offend Se Chan.
I don't know those points though.
This could become an issue,
so please edit it out
if it's inappropriate.
What is it? Is it that bad?
There's no such thing.
He's being ridiculous.
- I'm serious about this one.
- Try me.
You want me to go first?
- Haha, you go first.
- Let's see what it's about.
This actually happened.
Edit it out
if it's too inappropriate.
I got your permission.
You stole Dream's bicycle, right?
(You stole Dream's bicycle, right?)
- Gosh, that's...
- No, it actually happened.
- I have the footage.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Come on.
- You have the footage?
- You think I'd steal a kid's bike?
- Yes.
- It's the red one.
- You think I'm a bicycle thief?
- It's gone.
- That's ridiculous.
- I'm serious. It's really gone.
- That's nonsense.
- But this is...
- If I report it, you'd be arrested.
Mine is similar to his.
Let me read mine next.
You stole money
from my wallet earlier, right?
(You stole money
from my wallet earlier, right?)
- Why would you make me a thief?
- You stole my cash last week, no?
- Darn it! That's nonsense.
- You are...
- Why would you...
- You'll offend me with those?
- Why would you steal a bicycle?
- All right.
- Next.
- Can I go next?
- But I'm not sure if it's right.
- Go ahead.
I want to land a knee kick
on your teeth from time to time.
(I want to land a knee kick
on your teeth from time to time.)
- She's good.
- That's intense.
(She wants to push in his
protruding teeth by kicking them.)
- She's good.
- It's funnier because she said it.
- That's intense.
- Like this.
- Young Ji is intense.
- Are you a hate commenter?
- She's good with it.
- She's like a hate commenter.
It's infuriating.
Mine was weak compared to hers.
It's upsetting although it wasn't
directed at me.
That hurts.
She wants to kick his teeth...
What is that?
(A portrait of Se Chan)
- What is that?
- It looks just like him.
What's that? Why are my teeth...
Is that a potbelly or what?
At least she drew his eyes
like jewels.
- He has pretty eyes.
- They are like jewels.
His eyes are glistening.
- I have a double chin.
- The answer is Yang Se Chan.
Se Chan, you play golf diligently.
But it doesn't suit you.
(Jong Kook's hate comment is mild.)
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo.
If you think about it,
he isn't mean...
to people he cherishes.
- Jong Kook, don't you have...
- He treats me differently.
- much affection for me?
- Seriously.
- I can't believe you.
- He is serious about golf.
Please choose the winners.
Young Ji's comment places first.
Nothing beats that one.
Young Ji's comment.
Everyone acknowledges it.
Haha's comment places second.
Put it back.
- Jong Kook's comment.
- Okay.
- Thank goodness.
- Is the golf comment that annoying?
- It's golf.
- I can't believe it.
- You did it to win brownie points.
- This is ridiculous.
- I won fair and square.
- I am sensitive about it.
- Jong Kook pressured him.
- That shouldn't be allowed.
He didn't pressure me.
Up next is Jae Suk.
I will be objective.
Your body is so cute.
It's just like Dream's.
- Gosh.
- It's true.
You are a flippant man
with a hopeless face.
- You are uglier than me.
- My goodness.
(An attack on his looks
makes him lose his cool.)
- That's so aggravating.
- That's truly aggravating.
Up next is So Min.
So Min.
There is a group chatroom
without you.
(There is a group chatroom
without you.)
- This one is true.
- Really?
To be honest, we had a get-together
without you yesterday.
- Gosh.
- Are you serious?
No. It's a joke.
Throw a white handkerchief.
- Stop it.
- Give So Min...
- a white handkerchief.
- So Min is really angry.
- Shall we move on to Sae Ho?
- Sae Ho.
Why is everyone so intent
on making a comment about me?
I think your face got
athlete's foot.
You should wash up more.
(Athlete's foot on the face
will shock the academic circles.)
- What?
- What are you doing?
Why are you on the show
for two weeks?
He really felt that blow.
Hey. What's that?
What's that? Come on.
- It resembles you.
- Come on.
- It looks exactly like you.
- It resembles you.
- Sae Ho.
- So Min drew well.
- Suk Jin is last.
- Okay.
You smell like grandpa
when you walk by.
(It's an attack
on his age and smell.)
You little...
Suk Jin! What's wrong?
That was bound to bring swear words.
I was supposed to anger you.
Suk Jin really became angry.
(Ta-da)
(She imagined how
Suk Jin would look in the future.)
- Where is his hair?
- Hey.
Why did you make me bald?
- Where is his hair?
- I have a lot of hair!
It's a secret
that he is losing hair.
We don't have time for this.
We need to hurry up and invest.
The year is 2017.
You will receive coins
at a new location.
That's good.
- Okay.
- That's good.
All right.
Shall we enjoy investing again?
(January 1st, 2017)
- Will I be able to get back up?
- All right. I got it.
(Sae Ho is currently 1st
in the asset ranking.)
This is where it gets tricky.
Let's just stay in the middle.
(Jong Kook goes straight
to acquire information.)
All right.
They will take a long time.
- Welcome back.
- Hi.
I will check out a hint of A IT.
- A IT.
- B is...
There you go. Oh, my gosh.
(A IT released
a new product package.)
If it was released to celebrate
the tenth anniversary...
Could it be...
Could it be iPhone?
Hold on. That means
this top item was released in 2008.
It's iPhone. Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
I know that iPhone came out in 2008.
I will use all of my assets
to purchase the A IT stocks.
Yes.
(He is certain that A IT is Apple.)
(Ji Hyo checks the information
on A IT as well.)
Is this Apple?
I have no idea.
Sorry. Thank you.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
- Let's work together again.
- Let's do that.
- Our common enemy is Se Chan.
- Yes.
We need to crush him.
- That's what I think.
- A IT is Apple.
(She shares that A IT is Apple.)
A IT. It isn't B IT.
Stop spreading false information.
Okay.
Sae Ho, can you move out of the way?
(Can you move out of the way?)
Are you bragging about your wealth
with your hands in your pocket?
I am in a bad condition,
so please be understanding.
Why are you in a bad condition?
I couldn't make people laugh
earlier.
- I couldn't do well.
- Don't get hung up on it.
Sae Ho, that's
what's funny about you.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I am glad.
- That's what's funny about you.
I couldn't badmouth people.
Should I invest
in E Biotechnology again?
This is the last round for me.
It will be over for me
if I don't make money.
How much money do you have left?
I have 200 dollars left.
In that case...
In 2019, 2020, and 2021,
the US stock market enjoyed a boom.
It's a matter of finding the stocks
that will skyrocket.
There is one company
everyone is looking for.
Everyone wants to know
which one is Tesla.
We don't know if it's
C Automobiles or D Automobiles.
(Tesla was at the center
of the US stock craze.)
(Is either C Automobiles
or D Automobiles Tesla?)
- My nickname is Jisla.
- What?
I applied for a car in 2017.
I am sorry,
but please move out of the way.
I am passing through.
I applied for a car in 2017,
so I know
all about Tesla's stock price.
I am sorry, but please tell that
to the person who asked.
I am talking to myself.
I applied for a car in 2017.
so I know how
the stock price changed then.
I know whether it's C Automobiles
or D Automobiles.
Excuse me.
What do you want to learn?
C Automobiles.
"President Trump decides
to impose additional tariffs..."
"on imported steel and aluminum
for the domestic economy."
Economy?
(C Automobiles, Level 1)
President Trump.
Domestic economy?
Domestic.
- Domestic.
This country.
Country.
- This is about the US.
- Yes.
The US economy.
Domestic is... This country.
Did Trump fly economy?
- Trump.
- Taxes.
- Taxi?
Domestic economy.
This is important. "Imported."
C Automobiles.
- Will you go all in?
- Yes.
It's the 15th.
(Is C Automobiles Tesla?)
Please wrap up.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Welcome back.
- Hi.
Last year was a miracle year.
- Really? What happened?
- Yes.
Plus 400 percent.
- Plus 400 percent?
- Plus 400 percent. Yes.
- I want to check one more thing.
- Okay.
E Biotechnology.
(He purchases
the level 1 information.)
"President Trump
imposes additional tariffs..."
"for the domestic economy."
(E Biotechnology, Level 1)
What is this?
- Is it good?
- Well, I don't know.
Which word are you talking about?
What's "additional tariffs?"
I don't know that one. I don't know.
(Additional tariffs)
(E Biotechnology, Level 1)
It seems like a decision
that helps the domestic economy.
I don't know.
Will the stock price rise again
for E Biotechnology?
Do you have any more money?
Information on E Biotechnology...
was about Trump doing something.
Wouldn't the stock price drop
for E Biotechnology now?
It might go up again.
- Really?
- Yes. It might go up again.
(It's hard to quit after a taste
of biotechnology stocks.)
- Hello.
I am looking for an SUV
I can use with my family.
You are here to see an SUV.
Please come this way.
- All right.
- Which one are you thinking?
- I talked to my family about it.
- We have various options.
We have everything from supercars.
You look like someone
who is in the know.
We have an incredible supercar
that just came in.
- Is that so?
- If it's for the family,
an SUV supercar will work well too.
I am a model for a used car company.
I am sorry.
I will have to buy a car there.
Why did you even come here?
I am sorry. I forgot.
- Give it some thought.
- Okay. I am sorry.
He wasted my time.
I want to purchase the A IT stocks.
A IT.
I will use all of my money
to purchase the A IT stocks.
(She is certain that it's Apple.)
I will purchase 20 shares
of E Biotechnology stocks.
I will use the rest
to invest in A IT stocks.
- A IT.
- That will be 30 shares.
Guys, I am feeling...
particularly generous right now.
If you want to succeed, come to me.
Okay. I am struggling so much.
How much money do you have?
I have a little over 300 dollars?
Will you trust me and follow me?
I know exactly what I am doing.
What will you invest in?
I will do what you do.
Will you trust me and follow me?
- Sure.
- I want to help you.
Okay.
I remember the stock price.
In 2017,
Tesla stocks cost about 70 dollars.
Don't lie.
You will change it in the end.
- No.
- Is it time to invest in it?
(D Automobiles' stock price
is close to 70 dollars.)
I will go all in on D Automobiles.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
All right.
I will use all of my money
to invest in D Automobiles.
- D Automobiles?
- Yes.
All right.
(Meanwhile,
Jae Suk heard something.)
What is it?
I will invest in B IT.
- Will you use all of the money?
- Yes. B IT.
(He thinks it's too early
to invest in automobiles.)
- I invested all of my money, right?
- Yes.
(He secretly invests
all of his money on B IT!)
Gosh.
(The long-term investor
of C Automobiles is in a daze.)
Jae Suk, what did you invest in?
(Jae Suk, what did you invest in?)
B IT.
Please take out half of the money
and invest in B IT.
(She copies Jae Suk
and invests in B IT.)
Please wrap up.
It's Christmas again.
It's Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
- Let's earn money one more time.
- Everyone.
Let's earn money one more time.
It's the end of the year.
It's December 25th.
- Please.
- Merry Christmas.
Please wrap up.
Maybe I made a mistake.
- I am nervous.
- If I fail again, I am done for.
- It will be bad if I fail.
- In 2017,
- I signed up...
- I hope I didn't make a mistake.
for a car.
Totally.
- Please.
- Please let me succeed.
- Go up.
- Let's go.
- Tesla.
Please.
Do you think it's Tesla?
- Let's go.
- Please.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo invested
almost all in A IT.)
- Please.
- Here we go.
Maybe I should've invested
more money.
(Jae Suk invested all money
in B IT secretly.)
- Please. This is my last chance.
- Here we go.
(Jisla is sure
about D Automobiles.)
Please. I invested all I had in it.
Suk Jin, I trust you.
- It's okay. I made my own decision.
- Good.
- The stock prices of 2018...
- So Min, I'm so nervous.
- Please. I trust you, Jae Suk.
- Please go up again.
- Let's go!
- Let's go... What?
- Okay! 67 percent, So Min.
(Stock Market of 2018)
- Gosh.
- Ji Hyo.
- I Media went up so much.
- C Automobiles went down again.
- Ji Hyo, what do we do?
- Darn.
Okay! 67 percent, So Min.
(B IT: plus 67 percent)
- I Media went up so much.
- C Automobiles went down again.
- Let's go... What?
- Okay! 67 percent.
(D Automobiles: minus 9 percent)
- Darn it.
- My gosh.
(D Automobiles that he assumed
to be Tesla fell.)
- I Media went up so much.
- C Automobiles went down again.
(D Automobiles: minus 9 percent)
- Darn it.
- So Min.
- Gosh.
- Ji Hyo.
(A IT: minus 13 percent,
E Biotechnology: minus 50 percent)
- It's okay.
- Sixty seven percent! Okay!
- How did it happen?
- That's right!
- That's right! Okay!
- I should've invested in I Media.
In what company did you invest?
Gosh, I should've invested
in I Media.
So Min.
I Media went up 100 percent.
- It went up 67 percent. Okay.
- Great.
I Media went up 100 percent?
(Haha lost again.)
- I didn't lose much.
- Good.
I Media? I should've invested in it.
(He made a profit
while the market was down.)
Okay.
The fluctuation is so big.
- I'll help you out.
- You must've lost 50 percent.
The stock market is down.
Gosh, E Biotechnology.
In what company did you invest?
Mine didn't go up either.
- Gosh, which one is it?
- You see...
- Which one is Tesla?
- I should never invest in stocks.
I realized that I should never
invest in stocks.
Why? What's wrong?
- I shouldn't...
- You pick a bad one.
I keep choosing the company
whose shares dropped sharply.
- All that I chose dropped.
- They all plummeted.
(Song Ji Hyo: 638 dollars,
Cho Sae ho: 2,323 dollars)
Gosh, I'm doomed. Darn it.
(As E Biotechnology dropped
50 percent, he lost a lot.)
I mean, I heard something about
President Trump. Why did it fall?
(I mean, I heard something about
President Trump. Why did it fall?)
Suk Jin, it said something about
President Trump. Why did it fall?
It must've been bad news.
But I can't...
I can't give up on A IT. I'm sure...
I heard from my friend
that it went back up.
- Are you sure about it?
- Sorry?
Are you sure about it now?
- I think it's D Automobiles.
- What?
This is our chance.
- I only understood "Trump."
- Suk Jin.
Let's go
and invest in D Automobiles.
All right.
Let's go with D Automobiles.
By the way, why did I Media
increase so much?
My, everyone seems so serious.
- Do you have a good feeling?
- That's it.
I have D Automobiles now, right?
I won't change anything.
- Will you keep it as it is?
- Yes.
I'll go all in on D Automobiles.
I'll use all my money
to purchase the A IT stocks.
- Suk Jin, I'll be here.
- Okay.
Here we go. Please.
Please.
This is driving me nuts.
- Let's go!
- Please.
- All right.
- Please!
The stock prices of 2019.
Reveal the prices.
(The stock prices of 2019 will be
revealed shortly.)
Gosh. Darn it.
What? Has it come out?
What is it? Suk Jin.
(A IT: plus 86 percent,
D Automobiles: minus 8 percent)
- Has it come out?
- It's A IT.
What is it? Suk Jin.
(A IT: plus 86 percent)
I should've invested in A IT.
(A IT increased by 86 percent.)
(D Automobiles: minus 8 percent)
(D Automobiles's stock price
went down again.)
What is it? Suk Jin.
(Haha is too afraid
to check the price.)
What did you purchase?
Did you purchase A IT's stocks?
(Cho Sae Ho's account balance:
4,306.5 dollars)
Sae Ho, you're incredible.
- It went up just as you said.
- Did he purchase A IT's stocks?
A IT.
I went all in on A IT.
I told you it was going to go up.
Suk Jin.
(D Automobiles dropped
for 2 years in a row.)
(He's swearing with his eyes.)
I guess it's not Tesla.
(I guess
D Automobiles is not Tesla.)
This is good.
I'm so excited!
(The patient investor is on a roll.)
- It must not be Tesla.
- And I...
There's no way
that's Tesla's stock price.
- It's never cost that much.
- Tesla...
That makes no sense.
- Jae Suk.
- I'm so excited!
- I should've invested in A IT.
- Jae Suk.
Shares of D Automobiles will go up.
For two years in a row.
It'll keep going up.
(D Automobiles' stock price will
go up this year?)
Can I sell my stocks?
Gosh. I have to recover my loss.
(Jae Suk is planning to get
reliable information.)
D Automobiles.
(He purchased
the level 3 information.)
(COVID-19 raised the expectations
about eco-friendly cars.)
(The stock price increased.)
(The stock price increased
due to the rising expectations.)
Tesla's stock price...
didn't keep going up.
The stock price of one of them will
skyrocket in 2019.
We could make a huge profit
from investing in that company.
- It's important to find it.
- We should find it.
(Then is this year a good time
to purchase its stocks?)
Thank you.
- Gosh. Tesla must have...
- Well...
I'd like to invest all my money
in D Automobiles.
(Jae Suk decided to invest
in D Automobiles!)
D Automobiles. Let's go with
something we can be sure about.
(Jae Suk purchased
43 shares of D Automobiles.)
I'll pull all out
and invest in D Automobiles.
(Se Chan used all his money
to purchase D Automobiles' shares.)
(He invested in D Automobiles
and suffered losses for 2 years.)
All that I pulled out of went up?
Haha, how much money do you have?
Me? I'm dirt broke.
I used all my coins.
I can't even get information.
(He exchanged his points for cash.
He's broke now.)
I should do something about it.
- This won't work.
- I just have a feeling.
Gosh. I'm so upset.
This is ridiculous.
I mean, it doesn't make sense.
I think
you gave me false information.
- D Automobiles.
- Two, four...
- Level one?
"COVID-19 outbreak."
(Level one information
on D Automobiles)
What does "outbreak" mean?
Break. Break out.
(Level one information
on D Automobiles)
Steak...
Outbreak Steakhouse?
- No.
Oh, "outbreak?"
(He must've lost his mind
as he lost his money.)
- Who's the CEO?
- I mean...
Maybe Tesla isn't one of them.
I don't think it is.
But this is...
What does this have to do with it?
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
Gosh, I'm so upset.
Which one is Tesla?
- Everyone is...
- When will Musk come out?
Everyone is trying to find
Elon Musk.
- Where on earth is Elon?
- Hey.
Hey.
Mr. Choi.
Is Tesla on the list or not?
Just tell me that.
Come on.
- Everyone is losing their mind.
- Where is Tesla?
- Just tell me if it's on the list.
- Everyone...
Everyone is talking about it.
Hey, Hyo Im.
Just tell me that.
Is Tesla on the list or not?
I don't think it's on the list.
Won't IT stocks keep rising?
- It's 2019.
- Yes.
COVID-19 broke out in that year.
- That's right.
- And that means...
After the outbreak of COVID-19,
media stocks rose.
(Hur Young Ji's account balance)
I'll use all my money
to invest in I Media.
(She went all in on I Media
hoping for a COVID-19 boost.)
Everyone,
I will give you a good tip.
At the end of 2019,
COVID-19 released.
"Released?"
Are you talking about an idol group?
(The 19-member group Covid
released an album.)
- Come on, Droducer Choi.
- "Droducer Choi?"
- By the way...
- Why do I feel like I'm drunk?
I feel like I'm drunk. Why...
It must be Tesla
based on the information I got.
(Where could Tesla be?)
E Biotechnology.
(Jong Kook came to get information
on E Biotechnology.)
"COVID-19 outbreak."
(COVID-19 outbreak)
F Biotechnology.
(He purchases information
on F Biotechnology as well.)
Big news.
"COVID-19 outbreak."
Oh, okay.
(Biotechnology companies
and COVID-19...)
It's time...
It's time to invest in Pfizer.
(Jong Kook owns 18 shares
of D Automobiles.)
I'll invest in E Biotechnology
and F Biotechnology equally.
(He pulled out of D Automobiles
to buy the biotechnology stocks.)
I'd like to... I'll go all in
on biotechnology stocks.
- Biotechnology stocks?
- Yes.
I'll purchase as many shares
of E Biotechnology as I can.
(He went all in on E Biotechnology
once again.)
I want to feel the joy.
(I hope to feel the joy of getting
a 400-percent gain once again.)
(C Automobiles)
C Automobiles' stock price has never
increased until now.
I think it will go up at least once.
(So Min has invested
in C Automobiles for many years.)
- I don't have any either.
- I don't know how much it'll go up.
(Jae Suk feels bad for them,
and gives them a tip.)
- What should we do?
- Right.
- Go all in on D Automobiles.
- What?
D Automobiles.
It's certain that it'll go up.
I'm sure of it, but I don't know
how much it'll go up.
Something else might go up more,
but we have no choice.
(So Min made a profit
with Jae Suk's help last time.)
Hey, Sae Ho.
I'll pull out of C Automobiles
and invest in D Automobiles.
(She changed her plan
and invested in D Automobiles.)
Jong Kook.
Do you think
Tesla is on the list or not?
(Jisla, who's unsure,
asks for everyone's opinion.)
It must be on it, right?
- Yes, I think it is.
- But it doesn't make sense.
Sir.
- Mr. Ji.
- Yes?
- Did you pull out of it?
- No.
Right?
I'm too upset to pull out of it.
I'm too upset to pull out of it too.
Why...
- There's no way it's not included.
- Wrap it up now.
I'll pull out of B IT.
(Haha seems to have
made a decision.)
And...
I'll use all my money
to invest in D Automobiles.
I'll recover all my losses at once.
I just...
All I can see is the car company.
It's my last chance.
(He's invested in D Automobiles
for several years and lost a lot.)
- I'll keep it as it is.
- Okay.
I believe
that this company is Tesla.
(Suk Jin owns 18 shares
of D Automobiles.)
I can't think of anything else.
- I'm worried.
- Why?
I'll go with Tesla alone.
But it hasn't gone up yet.
- Let's tear it again.
- Everyone.
(Sae Ho invested in E Biotechnology
to hit the jackpot once again.)
- Now...
- I hope I won't be in last place.
Gosh. Wait.
I made the wrong decision.
It was the year
of the COVID-19 outbreak.
Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
Please gather around.
(Jae Suk, Se Chan, Suk Jin, and Haha
went all in on D Automobiles.)
(December 30, 2019)
(December 31, 2019)
(The long-awaited 2020 has
finally begun.)
(Everyone knows that 2020 was
the year of cataclysmic events.)
A disease that started
in Wuhan, China...
The number of new outbreaks
reached 90,000...
Let's go.
The stock prices of 2020
will be revealed.
Musk.
(The stock prices of 2020
are revealed.)
Musk.
(Screaming)
So Min!
(Stock Market of 2020)
(D Automobiles,
F Biotechnology, I Media)
(D Automobiles' stock price
rose by 1,100 percent.)
So Min!
(Haha's account balance:
5,940 dollars)
(It's the big break
they have been waiting for!)
It rose by 1,100 percent!
So Min! It rose by 1,100 percent!
So Min! We did it!
Yes! We did it!
(E Biotechnology)
Thank goodness
I didn't buy a lot of stocks.
(It's a small win compared
to the 1,100 percent increase,)
- Big news!
- So Min!
So Min!
(Se Chan's balance is close
to 10,000 dollars.)
So Min! It rose by 1,100 percent!
It rose by 1,100 percent!
(The earnings rate
of 1,100 percent is unbelievable.)
- Yes! We did it!
- Tesla did it!
I survived!
- We did it!
- Let's go!
- Let's pick this up.
- It rose by 1,100 percent!
- I earned 660 dollars.
- That's incredible.
- Was it like that back then?
- Seriously.
- Did it increase by 1,100 percent?
- Money.
- How much do you have now?
How much do you have now?
My goodness.
- Hey.
- Do you have over 10,000 now?
I love it. I did it.
I decided not to invest
in D Automobiles this time.
How much do you have now?
Do you have over 10,000 now?
(Tesla investors' balance
increased by 11 times.)
Life is all about
getting a big break.
That's right.
Is this the power of stocks?
It rose by 901 percent.
(Yoo Jae Suk's account balance:
28,380 dollars)
(Jae Suk's balance is close
to 30,000 dollars.)
Did it increase that much?
Everyone, what did I tell you?
I bought a car from that company.
I know so much about it.
You earned a lot of money, right?
Yes. I have 6,000 dollars now.
(Haha avoided going bankrupt.)
Tesla was bound to be successful.
I should have trusted in Tesla.
(Jong Kook went from D Automobiles
to E Biotechnology.)
I invested in it two times
and took out the money this time.
The rankings
must have changed a lot.
Suk Jin.
I mean...
It was going too slow.
(Cho Biotechnology used to be
in 1st place.)
I am too depressed today.
I will pay 50 dollars
for the Choi Hong Man impression.
Really?
Hello, I am Choi Hong Man.
- Okay.
- It's nice to meet you.
- I am in your care.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
E Biotechnology.
Let's see some specialties.
Do we have two rounds left?
- Yes.
- It's so fun to invest in stocks.
Why does Coca-Cola taste like
alcohol?
We have two rounds left, right?
The remaining rounds
will make a difference.
Jae Suk, shall we invest
in D Automobiles again?
Jae Suk, will the price rise again?
It will rise again.
But...
there is biotechnology.
Seriously.
Will it be biotechnology or...
I will buy coins.
(Will it be biotechnology
or D Automobiles?)
One of those biotechnology companies
could be Pfizer.
That's right.
("Due to the COVID-19 Vaccines,
the Stock Prices Rise")
(COVID-19 vaccines definitely made
the stock prices rise.)
I will need to go with my hunch now.
I didn't even think about Pfizer.
- I will need to choose one.
- Time for diversified investments.
Diversified investments.
- Hi.
- Hello.
(Jong Kook is interested
in investing in vaccine stocks.)
How is it going, man?
Top and bottom. F Biotechnology.
Let's take a look.
Running News, 2021.
President Biden says
90 percent of American adults...
will be vaccinated.
Okay.
(Level one information
on F Biotechnology)
- Okay. Thank you.
- Okay.
Thank you. No problem.
(Jong Kook is certain that
F Biotechnology released vaccines.)
I will invest all of my money
in F Biotechnology.
You have 105 dollars left.
(He eats carbohydrates
due to stress.)
- Buy E Biotechnology stocks.
- E Biotechnology?
Shall we buy information
on F Biotechnology?
(Jae Suk and Se Chan are
also interested in F Biotechnology.)
- F Biotechnology.
- Shall we do that?
F Biotechnology.
(He purchases level 3 information
on F Biotechnology.)
F Biotechnology.
(President Biden's announcement
about vaccinating Americans...)
(makes the stock prices rise
for biotechnology companies.)
(F Biotechnology's stock price
goes up.)
I get it.
Perhaps it's too early...
We need to invest
all we have in F Biotechnology.
Really?
Instead,
I will spread false information.
I won't say anything
about F Biotechnology.
People earned a lot of money,
so don't say anything
about F Biotechnology.
Wouldn't that be too dangerous?
No. I will take care of it.
Just go on your way.
I didn't hear anything.
I will invest everything
in F Biotechnology.
(Jae Suk invests everything
in F Biotechnology.)
Use all I have
to buy the F Biotechnology stocks.
- Okay.
- F Biotechnology.
Don't let anyone see it.
Sae Ho.
- You like designer brands, right?
- Yes.
Then you should invest in fashion.
Invest some money.
- It's the end of October.
- What should I invest in?
(He spreads false information
in a careless manner.)
- I will invest in biotechnology.
- Biotechnology.
I will invest all I have
in E Biotechnology.
(He insists on E Biotechnology.)
Jae Suk, please give me
some information.
(Ji Hyo bribes Jae Suk
for information.)
Give me something.
F Biotechnology.
Will the stock price rise further?
Yes.
F Biotechnology.
Black market dealings
are rampant here.
- It's a mess.
(These investors specialize
in black market dealings.)
Mr. Ji.
Diligent investments led to success.
D Automobiles' stock price
will rise to four figures.
(Suk Jin wants
to invest in D Automobiles again.)
We have to go all in.
- Now?
- Now.
Will the price go up again?
Again?
I will wait outside. Close the door.
Welcome.
(Suk Jin enters
the Information Exchange.)
- You don't have...
- Excuse me.
Please take good care of Mr. Ji.
Please take good care of him.
- Are you ready?
- Yes. I am a rich man.
- Eleven times.
- A rich man?
This time...
is a very important time.
What?
- D Automobiles.
- Okay.
Seven coins.
(He purchases level 3 information
on D Automobiles.)
Okay.
"The skyrocketing stock prices
of D Automobiles..."
"makes the investors warn
of the stock market bubble."
"But a rush of private investors..."
(Will the stock price rise again
for D Automobiles?)
"makes the price go up further."
(The stock price will rise again.)
Is that good information?
Yes. Good.
(Meanwhile, Haha)
Listen.
This is how you invest in stocks.
You earn and lose.
(He makes a nonsense speech
about stocks.)
You study the situation
in various ways...
and aim for a big break.
The price of the stocks I bought
rose by 1,100 percent.
(The icon of big breaks, Haha)
Suk Jin, how did it go?
How was the information
that was worth seven coins?
Please wrap it up.
- Seven coins.
- We should switch companies.
- Really?
Seven coins.
(He betrays Haha right away.)
Two rounds remain.
The bubble will burst.
(Suk Jin gives Haha
false information.)
The bubble will burst.
We should switch companies.
- What should we invest in?
- That's the question.
We have to invest everything.
Shall we receive information
in English?
- I will sell everything...
- I don't need it.
- and invest in F Biotechnology.
- Stop talking nonsense.
I will spend less money
on I Media...
- Let's go!
- and all in E Biotechnology.
- Hot dog.
- Please wrap up.
(It's time to wrap up.)
Haha.
- What?
- What should I do?
What is it? Suk Jin, come on.
You are so mean.
How could you betray me?
How could you do this to me?
- Shall we go together?
- Yes! How could you betray me?
Looking at your face
made me feel guilty.
How could you think to do
something like that?
Will the price go up again?
- Yes.
- Will the price go up again?
Keep the stocks as they are.
(He tells Haha the truth.)
Why did you do that?
For a second,
I wanted to fool you.
(Laughing)
But your face looked so innocent.
I invested all of my money
in that company, right?
- Yes.
- All right.
This is the group of people
who earned money with Jisla.
Merry Christmas.
- Okay.
- Merry Christmas.
Let me succeed once again.
All right.
Mr. Haha, do you trust me?
Mr. Ji.
(Suk Jin and Haha invested
in D Automobiles.)
- E Biotechnology will rise too.
- This is driving me crazy.
(Se Chan and Jae Suk are
big E Biotechnology shareholders.)
- Biotechnology in general will.
- Here it comes.
- Let's go.
- All right.
Let me lie down in happiness.
- Let's go.
- Here it comes.
(How will the stock market be
in 2021?)
- Please.
- Let's go.
I am so nervous.
The stock prices of 2021...
will be revealed.
(The stock prices of 2021
are revealed.)
- It rose.
- Good.
(Stock Market of 2021)
(D Automobiles, E Biotechnology,
F Biotechnology)
(F Biotechnology)
(F Biotechnology's stock price
rose by 50 percent.)
- Thank goodness.
- We did it.
E Biotechnology.
(D Automobiles' stock price
rose by 67 percent!)
- Look at that.
- E Biotechnology.
(And...)
(E Biotechnology)
(E Biotechnology betrayed him
again.)
E Biotechnology!
E Biotechnology.
- No way.
- E Biotechnology.
(He lost one-third of his asset.)
Now comes one last year.
- This is the last.
- Yes. It's the last.
Gosh, this is what's important.
You should predict
the stock prices of this year.
- The stock prices of this year?
- Yes.
- This year?
It's about this year.
(The stocks on NYSE plunged with
concerns about economic stagnation.)
(Due to the economic stagnation
and inflation shock,)
(the world stock markets
have plummeted.)
In the year 2022,
with the end of COVID-19...
With the end of COVID-19, the stocks
of fashion companies went up.
It has gone up by 300 percent?
(That makes it even harder to
predict the stock prices this year.)
What's important is the last year.
I have to take risks
if I want to win first place.
How many of us will get a penalty?
What's important is
not to get a penalty now.
Jae Suk. If it includes this year,
things are terrible for the media.
- And even the automobile companies.
- The stocks of Tesla fell a lot.
How was it this year?
It went down.
Tesla's stock price declined.
I found a dime.
This year must be the real trap.
The year 2022 is really tricky.
(They are trying to figure out
safe items in order to survive.)
I bet it's J Airlines and G Fashion.
I'm thinking of J Airlines too.
Gosh, didn't he have a lot of money?
How did it plummet like this?
Whose account is this? Sae Ho?
It does look like
you're in New York.
This is Sae Ho's account.
(Gobbling up the New York hotdog)
- It looks like New York.
- There you go.
(The K-stockbroker has got
the wrong idea about the US.)
I feel bad for him.
(I feel bad for him.)
(The stockholder of E Biotechnology
is worried sick.)
Gosh, E Biotechnology.
(The stockholder of E Biotechnology
is worried sick.)
Gosh, E Biotechnology.
Come on over
(He greets Sae Ho
without knowing how he feels.)
Oh, you look like
you just got run over by a bus.
- Are you feeling okay?
- No, I'm not okay.
What can I do for you?
- Please show me E Biotechnology.
- Okay.
(Please show me E Biotechnology.)
Okay. This is E Biotechnology.
Quick. Read it.
This one's your last lifeline.
This is my last time.
"Running News 2022."
(He's still hung up
on E Biotechnology.)
(Please...)
"US Stock Exchange announces
CPI for this year."
(US Stock Exchange announces
CPI for this year.)
"The US Stock Exchange announces
CPI for this year."
Good news?
I don't know.
Please tell me.
I know. I want to help you.
But I just don't know.
I have no more money.
I don't have any money either.
But I just don't know.
- Okay. I have no coins.
- All right.
Good.
- His tie...
- E Biotechnology...
- makes me cry and laugh.
- You...
I'm back.
I'll invest in E Biotechnology.
- All your money?
- Yes.
- All of them.
- How much do you have?
Sae Ho. How much is your seed money?
I have about 2,000 dollars.
- You have 2,000 dollars?
- Yes.
I'll give you 100 dollars.
Will you polish my shoes?
(I'll give you 100 dollars.
Will you polish my shoes?)
- Where?
- What? Look at him.
Just give me your shoes.
Give me. I'll do that.
- I have no reason to say no.
- Okay.
- How much can you give me?
- I said 100 dollars.
Put it on here.
(He starts polishing
Se Chan's shoes right away.)
Polish mine too.
(Throwing)
(Working hard)
Put it on here.
Aren't you the one who succeeded
with E Biotechnology?
- Sae Ho.
- Hello.
Hello. Please have a seat.
- I'm fine.
- Please sit.
I'll do it later.
- Put it on here.
- Do you have coins?
I don't have coins or anything.
All I have is this piece
of newspaper. Put it on here.
- I'm sorry.
- Put your foot on here.
- I'm busy.
- Sir.
He had like tens
of thousands of dollars.
I don't want to have
my shoes polished.
- Pay me at least ten dollars.
- My gosh.
Thank you.
- Here.
- All right. E Biotechnology.
E Biotechnology.
Sae Ho keeps saying
E Biotechnology the whole time.
With E Biotechnology, at first...
I know. You made 400 percent.
I made 400 percent.
So I can't give up on it.
I bet E Biotechnology will rise.
You don't have much time left.
Make sure to use your coins.
- Okay. I'll go use up my coins.
- How many do you have, Young Ji?
Hang on. I need to take a risk.
What's the most promising item?
H Sports.
(Mr. Ji checks the investment items
for the last time.)
C Automobiles is still cheap.
(C Automobiles is still cheap.)
I should go with the tide.
I'll go with C Automobiles.
The only thing.
It's been growing recently.
(He's interested in C Automobiles
that shows a recent growth.)
I should jump onto a running horse.
And I should avoid
grabbing a knife that's falling.
I will withdraw all my money
from Tesla.
I'll withdraw all of them.
I'll go all-in here.
This is the final battle.
(He's in 2nd place now,
so he takes a risk to be the 1st.)
I should take the road not taken.
I'll go with C Automobiles.
- Go all-in?
- I'll go all-in. I have to.
C Automobiles.
(He chooses C Automobiles
only with his gut feelings.)
(Yoo Jae Suk's
account balance: 42,570)
The stock market in 2022...
is not so promising.
So I need to manage the money well.
The IT... I have no idea
What B IT is.
(B IT catches his eye.)
(B IT: minus 16 percent)
I have no time. B IT.
Hang on.
B IT.
"Elon Musk rises..."
- "as its major shareholder..."
- "Elon Musk rises as..."
"buying stake in B IT."
(Elon Musk rises as its major
shareholder buying stake in B IT.)
(Thinking carefully)
What is a shareholder?
(Elon Musk rises as its major
shareholder buying stake in B IT.)
Twitter!
(Twitter!)
(Twitter's stock price went up when
Musk became its major shareholder.)
- B IT.
- All of them?
Yes.
(He invests all his money in B IT.)
I think... Gosh, I figured out
what it is at the last moment.
B IT. I'll buy 100 stocks.
- A hundred?
- Yes.
- J Airlines.
- Okay.
About 100 stocks.
I'll divide it in half
and put the half in J Airlines.
Put 50 percent in B IT,
30 percent in J Airlines,
- and 20 percent in G Fashion.
- Okay.
- You can keep 50 dollars.
Thank you for taking care of this.
I'll see you in Korea
after I succeed.
I'm running a risk.
What if the stock price plummets?
- I don't know.
- Seriously,
I used my coins
to get this information.
Close my account.
I don't know.
I risk my life for this.
- We don't know it.
- I'll go all-in.
Please wrap things up now.
- This is the last day.
- Don't blame me.
Are you going to...
I don't invest in stocks,
so I have no idea.
(Jong Kook has no information, so
he hasn't made his investment yet.)
- I'll invest in Apple.
- We don't know it yet.
I'll invest in Apple. A IT.
Half in A IT and
the other half in F Biotechnology.
A IT and F Biotechnology.
One more in F Biotechnology.
- F Biotechnology?
- Yes.
Please gather around.
I'll announce the final prices.
- Okay.
- It's the 29th.
- The 29th?
- Finally.
- It's the new year.
- Oh, no.
- Let's go.
- This is driving me crazy.
(It's time to announce
the stock prices of this year.)
E Biotechnology!
Let's go.
I jumped on a running horse.
(Suk Jin and Jae Suk made risky
investments at the last minute.)
- I jumped on a running horse.
- Let's go.
- All right.
- That's C Automobiles.
It's this year.
This will determine the rankings.
(Yoo Jae Suk's account balance)
(Jae Suk's B IT?)
(Suk Jin's C Automobiles?)
(Or Sae Ho's E Biotechnology
that he's kept with perseverance?)
(Who will be the winner to laugh?)
Please show us.
(The stock prices of this year
are revealed.)
(The stock prices are
being adjusted.)
(Stock Market of 2022)
(B IT: plus 22 percent,
C Automobiles: plus 100 percent)
(E Biotechnology: minus 45 percent)
- It went up!
- I did it.
- It's 100 percent!
- J Airlines...
- It's 22 percent.
Good.
- It's 22 percent!
- My goodness.
(Jae Suk's B IT
went up by 22 percent.)
It's 22 percent!
(Three items went up
in this plummetting market.)
(Jong Kook's A IT also went up
by 29 percent.)
They all went down.
B IT and C Automobiles. Okay!
- E Biotechnology.
- E Biotechnology!
(E Biotechnology: minus 45 percent)
(Passing out)
- My goodness.
- Okay.
(E Biotechnology: minus 45 percent)
(The end of Sae Ho's
E Biotechnology)
(He experienced paradise
and fiery pit with E Biotechnology.)
I think I'm the winner.
I got none of them.
(E Biotechnology: minus 45 percent,
F Biotechnology: minus 67 percent)
(The girls in the lower ranks went
down with the biotechnology stocks.)
- It all went down.
- Thank you.
- Biotechnology.
I made 10,000 dollars
at the last moment.
- Thank you.
- Show us the results.
Let's check your rankings.
- I'm so nervous.
- I finally see the light.
It went up at the last minute.
I'm doomed.
I went all-in on C Automobiles.
I might win first place.
(I might win first place.)
- All right.
- Everyone.
- The results are in.
- Okay.
Is it interesting?
- All right.
- Is there a twist?
Young Ji, come over here.
- Did the rankings change?
- The first place.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk.
(Who is the 1st place,
the master of stock investment?)
I bet it's Suk Jin.
He made 51,820 dollars.
(He made 51,820 dollars
only with 500 dollars.)
It's Yoo Jae Suk.
(Yoo Jae Suk is the 1st place.)
I couldn't beat him.
- The second place.
- Congratulations.
Ji Suk Jin who made
39,600 dollars.
I knew it.
- At the last minute...
- That was so close.
The 3rd place is Yang Se Chan
who made 15,840 dollars.
(3rd place, Yang Se Chan
with 15,840 dollars)
- Yes!
- The fourth place is...
Haha who made 12,650 dollars.
(The 4th place is Haha.)
- You had only 200 dollars.
- I came from behind.
- How did you do that?
- I was the last.
From 200 to 12,000 dollars.
I made a comeback using my coins.
The fifth place is Jeon So Min.
Gosh, So Min.
- So Min, that's so cool.
- So Min, well done.
The sixth place is Kim Jong Kook.
- Yes.
- All right.
Now we have
the 7th, 8th, and 9th places.
(Now there are three people
in the lower ranks.)
- I'm doomed.
- The seventh place is...
Hur Young Ji with 2,204 dollars.
Wait. What's with
the biotechnology guy?
(Anxious)
Isn't he the biotechnology guy?
E Biotechnology.
Wasn't he the first place
in the middle of the race?
- He was doing really well.
- All right.
Ji Hyo and Sae Ho are
the 8th and 9th places.
Please. I don't want to be the last.
The last is...
(Who will be the last
to get the penalty today?)
Cho Sae Ho.
- Sae Ho.
- Ji Hyo, you survived.
(Cho Sae Ho is the last.)
(The biotechnology guy ends up
getting the penalty.)
- Ji Hyo, you survived.
- She survived.
- E Biotechnology!
- You survived.
- I survived!
(Ji Hyo survived
at the last minute.)
- My gosh.
- She survived.
(Joy and sorrow)
E Biotechnology.
Today's prize...
Since this is about the US stocks,
we prepared something about the US.
The first place wins
the high-quality American beef,
- the Black Angus beef set.
- My gosh.
And the LA ribs.
The second place gets
only the LA ribs.
(The two investment geniuses
get the beef sets.)
- And today's penalty...
- What is it?
(Today's penalty is announced.)
For being ignorant
of the US stock market,
you will write a letter
of apology in English.
Oh, no.
(Writing a letter of apology
in English)
Oh, no.
- That's the worst.
- In English?
- What?
- He needs a translator.
But Sae Ho needs to leave now.
So I want you to take a video
of you writing it down...
and send it to me.
Sae Ho has aged suddenly.
- A letter of apology in English?
- Sae Ho.
Your face has got all wrinkly.
- He's got a lot of wrinkles.
- A letter of apology in English?
I can't even write it in Korean.
In cursive letters.
I'd like to apologize...
to those who supported me and
my family for disappointing them.
"The letter of apology. Reflection."
"Cho Sae Ho."
"I'm sorry, everybody."
"I feel bad for everyone."
"It was my mistake."
"My mistake."
"I think it was so easy."
"I thought it would be easy."
"But it wasn't."
"But it wasn't like that."
"Then I failed."
"So I failed."
"So..."
"I hate myself."
"Please give me one more chance."
"I will do my best next time."
"I want to go to Running Man."
"I'm really sorry, everybody.
One more time."
"Again, I'm really sorry
to everyone."
(Sae Ho's bad day is over
with his lame English.)