It's so cool.
Hello.
- This smells like Southeast Asia.
- It feels like we're in Singapore.
It smells like Southeast Asia.
Doesn't this feel like Singapore?
- This is nice.
- Singapore.
- I like it.
- This is what I always do.
- This is so nice.
- I imagine I'm in Singapore.
- I love it.
- Don't you like my glasses?
- What are the glasses?
- Did you buy them?
Actually, they are
Jong Kook's glasses.
(Kim Jong Kook,
the owner of the sunglasses)
Why are you wearing them?
Jong Kook didn't want to wear them,
so I put them on instead.
You can have them.
Jong Kook, try these on.
- No.
- Just try them on once.
Just this once.
- No.
- Go ahead. Let's see how they look.
- Just try them on.
- What?
- Hey.
- Please.
- Stop it.
- Just try them on.
- Go ahead and wear them.
- I don't want to.
(Twenty minutes ago, the members
were gathered at the parking lot.)
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Hi.
What's with the glasses?
I have creases in my eyelids today.
- Let me see. You have creases?
- I'll just take them off.
- Jong Kook.
- Put them back on.
- Jong Kook, please.
- I just liked them.
- No.
- You looked cool.
- I don't need them.
- Just wear them for us.
- I shouldn't have mentioned that.
- It's Suk Jin's fault.
Jong Kook doesn't want to wear them.
- Try them on.
- I said no.
- Go ahead.
- No.
- I'm not wearing them.
- Hey.
Hey, why would you do that?
- I don't want to wear them.
- What's the big deal?
- The glasses...
- I'm not wearing them.
Just put them on. I want to see
how they look on you.
- Stop it.
- All right.
I told you to stop!
- The thing is...
Suk Jin ruined everything.
He ruined it.
- As soon as he got here...
- Because I blabbered on it.
- Exactly.
- When we saw Jong Kook,
we said, "You look good today."
And he just left,
looking a little shy.
So I thought, "Okay, it's done."
(Okay, this is it for today.)
- "We got it."
- "I'll talk about it."
I didn't say anything.
But Suk Jin
suddenly showed up and...
- "Hey, what's with your glasses?"
- That guy in the net sweater.
I just said one thing.
- "What's with your glasses?"
- I didn't sound like that.
- What is it then?
- "Hey, what's with your glasses?"
- I sounded like this.
- No. "What are the glasses for?"
- You sounded more like this.
- Did I?
You know what Jong Kook is like.
- He finally decided to wear...
- Exactly.
the glasses that match his shorts.
My eyes get saggy as I grow old.
So I get creases in my eyelids.
- They are not saggy.
- Jong Kook. Try them on once.
Seriously, no!
- Stop it!
- Hey.
Don't come close to me.
These are what you were wearing
just a while ago.
- Don't do that.
- He got off the car...
wearing them.
I was just wearing them for a while.
- You're lying.
- Forget it.
Ji Seon says you've been wearing
tinted glasses a lot recently.
- Jong Kook.
- That's not true.
I'm saying this
because they looked good on you.
No. Forget it.
- He's right.
- Don't come close.
- Just stop it.
- It was so close.
- Jong Kook.
- So close.
- Just stop.
- Hear me out.
(Stop it!)
Stop it!
- What...
- My gosh.
Stop it. Okay?
- Gosh, it hurts.
- My goodness.
(He uses force to stop the prank.)
Gosh, I'm so upset.
- That was so close.
- I know.
What's wrong with Seok Sam?
Hey, let me try them on.
- Why would you wear them?
- No.
- I'll try them on.
- I bet they will look good on you.
- Let me see.
- They look great.
- Do you like it?
- They're pretty.
(He tries to make up for it
by wearing them himself.)
- They look so cool.
- You look unique.
It's like "Incredible Moment."
- They're pretty.
- In a net vest.
- A guy in a net vest.
- It's like "Incredible Moment."
A guy who always wears
tinted glasses and a net vest.
- You look cool.
- Do you like it?
- They look good on you.
- I don't know how to describe it.
You look ten years younger.
You look like a guy in his 50s.
Suk Jin loves to hear this.
You look ten years younger.
I know you're lying.
- No, I'm not.
- You do look ten years younger.
- That's not true.
- He likes that.
Suk Jin, you look
ten years younger.
Seriously, you look
Suk Jin, you look like
you're in your 30s.
We're serious.
- You look young.
- Ten years younger.
- In his early 40s.
- You look 10 years younger.
You think so?
Gosh, we talked about
a pair of glasses for a long time.
- By the way...
- It was so close.
I went to Jeju Island
with my family.
- That's right.
- You did?
And I got a tip-off.
- What?
- About what?
You went to Jeju Island, didn't you?
- Me?
- What?
(Se Chan, you went
to Jeju Island, didn't you?)
Yes. You did, right?
- Recently?
- With who?
- I don't know when.
- With Jin Ho?
- He went there with Jin Ho.
- With Jae Joon.
- No.
No. You...
I got a tip-off that you were
with a woman.
(Did Se Chan go to Jeju Island
with a mysterious woman?)
- What? He just...
- Me? No.
- Seriously...
- Hey, tell us.
- He's caught.
- That's not true.
- I went with Jin Ho and Jae Joon.
- Ji Hyo.
- No.
- When Se Chan saw us earlier...
- As soon as we met,
- Oh, right.
he talked about a yacht party to us.
A yacht party.
(He talked about a yacht party?)
He did talk about a yacht party.
- He did.
- No, I didn't.
- Look how he's reacting.
- He...
As soon as we got here...
- That's ridiculous.
- He did talk about it.
- Hey.
- It was a smokescreen.
- He used Jin Ho and Jae Joon...
- He's been...
- as a smokescreen.
- Let me tell you.
- So...
- He's been busy playing golf.
- No.
- Look at him.
- That sly...
- You rented a car, right?
- Yes.
- You rented a car.
- I had some tea with a guy there.
- I see.
"Se Chan was here before."
- He said this.
- He went there.
So I said, "Oh, really? I see."
Se Chan looks nervous.
This is a scoop.
I know what a spy looks like.
- He looks nervous.
- He looks strange, right?
He's definitely hiding something.
I know.
He looks so anxious.
- He's anxious.
- Jae Suk, that's slander.
I can tell when I see his face.
- I'm sure...
- Isn't it that...
- you went there with someone else?
- I went with Jae Joon, Jin Ho,
and some other people.
Some other people?
Jae Joon, you...
- And...
- Jin Ho.
Jin Ho.
- That's three.
- Three.
And there were another three.
- They are some other people.
- That makes six.
(The rest 3 people are
shrouded in mystery.)
- Where are the rest 3?
- Where are the other 3?
What are you talking about?
(The mystery of the trip
to Jeju Island is getting bigger.)
Jae Suk, Jae Joon is...
- Was Eun Hyeong there too?
- The other three.
- She joined us later.
- She joined you later?
- So...
- They are smokescreens.
You should tell us about things
like that in advance.
- Right.
- Tell us when you're back.
- He's right.
- "I'm back."
- You should tell us the truth.
- You know what?
- You guys...
- That was a long time ago.
You guys might think...
they would keep it a secret.
- Right.
- But people talk.
- People can see you.
- They talk about what they see.
He's really flustered.
That was a long time ago.
I can't believe this guy.
People talk.
He didn't tell me though.
- Fortunately...
- He didn't say anything.
- He didn't say a thing, but...
- Then how did you find out?
"I can't tell you anything."
"I guess he came with a woman."
Of course, he can't.
- He couldn't say anything.
- He didn't say a thing.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- No.
You look cool these days.
Se Chan went to Jeju Island
with some girls!
What are you guys doing?
- That was a long time ago.
- He's a man.
- What happened to Jin Ho?
Do you still call her?
- Did she pick him over you?
- No.
It didn't go well.
(It didn't go well.)
"It didn't go well."
That's the term.
It didn't work out.
- Oh, no.
- I know what he means.
You should've told us about it.
- Right.
- We would've tried to help you.
You know I'm...
an expert in that field.
- What do you mean you're an expert?
- You should be careful.
I'm a dating expert.
I give dating advice.
- No, that's dangerous.
- Sure.
I was going to set So Min up
with someone,
- but I told her to wait.
- Wait.
I need to know more about him.
But he's been putting me
on hold for two years.
- It's been two years.
- You should give up.
Two years.
I put her on hold.
- Around this time two years ago...
- Okay.
- Two years ago?
- Last year?
You were told to share the R coins
equally to avoid a penalty,
- but you failed to divide them.
- We did?
(In 2020, Sharing Playbook)
(They took as many coins
as they wanted after each mission.)
Hang on.
(They wouldn't be penalized
if they shared the coins equally.)
(Empty)
- Forget it.
- What's wrong?
If you shared the coins equally,
you wouldn't have been penalized.
But someone wanted to win the prize,
and you failed
to split them up evenly.
That's right.
Today, we'd like to test
your loyalty and conscience again.
It's the 2nd Sharing Playbook Race.
- Again?
- We're doing it again.
The rules are the same as before.
After each mission, starting with
the person in the first place,
you'll take as many coins
as you want.
It will never work.
Unlike last time when the number
of coins decided the prize...
(Unlike last time when the number
of coins decided the prize...)
This time, the number of coins
will decide your penalties.
Penalties?
There will be
four different missions.
So you will divide
the coins four times.
Each time, you will get 35 coins.
That means you will be given
a total of 140 coins.
And you will take
as many coins as you want.
And the number of coins you have
will decide what penalty you get.
Please bring in the board.
- I need to see the penalty.
- When will we ever be...
able to avoid a penalty?
We just need
to share the coins equally.
Then we won't get a penalty.
Two years ago, we had that brat.
He's hot here today.
- You mean Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
He's not here anymore.
We need more than 50 coins
to avoid a penalty.
Gosh, we need 50 coins.
- We need more than 50 coins.
- How many are there in total?
There will be a total of 140 coins.
This is so easy.
- It's hard, Haha. It's 140...
- We just need to share them.
Seven multiplied by two
equals fourteen.
This one requires
at least two extra hours.
- Just get to the place.
- You know what?
And it's really scary.
The sky bridge is terrifying.
You know what this is.
What's that?
- Seriously, I can't do that.
- It's so scary.
Why would we do that?
(That's the world's highest bridge
at 541m above the ground.)
(They have to cross
the 11-meter-long bridge.)
- Seriously, I can't do that.
- It's so scary.
- Why would we do that?
- I'm not scared,
- but it's just bothersome.
- Why would one do that?
- Why would you do that?
- It's just bothersome.
You need to go to Jamsil.
I know. I don't want
to go to Jamsil.
I don't understand
why people enjoy it.
- And I don't want a costume.
- I don't like the costume thing.
(2-3 coins: Wear a costume
and makeup for the opening.)
(Running Man has shown
high-quality makeup...)
(with special effects
makeup artists.)
(And the video clips will be
preserved forever.)
This must be really embarrassing.
- BTS? My gosh.
- This is the worst.
- I just can't do this.
- I don't want to do this.
I don't understand...
- why people enjoy it.
- So it means we should...
- have at least seven coins.
- Let's give it a try.
- No, we need 11 coins each.
- Right.
Then it won't be so bad.
We can do this.
- Let's not cheat.
- If someone gets more coins,
- he can share them with others.
- Right.
- I'll share mine.
- Good.
You can't share the coins
you already took.
- Once you take coins, it's over.
- All right.
So we shouldn't
bring too many coins.
Let's have at least
seven coins each.
Guys, just make sure
not to take too many coins.
When we take coins? Okay.
It's 35 coins each.
Let's help each other.
We need at least this.
- At least seven coins.
- Good.
It's just seven coins.
- We have to do this.
- We should help each other.
In the middle of this year,
we should show our teamwork.
Don't put anyone in trouble.
What?
- You are dangerous.
- Even you find it funny.
You're dangerous.
Let's show our teamwork.
- In the middle of the year...
- You know what?
I bet he will be dancing
to BTS' song wearing the glasses.
In Jamsil. On the sky bridge.
I think you will be dancing
in the tinted glasses.
If you share the coins equally,
you'll take rubbings of your faces.
- What?
- If you split up the coins evenly,
- you'll make rubbings.
- That's not bad.
But the story of Se Chan's trip
to Jeju Island...
has had a strong influence on me.
It has nothing to do with this.
- I'm not feeling well.
- By the way,
it would be strange
if he went on a trip with you.
He's right.
So Min, I know you also
go on a date...
- with some guys.
- Right.
But he is...
- I mean...
- She was on my YouTube channel.
She wanted to go
to the US with Se Chan.
- That's what I suggested.
- I thought about it.
- She even said that.
- Just me and her?
No, including me.
- I said that.
- The three of us.
Why would I go to the US
alone with you?
Wait, Jong Kook.
You didn't say anything...
when I wanted
to go to the US with you?
(I told you to take me with you.)
(Cold)
Will you just stay quiet?
He didn't see this coming.
- Jong Kook is flustered.
- It's not like that.
Hey, it's just...
It would be strange
if we go to the US together.
- That doesn't make sense.
- This is what So Min said.
When Jong Kook goes
to the US for a concert,
she wants to tag along.
And he said, "Sure. You can come."
"Can I go with Ji Hyo?"
"No, not Ji Hyo."
- That's not it.
- See?
- He said that.
- I didn't mean I'd go alone.
- I said I wanted to go with So Min.
- Exactly.
- But he said I couldn't go. Why?
- I mean,
it would be strange
for us to leave together.
- He's afraid of rumors.
- Here's the thing.
It looks like we're using So Min...
- as a smokescreen.
- If you three leave together,
it will look like
So Min is a smokescreen.
Exactly.
He knows that
because he has experience.
Then all three of us can't go.
It would look like a double date.
- The four of us?
- Yes.
I never intended to go
with the three of you.
- He's too busy.
- You all can't go.
No one goes to the US.
- I have to go.
- You can't.
- Don't go.
- I...
- I have to perform there.
- Don't go.
It will be all settled
if I join you.
- Take me with you.
- But...
- It's all settled.
- If you join then,
the purpose of the trip will change.
It's like a trip with parents.
If I join you, it will just look
like a trip with colleagues.
Ji Hyo is so funny.
All right. Let's begin...
the first mission to distribute
the first batch of coins.
Let's chant together
before we start.
- We can do this.
- Let's help each other.
- We should help each other.
- Right.
- I just need seven coins.
- We can do this.
- One, two, three. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Seriously, I'll do that.
- Sure.
(Will they change after 2 years?)
- I need only seven coins.
- All right.
Here's the first mission...
where you need good gut feelings
and supernatural powers.
- It's called Let Me Clock In.
- What is in?
- Clock in?
- What's that?
You will first check
the starting point.
Then you will put on a blindfold
and start walking.
You will fold your hands
behind your back...
and walk as much as you want
toward the door.
When you stop, you should stick out
your nose as much as you can.
The points of the spot
where your nose is placed...
and the number of steps you took
will be put together.
The one with the lowest points
will be the winner.
Simply put,
- there will be a door.
- Okay.
And you need to get
as close to the door as possible.
(The one who goes closest
to the door will win.)
- But...
- What if we touch the door?
you need to take
as little steps as possible.
The number of steps... I mean...
- Like this.
- You need to take long strides.
(Shaking)
- Like this.
- You need to take long strides.
The one who takes only
three steps is more likely to win.
- He doesn't understand.
- I shouldn't have told him.
- He would've done this.
- He's so lovely.
He's so cute.
He just can't wait to get a penalty.
He wants to go to Jamsil.
Can we do this?
We're not supposed to practice.
- My goodness.
- This is hard.
If you touch the door,
you get zero points.
- I see.
- Is it okay to go out of my way?
- Is it okay to practice?
- Can we practice?
- No.
- You can't do that.
- You can't practice.
- They are so uptight.
- You're not supposed to practice.
- Okay.
Hey, what are you...
(He takes a long step
after criticizing So Min.)
Why are you practicing it?
- You can't do that.
- All right.
I just walked.
You don't have to try so hard.
We will take only seven coins each.
- That's right.
- Sure.
- Why are you trying so hard?
- He's right.
- Jae Suk, what are you doing?
- Stop it.
You said you wouldn't practice it.
You don't have to try so hard.
- What are you doing?
- It's okay to get zero points.
- Why did you practice it?
- I didn't practice it.
- I should try going this way.
- All right.
All right.
Stop walking around.
(He's done
with the nose simulation.)
Why did you do that?
It's no big deal.
- Why are you trying so hard?
- Why?
- We'll just take seven coins each.
- What?
- Stop it.
- Let's just take five coins each.
Five times seven is thirty-five.
Who will go first?
- I'll go first.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Okay.
- You can make some noise...
to distract her.
- Can I kick her when she walks?
- No.
What if she goes out of the way?
Then it will increase the number
of her steps as she comes back.
- I shouldn't have gone first.
- It doesn't matter...
- because we will share the coins.
- We will get five coins anyway.
So Min. Why did you
want to go first?
- Why did you do that?
- You go first.
What do I do? Okay.
I shouldn't have said that.
Ready.
We're a team.
Start.
- Oh, gosh.
- She's good.
(One step)
(Two steps)
- You should keep counting.
- Oh, my. Be careful.
(Five steps)
You should keep counting.
(Six steps)
- Hey, stay on the mat.
- Oh, gosh.
- Hey.
- Seven.
How many steps did you take?
(She's walking straight
in the accurate direction.)
(Nine steps)
(She got close to the door
only with ten steps.)
(She's right in front of the door!)
(Could she get
as close to the door as she could?)
(She gets surprised and groans.)
(She hit her nose on the door.)
- You got zero points.
- Zero points.
(Frog hurt her nose
as she got too close to the door.)
Is your nose okay?
- Are you all right?
- You were getting too close to it.
- Are you okay?
- Gosh. What happened?
Why did I... That's weird.
I didn't think I was that close...
- I guess I was wrong.
- She did well in the beginning.
You got zero points.
You're in last place.
- She's in the last place?
- Yes.
- Do we put our noses on the floor?
- No.
- You should stick it forward.
- Why would you put it on the floor?
- I didn't know.
- What should I do?
- Why would you put it on the floor?
- Should I squat down like this...
- What's wrong with him?
- Why would you do that?
- I can just stick my head forward?
(Seok Sam always understands
game rules differently from others.)
What is he talking about?
I'll start.
(Next up is Haha.)
- That's 2.
- Yes, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Do you remember
how many steps you took?
(He walked with long strides.
He's already halfway through.)
(Ji Hyo puts her palm in front of
his nose to disturb him.)
(Haha stops.)
(He walks with shorter steps now.)
- He got confused.
- Right.
(Will their plan to disturb him
work out?)
- He's almost there.
- Yes.
- He's close to it.
- No.
(He sticks his nose out carefully
as if he'd made up his mind.)
Is that it?
- You're a coward.
- That's it.
- He's a coward.
(The coward stopped
halfway through the track.)
- Gosh, seriously.
- You should've moved further.
- You coward.
- You got 19 points.
You're a coward.
You should've moved further.
I'll start.
(Next up is Se Chan.)
(Striding)
He has muscular calves.
Five.
(He's moving forward fast
with his muscular calves.)
Six.
(Sticking her lips out)
(The cheesy girl sticks her lips out
toward Se Chan.)
Seriously, she never stops.
Hey, what are you doing?
(They're about to kiss.)
Go ahead if you think you can do it.
You're really something.
Is that it? Okay. Stop.
Seven steps and two points.
You got nine points.
Okay. I'm in the first place.
- You're in 1st place.
(Se Chan got a total of 9 points
including 7 steps and 2 points.)
(Se Chan is currently
in first place.)
Good job.
I'll take only five coins.
- Hey, why did you do well?
- Just take five coins.
- Take no more than that.
- Why did you do well?
You took 14 steps.
Your total score is 18 points.
Eight points and nine steps.
You got seventeen points in total.
- Your total score is 18 points.
- I got 18 points?
(Jong Kook: 18, Ji Hyo: 18,
Suk Jin: 17, Jae Suk: 17)
As a result of the first round,
So Min is in last place.
And Se Chan came in first.
- Okay.
- Oh, my.
Jae Suk placed second.
- It must be really important.
- Suk Jin placed third.
Jong Kook placed fourth.
- Ji Hyo placed fifth.
- I can't believe this.
Haha placed sixth.
And So Min placed seventh.
- Please leave some for me.
- Of course.
We all agreed to take five each.
I didn't do my best.
- Of course.
- I'll take only five coins.
Don't worry.
- Right.
- You don't have to worry about it.
If our plan falls through
in the beginning,
- it will be that way to the end.
- That's right.
Haha's right. If you don't leave
coins for us, that means war.
- That means war.
- I'm serious.
Se Chan, you shouldn't take all
from the first round.
I'll take only five coins this time.
Okay.
Come on.
You have nothing to worry about.
- Don't provoke me from the start.
- It's ready.
- Se Chan, you can go now.
- Okay.
I think I'll be upset.
- I'll take five coins.
- I'll be upset.
- If there's nothing left,
- But Se Chan...
- I'll be upset.
- Don't do that in the first round.
If there are no coins left...
(The members seem so serious.
How many coins will Se Chan take?)
Wait.
(Contemplating)
(There are 35 coins
in front of his eyes.)
(Penalty List)
(The number of coins determines
the penalty they receive.)
(They promised to divide the coins
evenly regardless of the order.)
(The other members will be upset
if he doesn't keep the promise.)
(Se Chan picked up five coins
as he promised.)
Five coins.
What's the penalty for seven coins?
It's to have a bucket of ink
poured on you.
Gosh, that's not good.
Ten coins.
(He decided to betray the others.)
(Se Chan took 15 coins in a flash.)
I have 15 coins now.
That's good, right?
What's the penalty for 15 coins?
To have water poured on you.
No. I need more coins.
What's the penalty for 20 coins?
To make a rubbed copy of your face.
For 20 coins?
I have no choice.
I'll take 20 coins.
Please go that way
and get on the bus over there.
Got it.
The next member can go now.
Me?
I promise I'll just...
- I should've won the game.
- I trust you, Jae Suk.
I trust them.
Jae Suk, take only five coins!
Yes!
(But...)
(There are only 15 coins left.)
- How many coins did he take?
- There are 15 coins left.
- Fifteen coins?
- Yes. Fifteen coins are left.
- Fifteen?
- Yes.
You can take as many as you want.
(Jae Suk picks up coins
without hesitating.)
(How many did he take?)
I need to get
the least number of coins.
It's up to them. There could be war.
Absolutely.
I won't let it slide
if they provoke me.
- I'm...
- That doesn't mean anything.
I won't let it slide. I'm serious.
- Will they do it from the start?
- You're next after me.
You shouldn't expect anything.
- They'll probably betray us.
- Let's compete against them.
The third member, Suk Jin,
you can go now.
- Okay. I'll be quick.
- The 1st 3 will most likely do it.
Here?
This is it?
These are all that's left?
(Only four coins are left?)
There are four coins left.
Gosh. Those punks are unbelievable.
(Following Se Chan who took
20 coins, Jae Suk took 11 coins.)
I can't believe them.
(Suk Jin took all four coins
while grumbling.)
(There's no coin left now.)
Hey, that was not cool at all.
You guys, how could you?
- Why?
- Out of 35 coins...
- I mean...
- I took only five. What about you?
Did you take 30 of them?
- What are you talking about?
- You took five coins?
- Yes. How many coins were left?
- Gosh.
Four coins.
- Only 4 coins?
- There were 4 coins left.
- I bet you took all of them.
- Of course, I did.
You didn't even leave five coins.
Of course, I took them all.
- There's no coin left.
- You should take them out.
Come on. Take them out.
- There's no coin left.
- Are you serious?
Fine.
(He walks away angrily,
which means there will be war.)
I knew there would be no coin left.
(The next member Ji Hyo...)
(and Haha saw the empty tray.)
I feel so betrayed. Seriously...
There's no coin left.
(Everyone including So Min has
checked the coin tray.)
It's going to be a war.
- Jae Suk.
- The two of them took all of them.
Jae Suk,
you shouldn't have done it.
- Ji Hyo, it wasn't me.
- I'm disappointed.
- I'm disappointed too.
- I'm really disappointed.
- We all agreed to take 5 coins.
- To take 5 coins each.
- It could've been a great day.
- Who took...
- This means war.
- Forget it.
- Come here.
- Oh, no.
What are you doing now?
Hey, the two of them took
all the coins.
Look. Jae Suk took all the coins.
This means war.
- Let me pick them up first.
- I'm really upset.
I'm genuinely upset.
Be prepared for war.
- You came in last place.
- I'll teach you a lesson.
- Up to how many...
- We'll play four games in total.
- No. I mean, the sky bridge.
- One coin.
Up to one coin.
- Up to one coin?
- Yes.
I'll go cross the sky bridge
if I don't place first.
- Jong Kook.
- To make the staff members suffer.
- I think you're right.
- Yes? Right.
- I'll do that if I don't win.
- Gosh, I'm so upset.
- I took five coins.
- I see that Jong Kook is angry.
- This is...
- I'll go with the sky bridge.
- Jong Kook must be very upset.
- I've made up my mind.
- What's the penalty for 30 coins?
- It was empty when I went there.
(30 to 39 coins:
Drinking sophora root tea)
- It was empty.
- To drink sophora root tea.
- Sophora root tea?
- Ji Hyo, the worse penalties are...
Shut it, you punk.
- a bucket of...
- Exactly.
I only took five coins, Ji Hyo.
You punk, I don't want to hear
anything you say.
Okay.
- The five of us...
- Yes?
will aim to take down Jae Suk
and Se Chan no matter what.
- We have to win two games.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Those two will get a penalty.
- It's 5 against 2.
- He says that it's 5 against 2.
- Sorry?
- We don't have to film it today.
- We're their targets.
Do you understand?
We must work together.
- I think that Se Chan...
- Let's oust the two of them!
- Let's oust them!
- Let's do that!
- Listen.
- That's not necessary.
Suk Jin took a lot of coins.
Suk Jin will...
We took... I'll be honest with you.
I left more than ten coins.
(He's lying.)
- Suk Jin.
- It's true.
- That's true.
- Tell us honestly.
- I left more than ten coins.
- My gosh.
- After Jae Suk, it went faster.
- Hey.
- Exactly.
- Listen to me.
Does it make sense
that they left more than ten coins?
- Yes, we did.
- Of course.
It would make sense
if I took ten coins.
I bet you took 20 coins,
and he took more than 10 coins.
- No.
- You're wrong.
Suk Jin took more than ten coins.
- Why are you pretending you didn't?
- He took more than ten coins.
You know that I can't beat them
when they join forces...
- Okay. I believe you.
- You believe me, right?
I'll tell you honestly.
How many coins did you take?
Be honest with us.
- How many do you have?
- How many?
(Suk Jin suddenly said
he'd reveal how many coins he had.)
- Nonsense.
- You're lying.
(He lied that he had three coins.)
(Nonsense.)
Suk Jin. Everyone,
it's 4 against 3 now.
- Stop lying.
- No. I'm not lying. Hey.
- You have to believe me.
- We're sitting with our teams.
- You got the wrong idea.
- You got me wrong.
- Honestly, I took four coins.
- Stop lying.
I took four coins.
Now, try to guess.
Obviously, he took 20 coins,
and he took 11 coins.
- Stop talking nonsense.
- They took 20 and 11 coins.
- Suk Jin.
- That would be just as predictable.
- I'll tell you honestly.
- That makes sense.
- Se Chan said...
- I left eight coins.
that it would be predictable.
- That makes him look suspicious.
- Suk Jin is unbelievable.
- Totally.
What did he say?
He said that what you said was
too predictable.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Yes?
He's acting strange
because of his trip to Jeju Island.
- He can't think clearly now.
- You're defending him.
- He's defending Se Chan.
- He's not in his right mind.
- That's true.
- Anyway, it made things simple.
- But we can't edit it out.
We'll convince the staff
to edit that part out...
Yes?
- if you give us some coins.
- Right.
Am I allowed to give away coins?
(He's tempted.)
We'll begin the second mission
right away.
- Okay.
- It's worth ten coins.
In the second mission,
you will look back
at the past six years.
It's History Journal Running Man.
- History Journal Running Man?
- Gosh.
You will take turns
saying an episode number...
- of Running Man.
- An episode number?
The member who won in the episode
gets one point.
And the member who gets a penalty
loses one point.
Your total score will determine...
- your rankings.
- But...
those who got a penalty often are
at a disadvantage.
Isn't it unfair?
I'm at a disadvantage.
I'll probably lose a point
every time.
- Here.
- What's that?
These are the episode numbers
for each year.
- I don't remember clearly.
- I remember nothing.
- What's that?
- You can pick...
any of these numbers.
- Pick a time when you did well.
- I see.
The member who won the race
in the chosen episode gets a point.
But I didn't win in many episodes.
- You can pick a recent episode too.
- Got it.
- We can just remember the episode?
- Yes, that's correct.
- But I can't remember any.
- Okay.
We celebrated the 400th, 500th,
and 600th episodes.
- Yes.
- You can think of special episodes.
- Gosh, I can't remember any.
- The winner gets one point?
- I really can't remember any.
- I think I have a chance to win.
- I can't remember at all.
- Then...
Yesterday's episode was
the 610th episode.
- Don't look at that.
- When did I win?
- Any of you can go first.
- I never won.
- I don't remember.
- I don't remember either.
I'll just pick an episode randomly.
(I...)
(I pick Episode 600.)
- I pick Episode 600.
- I'll pick one randomly.
- Episode 600?
- It was a special episode.
- Where we teamed up together?
- Yes.
(The winner will get 1 point,
and the loser will lose 1 point.)
We can just reminisce about
those days.
In Episode 600,
Ji Hyo won the race,
and Suk Jin got a penalty.
(Suk Jin got a penalty,
and Ji Hyo won the race.)
It's the episode
where Suk Jin wrote a letter...
to thank the viewers
on behalf of the entire team.
- Oh, I remember that.
- One.
(Suk Jin wrote a letter
to the viewers as a penalty.)
(Episode 600, April 2022,)
(With Viewers
made with the viewers' ideas)
(At the final draw, Ji Hyo won,
and Suk Jin lost as expected.)
(Suk Jin wrote a heartfelt letter
getting emotional.)
(Their memories came back
as they heard about the result.)
- We shot the episode...
- I remember that.
- At a wedding venue.
- That's right.
Ji Hyo got 1 point,
and Suk Jin lost 1 point.
- Ji Hyo did a great job.
- I lost one point.
- I'll go next.
- Okay.
(Episode numbers by year)
Episode 490.
- Episode 490?
- Who won?
- Episode 490...
- In Episode 490...
(Running Countdown)
Kang Han Na and Heo Kyeong Hwan
came on the show.
(What? Did I win the race?)
- I don't think I've ever won.
- I think I won the race.
The race continued in Episode 491,
so we didn't have the winner
in that episode.
Then what happens?
Won't he get another chance?
- No, he won't.
- Oh, no.
- I'll just...
- Suk Jin.
- I pick...
- Only after they joined the show.
- I pick Episode 555.
- I see.
- Episode 555?
- Yes.
- I just picked a random episode.
- Gosh, I can't remember at all.
- I picked it randomly.
- All right.
- In Episode 555,
- What did we do?
we had the Empty Head Land race.
Suk Jin and Haha got penalties,
and the rest won.
(Suk Jin and Haha got penalties,
and the rest won.)
Really?
(The other members escaped
Empty Head Land by knocking.)
(Haha and Suk Jin who were spies
made the empty head video clip.)
Each of the 5 members got 1 point.
- Jae Suk did well that day.
- Be careful.
(Suk Jin picked the episode
where he got a penalty.)
Gosh, why did I...
I was a spy in that episode.
Right. I remember that.
Are we going to get coins
after this game as well?
- Yes, of course.
- This is driving me nuts.
When was I called Jeon So Bal?
That was the only episode...
- in which I won.
- I must be in the top two.
- I don't remember when it was.
- Those who have won many races...
are at an advantage.
Jae Suk hasn't done it.
I haven't done it yet.
- Wait. Was it before that episode?
- Jae Suk.
Pick Episode 609.
You'll get a penalty
if you pick that episode.
Pick Episode 609.
You'll get a penalty
for three weeks in a row.
Pick Episode 609.
I pick Episode 605.
- Episode 605?
- Episode 605.
Didn't you get a penalty?
- I think he did.
- In Episode 605,
Kim Ji Young, Hwang Seog Jeong,
and Hong Ye Ji came on the show.
- It wasn't long ago.
- Hold on.
Haha was the sole winner.
- That's right.
- He won.
- Yes, he won. He was a spy.
- How did I win?
- Oh, right. I was a spy.
- We failed to catch him.
- He was hiding.
- There was no penalty.
- He kept running from us.
- Right.
Yes, I remember that now.
- He was so sly.
- May I go next?
- What's the most recent episode?
- I can't remember the episode.
- Can I pick Episode 609?
- Yes.
- I pick Episode 609.
- Episode 609?
You picked it to take someone down.
(The target is obvious.)
- You little...
- It's Jae Suk.
In Episode 609, we went on vacation.
No one got a penalty.
- Oh, right.
- Good. Okay.
- I pick...
- Episode 608.
- I pick Episode 603.
- I'll check both episodes.
- Episode 603.
- In Episode 608,
- Jae Suk got a penalty.
- Gosh.
This is unfair.
In Episode 603,
we had The 1st Division Game race
where we used a roulette.
Jae Suk won,
and So Min got a penalty.
(Jae Suk won,
and So Min got a penalty.)
Right. So Min got a penalty.
That was good.
You picked the right one.
- Okay. I picked the right episode.
- Okay. Then I pick Episode 597.
Episode 597?
- Just one more, please.
- Let's keep going until we arrive.
Please let me find the episode
where I won the race.
So Min wants to find
the only episode where she won.
- The Jeon So Bal special.
- I've won just once.
- Really?
- Just once.
The guests were Park Ah In,
Kim Hee Jung, and Roh Jeong Eui.
So Min was the sole winner.
Suk Jin got a penalty.
- Darn it!
- How did you pick that?
How did you pick it?
Jae Suk and Suk Jin got penalties.
- He got a penalty...
- I got a penalty in every episode.
- How did you pick that episode?
- How did you do that?
- I thought of the episodes 1 by 1.
- She remembered...
Oh, I see.
- I'll go next.
- Around that time?
- That's amazing.
- I'll pick an old episode.
- I pick...
- I think I'll be in last place.
Episode 348.
- It was your 2nd week on the show.
- Our 2nd week on the show.
I got a penalty for weeks in a row
right after I joined the show.
All right. In Episode 348,
we went on a one-day trip
with Jang Do Yeon.
- Do Yeon.
- Right.
Jae Suk and Se Chan got
penalty stickers.
Gosh. Why are
those who got penalties...
always us?
Why us?
- Let me try.
- Sure. Go ahead.
Episode 632.
We haven't made 632 episodes yet.
(Episode 632?)
(It will air in the future.)
- Suk Jin, what's wrong with you?
- He saw the future.
- He's a time traveler.
- I pick...
- Who wins in that episode?
- A time traveler.
- It's not you.
- Episode 450.
- I pick...
- Who wins in that episode?
- A time traveler.
- Episode 450.
- Okay.
- I can't remember...
In Episode 450,
Lee Dong Hwi came on the show.
- Dong Hwi?
Jong Kook, Haha, and So Min won.
- Really?
- So Min?
And Jae Suk and Suk Jin
got penalties.
- Why is it always me?
- Not again.
I pick Episode 577.
Jae Suk and Se Chan got penalties.
- We got penalties?
- Oh, right.
Episode 604.
Suk Jin, Se Chan, and So Min
got penalties.
- Darn it.
- Oh, right.
- I lost in almost every episode.
- The one with black roses?
- Yes.
- Oh, right.
- I lost in almost every episode.
Ji Hyo is currently in first place.
- Really?
- Episode 598.
Suk Jin, Se Chan, and Jae Suk
went into the water as a penalty.
- Right. Darn it.
- I forgot about that.
- I remember that.
- The others won the race, right?
Why am I always the one
who got a penalty?
- I think...
- We got the result.
With 5 points, Ji Hyo placed 1st.
With 3 points, Jong Kook placed 2nd.
What? He placed second?
Haha and So Min are tied
for third place.
- They'll play rock-paper-scissors.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- So Min, you have a chance to win.
- Haha and So Min, go ahead.
Rock-paper-scissors, okay!
You did well.
Haha is in 3rd place,
and So Min is in 4th place.
Jae Suk placed 5th,
and Se Chan placed 6th.
- I'm doomed.
- Suk Jin placed seventh.
I'm doomed.
How many coins do we get this time?
- I wish I could place 1st...
- Do we get 30 coins?
- You get 35 coins.
- I wish I could win just once.
- Would you take all the coins?
- Suk Jin, we'll get five each.
- Of course.
- Guys, just take five coins.
Let's get out and collect the coins.
- Okay.
I haven't seen this in a long time.
We're doing this again.
The tray will be
on the conveyor belt.
Please go into the booth
according to your rankings.
Ji Hyo, you placed first.
- It'll be a war again.
- You placed first.
- I placed 1st.
- So Min, you placed 4th.
When will I be ranked high?
I want to place first
at least once before the end.
Let's all be reasonable.
You see, I have my own plan.
I don't even expect them
to leave any coins for us.
(Penalty List)
The water, fresh cream, and ink...
Those are the worst.
- Gosh.
- From 7 to 18 coins.
I want to avoid ink and cream.
I need at least 11 more coins.
I need 20 coins.
The face rubbing doesn't sound bad.
If I get 40 coins, I only have to
break a gourd bowl.
- Breaking a gourd bowl?
- Sophora root tea isn't so bad.
- I want an exemption.
- Flogging? I can bear with it.
- Flogging? Right.
- Yes. Flogging.
Suk Jin, what's your limit?
Dancing in the lobby?
- Dancing in the lobby?
- What's your limit?
- Dancing in the lobby.
- I see.
(4-6 coins: Dance to BTS
in the lobby without cameras.)
- I see.
- We'll begin now.
The conveyor belt will move.
Take as many coins as you want.
- Gosh.
- I left more than ten coins.
Everyone, take only five coins.
Just take one.
(The coin tray started moving.)
Just take 5 coins each.
Let's divide 35 coins evenly.
Ji Hyo, come on.
(Ji Hyo takes 15 coins.)
- Don't be too greedy.
- Okay.
I'm sure Ji Hyo didn't take
all the coins.
- Of course, she didn't.
- Don't take too many.
Did Ji Hyo take them all?
(There are 20 coins left.)
Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, leave some for me.
You're a reasonable person.
- Jong Kook.
- Let's divide 35 coins evenly.
- Let us have one coin each.
- You're a reasonable person.
(Jong Kook said he didn't need coins
because he'd cross the sky bridge.)
- Oh, I see.
- Jong Kook.
(4-6 coins: Dance to BTS
in the lobby without cameras.)
(7-10 coins: Have a bucket of ink
poured on you.)
(15-18 coins: Have a bucket of water
(He takes 15 coins suddenly.)
You might not place first again.
Just take them all.
No, I mean... Listen. Come closer.
Let's take 15 each
and get the water bucket penalty.
That sounds good.
- We take 15 each? The water bucket?
- Yes.
- Okay. That sounds good.
- What do you say?
(That's why he took 15 coins.)
Don't stick your head out.
We can't see your hands anyway.
It's blocked.
Stay inside the booth.
- Just let us have one each.
- But we want to see you.
You can see my hands.
- Gosh, seriously.
- You can see my hands.
- Jong Kook!
- Gosh. Hey.
- Haha.
- I'm older than you!
Haha!
- I bet he didn't leave any coins.
- Haha.
- There's no coin left.
- I guess it's empty.
- Okay.
- Really?
- They took all the coins.
- I guess it's empty.
- Ten coins...
- I don't expect to get any coins...
- because So Min is right before me.
- They took 20, 10, and 5 coins.
My gosh. They're so mean.
I mean...
- So Bal.
- I mean...
(There's nothing.)
- There's none left?
- Unbelievable.
(Flustered)
There's none left?
- Keep it coming.
- This was expected.
This is how I see it.
It's no use if you finish
below third.
- This is how I see it.
- You can't finish below third.
This is war.
Only winning matters at the moment.
I haven't seen a single coin today.
- I'm good.
- This is war.
- Please step forward.
- Let's go.
- Darn it.
- This is war.
- Where to?
- Suk Jin.
- What?
- We need to unite.
Yes, we should unite.
(So Min's the only one
with no coins.)
Are you kidding me?
- I can't believe it.
- If it weren't for Ji Hyo,
I could've ended up
on the sky bridge.
The two of you...
Suk Jin, please know
that we didn't get greedy.
What good does that do...
- when we're left with nothing?
- But Suk Jin...
- We were reasonable.
- You know...
- As if.
- So Min sees herself in Jamsil.
Exactly.
The tone was set this way...
- in the first round.
- I know.
- We couldn't help it.
- Now,
we'll play a simple game
where you can win ten coins.
- What is it?
- I'm going to win this one.
You will call anyone you know.
The three members whose calls
were answered the fastest...
will receive 5, 3,
and 2 coins respectively.
- We'll go one by one?
- We'll each make a call?
Yes, one by one.
This is crazy.
Someone who'll answer quickly?
- The fastest...
- Can it be anyone?
You can call anyone.
- I'm calling my wife.
- It can be anyone.
- Here we go.
- My wife might not pick up.
Please put it on speaker.
(Start)
Someone fast. Someone who isn't...
- working right now.
- Who should I call?
I'm curious too.
Hold on.
What's with her?
(Flustered)
We just talked a few minutes ago.
It's over for him.
- Hey, honey.
- Hello?
I'm here on Running Man.
I'll call you back, okay?
- Okay, good.
- I'll time you now.
This is bad news for me.
Would a celebrity
be a better choice?
- Can I go?
- Go ahead.
Please pick up.
I wonder who'll pick up immediately.
(Start)
(Who is So Min calling?)
Don't do this to me.
- She's calling her dad.
- Dad, come on.
- Really?
- You normally pick up instantly.
He picks up my phone in seconds.
Someone who'll answer quickly?
Dad!
(She surpasses Haha's record
which was 15 seconds.)
- He must be playing soccer.
- What's with you today?
- But my dad...
- There must be a soccer match.
- He always has his phone on him.
- Hello?
- Dad...
- What's her record?
- What is it?
- It's nothing.
- She's at 21 seconds.
- She failed.
I'll call you back.
- He has a sweet voice.
- Why did it take you so long...
to pick up?
- Who will it be?
- I'm calling Chang Hee.
- What?
- But I was going to call him.
- Go ahead, then.
They're arguing over Nam Chang Hee.
- Chang Hee...
- I'll call Chang Hee, then.
Then I'll call Sae Ho.
- Will you go first?
- I'll call Chang Hee.
He stays busy, so you never know.
- Doesn't he have a radio show?
- Please be in the middle of a show.
- I hope he's working right now.
- He has work today.
- His radio show.
- Please pick up, Chang Hee.
- Hi, Jae Suk.
- Chang Hee!
(It only took him 5 seconds!)
- No way.
- Chang Hee!
- How can this be?
- You're my savior.
- But Chang Hee was mine.
- Nam Chang Hee!
You are Nam Chang Hee
Where are you right now?
- It's as if he was on standby.
- I'm home at the moment.
- My gosh.
- Push back the interview.
You answered even before
your bell rang.
- You answered before it rang.
- Hang up, will you?
Chang Hee, thanks.
I'll call you later.
Sure thing.
- Who can I call?
- All right.
I'm calling my friend Sae Ho.
- I hope he doesn't answer.
- Go ahead.
- Come on, Sae Ho.
- This...
He's on standby on Mondays.
He'll need to answer
in four seconds.
Sae Ho, please.
It's a Monday.
- Se Chan.
- Sae Ho!
- No way.
- Sae Ho, you're the best!
(His record is 4 seconds.)
(No way.)
- Thank you so much.
- I should've called him instead.
I should've called Sae Ho!
- Sae Ho, we'll talk later. Thanks.
- Sae Ho didn't cross my mind.
- Sae Ho...
- I'll call you back.
He must've been on standby.
Okay!
- Sae Ho didn't cross my mind.
- My record is five seconds.
You should've called Sae Ho instead.
The game's already over for us.
- I should've called Sae Ho instead.
- That was fast.
I'll go next.
Jong Kook, go ahead.
(Jong Kook's up next.)
- That was fast, right?
- He picked up at lightning speed.
- Hello?
- That was fast.
Hey, Carlow.
(He's in 2nd place
along with Jae Suk!)
Five seconds.
He's the editor
for my online channel.
It's Carlow.
Of course his editor
would pick up immediately.
He works for you.
He's your...
He stays busy, you see.
- But you're his boss.
- I'm not.
He's a freelancer.
- Unbelievable.
- He has his own company.
Anyway, it took you five seconds.
- Okay, I'll go next.
- Thanks and bye.
- So Min...
- I shouldn't have called my dad.
- I'll go next.
- Sure.
How could my dad do this to me?
Yong Man wouldn't pick up.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Soo Hyun!
(It took her a second to pick up.)
Soo Hyun, you're my savior!
It was 1.5 seconds.
- She must've been on her phone.
- You're my savior.
Was she given word in advance?
- No way.
- This is crazy!
- One second?
- She had to be on her phone.
- Okay, I'll call you back.
- Sure thing.
- Last but not least...
Seok Sam's up.
- Nice!
- You...
You have to come in third.
Call someone
who'd be on their phone.
I'll call someone who works
with me on my channel.
I hope he picks up quickly.
- I hope he doesn't.
- He made the call.
I don't think he'll pick up.
Put it on speaker, Suk Jin.
- It's over.
- It's already over for me.
(It's already over.)
- Hey.
- That's eight seconds.
- I was filming and...
- I came in last again.
It's part of a game we're playing.
I'll call you back later.
- It wasn't bad.
- Got it.
His record isn't bad.
But the top three are untouchable.
Eight seconds
is a good enough record.
Ji Hyo came in 1st and
Se Chan came in 2nd.
You'll play rock-paper-scissors
to see who's in third.
(A game of rock-paper-scissors
will determine who's in 3rd place.)
- All right.
- As if this means anything.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Scissors. I won!
Okay, it's all good.
Getting a few more could
make you suffer something worse.
- I shouldn't take these.
- You know what I mean, right?
This is bad.
- The next one's face rubbing.
- I shouldn't take these.
- Could I give mine to others?
- You're right.
- Water bucket is better.
- This is bad.
- I badly want the whipped cream.
- We have a long way to go though.
We have a long way to go.
I still don't have any which means
I'll be on the sky bridge.
The sky bridge.
The next game...
will help improve
your improvisational skills...
which is a necessity
as a member on Running Man.
(On Running Man,
being good at improvising is key.)
The game is called...
- Too Many Personas.
- What is it?
(Running Man is a boss
at comedic sketches.)
(The sketches on Running Man
aren't usually scripted.)
Have you kissed a guy before?
(They were subjected
to various situations.)
(To stay on the show,
one must know how to improvise.)
(The game will help them
improve those skills.)
(Blind improvisational
comedy sketches)
Behind where
you were seated just now,
there are four rooms...
that are of different concepts.
For instance, you might find
a teachers' lounge.
We'll be improvising.
The second you enter
and take off your blindfold,
you will have to get into character.
Every time you say something
that fits the scene,
- we will give you points.
- That fits the scene?
- That fits the scene.
- I see.
If it were a teachers' lounge,
you can get points
by acting like teachers.
If you say something
that doesn't fit,
you won't score any points.
Suk Jin, I'm worried about you.
- You're bad at improvising.
- I might say something funny.
It won't be fair for those
who didn't go to school.
(If it's a teachers' lounge...)
- I'll have to avoid it, then.
- There are four different rooms.
You'll know once you head in there.
Got it.
Please don't let it be
the National Assembly.
Please note that after a while,
we will send in a certain object.
The object must be melted
into your improvisations.
Oh, no. I'm not that good
at improvisations though.
Once your time is up,
we'll announce it
through the megaphone.
In the hallway,
you'll find out who's been cut.
That person will come in last.
- All right.
- Please standby...
- while the cameras move in first.
- What do I do?
You have at least one coin, right?
- Of course.
- The water bucket is the best.
I'm the only one without any coins.
- Sophora root tea isn't so bad.
- So Min.
You need to go to Jamsil,
so cancel any plans you have.
If you were going to get a facial...
(So Min calls someone.)
Is it your dad?
- Who are you calling? Busan?
- My dad.
- Dad.
- Bucheon?
What took you so long
to pick up today?
Why? Is something wrong?
Gosh, I came in last.
(She complains to her dad
about picking up too late.)
You normally pick up instantly.
She's complaining to her dad.
So Min, come on.
Your dad has his own life...
and can't be glued to his phone.
It was a game and I came in last.
Why are you complaining
about it to your dad?
(She complains even though
she's the one bad at games.)
The others picked up instantly.
Maybe I should've called Mom.
All right, Dad.
(The cute daughter stops pestering.)
Bye.
If you move to the door,
we'll put the blindfold on you.
- Let's move.
- Get ready for a skit.
- Okay.
I should.
- Get ready for the skit.
- Get ready.
I will just follow Se Chan.
I'm ready.
- All right.
- Do I put on the blindfold?
- Or what happens?
- It's like the room escape game.
As soon as we enter...
Do we all start together?
Do we start together?
- What's going on?
- What's this?
- What are you doing?
- They're putting something on us.
What is this?
- They'll tell us to take it off.
- Take off your blindfold.
Okay.
- What is this?
(The first skit is...)
- What's this?
- Let's start the meeting.
(Doctors Academy Conference)
Doctors Academy... My.
(Glancing)
- Let's sit down.
- Yes.
- Dr. Yoo.
- Take a seat.
First, it's the intubation.
Connect him to the ventilator.
Get ready for the ligation.
A total of 14 is seen
in the CT scan.
That's what the CT scan shows,
but there could be more.
Yes. Let's begin now.
- It's going to be fun.
- I don't watch medical drama often.
Me neither.
(They never tried the doctor skit
due to lack of knowledge.)
- This is going to be fun.
- It's like the room escape game.
- Let's sit down.
- Yes.
- Dr. Yoo.
- Take a seat.
- What's this?
- My goodness, Dr. Ji.
- You're working after a long time.
- Did you...
- all have surgery?
- We're all wearing surgical gowns.
Are you ready for the seminar?
We do it every day.
- Dr. Jeon. Have a seat.
- It was a tough surgery today.
Dr. Song. What surgery
are you talking about?
- Dr. Ha. I'm sorry. I...
- Now that surgery is over...
- had organ transplantation today.
- What transplantation?
An organ transplantation.
You're an orthopedist. Why would you
perform organ transplantation?
Put your shoes on.
It seems it was one long surgery.
- Dr. Jeon.
- What?
- Are you doing organ trafficking?
- Why...
Why would an orthopedist perform
organ transplantation?
I'm a thoracic surgeon.
- What?
- I'm a thoracic surgeon.
Heungboo? Did you say Heungboo?
Are you getting turned on?
(Heungboo is dumbfounded)
I'm Nolboo.
I'm too tired. Let me just...
- Dr. Yang.
- Yes.
The word says
you didn't go to university.
I became a doctor without going
to university? That's not true.
Dr. Yang. How did the seminar go
in Jeju Island?
Oh, the seminar in Jeju Island?
It was very interesting.
There are a lot of comments
about it.
- People gathered and...
- I'm sorry,
but do you know what a seminar is?
A seminar?
Isn't that where you go and study?
Dr. Yang. Can you spell out seminar?
Hey. How dare you tell me
to spell it out?
- "Hey."
I'm getting a new MRI machine.
How about a group purchase?
- A group purchase?
- It's very expensive.
- MRI and CT scan.
What's your major?
Me?
- Neurosurgery.
- Pardon?
- Neurosurgery?
Neurosurgery? What do you do there?
(Laughing)
Dr. Ji.
What do you do?
- Dr. Ji.
- Do you want to hear it?
When I was on rounds today,
the patient...
seems to need surgery.
How are you going to do that?
- He doesn't need surgery.
- All of a sudden?
- Do you know what is going on?
- What?
- Hey.
- I'm sorry,
but where did you go on your rounds?
I hear the empty can sound
from her head.
- It's empty.
- Really?
I've already done suction
on that patient.
- Suction?
- Isn't that for dentists?
You do that during surgery.
That's for dentists.
- Sir.
- You do that during surgery.
- Do you know who that is?
- Who?
(Hippocrates, father of medicine)
Hip-hop something.
- Hippocrates.
Did you say hippo?
I said hip-hop.
- Hippo?
- Hiphopcrates.
You all know his oath.
Let's recite it.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Can you recite the Hippocratic Oath?
As you all know...
- Let's do it together.
- Shall we do it together?
- Shall we?
- All together.
- Oath.
- I...
In order to...
Let's say one word each.
Next person.
In order to...
Become a proud doctor...
- What?
- Go ahead. You know it.
But we must not joke about it.
It's a skit. It's fine.
It's a skit, but it must...
Then do it for real.
It must be based on facts.
Recite the real oath.
- You want me to do it?
- You know it.
Hippocratic Oath.
- Oath.
I am...
A pushover.
I am a pushover.
- I'm okay.
- Dr. Ha is funny.
- He's funny.
- I'm a pushover.
What's your major?
- Someone's here.
- Dr. Song is very quiet today.
You have a patient.
- My.
- What's this?
(They get pork belly
all of a sudden.)
(You earn points if you put on
the appropriate skit with the prop.)
(Nervous)
(What am I supposed to do
with that?)
- My.
- What's this?
This is serious.
It's full of fat.
It's a serious fatty liver problem.
This guy's in very
serious condition.
If I were to comment...
How dare you?
Check the patient's vitals first.
As you can see, he has too much fat.
He didn't take care of himself.
Why are you suddenly
taking his pulse?
Don't touch the patient
with your hand.
Dr. Ji.
You need to sanitize your hands
before taking the pulse.
Are you an oriental medicine doctor?
Don't take a pulse here.
You're supposed to make it realistic.
Exactly.
Let me get some blood.
- Let me get some blood.
- It's already been removed.
Do you know where the vein is?
It's right below the bone.
(Laughing)
- Where's the artery?
- It's above the bone.
- I...
- Wait!
Leave the pork belly
to me and Dr. Kim.
You're pork belly experts.
I just measured the blood pressure.
It's at 401.
Is that so?
- The rates...
- Hold on.
The vitals are unstable.
- Vitals? What are vitals?
- And...
The pulse.
But...
My goodness.
- Let's diagnose his illness first.
- Wait.
This isn't domestic.
Are you neglecting him
because he's from abroad?
What kind of nonsense is that?
(Action)
(Sniffing)
She's right. It's from the US.
- Can you tell from the smell?
- Yes.
I don't know anything
about medicine.
He seems to have a tumor.
- A tumor?
- You mean the bone?
- Don't you know what a tumor is?
- The cartilage?
- I got a call. I'm going to the ER.
- Where?
- I got a call. I'll be right back.
- If it's malignant,
it might be a serious problem.
She's using the lines she said
in her previous drama.
(Locking)
- You need to say the truth.
- It's locked.
- Okay.
- This is...
- absurd.
- Who is it?
Who is it?
Can't you take it more seriously?
- Why do you keep walking around?
- We have a patient here.
- Hey!
- Wait a minute.
So Min. You're acting alone.
So Min.
Can't you cooperate with us?
That doesn't match the situation.
She's pretending
her patient is dead.
You're acting like it's a drama.
- Shush.
- She's...
She's suffering from mental illness.
You know she's a patient.
Play along.
- Let's play along.
- Yes. She's a patient.
Her dream was to become a doctor.
Let's give her a break.
- Dear doctors.
- Yes.
Please move to the hallway.
- To the hallway?
- Yes.
Why does he want us in the hallway?
Don't go any further.
Stay in the hallway.
We'll announce who is eliminated.
The eliminated person.
(When you make sense,
you get a point.)
Weren't we pretty good?
This is pretty hard.
- It was hard.
There are blindfolds.
- The first...
- I don't know any medical terms.
- person to be eliminated.
- I put on method acting.
(Revealing the first
eliminated person)
(Please wait here.)
Here it is.
(Song Ji Hyo is out.)
Song Ji Hyo.
- Why me?
- You were quiet.
- Please go out the door.
- You need to leave.
- You have to leave.
- Get out.
- Ji Hyo is out.
- Is this a survival?
- What?
The rest of you should put on
the blindfold again.
- It's a difficult skit.
- It's hard.
That was such an absurd prop.
- It was pork belly.
- And there is no operating table.
We need to perform surgery,
but there's no operating table.
(What's waiting for them
in the next room?)
- Take off your blindfold.
- Okay.
- Take it off?
- What's going on?
(Take off the blindfold.)
- Take it off?
- Do we take it off?
What is this?
(Judges' gathering)
A self-defense is not a preparation
for past or future invasion,
but it must be a preparation
for invasion in the present.
Do we take it off?
- All right.
- All right. Let's have a seat.
- Do I take the blindfold off?
- Head Judge.
- Oh, yes.
- Grab a seat.
- Why...
- You should sit in the middle.
I'm the head judge.
What are you talking about?
- Keep quiet in court!
- Are you the head judge?
- Did you...
- Did you take the bar exam?
- I did. I took the 29th bar exam.
- I'm sorry,
didn't you pass the exam
after I did?
- We all passed in the same year.
- Though I was a bit late...
You must uphold
the majesty and order in court.
I know you're older,
but you're my junior.
Though I was late...
You were too late.
Excuse me, manager?
- Bring me the document.
- Aide Yoo.
- Yes?
- Bring me some tea.
What?
Can't you see
I'm in the judge's robe?
- Take it off.
- Constitution Article 7 Protocol 3.
Don't lean. Don't you know?
- And...
- That's nonsense.
some people went to law school.
- Law school? I majored in law.
- Wait.
- Yes?
- Didn't you go to I Love School?
No.
I went to Yongmoon High School.
- Which law school did you go to?
- What?
I took the bar exam.
The bar exam? I knew it.
You were suddenly
talking about law school.
When did you pass it?
- What?
- When?
When did you pass?
What about you?
- He's a junior.
- I'm the 29th.
- I'm the 25th!
- You're the 25th?
I'm the 23rd.
I'm the 21st.
How dare you?
He slapped me hard.
Wait.
- Look.
- Sorry?
How about you?
- I...
- How about you, Judge So Min?
I had connections.
It seems like you don't know,
but you can't become a judge
through connections.
I can't?
You should have good grades
at the training institute.
- I should?
- Of course.
- She knows nothing about the law.
- By the way,
I really like Judge Kim.
- He wrote history.
- When?
"From a Thug to a Judge."
- Have you read that book?
- I actually...
had a grudge about the ruling.
- Right.
- And I decided to become a judge.
- Is that possible?
- Judge Kim.
You know the law
you accepted recently.
- "The law you accepted?"
- From the Constitutional Court?
- It sounded like "silver grass."
It's harsh to sentence the defendant
to a three years imprisonment...
for urinating in public.
- He didn't just urinate.
- Okay.
He was naked when he did it.
(Standing up)
Ms. Jeon.
What's the matter, Judge Jeon?
- Judge Jeon.
- Judge Jeon, what's wrong?
I...
despise the boy.
- But So Min.
- Why...
You're not in a drama.
Did you see it on Netflix?
- Do you want to be in a drama?
- Yes.
You must know this.
- The number of judges...
- I know.
at the Constitutional Court.
- Of course, I know.
- Three.
- That's the basic.
- Why wouldn't we know?
- I know.
Do you know
what the Constitutional Court is?
- I know.
- What do they do?
- They judge the constitution.
- How many judges are there?
How many judges
are at the Constitutional Court?
- At the Constitutional Court?
- We learned it.
- How many? You learned it.
- At the Constitutional Court?
There are three judges
at the "Current" Court.
It's "Constitutional,"
not "Current."
It's Constitutional Court.
"Current Court."
It's not current, past, and future.
- It was a joke.
- And there are nine judges.
- What do they do?
- It's nine.
The Constitutional Court...
makes the final decision
about state affairs.
Why do they make the final decision?
Such as the impeachment
of the president.
No. They decide whether it violates
the constitution or not.
They make the final decision
about that.
Okay, you're smart.
The nine judges...
- Wait.
- You...
- "You're smart?"
- You're smart.
- That's not what I'm trying to say.
- Junior Ji.
- "Junior Ji?"
- It's a simple...
You passed the 25th bar exam.
That's true,
- but this punk passed the 28th.
- "This punk?"
- I think you're my junior.
- Hey.
- According to the law...
- Do you even know it?
Come on.
Stop.
- You're weird.
- Stop it.
How can you sentence him
to a three years imprisonment...
for urinating in public?
- In Korea...
- He's my junior.
- That's enough.
- Urinating in public...
- I said he had been naked.
- Three years?
- All right.
- Sir, what upsets me...
is that this punk stole
my son's bicycle.
- What?
- Who is he to judge?
- Okay.
- Hey.
- What's outside belongs to others.
- Everyone is equal...
- in front of the law.
- What?
For stealing...
Listen. We're here today...
- as we need all hands on deck.
- Okay.
- So I want to ask you this.
- Ask what?
- About urinating in public.
- Okay.
It's a minor offense.
We can finish it quickly.
But he sentenced him
to three years' imprisonment.
He filed a lawsuit.
His friend turned on the headlight
of the car...
towards him who was urinating.
So he felt humiliated.
He filed a lawsuit
as he had felt humiliated.
- For the invasion of privacy.
- Privacy.
- And many other things.
- He made him nervous.
- Did he pee not hard enough?
- The judges...
- Burbling.
- are divided...
- about this.
- I know this case.
I know it,
but I side with the one
who urinated.
- Honestly...
- You're at his side?
His friend
turned on the headlight...
- in front of him.
- What?
Who is it?
We're in the middle of a meeting.
- It's the evidence you requested.
- We're in the middle of a meeting.
(Doenjang, the evidence, is here.)
He took this.
So he pooped.
Is urinating pooping?
(Another accusation against A)
- He could've stopped here.
- It's poop.
He could've stopped here,
but he pooped on the street
as it was urgent.
- He pooped.
- Yes.
- To find clear evidence,
- So we took...
- give it a taste.
- this poop...
- from the scene.
- Give it a taste.
(Dipping)
It's poop.
- I said it's poop.
- You touched poop.
- He pooped in public.
- Pooped in public.
He has healthy intestines.
Considering the color
and the volume,
he must've not been able to hold in.
- He has healthy intestines.
- You should understand him.
He would've not pooped
if it hadn't been urgent.
- Okay. Sit down.
- I know.
- Make a decision.
- Hold on.
What do you want to have?
Solomon's seal tea.
Wait. We stopped
talking about the law at some point.
(We stopped talking
about the law at some point.)
(Spitting out)
- Excuse me.
- Right now...
What was it?
- All of a sudden...
- Come on.
- Judge Jeon.
- We stopped talking about the law.
- Let's just have dinner.
- Forget about other things.
Do you think he will have dinner?
Let's just drink something...
- as we have something to drink.
- Sir, where will we have dinner?
- Hey!
- Why?
Do you think we're joking here?
You're wearing shorts.
Seriously...
- You punk.
- Hey.
- Do you think it's a joke?
- You're wearing a cap.
- You punk.
Hey, your glasses don't have lenses.
He's nitpicking
as he got nothing to say.
How dare you come here in shorts?
- Look at his glasses.
- It's ridiculous.
I mean... Look.
You're playing a judge.
Stick to the original plot.
How dare you come here in shorts?
He's not a judge.
Is the court a joke to you?
You're ridiculous.
Judge Kim is wearing them as well.
Come here.
Do a plank.
Jae Suk, what's wrong with you?
Do judges do that?
- This is unfair.
- Come here.
- Hey.
- Let's...
talk about the law.
Didn't you come wearing jeans?
- Hey.
- Right?
You should wear pants at least.
He's wearing shorts too.
- He's wearing shorts too.
- What?
You guys should be careful.
Judges, gather in the hallway.
He's so ignorant.
Being a judge is difficult.
- I can't do it.
- I'll just get eliminated.
- It's hard for me.
- It's hard.
I don't know what's next, but...
- I mean...
- I can play a teacher or something.
- Playing a judge is hard.
- He's wearing shorts.
- How can I act like a judge?
- I can't play a judge.
I can't.
It was like, "Okay. I got you."
I'll announce the person
who is eliminated.
- I'll announce it.
- Me too.
(Who is the second person
to be eliminated?)
Playing a judge is...
(Se Chan is eliminated.)
Thank goodness. I can't do it.
- I can't do it either.
- Because of the "Current Court."
- Why are you eliminated?
- It's the "Current Court."
- I can't do this.
- Please leave, Se Chan.
Wear your blindfold.
I'll get used to it.
I can't play a judge. It's hard.
The judge at the "Current Court."
They're dying.
They're like, "I can't do this."
This is hard.
- Let's go.
- I'll get eliminated this time.
- Me too.
- Where are we?
Okay.
Can we take it off?
- Take it off.
I'm in trouble.
- What's this? We're scientists.
- Scientists.
(2022 Noble Prizes in science go
to 5 scientists including Jae Suk.)
(You need to know difficult science
terms to play a Noble Prize winner.)
- Let's sit.
- Let's sit down.
- Gosh, this is...
- We...
Here they go again.
They will sit down,
check the hierarchy, and argue.
- Scientists who came to receive...
- Sit down.
What did you study?
I studied stem cells.
What stem cells?
- Muscles and tendons.
- Okay.
- Muscles and tendons?
- Yes. For regeneration.
Stem cells...
to regenerate...
damaged muscles and tendons.
- Isn't he a YouTuber?
- Yes?
- I saw you often.
- I do that too.
- I have my own channel too.
- You do?
- How about you?
- Actually,
I'm the first one...
- The kidney of a pig.
- The kidney of a pig?
- Transplant?
- Oh, I see.
You're running
a pork belly restaurant?
- The kidney of a pig.
- Pork...
I transplanted it into a human body
for the first time.
The person has survived
for eight years.
- Didn't he pass away recently?
- Who is it?
- Sorry?
Would you even know
if I say his name?
Why do you speak informally?
- Gosh.
- Is he alive?
He's James.
There they go.
They will start arguing. Look.
In addition,
as the result was successful,
I had more time.
So I made seedless avocados.
- Seedless avocados?
- Don't you like avocados?
- Are you a successor of Dr. Woo?
Seedless humpkins.
You're the doctor from
"Parasite," right?
- He's...
- It's...
Seedless "humpkins?"
(He got his tongue twisted
as he couldn't think of adlibs.)
Seedless what?
What are seedless "humpkins?"
Isn't he Dr. Nose?
Dr. Nose?
- Oh, Dr. Nose?
- Dr. Nose.
The master of origami, right?
Dr. Nose is a nickname.
- It's a nickname.
- Yes.
- I...
- So...
Come in.
(An item for the skit is coming.)
This is what I study. Give it to me.
(They flock
as soon as they see the stone.)
So it was here.
This is the heart of a pig.
No, it's not.
- It's the heart of a pig.
- It's a stone.
- It's from the moon.
- I didn't know it was here.
It's from the moon.
Watching them here,
I can see those who are uneducated
can't join.
Those who are uneducated can't join.
Haha and So Min are quiet.
I study human history.
I've been studying
the Old Stone Age again.
- That's what you've been doing?
- I study how to prevent aging.
So you study skin?
- I'm sorry.
- How old are you?
- Anti-aging properties.
- Excuse me.
- I...
- Anti-aging properties.
- Actually, this is...
- Yes.
Ji Hyo.
- Is this Ji Hyo?
- Did she turn into this?
- She was born as a stone.
- She was born as a stone?
She wanted to be born as a stone.
- That's what she said.
- I turned her into a stone.
This is an artificial heart I made.
- What?
- It's beating.
- You know what?
- What?
I don't think
you're good at role-playing.
It looks like a liver.
- The shape is...
- I think it's a liver.
This is...
- Isn't it more like a liver?
- This is a heart.
I think you're practicing BTS dance.
This is...
- Guys.
- This is the human heart.
I don't know if I can say this,
but you know Nature,
- Nature?
- the world's leading journal.
- I know Nature.
- I know it.
- Recently,
the world praised me for my work
on anti-aging substances.
I'm sorry, but do you not use
those substances for yourself?
- The ones you developed.
- I...
I'm not sure if you're going to
believe it, but I was born in 1930.
- You were born in 1930?
- I was born in 1927.
(He attacks him as soon as he said
his age as if he has been waiting.)
- How...
- Is it the anti-aging properties?
- What did you use?
- Yes.
- Hey.
- Why?
- You were born in 1927?
- You can't do it to someone older.
- He's older than you.
- Were you born in 1927?
- Yes.
- Sir.
You punk.
They always...
- Don't use a casual tone with me.
- You were born early.
- In which year were you born?
- Me?
- That's right,
- I was born in 1966.
You punk.
There is no way
you were born in 1930.
I was born in 1930.
You don't look that way.
- You went through liberation.
- That's right.
- He went through the war too.
- For a second...
Here is the thing. Back in the day,
- my family members were nobles.
- I see.
Do you think
our family members were commoners?
- So my old habits came out.
- I am sorry,
but you stopped talking
about science.
I waited for this moment.
You stopped talking about science.
- You are talking about history.
- No.
I am sorry that I slapped you.
I had a mortal enemy.
A mortal enemy?
- Why did you suddenly kiss a rock?
- Why did you kiss a rock?
My goodness.
What did you do to Ji Hyo?
What are you doing?
Why did you suddenly kiss a rock?
- Why did you kiss Ji Hyo?
- What did you do to Ji Hyo?
What was that?
- Suddenly...
- This is my invention.
- Still, it's Ji Hyo.
- This isn't Ji Hyo.
You punk.
- Suddenly...
- Why did you kiss Ji Hyo?
- It's my artificial heart.
They are fighting again.
- Why did you kiss Ji Hyo?
- Is this Ji Hyo?
- All right, everyone.
- Okay.
Now, I will share...
- the research findings.
- Go ahead.
- Give me a break.
- Share the research findings.
- Let's hear them.
- Hey!
He will share the research findings.
He thinks he is a doctor.
Give me a break.
- Go ahead.
- Let's hear them.
I want to find out
how he got the Nobel Prize.
Like I said earlier,
my research covered
the origin of mankind...
and the Paleolithic Period.
You might think
that this is a simple rock,
but there is a reason why
it was used as an axe.
- Keep going. What is it about?
- What?
- Keep going.
- Scientists.
- Yes?
Please gather around
in the corridor.
I didn't get to talk about
this rock.
- That was insane.
- It was so hard.
I hope I survive.
- Are there four rooms?
- Who will be eliminated this time?
- Let's see it.
- For goodness' sake.
(Who will be the third member
to get eliminated?)
- Let's see it.
- For goodness' sake.
- Okay.
- So Min.
(So Min got eliminated.)
- I understand.
- So Min got eliminated.
- So Min.
- Jae Suk.
So Min, take the rock.
Take it. It will be funny.
- It won't come out.
- All right.
- Take off the blindfold.
- Okay.
(What will be the setting
for the last improv comedy?)
Right now...
(Summit meeting)
I am the president.
This weekend,
the G7 Summit will take place.
(R4 Summit)
(Gosh.)
- My goodness.
- I am the president.
(The 4 presidents enter.)
- Pretending to be a doctor...
- There is a pattern.
- was too...
- When they enter,
they briefly play their roles.
Then the topic of age comes up
and they begin to fight.
- That's it.
- I couldn't enter the conversation.
I couldn't. Is it a summit meeting?
How... Now...
The heads of the four countries
came together for a summit meeting.
It's nice to meet you.
- Today,
- I must sign this.
- we have many things to decide on.
- I have something to do.
I apologize, but I need to launch
a nuclear weapon.
Pardon?
- A nuclear weapon?
- Are you insane?
- President Ji.
- Well,
- it's only an experiment.
- Listen.
Where are you having
that experiment?
We are here to discuss
the spread of nuclear arms.
- It's a sensitive issue.
- It's a sensitive issue indeed.
How could you bring it up so easily?
- It's just that...
- Listen.
When will you pay me back?
- Do I owe you money?
- When will you pay me back?
How much do I owe?
For goodness' sake.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
I apologize for calling you
by your name.
President Ji.
- Seriously.
- Call me Pre-Ji.
How did you become the president?
I became one
through a national election.
- I am sorry, but...
- Was there an election?
- Of course.
- You used illegal means.
What are you talking about?
- Don't say that!
- I heard such rumors.
(He is bad at acting.)
They will talk about
seniority again.
You turned the nation upside down.
- Because of you,
- It's a matter of my country.
- people are suffering.
- In your country,
- people want a new president.
- It's insane.
For how many years
have you been the president?
The approval rating is
at 68 percent.
- Excuse me?
- What's your approval rating?
- What's up with that tone?
- Yours is at 15 percent.
- Hold on.
- No one can become the president...
- with that approval rating.
- Hold on.
There are rumors
that you fabricated the rating.
You took over the media.
You fabricated the rating.
You banned social media.
- What is my country anyway?
- You banned handwritten letters.
- Seriously.
Which country is it?
That's another country.
- Pink country, yellow country, etc.
- Is that so?
They will talk about
private matters now.
Four countries' summit meeting.
Did you go on a hunger strike?
Baldness runs in my family.
- You have hair.
- Baldness runs in my family.
(As expected, they begin to talk
about private matters.)
- For goodness' sake.
- I can't believe these people.
Protruding trap runs in your family.
- Trap?
- Listen.
Criticizing appearances
won't do you any good.
- What are you talking about?
- You have a protruding trap.
Among these four people,
I am number two
in terms of appearances.
- For goodness' sake.
- This is driving me crazy.
- What are you talking about?
- We are number one and number two.
- Give me a break.
- You are at the very bottom.
- And...
- What will you do if it's a lie?
- President Kim.
- Yes?
I don't know about anything else,
but you give children
protein-centered meals.
- All the kids are getting gout.
- The kids...
Children need to eat balanced meals.
Those brats should look
after their own health.
"Those brats?"
They are responsible for it.
- They are your people.
- As the president,
you should look out
for the citizens.
- They eat other food too.
- By the people, for the people.
Other food they eat
will give them...
- carbohydrates and fat.
- How did you become the president?
The government
just gives them protein.
- How did you become the president?
- Excuse me?
I fought, okay?
We had a UFC-style election.
- You fought?
- Yes.
- Was that how you got elected?
- That was how I got elected.
- Let's not mind him.
- Excuse me?
- We should talk without him.
- What's the GNP in that country?
- Mister.
- Forget about GNP.
- I have a problem with this.
How could you doodle...
- during a summit meeting?
- I didn't doodle.
- What are you doing?
I was thinking about GDP and GNP.
GDP and GNP?
What's the GDP in your country?
- He is saying everything he knows.
- What's the GDP in your country?
It's over 50,000 dollars.
I bet the Ji family
monopolized everything.
- Seriously.
- In the past few years,
everyone struggled due to COVID-19.
We should think of a solution.
Opening up the borders
to tourists is a sensitive issue.
- Okay.
- Come to my country.
- Come. Send the tourists.
- Why won't you open up the borders?
I will talk
to the ministry of foreign affairs.
- Come.
- Hold on.
Their citizens can come,
but not yours.
- Your citizens can't come.
- Why not?
- Hold on.
- He is a nuisance.
It doesn't matter...
because neither my citizens nor I
want to go to this country.
All my citizens were upset
about President Ji participating...
- in this summit meeting.
- Nonsense.
The country is too small.
- In this summit meeting.
- Nonsense.
The country is too small.
- Stay still!
- Hold on.
- Please give me one.
- Hey.
- Stay still!
- Hold on.
- Please give me one.
- Hey.
- Stay still!
- Hold on. Please give me one.
This is the reason why
I asked for a summit meeting.
- Sit down.
- Calm down.
- Calm down. I will use this.
- That's a chamber pot.
- I will throw this.
- He wants to pee.
- I will detonate a bomb.
- Stay still.
- I have a bomb.
- I will throw this.
- Sit down.
- Stay still. I will pour this.
- Stay still.
- I will pour this.
- I will put this on my head.
- Sit down.
- Stay still.
- I will put this on my head.
- Sit down.
(He suddenly provokes them.)
- Stay still.
- Don't come near me.
- I will put this on my head.
- Stay still.
- Step down as president.
- What?
- I will do that if you save me.
- Step down.
- Sit down.
- You have been one for too long.
I was elected by the people.
- Sign it.
- Sign what?
Sign a document
that waives taxes on my citizens.
Customs.
Customs clearance. That thing.
Don't you know the words?
- Listen.
- Aren't you the president?
Waive the duty.
- Duty-free.
- But the free trade policies...
- Don't make me shoot.
- Okay.
- Where are you going?
- It's nothing.
- Hey. Where are you going?
- What are you doing?
- He is trying to run.
- Sit down.
- Duty-free.
- Sign it.
- Okay.
- President Kim.
Let's have an FTA,
a free trade agreement.
FTA?
I will give you FTA.
- I will do that.
- Why are you using a dialect?
I will give you FTA.
- Don't make me shoot.
- Shoot!
(Shooting relentlessly)
It's a war!
- Shoot!
- Die!
(A water bomb war breaks out.)
It's a war!
Die!
- Hurrah!
- All of us will die.
All of us will die.
Die!
- All of us will die.
- Die!
- Freedom!
- It's a disaster.
The summit meeting ended like that.
- All of us will die.
- Die!
- Freedom!
- It's a disaster.
- A disaster.
- Presidents, please gather around.
We are really bad at this.
Each one is the same.
- The buildup is the same.
- Seriously.
- The buildup.
- You begin.
- We say everything we know.
- "How old are you?"
(Pattern 1: Use a polite tone
to ask everyone to sit down.)
(Pattern 2: Bring up seniority
when you have nothing to say.)
(Pattern 3: When someone answers,)
(claim that you have seniority.)
(Waiting for the talk of seniority)
(It always ends as a dogfight.)
(Every improv comedy
proceeded the same way.)
The costumes change,
but the plot doesn't.
We wait for someone to ask,
"How old are you?"
We fight because we have
no knowledge.
Thus, Ji Hyo is in 7th place
since she got eliminated 1st.
Se Chan is in 6th place
and So Min is in 5th place.
- I won't get any coins, right?
- As for the four remaining members,
we counted the advanced terms
and expressions you used.
In first place is Jae Suk.
- In second place is Jong Kook.
- Why?
- In 3rd place is Haha.
- Why am I in 4th place?
- In fourth place is Suk Jin.
- I used advanced terms.
GDP.
- This changes things.
- What should I do?
- Can I enter?
- Yes.
Okay.
Can you leave some coins behind?
Jae Suk, leave us some coins.
- Let's see.
- I need one more for flogging.
(Jae Suk is in 1st place
with 13 coins.)
Jae Suk, you don't need
to take a lot.
I don't have any coins.
Leave us some coins.
Of course.
Watch your hands.
(Thirty-five coins begin
to get distributed.)
(He charges at the coins.)
(Taking all the coins)
He is taking them all.
He isn't leaving any coins behind.
(30-39 coins:
Drink sophora root tea)
(He takes 20 coins.)
There is no need for hope.
- Listen to that sound.
- He took all the coins.
All right.
Please. They might strategize
and not take any more coins.
- I don't have any coins.
- Who will do the flogging?
Jong Kook, you don't need
that many coins.
You have a lot of coins.
You don't need more.
(Which penalty
will Jong Kook choose?)
- It's because...
- Settle with the fresh cream.
I am done.
(Haha only has 5 coins.)
Haha.
- Go easy on us. Dance to BTS.
- I guess there aren't any coins.
Haha, dancing to BTS
is a better choice.
Haha, you will dance to BTS, right?
- Haha, I don't have any coins.
- You get greedy.
If you take more coins,
you will get a bucket of ink.
Ink and fresh cream are the worst.
Hold on.
I decided to be nice
and left some coins behind.
I left some coins behind.
- I left some coins behind.
- Okay.
(He only took 1 coin.)
I took it easy.
(Only 4 coins remain.)
- I guess there aren't any.
- Right?
- I took it easy.
- Se Chan, I guess there aren't any.
So Min will need to go to Jamsil.
I will need to go to Jamsil.
(Suk Jin currently has 4 coins.)
Let's dance together.
He is choosing
between penalties, right?
That's right.
He is choosing a better one.
(Thinking hard)
Everyone prefers different things.
(Will he dance to BTS
or get a bucket of ink?)
Okay. I will think about it.
Suk Jin decided to dance to BTS
so that he can stay clean.
- That's right.
- I left some coins behind.
(Two coins reach So Min.)
So Min can choose the next penalty.
She will carry out the penalty
for the opening next week.
(2-3 coins: Wear a costume
and makeup for the opening.)
Let's wear a costume
and makeup for the opening.
It's the most bothersome.
- The opening or the sky bridge.
- The opening.
You have a choice now.
- You gave her that choice.
- Yes.
- So Min.
- I gave her that choice.
- Go with the opening.
- You have one more chance.
Didn't you take any?
I can't believe it.
I left those coins for you.
I prefer the sky bridge.
(Se Chan currently has 23 coins.)
Okay.
Next.
The coins reached the end.
(The coins reached the end
for the first time.)
- Everyone is adjusting now.
- All right.
- Okay.
The distribution is over.
Please gather around.
(The 2 remaining coins
go to Ji Hyo.)
I will give you the rules.
This is your last chance...
- to avoid the worst penalty.
- What is it?
A single choice will change
the rankings...
- in Choice Playbook.
- Oh, no.
On the three tables
that will be brought in...
- will have signs for places.
- Really?
- The first place.
- That's so simple.
Table 1 has the 1st and 7th places.
(1st and 7th places)
Table 2 has the 2nd and 6th places.
Table 3 has
the 3rd, 4th, and 5th places.
Pick the table you want.
If more people want the same table,
decide by rock-paper-scissors.
So Min, you have to aim
for the first place.
Who will go
for the 1st or 7th place?
- The 1st or 7th place?
- The two of them.
- Hold on. The 1st or 7th place?
- Me too.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Come on.
- Why?
The member who is the first place...
- won't leave any coins behind.
- Seriously.
- He or she will take everything.
- So we have to aim for it.
- I will go for table one.
- Same here.
The 1st or 7th place.
- Which one?
- The 1st or 7th place.
There are 4 people
who want the 1st or 7th place.
- The 2nd or 6th place.
There are 2 people
who want the 2nd or 6th place.
Two of you will go to the table
with 3rd, 4th, and 5th places.
- The 1st or 7th place.
- Yes.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(So Min and Suk Jin won.)
The 2 of you will go to the table
with 3rd, 4th, and 5th places.
- Please.
- One of you will also go there.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play
rock-paper-scissors as well.)
Bring in the tables.
(The table with 2nd and 6th places:
Ji Hyo and Se Chan)
- The seventh place.
- I love it.
You will either be
the 1st place or 7th place.
- If So Min gets the first place,
- That's right.
she will get the sophora root tea.
- Hold it up at the same time.
- Who knows what So Min will pick?
- This is nerve-racking.
- Sophora root tea.
I am so nervous. What should I do?
- I should have gotten this table.
- Look at that.
I should have gotten this table.
This one looks dreary.
I will choose the other one.
- All right. Just grab it.
- Hold it up at the same time.
- All right.
- Please let it be the first place.
If it's the first place,
you will be set.
Hold it up. One, two...
(Who will take the 1st place?)
Three.
(7th place, 1st place)
(So Min got the 1st place.)
(Screaming)
(She runs around screaming.)
Jong Kook, it's meaningless.
- It's meaningless.
- She will take all the coins.
(A miraculous story
of the Jamsil sky bridge girl)
Okay!
(Jong Kook, it's meaningless.)
She will take all the coins.
So Min will take all the coins.
She came from behind.
- Okay.
- She came from behind.
Please go ahead.
She might not take all the coins.
You never know.
- You never know.
- The 2nd or 6th place.
- Which one do you want?
- One, two, three.
Ji Hyo got the second place.
It's meaningless.
One, two, three.
- The 3rd place.
- The 4th place.
Please enter the box.
- The fourth place...
- It's meaningless.
It's meaningless.
I won't get any coins.
It's meaningless to be first place.
All right.
- It's too bad.
- Tell me about your stories.
We have no stories. Just go.
- Just go.
- No.
We have enough coins
for the penalties we want.
We are satisfied.
You can have the sophora root tea.
Hold on.
- Sophora root tea.
- How many coins do you have?
- I can't tell you.
- Come on.
So Min, I know you want to enjoy
the power, but just do it.
- We are okay.
- I have to take...
the remaining coins, right?
Yes.
If I end up taking more coins...
(Suk Jin is worried about
taking more coins.)
- You won't get coins.
- A bucket of ink, right?
- We will start the conveyor belt.
- Okay.
So Min should take everything.
I bet she will take all the coins.
- She should do that.
- I bet she will do that.
So Min doesn't have any coins,
so she will take everything.
- Take 30 coins for the tea.
- Yes. Take 30 coins.
That's right.
You don't need to go all the way
to the sophora root tea.
You need 30 coins
for the sophora root tea.
Take 24 coins for flogging.
Let's leave the remaining coins
and give Suk Jin a bucket of ink.
Yes.
- You don't need to do that.
- What do you think?
- I will get the tea.
- Let's give him that penalty.
- That's right.
Hey!
Hold on.
(Meanwhile, So Min thinks hard.)
I picked the penalty I want.
Go on.
Flogging isn't so bad.
- What?
- That's right.
So Min, what's this? Hold on.
Why?
(So Min left 20 coins!)
(Ji Hyo takes 10 additional coins.)
So Min, which penalty will you get?
The water bucket.
Are you satisfied with that?
That way, they will receive
worse penalties.
- You are incredible.
- Worse penalties.
I respect you so much.
That way, they will receive
worse penalties.
You dance to BTS
if you have 4 to 6 coins.
- Suk Jin has at least four coins.
- There is no need...
to worry about me.
(The remaining coins
get delivered to Haha.)
(My goodness.)
(There are 10 coins.)
(Haha gave up
and settled on dancing to BTS.)
(Dance to BTS and get applauded
in the lobby without cameras.)
(He controlled
the number of coins for that.)
(He has an unexpected choice.)
Haha, leave some coins behind
for the ink bucket.
(7-10 coins:
Get hit with an ink bucket)
Die.
(Never mind then.)
(Haha sacrificed himself
for the ink bucket project.)
- Is he sending the coins?
- What?
- He is loyal.
- Why are there so many coins?
- Really?
Perhaps your plan will fall through.
Hold on. Maybe
I should take some coins.
You need to spare me 3 or 4 coins.
Where?
(He becomes nervous.)
- If you want the ink show...
- The ink bucket.
- If you want the ink show,
- I see.
I should get four coins.
Then the ink show will take place.
I see. Jong Kook,
do you want the sophora root tea?
If it's possible, I will go for it.
Otherwise,
I will enjoy the ink show.
(They begin to calculate
the number of coins.)
- In that case...
How many coins does Suk Jin have?
- Let's enjoy the tea together.
- I will leave you ten coins then.
I will send you four coins.
Five coins for the fresh cream.
(7-10 coins:
Get hit with an ink bucket)
- Suk Jin.
- All right.
(Suk Jin shows a mysterious smile
when 4 coins reach Se Chan.)
- How many coins do you have?
- I can't tell you that.
- What?
- Can't you tell me?
- I can't tell you that.
How bothersome.
(The ink show is about to open.)
How many coins will you give me?
Enjoy that ink.
(Enjoy that ink.)
Please take the remaining coins.
He has to take them.
Must I take them?
Yes.
Please count the coins you have.
(They will reveal the final number.)
- So Min, how many do you have?
- I have 15 coins.
So Min has 15 coins.
I have 31 coins.
Ji Hyo has 31 coins.
I have six coins.
(Dance to BTS and get applauded
in the lobby without cameras.)
Haha has six coins.
I have 33 coins.
Jae Suk has 33 coins.
Sophora root tea.
I have 23 coins.
Se Chan has 23 coins. Face rubbing.
I have 31 coins.
- Sophora root tea.
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, how many do you have?
(The last member, Suk Jin)
- I have 10 coins.
- He has 10 coins.
He will give us the ink show.
(The ink show will take place.)
- He got exactly 10 coins.
- Had he gotten 1 more,
- it would have been fresh cream.
- Are you a team?
- Had you given me 1 more,
- I told you that he has 6 coins.
it would have been fresh cream.
Must you see me get hit
with an ink bucket?
- Next week, it will be a war.
- You didn't tell us the number.
Let's bring in
the sophora root tea first.
- Two cups of sophora root tea.
- It's bitter.
There is a variety
of penalties today.
The taste makes your stomach churn.
This is...
I can smell it from here.
- All right. Thank you.
- The sophora root tea.
- It's good for your health.
- It smells really...
- It has a strong smell.
- I can smell it from here.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
- Don't do that.
(Shutting her eyes tight)
Drink it up.
The three of them are done.
Next is face rubbing.
- Close your eyes.
- This is the worst.
- He looks like a fish.
He's really ugly.
He looks just like a fish.
I think I need to do it again.
What's that?
Se Chan got the worst penalty.
I know. This is the worst.
Now bring in water buckets.
One, two, three.
(So Min wanted the water bucket.)
(She gets a cool shower.)
It's so cold.
All right.
- Life can't always be fun.
- Are you all right?
This will also leave me
with a good memory.
Oh, no.
(The ink show)
- Oh, no.
- It's a face rubbing.
You should take a face rubbing.
Suk Jin. You don't need
black spray on your head.
He has a good head of hair.
You have very thick hair.
Gosh, this is the worst one.
- This is the worst.
- This is horrible.
This is too much for ten coins.
You don't need to dye your hair.
Thank you for your hard work.
Haha will go downstairs now.
All right.
- Thank you all for today.
- Thank you.
Your penalty is better.
This is so awkward.
How would I do this?
Am I supposed to dance
just like this?
(Am I supposed to dance
just like this?)
In the middle?
Gosh, this is so embarrassing.
(A huge stage for him)
Gosh, I just can't bring
myself to dance.
I can't do this. My goodness.
(He needs to dance
and get applauded here.)
Can you join me, Jae Suk?
(It's a lonely performance
without cameras and colleagues.)
Gosh, I just can't start dancing.
(The BTS song is playing
on Haha's phone.)
I can't do this.
(Walking by)
(Dancer Ha starts dancing.)
(In the indifference of people,)
(he shows his performance art.)
(People start paying attention
to the middle-aged man's grooves.)
(Making a bow)
(He tries to interact with
the audience to get applauded.)
(But all he gets is
a lukewarm response.)
(What the heck...)
(He tries to target
some of the audience.)
(A dance performance from up close)
(The performance ends
with a grand finale.)
(Right at the moment...)
(The audience finally gives him
a welcoming applause.)
(Thank you!)
(Running away)
(Dancer Ha fought
against humiliation...)
I'm so embarrassed.
(and finished his penalty.)
(Once upon a time...)
(What are you?)
(I'm Nolboo, you punk.)
(Two Nolboos under the same roof?)
(Which one of you is Nolboo?)
- I'm Nolboo.
- No, I'm Nolboo.
(Someone is lying.)
(Two people are insisting
that they are Madam Ppaengdeok.)
- Can I get some food?
- What are you?
(And there are three Heungboos?)
(That Heungboo...)
(is somewhat bleary-eyed.)
(He's trying to seduce someone.)
(Heungboos can't fall in love
with each other.)
(Into traditional fairy tales...)
(They have to single out the fake.)
(Uninvited guests who are here
to ruin the fairy tales)
(A chase to identify the fakes)
(His face...)
(It's just that he's ugly.)
(They are all thrown
into confusion.)
(How will the fairy tale end?)
(Running Chronicles)