(For the first time on Running Man,)
(Jong Kook has
a housewarming party.)
(Se Chan began alone
in the parking lot.)
No one's here yet?
What are we doing today?
Why are you all here?
There's a van.
There's So Min.
(He's puzzled
by the dash of the camera.)
So Min isn't shooting.
(Looking around)
Has the shoot begun?
It doesn't look like it.
(Has the shoot begun?
It doesn't look like it.)
No one's shooting.
It hasn't begun yet.
- It hasn't begun yet.
- What's going on?
- What are you doing?
- See?
What are you doing?
- I don't know.
- Hello.
Are you a spy?
- No. He just started shooting.
- Yes, you are.
- No.
- You are.
Why do you have a camera alone?
- I don't know. Hello.
- Hi.
Why is a camera there?
I don't know. They suddenly
turned the lights on...
- and started shooting me.
- The camera followed him first.
- The camera kept shooting him.
- No.
- I saw it.
- You saw it too, right?
- No.
- Why are you so puffy?
See?
- I ate gamjatang so much yesterday.
- Doesn't he look puffy?
I ate so much gamjatang yesterday.
- Was it that good?
- I ordered extra bones.
Now that you look puffy,
- you look young.
- Really?
- Do I look plump?
- Yes.
Yes.
This is Jong Kook's house.
Ji Hyo.
You look like you came down
from his house.
This is our new house.
Good.
- You're amazing.
- You've been invited.
- Make yourselves home.
- I like how it's not too much.
What about food?
- I already got the food ready.
- Really?
Just wait and see.
Is it "Same Bed, Different Dreams 2:
You Are My Destiny" today?
No. I thought
it was "Master in the House."
I thought we were going to
"My Little Old Boy" studio.
- I think it's "Master in the House."
- It's a mix of many shows.
(This house looks familiar.)
(There were only rumors
about the ugly son's house.)
(A pair of socks left alone)
(The owner of the dull place...)
(that is full of black gym suits)
(533-month-old Kim Jong Kook)
It's nice to film at home.
I mean it.
(The house owner looks comfortable.)
Do they all know
they're coming to my house?
- They're all downstairs.
- Really?
- Isn't this Jong Kook's house?
- Yes.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
That was the first time.
- Hey. That was the first time.
- Why do you keep repeating it?
I never repeated it.
That was my first time.
His house is dark.
Let's go up.
The elevator is...
Which floor?
- Ji Hyo. Which floor?
- Floor X.
- I knew it.
- Ji Hyo knows.
(She can find her new house easily.)
You know.
Of course.
Ji Hyo. Then can we
not press the bell?
We're not that close yet.
Do you know the password?
That's why you're amateurs.
- Why?
- Why are we amateurs?
- There he goes again.
- He's showing off again.
There he goes again.
Do you know anything?
Look at his teeth.
He can't stop smiling.
- He's trying to tease us.
- He wants to tease us.
His teeth became more crooked...
- before teasing us.
- Jae Suk.
- Do you adjust them every morning?
- No.
- Before leaving?
- I turn them in the morning.
He can take them out.
I've been here a lot
for "My Little Old Boy."
He got a nice bicycle.
Jong Kook has a bicycle?
- Isn't this yours?
- That's mine.
- That's obviously Ji Hyo's.
- It's mine.
Ji Hyo.
- How do you go in?
- What's the password?
Why doesn't it... It's on.
Ji Hyo knows the password.
You should've just stayed home.
(Beeping)
(Alarming)
What are they doing?
Why are they pressing the password?
Seriously.
Open it.
- Jong Kook.
- Why are you pressing the password?
- Ji Hyo says she knows.
Darn it.
Don't be ridiculous.
- He caught us.
- What's she talking about?
Ji Hyo said she knew,
so she pressed it.
I know we're shooting at your house,
but it's still a shoot.
- What are you doing?
- What is that?
You need to put on clothes.
I am wearing clothes.
I don't need to dress up for home.
- Isn't this "My Little Old Boy" studio?
- What's this?
- What?
- Isn't this "My Little Old Boy" studio?
- Here...
- Have a seat.
- Let's get changed.
- Jong Kook. Can I get changed?
- Jong Kook.
- Can I get changed?
- You're wearing it inside out.
- No.
Sit here.
Jong Kook. Can I get changed?
- Sure.
- You're wearing it inside out.
- No, this is right.
- I take this too.
- I got one for free.
- Is this "My Little Old Boy" or what?
- This is "My Little Old Boy" studio.
- Can I have some coffee?
- This is my seat.
- I sit next to you.
- Can I have some coffee?
- This is Jong Kook's chair.
Jong Kook.
The floor became your closet.
Can you hold this?
- So it won't touch my hair.
- The floor became your closet.
Jong Kook. You have the AC on.
- What's gotten into you?
- You never do that.
You got more stuff.
It's packed.
- Jong Kook.
- Thank you.
How do Jong Kook's clothes
look on me?
(Jong Kook's gym clothes)
- Jong Kook's clothes.
- You look...
- like a world champion's father...
- What?
- visiting his son's house.
- Jong Kook. How do I look?
- It's nice.
- Jong Kook.
- Why are you wearing sleeveless?
- Jae Suk.
- Let me use the restroom.
- This is my best outfit.
- Okay.
- There's no place to sit.
- Sit here.
Just sit anywhere.
- But there are clothes.
- Hang on.
I'm taking this chair.
- Why?
- In case Suk Jin takes it.
- There's more space here.
Why are you keeping clothes here?
They're all gym clothes.
They're organized in their own way.
- How are they organized?
- Leave them alone.
Still, he changed a lot, right?
- What?
- He even turned the AC on.
- You turned the AC on.
- Why did you turn it on?
- I think...
- Hey.
I turn it on when it's necessary.
There are so many people
in my living room.
It's the first time my feet are cold
at home.
I didn't know you had an AC at home.
Your feet are cold at home?
Since last year, it's the first time
I'm using it in the living room.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You didn't turn it on last year?
- No.
(He paid 0 for AC last year.)
Why are you brushing your teeth?
(He's brushing his teeth
out of nowhere.)
Jae Suk.
Because my mouth didn't feel clean.
Did you eat something on the way?
Suk Jin. If you do that,
that will ruin the couch.
- If he were a kid,
- Jong Kook.
I'd say he was not disciplined.
- Stop it.
- Don't.
(He wants to do it more
when people stop him.)
- Suk Jin. You better say this.
- It'll become an issue.
- What?
- "Don't curse at me."
You should say it.
(Here's the "Don't curse
at me" incident.)
(He suggested his random
steamed egg to So Min.)
(Getting angry)
(Suk Jin predicted his future.)
What do you mean,
"Don't curse at me?"
Suk Jin.
(Despite his long experience,
he appealed to viewers.)
You should say that again.
- It's time for you to say it.
- No.
- It's not that serious.
- People will blame you.
- Right?
- It'll be an issue.
People will blame him.
That day,
as soon as I said that,
I realized people would blame me
for it.
My mom blamed you so much.
We watched that episode together.
What did she say?
"What's wrong with that prick?"
(That's what her mom said.)
(That wakes him up.)
Ma'am. I'm sorry.
- She's more like a friend.
- She's a friend.
- A friend.
Sis. I'm sorry.
I didn't do that
because I hated her.
How can you be so mean
to your friend's daughter?
It's not that I hate her.
I was only trying to be funny.
Please don't take it wrong.
"Don't curse at me, sis."
(Laughing)
So Min. Isn't that chair cozy?
- It's so nice.
- Right?
- I'll let you experience it.
Is this a rocking chair?
It's a really old chair.
Is this the chair you've used
since your parents' house?
This is awesome.
Jong Kook.
- You have a good reaction.
- Enjoy your rest.
- This is so nice.
- Right?
That's 18 years old.
This is really nice.
It's perfect for you two
to lie down.
- Really?
- It's perfect.
It's just big enough.
Se Chan.
(Se Chan.)
(She summons
her business boyfriend.)
I'll bite you with my front teeth.
Look at her eyes.
(The chair is enough to make
the cheesy girl happy.)
I imagined it.
- That's funny.
- That's hilarious.
- It's nice to film at home.
- Yes.
- What...
- We should take turns...
- and film at home.
- What's Ji Seon doing today?
She was actually here today,
so I sent her home.
- You still need clothes.
- She said she'd leave after lunch.
- Clothes?
- You need clothes.
I am wearing clothes.
- They're comfy.
- Is this "Master in the House..."
or "My Boss?" I mean...
- What's that called?
- "My Boss?"
"My Boss?"
- Hey.
- Sorry.
It's "Same Bed, Different Dreams 2:
You Are My Destiny."
"Same Bed, Different Dreams 2:
You Are My Destiny?"
Or is it "My Little Old Boy?"
Someone needs to get married for...
"Same Bed, Different Dreams 2:
You Are My Destiny."
(Is she using 2 wipes at once?)
I heard SBS bought this house.
- I heard you're living in a studio.
- This is their studio.
Cameraman Chan Hee also...
Hey. Use only one wipe at a time.
Or Jong Kook will curse at you.
- I just felt guilty.
- You can't use two.
- No.
- Don't you know...
- whose house you're at?
- Why did you use two?
(Why did you use two?)
It's a habit.
Clean your hands first
and wipe the floor with it.
- Okay, Jong Kook.
- Get it?
If you use more than
one wipe at a time,
Jong Kook will curse at you.
Ji Hyo even uses it again
after blowing her nose.
Did you think I'd throw this out?
I'm not.
I'm going to use it again later.
- Right.
- Don't be a hypocrite.
- Why do you do that?
- Suk Jin.
There's a clip of your fake life
on YouTube.
(Suk Jin is the biggest example
of a hypocrite's life.)
- A fake life.
- That went viral.
- Right.
- My fake life.
- For real?
- Yes.
Because he's a real hypocrite.
By the way, this place...
- What?
- What about it?
Well...
It's nice.
Isn't it nice to live alone?
- Yes.
- What's it like to live alone?
- You should visit me often.
- What?
- Is it nice to live alone?
- You should come and visit.
What's it like to live alone?
- Are you lonely?
- It's so nice.
- But sometimes you get lonely.
- Never.
Jong Kook will live alone,
- and when he's about to die,
- Die?
- he'll take the 10kg...
- The dumbbell?
- dumbbell.
- Tied to him.
We should send him
with a dumbbell tied to him.
- Since I don't have a child,
- Yes.
- I could donate my assets.
- That'd be amazing.
- He must've earned a lot.
- It would be really nice.
You see, sometimes I find it hard
to believe...
- that he makes a lot of money...
- Yes?
because he's not interested in
luxury goods.
- He doesn't spend much on them.
- Right?
- I wonder what he spends...
- If I get married...
If I get married, I'd spend
the most money on my wife and kids.
- But I'm still single.
- Surprisingly, So Min imagines...
what it could be like
if she were with you quite often.
- No, it's not like that.
- She wants his money.
- She...
- That's why she imagines that.
I talked to So Min on the phone
three days ago,
and she said, "Jae Suk."
- Was she making a plan?
- "I don't think about it often."
"But I have thought about it
a few times."
- "If I..."
- Yes.
- Ji Hyo is drinking water.
- "married..."
- "Jong Kook..."
- It's not like that. Trust me.
- She keeps drinking water.
- Hey.
She must believe she can buy
whatever she desires.
You don't have a chance with him.
- So Min.
- Ji Hyo won't let that happen.
- You have an enemy to remove.
- "No! My money!"
- But...
- My gosh.
Let's order delivery food.
- Let's do that. I want a burger.
- We can cook some ramyeon.
- A burger sounds good.
- Sounds great.
- Let's cook some ramyeon.
- Stop it.
What are we going to do today?
- Can we just hang out here?
- Yes, that's the plan, but...
- Are you serious?
- You can order food if you want.
There's a gukbap restaurant
that Jong Kook often orders from.
- Great.
- Yes, I order gukbap...
- The one he has every morning?
- Yes.
Jong Kook, how about budaejjigae
from that place...
- so we can reminisce the old days?
- Reminiscing about the old days?
- What do you mean by that?
- Gosh.
- I was so taken aback.
- What does that mean?
I thought, "What memories do we have
to reminisce about?"
- Ji Hyo, that was a good one.
- The budaejjigae with chicken.
- I have no idea...
- Don't you remember that?
- I don't think we had it together.
- This is hilarious.
- Have you forgotten about it?
- No, I know we had it together.
- I remember it.
- Ji Hyo, you're doing great.
- Ji Hyo even looks so pretty today.
- You remember it, right?
- Indeed. She looks pretty today.
- We had 401 budaejjigae.
Let's try the gukbap
that Jong Kook has every morning.
I'll order it
if you really want to try it.
Let's eat it. I'm serious.
- Don't spoil them by ordering it.
- No. Jong Kook.
- Come on. Let us have it.
- It's okay. I'll order it for you.
You had Naju beef bone soup
without us.
- I brought R coins too.
- Don't spoil him.
- Should I not order it?
- No, you shouldn't.
- Haha, I'll buy it for you.
- Right.
I'm not saying it
because I don't have money.
I'll buy it for you.
He's trying to stop him
from ordering food for us.
- He had Naju beef bone soup.
- Haha...
Haha hates it most when Jong Kook
and I pull a prank on him together.
Just order it if you want.
You don't need their permission.
I'll order it by myself.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
- What will you guys have?
- What do you want to eat?
I want a cheeseburger.
Suk Jin hasn't treated us
in a while.
- He's so cool.
- I'm touched.
Are you treating
the staff members too?
- No.
- You should treat them too.
- He answered right away.
- Thank you, Suk Jin.
"No."
(He answered honestly
only in 0.5 seconds.)
How many are our staff members?
- About 20.
- Are there 20 of you?
- Yes.
- I'll order food for you guys too.
(I'll order food for you guys too.)
- Are you serious?
- What?
- Why?
- Do you mind if we edit it out?
"Do you mind if we edit it out?"
That's the scariest thing to hear.
- Please don't cut it all out.
- They won't make him look good.
- Show just a little bit, please.
- It doesn't have to make it to air.
- It's so funny.
- But I'd like you to know...
that we'll do a product placement,
and it's a tteokbokki brand.
- I see.
- Then let's eat that.
- So don't eat too much.
- Can't you wait an hour?
- I can wait for an hour.
- Let's wait for an hour.
- There's something we prepared.
- What is it?
One of the popular things
people do these days is...
a likability test with an AI.
- A likability test?
- Is there such a thing?
- What would an AI know about it?
- With an AI?
- Take a look.
- Let's take a look.
- Okay.
- Did you have us tested?
- Let me see.
(As a result of letting an AI
assess the members' likability...)
Have a look at this too.
He's in the top ten percent.
- Who?
- Jong Kook is ranked high.
- Really?
"The charming type that can be
in favor of anyone."
(Top 10 percent of likability)
"The most popular type.
There are many people..."
"who like you
although they never tell you that."
(Fully satisfied)
- But check out Se Chan's result.
- Okay.
- He's also ranked high.
- He's in the top ten percent.
- Nonsense.
- Me?
- It's not total nonsense.
- This is...
"The charming type that can be
in favor of anyone." It's the same.
- Right.
- Maybe his photo...
- It's the same as Jong Kook.
- The AI recognizes me.
Next up is Haha.
- He's in the top 30 percent.
- Good.
"The comfortable, likable type."
- "Approachable and trustworthy."
- That's right.
"Since you look friendly,
many people like you as a friend."
"But you need to approach someone
you're interested in first."
(Darn it.)
- That's so true.
- I agree.
- It's accurate.
- You need to approach her first.
- Not many would approach him first.
- True.
- That's true.
- Most people want to be his friend.
- Ji Hyo's result is the same.
- Next up is Ji Hyo.
"Top 30 percent of likability,
the comfortable, likable type."
- "Approachable and trustworthy."
- She is?
- I'm not sure if this is reliable.
- Ji Hyo?
- And the comments are the same.
- Let's check out our results.
- What's wrong with it?
- "Top 30 percent of likability."
"The comfortable, likable type."
Oh, that's me.
I'm in the top 50 percent.
"Average likability."
"The ordinary type that can change
by the overall look and clothes."
- I see it's not completely wrong.
- The AI is right about that.
"People often say you'd look great
if you were dressed nicely,"
"but you never take their advice."
- This is accurate.
- It's not total nonsense.
- Right.
- It's really accurate.
- Look at this.
He's in the top 70 percent.
(Only one member is left.)
(He's ranked the lowest of all.)
"There's a need for change
in your appearance."
"The type that needs to make efforts
to boost confidence..."
- "and manage his or her image."
- That's true.
"This type of people don't
have a face..."
"that's commonly recognized
as likable."
"But those with high self-esteem are
recognized as unique."
- This isn't an accurate assessment.
- I know, right?
- I'm in the lowest 30 percent.
- That's right.
You're in the top 30 percent
of unlikeable people.
Gosh, seriously.
Is he unlikeable
from an AI's perspective?
(Seok Sam is ranked the lowest
when it comes to appearances.)
- Something's wrong with the AI.
- In the top 50 percent?
- He's in the last place.
- There are all sorts of tests.
- I'll tell you about the rules now.
- Okay.
- Today's race is House Jong Kook.
- Yes.
This is a belated housewarming party
for the first time on "Running Man."
Isn't it too late for that?
He moved here a long time ago.
It's been a long time.
For Jong Kook who happily invited
us all to his house,
we prepared gift certificates
as a gift.
(The staff prepared
gift certificates as a gift!)
That's so nice of you.
But it wouldn't be fun
if we just give him our gift.
You'll be given a mission...
- every 30 minutes.
- Good.
The worth of the gift certificate
he'll get will go up if you succeed.
I see. Help me get the one
that's worth the most.
You get 500 dollars...
- for each mission you complete.
- My gosh. Did he say 500 dollars?
You can get up to 2,500 dollars
by playing 5 different games.
Jong Kook will receive
half of the amount you achieved,
and we'll donate the rest
to charity.
(Half will go to Jong Kook,
and the rest will be donated.)
Really?
- Really?
- That's great.
- Let's do this.
- I'll take this seriously.
- I don't need that much money.
- It's for Jong Kook.
- Yes. It's for Jong Kook.
- I mean it.
- All right.
- You can get a new TV or something.
- Since it's a housewarming party,
- I don't need a new TV.
you must spend the day
without getting stressed out.
We'll measure the stress levels
of the six of you.
Those of you whose stress levels
are higher...
when we measure them
after the race ends get a penalty.
But how are you going to measure it?
- We'll give you a device for it.
- Is there a device to measure it?
We'll measure
your stress levels now.
- And you'll keep wearing it.
- Yes.
- We'll measure it again...
- The higher it is now, the better.
- Jong Kook, help me.
- I'm actually stressed out now.
Me too. I need to poop right now.
I'm so stressed out.
(All of them except for Jong Kook
wear a stress measuring device.)
- I'm stressed out.
- How does it work?
It's a state-of-the-art device,
right?
I didn't know there was a device
like this. Ouch.
- Why did you pinch me?
- Get stressed out. Good.
Why did you put it upside down?
(It's upside down.)
I wouldn't mind
if you stressed me out.
I need to get stressed out...
No, in the opposite direction.
(It'd be advantageous
if their stress levels were high now.)
Jae Suk, did you get the result?
- It says it's still measuring.
- Why would you be stressed out?
No, I'm still...
- Do I check it like this?
- Did you get the result?
- Everyone else has received it.
- Why would you be stressed out?
Why am I the only person who hasn't
received it? This stresses me out.
I was told to wear it tightly.
Good. It's my turn.
It says I'm relaxed right now.
- Is this upside down?
- Hasn't a number appeared?
- I'll check it for you.
- It's 29.
- Twenty-nine?
- Yes.
- That's very low.
- Is it low? Jae Suk.
- I guess he's not stressed out.
- It's 29.
- Wait. That's not good.
- Why?
- Later on...
- Raise it.
(The higher the first result is,
the better it is for them.)
- Shout out loud just as I did.
- Wait. Let me check it again.
So Min.
- You see, I'm already...
- Slap Jae Suk in the face.
The noises they're making are
stressing me out.
Suk Jin, stop it.
(He's trying to stress himself out.)
It's going up a little
since I made myself upset.
- You never get anything right.
- I'm so stressed out.
Gosh, I'm so stressed out.
- Darn.
Oh, mine is quite high. It's 48.
Forty-eight?
- Mine is 42.
- Got it.
She's quite stressed out too.
Gosh, I'm so stressed out.
I'm stressed out.
My stress level is 56.
- Haha, that's good.
- Gosh, I'm stressed out.
Why does it say
the measurement has failed?
Jae Suk, wasn't your result 29?
- Let me measure it again.
- Is it 29?
- No.
- I see. Yours is 29?
I guess he's not stressed out.
I just got the result. It's 51.
- That's quite high.
- You're lying. It was 29 earlier.
- It's 51. See it for yourself.
- That's good.
- I guess I got stressed a little.
- I think so.
- The first result stressed me out.
- Right. That stressed you out.
- That gave me stress.
- Because you might get a penalty.
It's not fair that he was allowed to
measure it again.
It's not fair.
- Then we'll use the average number.
- Okay.
We got everyone's first result,
and we'll get the data transferred
every five minutes.
My stress level went up to 60.
- It's 60 now.
- You can't change it.
- I know. I'm so stressed out now.
- Earlier, your stress level...
We'll use that number
to calculate the average.
We'll start the first mission
right now.
- What is it?
- You can get 500 dollars...
- or nothing.
- Got it. That's good.
Not even the smallest error is
allowed in this mission.
- It's Relay Human Tape Measure.
- What is it?
- Relay Human Tape Measure?
- You get to decide the order.
Starting at the workout room,
stand at a distance from one another.
We'll show an object
to the first player in that room.
The player measures the object
using his or her hands.
Then the player shows
the next player the size.
The final measurement must be
within a margin of 1.5cm.
- Using our arms?
- That's easy.
- Of course, we can do that.
- It doesn't sound fun at all.
- It's a piece of cake.
- Right.
- It's not difficult.
- I don't think it will be easy.
- We just have to be still.
- All right.
- The first player is important.
- Maintain the distance.
Who wants to be the first player?
- Who should be the first player?
- It should be Suk Jin.
I'll be the 2nd or 3rd player.
- Then I'll be the first player.
- Go ahead.
- I'll go first.
- It could be a tiny object.
- Go ahead.
- So Min, will you go next?
- Yes. I'll be the second player.
- You can do this.
I'll be the second last.
- I'll go last.
- You're the last player.
- Okay.
- Should we just stand like this?
- Okay. Are you ready?
- Okay.
- Go, Se Chan!
- Let's do this!
The first player must never tell
the others what the object is.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- That's right.
- Everyone, stay calm.
- Try not to get stressed out.
- It won't be hard.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
- Don't worry.
- It's easy.
Jong Kook, can I have
a cup of coffee before we begin?
Sure. Go ahead.
- Hey.
- It's in the fridge.
- We're about to begin.
- You might...
You might get stressed out
because it's hard to open the lid.
- I understand.
- It's a little tight.
I mean, we should enjoy ourselves...
- not to get stressed out.
- Absolutely.
- Have as much as you want.
- Hey, I see...
you already opened this one.
- Which one?
- The bottle in the front.
- It's already open.
- Oh, I see.
You can have it
or open a new bottle.
You two look really close
to each other.
Hey, that wasn't open.
- It's a new bottle.
- Yes, it is.
- It's really good.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan is showing off
his strength.)
(Grunting)
(Groaning)
That's the weight
that Jong Kook's mother uses.
- What? This is?
- Yes.
For real? Gosh. Why is it so heavy?
(He fusses while using the weights
used by Jong Kook's mother.)
- His mother must be very strong.
- He said she could do it easily.
- Really?
- Yes.
What is this? Hold on. My goodness.
Wait. We're in trouble.
Se Chan, come out when you're ready.
He's coming out.
- That looks fun.
- What?
- Why?
- It's too small.
- Is it small? That should be easy.
- But...
Hey, you should've kept your elbows
at your sides when you measured it.
He didn't? Gosh. He should've.
- It's okay.
- It won't be easy.
- Measure it.
- Hey.
- Hey, So Min.
- All right. I know.
- I see what you mean.
- Stop it.
- It's not like that.
- It's the width, right?
(It's the same as
the width of my chest.)
Hey!
It's the same as
the width of my chest.
(She shares information
that's not related to the game.)
- Hey.
- It's wider than that.
It's wider than that. Good.
Keep them at your sides.
So Min never stops trying
to make it romantic.
You're keeping your hands
close to your chest. That's why.
I told you to keep your elbows...
- What are you doing?
- Keep your elbows at your sides.
Why are you keeping your hands
close to your chest?
So Min, stretch out your arms
a little bit.
I mean, watch me.
- Just put your elbows here.
- So Min, what are you doing?
- Why around your chest?
- So Min.
- Gosh, seriously.
- That's just weird.
Look. Keep your elbows
at your sides like this.
- She's so hilarious.
- I can't believe her.
- How should we do it like that?
- Seriously.
Just keep your elbows at your sides.
Ji Hyo, you go next.
- Come over here.
- You should enjoy yourselves.
- It's the width of my chest.
- This is...
Why did you leave so quickly?
- Jae Suk.
- Hey.
- This is...
- Why did you...
(It took him only one second.)
- Take your time.
- Don't be halfhearted.
- Don't rush it.
- I think it's narrower.
- It's...
- It's narrower, right? I'll...
- No, it's not.
- I think it's gotten smaller.
- No.
- I'm accurate.
- That's the width of my chest...
- It's narrower than before.
- I agree.
- It's narrower than the width...
- Yes, I'll widen it slightly.
- It's the same.
- I'll widen it.
- No, don't do that.
- It's narrower than before.
It's narrower than before.
- That's not true.
- I'll widen it a little.
No, don't widen it.
The margin of error is only 1cm.
- I should measure it like this.
- Widen it slightly.
- It's good now, right?
- No.
- Inward.
- That's good enough.
Move them outward.
It's exactly the width of my chest.
Yes, I think this is correct.
Just this wide.
- Come closer. Let's do it again.
- Okay.
(They got as close to each other
as possible.)
- It's straight, right?
- Yes.
- Let's get even closer.
- That's good enough.
Can't you put them on your waist?
- No.
- You're right.
I mean, the widths of chests are
quite similar to one another.
I'm ready. Bring the tape measure.
- This is the right size.
- It's too big.
No. This is exactly the width
of my chest.
No, you're wrong.
- Can we lift it up?
- Of course.
- There's no difference.
- Okay.
- Measure it.
- I think we pulled it off.
- I think so too.
- It's 33cm.
It's 33.5cm.
- Is it 33.5cm?
- Yes.
- It's 33.5cm.
- Please step back.
- Is it 33cm?
- Our record is 33.5cm, right?
What is it?
(The object turns out to be
a dumbbell.)
- It looks too narrow.
- Please give me the tape measure.
- Put it down.
- So Min.
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
- What's wrong with you?
Stop it.
You're at my place, you punk!
I wanted to measure the width.
(The length of the dumbbell
should be between 32cm and 35cm.)
(It's 28cm long.)
- You failed.
- Gosh.
(They failed
at their first attempt.)
- How long is it?
- It's 28cm long.
- See? I said it was narrow.
- You were right.
- Suk Jin...
- Why did you widen it?
Ji Hyo was accurate.
Suk Jin,
- why did you change it?
- Why did you decide on your own?
- How long is it?
- He said it was narrow.
- They said it too.
- Is it 28cm?
- He said it was hard.
- Why was it hard?
- It was hard to measure it.
I was right about it.
- The staff members knew...
- Ji Hyo, it was accurate.
- It's 28cm long. Look.
- You shouldn't have widened it.
- Right?
- Come on. Stop it.
Hey, enough.
I was right, Jae Suk.
It's 28cm wide.
Suk Jin shouldn't have...
- widened it just as he wanted.
- I won't do it again.
- Go ahead and measure it.
- Se Chan...
We should pull it off this time.
- What should I measure?
- It's a foam roller this time.
- Pardon?
- A foam roller.
Home run ball?
No, the object over there.
- What is this?
- It's a foam roller.
Oh, is this it? Wait.
Are you ready?
- How did it go?
- You can come out.
He's coming out.
- Come and stand here.
- Let's make it work.
- Se Chan.
- Remember that, okay?
Be careful
when you pass through the door.
Wait. I can't pass through the door.
Come out.
Hey, turn around.
- You need to feel it.
- You should turn around.
You should be confident
that you can control your body.
Hey.
How does it even work?
That's not how it should be done.
- Hey.
- Is it too long?
Couldn't you do it like this?
- Keep your elbows at your sides.
- Can't you do it like this?
Can't you do it like this?
- Right. That's good.
- That's good.
- Let's do it that way.
- No!
But she just...
- widened it.
- Good. Yes, keep going.
- Good. Keep going.
- That'll cause an error.
Hey. It's okay. So Min, keep going.
- No, that'll cause an error.
- That's good.
We failed already.
No, we've got this.
- Now, come here.
- Don't move your arms.
- That's good.
- Come.
- Come just as you are.
- Move.
- No, stay there.
- Right. That'll work.
- Just stay still.
- That'll work.
- Just as you are. Don't move.
- Stay still.
- Right. Keep your elbows there.
- Come just as you are.
Don't move your arms. Good.
We are...
You'll be surprised...
- to see us pull this off.
- We're amazing.
- We're good at group missions.
- Come.
- Come without moving your arms.
- I'm worried...
- about Jae Suk though.
- Don't worry about me.
- He worries me.
- I...
- I didn't touch you.
- Don't give the next player a tip.
- Okay.
- I can keep my arms steady.
- No. Keep your elbows at the sides.
- Keep your elbows at the sides.
- Keep them at your sides.
- Keep them at your sides!
- Like this.
- No.
- Don't stress me out.
- But Jae Suk.
I'd get stressed out
if you forced me to do so.
- Keep your elbows at your sides.
- Jae Suk.
- You're stressing me out.
- But...
- Why would you get stressed out?
- Keep them at your sides.
You're stressing me out.
- Wait.
- My gosh.
- You're giving me stress.
- Keep them at your sides.
I think it was wider
when Se Chan came out.
- Right. That's why I don't do this.
- Then widen it slightly.
My stress level keeps going up.
I must be stressed out.
It went up to 61.
- Keep your elbows at your sides.
- Let me do it my way.
- If I do so...
- You should...
- keep your elbows at your sides.
- No, it's okay.
- Keep your elbows at your sides.
- It's better that way.
No. I can measure it accurately
like this.
- He said it wasn't wider than this.
- Watch me.
- But this is a better way.
- Look.
Just keep your elbows at your sides.
- Come on. Do as I say.
- Ji Hyo, this is the exact side.
Why won't you...
- Why...
- Just give it a try.
- Try my way just once.
- Keep your elbows at your sides.
- Keep them at your sides.
- This will work just fine.
- Gosh. What's his problem?
- This is the accurate measurement.
- You should've listened to me.
- Keep them at your sides.
It's better that way.
He never listens to me.
- Turn around.
- We're doing so well.
You'll be surprised.
- Is this it?
- It looks...
- Wait.
- Ji Hyo, I think you narrowed it.
No, I didn't.
- I'll widen it a little bit.
- My measurement was accurate.
It wasn't accurate at all.
- It was accurate.
- I widened it a little bit.
Suk Jin, just turn around,
and Haha, come close to him.
- Okay.
- Suk Jin, turn around.
Don't get stressed out.
Let's speak nicely to one another.
- Let's talk nicely.
- No, it's too wide.
- You can measure it now.
- Okay. Turn around.
Dong Hoon, turn around
without moving your arms.
Please accept that much.
- Please accept it.
- It got bigger.
I know. It's wider than before.
It's bigger?
- It's 95cm.
- He's in a sitting position.
- It's 95cm, right?
- It's 94.5cm.
- Okay.
Okay. Now, bring out the object.
- What is it?
- Okay. What is it?
What could it be?
When I saw Se Chan measuring it...
(When I saw Se Chan measuring it...)
It felt a little strange.
- Why?
- What do you mean?
She's making this face again.
Honestly, I noticed it,
but I didn't say anything.
(She makes the face
frequently today.)
When I saw him spread his arms,
I wanted to...
(Hugging)
I see you wanted to hug him.
(Love Frog got distracted
during the game.)
(Smiling)
Enough is enough.
My gosh. Honestly...
- She's so peculiar.
- She's unbelievable.
It was a foam roller.
- This was it.
- It was a foam roller.
- I see.
- Is this it? It looks longer.
- No. It could be 95cm long.
- I think so too.
I think it's exactly 95cm long.
- Look.
- We have a chance.
I'll measure it now.
- How long is it?
- Please.
(The length of it should be
between 93cm and 96cm.)
(What could be the result?)
Is it 92cm? It's 93cm.
- My goodness.
- Awesome.
(They pulled it off!)
Awesome.
- We pulled it off.
- All right.
There's not even
a one-centimeter difference.
- This is amazing.
- Really?
This is amazing.
- See? I knew it.
- This is who we are.
Hey, this is "Running Man."
Bring it on!
You saw that, right?
See? I knew we'd pull it off.
- Right?
- Great job.
- I widened it a little bit.
- Come on.
- Jae Suk is so funny.
- We're awesome.
Bring it on.
- This is unbelievable.
- We all thought we were wrong.
- Who said that?
- You should've...
- I widened it.
- He says he widened it.
I widened it slightly.
No, you didn't.
I calculated using pi.
That's nonsense.
- Just eat a pie.
- I calculated the length.
We shouldn't get stressed out.
- We're good at games like this.
- Oh, my.
It's fascinating.
My stress level went down...
- to 45.
- Really?
- From 60.
- Right. You felt accomplished.
- We're awesome.
- That was good.
We surprised ourselves.
As a result,
you achieved 500 dollars.
(They achieved 500 dollars.)
- We got it.
- Let's go.
- We'll start the next mission.
- Okay.
- Let's get that 500 dollars.
You are the best entertainers...
- who can beat any idol stars...
- Of course.
in every game.
- Yes, we can.
The next mission is something
you can definitely pull off.
It's Loyal Squats.
- What? Loyal Squats?
- Will we do squats?
The 6 of you have to do 600 squats
in total to win.
(The 6 of them have to do 600 squats
to win.)
- How do we do 600 squats?
- The 6 of us?
But we're seven people.
Jong Kook is your coach.
- What?
- He's your coach.
- How do we do it without the ace?
- That's nonsense.
- One, two, three, four...
- Six hundred squats...
Each of us should do 100 squats.
You can do 100 squats.
I can't do 100 squats.
You're a famous YouTube creator
for your workout videos.
- Yes. They can do it.
- You shouldn't count it...
- when they don't do it properly.
- I'll even check the angle.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- You can do it.
- Okay.
You don't have to divide it evenly.
Just do 600 squats in total.
You can do 100 squats.
It's 5 sets of 20 reps.
Jong Kook, I have never done
squats in my whole life.
- Me neither.
- We should do it at once.
That's why it's hard.
- Sorry?
- We should do 100 squats in a row.
- You can do it.
- Can I do it my way?
I can't even do...
- ten squats at once.
- How do you do squats?
This is how I do squats.
While watching TV at home,
I sit on the sofa like this...
- No, that's not allowed.
- No.
(This is just sitting down
on the sofa and getting up.)
- You sit so comfortably.
- But...
- This is how it's done.
That's how grandpas do squats.
Did you just call me a grandpa?
- That's how grandpas do it.
- What?
He sat down too comfortably though.
- The three of you can go first.
- Us?
- Stop if you can't do any more.
- Okay.
Let's see you do a squat first.
- How can one do 100 squats?
- Jae Suk, go ahead.
It wasn't bad,
but keep your knees apart.
- Really?
- You have weak knees, so...
- Should I widen my stance?
- Yes, spread your knees out.
- How about this?
- Widen your stance.
- Yes, that's it.
- Perfect, isn't it?
- Yes, that's good enough.
- Two and three.
- Jae Suk, stop.
- That's perfect.
- Who's next?
- So Min.
I can't sit down
because of my jeans.
There's too much hip anteversion.
(There's too much hip anteversion.)
- Hip anteversion?
- Like this.
(Hip anteversion?)
Like this. It's common for women.
- One should lean backwards.
- It's not good for your knees.
That's right.
Be in a neutral stance.
Now, squat.
Don't push your hip out too much.
Wouldn't this stress us all out?
- Hold on.
- Wouldn't this stress us all out?
- Keep your knees out wide.
- This is stressing me out.
- Go ahead.
- Already?
- I almost made a mistake.
- I hate that tone of his.
Push your knees out
in the direction of your toes.
Squat. There you go. Nicely done.
Okay, that's good enough.
- Let us begin.
- Here we go.
Let's begin.
(Chatting)
Ready, get set...
(They chat when the others
are about to squat.)
- We're about to squat, guys.
- Pay attention!
- You can take your time.
- They're hilarious.
Se Chan thought Ji Hyo was me...
and punched her
in a place where it hurts.
- And then he apologized.
- Really?
(A few moments ago)
(Punch)
(He mistook Ji Hyo for Haha.)
What's wrong?
Did you punch her?
- This jerk...
- Did he think you were me?
He hit me where it really hurts.
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
It really startled me.
- Let's do this.
- Ready, get set, go.
- All right. One!
- Take your time.
- Two.
- Keep pace with each other.
(The merciless coach
will have anyone doing squats.)
- Slower.
- It's already a slow pace.
(But they're famous
for not listening.)
It's already a slow pace.
- Three.
- Don't.
- Five, six.
- Look at Suk Jin go.
- I do squats at home.
- Seven.
- Eight.
- All right!
- Nine.
- It's a good pace.
- Ten.
- My gosh.
- It's a fast pace.
I still have more in me.
- Twelve.
- I still have more in me.
Thirteen.
Fourteen. Keep the pace.
- Fifteen.
- It's too fast.
- Look at Jae Suk.
- Sixteen.
- He has proper form.
- Seventeen.
- It's too fast.
- Eighteen.
- If you can, keep going, Jae Suk.
- Nineteen.
- Twenty.
- Got it.
- I'm feeling it now.
- If you can do 200,
- that'll be admirable.
- Twenty-two.
Is that the right count? 23.
- And 24.
- That's 24.
- I think I did more.
- And 25.
That's why you should keep the pace.
- That's 26.
- Count with your inner voice.
- Jae Suk.
- That's 27.
(So Min legs give in
after 27 squats.)
- Hey!
- No, it's okay.
(So Min comes back for now.)
At least do 100.
(If one gives up,
someone else must do the rest.)
That's 35.
If you think about it...
- I can't.
- So Min, don't sit back too much.
What do I do?
- We'll do this for sure.
- I can't!
It's all right. Keep going.
- Keep going.
- That's 60.
One...
- Three.
- I can't do any more.
- So Min, you've got this.
- You can do this.
- You can do at least 100.
- Five.
- Six.
- Seven.
Seven.
- Gosh, look at Jae Suk.
- Eight.
Go, you sexy man!
- Ten.
- That's 70.
- One.
- Two.
- I give up.
- Three.
(So Min gives up after 55 squats.)
- So Min did 55 squats.
- Seriously?
- Five.
- Have you given up?
- So Min did 55 squats.
- You could've done more.
- Seven, eight.
- No, I can't.
Suk Jin, standing on that
gave you great form.
- Eighty.
- Seventy.
- One.
- Two.
- Four, five...
- Jae Suk, do 50 more.
- Six.
- Five.
- Seven.
- Six.
- Eight.
- Seven.
- Nine.
- How many are you at? 90?
- Yes, 90.
- Okay.
- One.
- Do 50 more.
Ten. That's 80.
Suk Jin, you're looking good.
- Good job.
- Six.
(Meanwhile...)
- Ten.
- Good job.
- Three.
- Six.
Look at them go.
- Keep going.
- Five.
- Nine.
- Six.
- Good job.
- Ten.
(Rather than it being fun,
it's about stressing them out.)
- Keep going.
- Eight.
- Nine.
- Six.
- That's 100.
- Seven.
(Jae Suk hit 100 squats.)
- Keep going.
- One. Two.
- This is stressing me out!
- Three.
(He swaps mental strength
for his physical strength.)
That's 90.
- Five.
- One.
- I'm touched.
- How many has Jae Suk done?
- Nine.
- He's at 110.
- I...
- Nice.
- Take a quick break.
- Keep going.
- Seven.
- Get back to it.
- Old man.
- Jae Suk.
If you don't do 150...
- We'll forfeit.
- We're going to give up.
Okay.
- I'm at 110.
- That's 92, 93...
- Can I stop?
- No, keep going.
That's 92, 93.
That's 94.
I can't keep going.
- No, you can.
- Six.
- How many are you at?
- Seven.
- Five.
- That's 108.
(He's already at 108.)
That's 110.
- This...
- One.
- This is the grandpa squat.
- Two.
- Three.
- That's how grandpas do it.
(The old man lets out a cry.)
- You only need 600 among you all.
- What?
- What was that?
- Eight.
- Okay, I'm sorry.
- Nine. 130.
- He apologized.
- What?
Suk Jin, at his age...
- He could yell at any time.
- That's 120.
Seven, eight...
- How many is that?
- Nine, 130.
- Nice.
- That's 130.
Just do 20 more.
I did 130.
- You're already seeing results.
- That's 130.
- My legs are about to explode.
- Just do 20 more.
One...
(Jae Suk's goal is 150 squats.)
- Four, five.
- We won't even bother.
- Six, seven, eight.
- Nine, ten.
- You only have ten left.
- One.
- Can you believe him?
- This is insane.
- Seven, eight...
- Jae Suk, my gosh.
Nine.
- Ten. Darn it!
- He did it.
Nine.
(Ten. Darn it!)
- He did it.
- That's 150 squats.
- You're the best.
- I did 150.
No way.
- They're as solid as rocks.
- The muscles...
See? Doing squats
is great for your health.
They're as solid as rocks.
- That's 140.
- Good.
Should I stop at 150?
Yes, 150 squats are enough.
- Darn it.
- 150 squats...
(He's truly annoyed.)
Keep going.
Go on. You've got this.
(He's back at it again.)
The muscles...
See? Doing squats
is great for your health.
- They're as solid as rocks.
- Keep going.
That's 147, 148,
and 149.
- And that's 150.
- There you go.
(Suk Jin managed 150 squats.)
(Suk Jin is still healthy enough.)
- Currently...
- How many is that?
You managed 355 squats.
- How many do we need to do?
- Only 245 more squats.
Only 245 more?
You must do at least 100 each.
How can we not?
- How can we not?
- You can do this.
Jong Kook...
Let's get him the 3,000 dollars.
- Correct my form for me.
- Let's keep a steady pace.
I have a short
Achilles tendon and...
(Groaning)
My body...
Suk Jin, are you all right?
And go.
- One.
One.
- Two.
- Three.
Haha, squat deeper.
Squat deeper. That's two.
Check your form
and widen your stance.
- Go on.
- Got it.
- Seven.
- How many did I do?
- You've done ten.
- Ten?
Ji Hyo, you're to hit 50 squats.
Five.
Six.
Se Chan, squat deeper.
Squat deeper.
- Se Chan.
- What the...
- That's it.
- The stress!
- That's the one.
- Let's do this.
- I know.
- Haha, watch your form.
Don't stick your butt out.
Yes, that's better.
Yes, that's how you do it.
That was 100. I'm done.
I did 111.
- You did 57.
- They hit the quota.
- That's it.
- You succeeded.
- Okay!
- Nice.
- Good job.
- They did it.
- This is killer.
- I'm glad.
I can't believe
you managed 100 each.
They're making us do this
to increase our stress levels.
- You're right.
- Just so you know,
one of you reached
a dangerously high stress level.
Who?
Suk Jin's stress level was at 93.
(Suk Jin's stress level
was dangerously high at 93.)
You were in the red zone.
- What did you expect?
- Dangerously high?
Is that for real?
- It went up to 93.
- Are you okay?
Suk Jin, right?
Does one die if it reaches 100?
Suk Jin almost opened the doors
to the afterlife.
I knocked, but no one let me in.
You're trying to increase
our stress level.
- You're trying to stress us out.
- That must be your goal.
You can relax now.
How are we supposed to relax?
- I bet the tteokbokki is spicy.
- Right.
No, it's just produce placement.
Suk Jin's on his phone
when we're supposed to be working.
- But we're not filming.
- He's on his phone.
- We're on a bathroom break.
- Are you checking your stocks?
- Unbelievable.
- No, my texts.
- He's on his phone.
- Mine went up.
Suk Jin was on his phone
when we're supposed to be working.
Tell him not to be annoying.
You two.
- Are you aware of what's happening?
- What?
Can you see that
we're keeping our distance?
- Sit over there.
- Why won't anyone sit here?
Someone should sit here.
Okay, I will.
His legs.
- This is nice.
- Isn't it comfortable?
- What's with your legs?
- They're not good today.
I hate how the seat suits you.
- What?
- Right.
It's as if
it was tailor-made for you.
(While they let their legs
take a break...)
- What's that?
- That looks nice!
- This is the real deal.
- No way.
- Gosh.
- It's from the neighborhood.
- Goodness.
- It's like a local brand.
- This looks great.
We should sit around the table.
(My Grandmother's Tteokbokki)
- It's like a local brand.
- We'll enjoy.
- Check this out.
- What on earth?
Everything looks incredible.
There's more.
- It's how I like my tteokbokki.
- Can you clean up over there?
No way.
- Check out this squid.
- Do you have any scissors?
Check out the fried squid.
- This is incredible.
- It was fried as is.
Squid is all protein.
- This is the real deal.
- That's good.
(A short workout
increased their appetite.)
That's so good.
Some are made with rice
and some with flour.
There are shorter ones too.
I love how they serve
a variety of dishes.
The tteok made with rice
is their best option.
- It brings me back to my childhood.
- This is great.
(The one they ate
at the stationery store.)
- The stationery store tteokbokki.
- This is delicious.
- The one sold outside the school.
- And the stationery store.
Se Chan, did you even go to school?
Going to elementary school
and middle school is mandatory.
Of course I was in school.
He went to school but never studied.
- I bet you had a lot of fun.
- Really?
I can't believe he asked
if I went to school.
- I want to mash the egg.
- Let's do that.
Only a few people know this.
- That's right.
- But...
- This is it.
- Have a dumpling.
- I don't really like dumplings.
This is it, guys.
- This is it.
- I wouldn't recommend it.
- Hey. This is crazy good.
- Isn't it crazy good?
- This is so good.
- It's so good.
It's taking long to eat considering
it being product placement.
- You're right.
- Right.
They put in their everything
to make this.
- This is really good.
- Jong Kook. Do you have some rice?
It'd be nice to mix rice in it.
I can heat it up.
- Can you heat up one?
- Sure.
- He listens to us well.
- Jae Suk.
I don't have plain rice.
- Hey! I only eat brown rice.
- That's good.
- The dumpling is nice.
- Give us spoons too.
Okay, Jae Suk.
Can you give me some water too?
Shall I?
It's hard not to give her water
when she asked like that.
- How can you not give her water?
- You're sitting...
- She's like the lady of the house.
- like you live here.
Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Can you give me a bowl?
Jong Kook, Jae Suk wants a bowl.
Jong Kook?
Here, Ji Hyo.
Jong Kook, get me a bowl.
Can you hurry up?
I don't want the flow to be stopped.
He's doing everything for us
because we're at his place.
I know. He's so kind.
Thanks, Jong Kook. My gosh.
Thank you.
I'll mix it
with a little bit of rice.
I've never seen anyone
mix it with rice.
How come?
- It's good.
He doesn't know how to enjoy it.
He doesn't know how to eat it.
This is why he doesn't get
product placement.
(The spokesperson for the advertiser
gives him a blunt comment.)
- Suk Jin, this is...
- What?
People love eating it this way.
It's really nice
to mix it with rice.
(Jae Suk's tteokbokki bibimbap:
Soup, brown rice, egg, laver flake)
- The advertiser will love it.
- Of course.
I can see why you get...
- so many commercial deals.
- Of course.
Advertisers adore me.
It's a waste to throw the sauce
out because it's so good.
(A reaction advertisers
would die for)
It's so good.
- Se Chan, try this.
- I wish there were more eggs.
- We mashed all of them.
- This one is really good.
- You'll go crazy for it.
- Really?
I think you need to
heat up more rice.
It's so good.
(Se Chan makes a fuss
and asks for more rice.)
This is crazy good! I'm serious.
I told you. It's crazy good.
- Try it!
- You know how Se Chan...
When we got chips
for product placement,
he said they'd be good with rice.
That's not true!
(For the gopchang flavored chips
product placement last year...)
(He'd look for rice first
regardless of the type of food.)
- But with this...
- Try making it.
- No.
- I'll judge it objectively.
- As soon as you take a bite...
- The shrimp almost jumped out.
I told you. It's really good.
It's really good.
- It's good.
- Isn't it?
- That's the reaction you'd get.
- Gosh, that is so fake.
- It's really good.
- It's not fake.
Suk Jin, this is for real.
Suk Jin, you must say it now.
There's not much left.
- It's fine. I won't eat it.
- But if you don't...
- You should try it first.
- It's okay.
It's really good! You'll love it.
This is crazy good.
- I didn't expect this at all.
- You'll really love it.
Then let me try it.
(Then let me try it.)
(Embarrassed, he asks for a bite.)
He finally asked for it
now that not much is left.
"Let me try it."
He needs to have a bite too.
He must have it.
This is really good.
- Jae Suk, this is so good.
- Let me try just a little.
- It's really good.
- It really is.
It tastes like
traditional tteokbokki.
Suk Jin, won't you treat us
to patbingsu?
- Suk Jin.
- Let's have dessert.
- I want iced Americano.
- We could have patbingsu or...
- We want dessert.
- Then...
- You want dessert?
- Let's go buy patbingsu.
- Yes.
- Then...
- We'll get it with your card.
- I want patbingsu too.
Let's play a game
and decide who'll go.
- The loser will go and buy it?
- Yes.
Using their own card.
- Okay.
- I don't have one with me.
- Is that so?
- Let me borrow your card.
I'll wire it back to you later.
- No, you should use your own.
- No, let me borrow it first.
- I'll pay it back for real.
- He said he'd wire it.
- Let me borrow your card.
- You have your card with you.
I don't have a card with me.
I use Samsung Pay.
- Then we can use that.
- You need my fingerprints.
- Then come with us.
- You can go with them.
I'm too lazy to!
We'll return the money.
- We'll return it for real.
- It's not that.
Then you can just give them
your thumb.
Slice!
- Only his thumb?
- He's scary.
- That's a scary joke.
- Then...
- Let's play a game...
- Let's do that.
- and let two losers go.
- Two losers.
- We can decide what to play?
- Yes, go ahead.
- We haven't played that yet.
- Guessing the drawing.
- No, you played it too many times.
- Why not?
What's wrong with it?
But that's what we're here for.
(Everyone has withdrawals
from the game.)
Aren't we supposed
to play guess the drawing?
I want to play guess the drawing.
Then let's play that.
That one.
Are you talking about Game of Wits?
- Please stop!
- Yes, Game of Wits.
- I don't want it.
- It's the fastest one.
- Why play that at my place?
- Let's not play it again.
- Even the viewers...
- must be sick of it.
- Get ready.
- Let's not play that at home.
- The viewers must be sick of it.
- Or we can play...
- One.
- Two.
- Three.
- Let's play...
- Four.
- Five. All right!
- Six.
We got one loser.
- How about we play this?
- We got one.
- Let's play Initial Game of Wits.
- Initial Game of Wits.
- That sounds fun.
- Right?
- That sounds fun. Wow, Suk Jin.
- That sounds fun!
- Right?
- You're so cool, Suk Jin.
- Initials.
- Initial Game of Wits.
"GG."
- Meat.
- Country.
- Opportunity.
- Furniture.
- High price.
- Organization.
- Haha, you failed.
- You failed.
- There's "health."
- "Health."
(Ji Hyo and Haha will be in charge
of desserts.)
Let's go, Haha.
- All right!
- It's Haha and Ji Hyo.
- Haha and Ji Hyo.
- Thank you for the dessert.
Let's go.
I want to have patbingsu.
- I want weak iced Americano.
- I'll give you 20 dollars...
if you go instead of me.
- Then I'll go.
- Okay, you should go.
- Twenty dollars? Are you serious?
- I'll pay you with KakaoPay.
- Wait.
- I'll wire you the money.
- Gosh, that's ridiculous.
- Give it to me now.
All right.
You should ask for 30 dollars.
Twenty dollars?
- She's going for 20 dollars.
- You're going?
You're going to go?
- Hey.
- Lower the price.
I'll go if you pay me 19 dollars.
(Trying to get the job
by appealing his cost-effectiveness)
- Okay. Nineteen dollars it is.
- Nineteen dollars.
- You should've said 50 dollars.
- That's 19 dollars.
- Nineteen dollars.
- You should lower five dollars.
Is there a cafe near here?
I'll go for 18.5 dollars.
Suk Jin, at how much will you go?
So Min mentioned 18.5 dollars.
Going on an errand.
(Thinking)
- I'll go for 18 dollars.
- Sold.
Eighteen dollars it is.
- Is it sold?
- All right.
- Sold!
- It's sold. Get going, Suk Jin.
- It's sold.
- Go ahead.
- You'll be paid 18 dollars.
He might have to spend 200 dollars
after receiving 18 dollars.
- Go ahead, Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin didn't want to go.
- You're sold at 18 dollars.
- You're sold, Suk Jin.
- Let's go.
- Hurry up.
- I'm not going.
- Why wouldn't you go?
- You're sold.
- I only went along with the joke.
Even the viewers won't be able
to understand it.
- Why wouldn't they?
- Does this even make sense?
- You're sold.
- They might think it's weird.
- I actually wired him the money.
- You called for it.
- I...
- He sent the money. You're sold.
I'll send it back.
I'll even wire 20 dollars.
- Just get going already.
- Hurry up. We have to go.
Haha sent you 18 dollars.
Go get desserts now.
You should go.
- Then you should hold an auction.
- Hey.
(Suggesting him another auction)
- I...
- I won't go if it's not 50 dollars.
- I'll go if it's 40 dollars.
- I'll never go if it's below 50.
- It's so funny...
- I'll go if it's 40 dollars.
- how he's so serious.
- Forty dollars?
That's too cheap, you brat!
- Just ask for 50 dollars.
- Jae Suk's been watching...
to offer a lower price.
- What on earth is this?
- It's hilarious!
- Ask for 50 dollars, So Min.
- I didn't get paid anything.
Forty dollars?
- Make it 40.
- He'll accept it if you ask 50.
How about 45 dollars?
- Forty-five dollars? Okay.
- Because he said fifty dollars.
- I know. I only want fifty dollars.
- Forty-five dollars it is.
I'll give you 45 dollars.
- Give it to me. I'll go now.
- This is weird math.
Why does he have to take it
this far?
(An unbelievable investor who uses
45 dollars after making 18 dollars)
What was that?
Why is it so expensive
to send someone on an errand?
Also... So Min.
- Sell it back to Haha.
- So Min. Hey.
Hey!
You should've asked for 100 dollars.
Isn't this costing him more
than patbingsu?
I got it.
- Gosh, it's so funny.
- So Min, I'll go if you pay me 40.
- Oh, gosh.
- Darn it.
You'd have gone to get desserts
by now already.
You'd have gone already.
You'd be ordering by now.
All right. I'll go if you give me
40 dollars.
- Then you'll go?
- Yes.
- Okay, I call.
- Will you wire it to me? Okay.
- Wait a minute.
- I made some money.
Who spent the most money here?
(Suk Jin lost 27 dollars,
when the other two made more.)
- He spent the most money.
- This is some strange math.
You were supposed to go anyway,
but I spent 45 dollars for nothing.
You should've thought carefully
before saying anything.
- I wired it because...
- He's a genius investor.
- You...
- He's a genius.
- Let's go.
- He made money.
Haha, if you give me 20 dollars,
I'll go by myself.
If you give it to me, I'll go alone.
You won't be able to carry them all.
- No, I can carry them.
- You should go.
Go ahead, Mapo-gu residents.
I want a weak latte, please.
- A latte?
- I want iced Americano.
- Iced Americano?
- I also want iced Americano.
- A weak one.
- If they don't have patbingsu...
Please don't make it sweet.
If they don't have patbingsu...
- You want iced Americano?
- Please make it weak.
Then I'll have
an iced vanilla latte, decaf.
You two won't remember
the order for sure.
Just text me what you want.
- You can't remember them.
- Just text me.
If you're going to Starbucks,
can you get their chips?
What chips?
(Haughty)
(Gosh, you!)
- He's so annoying.
- You did well.
- Well done, Ji Hyo.
- She did well.
- Get some snacks too.
- Please get me those.
He was like the terrible fours.
- See you later.
- See you.
(Done ordering desserts, including
Jae Suk the terrible four)
It's so humid.
It's very humid.
(Stressed by the humid and hot
weather as soon as they're out)
(Frowning)
Should we get hot drinks
for everyone? Let's get only ours...
- in ice.
- In ice?
(You want only our drinks
to be iced?)
Let's get them something
so hot it'll burn their tongues.
Come on, Haha.
But I really want to buy
a hot drink for Jae Suk.
He's so playful.
(The more they think about him,
the more annoying they find him.)
Didn't someone
order a vanilla drink?
Let's just order caramel macchiato.
He won't be able to tell.
Let's do that.
A weak cup of latte, and...
- Caramel macchiato, decaf.
- Make it decaf.
And iced.
- She knows the rest.
- We'll have six iced Americano.
- Six?
- Yes.
(While they half-heartedly
order drinks...)
I feel like I'm less stressed now.
I think I'm
constantly getting stressed.
Gosh, Suk Jin.
You're not so good with investments.
Hey, my stress level is at 77.
- That's high.
- Yours is rather high.
It's very high.
- So far, you've made 1,000 dollars.
- Yes.
This time, the five of you
will carry out the third mission.
The third mission is to hear
the latter part...
- and complete a proverb.
- Sounds good.
- Sounds fun.
- While they're gone?
(Reap the whirlwind)
(If they guess the first part
of the proverb correctly,)
(they'll get the answer.)
(Jumps onto the kitchen table)
(A naughty calf)
(Acorn)
(Measuring height!)
(With original answers,
they came up with new proverbs.)
(A fish)
We're guessing the latter part?
- It was difficult.
- Not the first part?
- It was really difficult.
- Isn't it...
It's
"To kill two birds with one stone."
What do you mean they'll tell us
the latter part?
- They'll say the latter part...
- of the proverb.
- We need to complete it.
We just need to complete it?
He's frustrating too.
It's okay if we complete it.
He doesn't have
a good understanding.
"Understanding."
Can't you just get it immediately?
- My heart is beating faster.
- He can't understand things.
(My heart is beating faster.)
- I'll give you three chances only.
- Okay.
- All of you should pass just once.
This will stress us out.
Who will go first?
- Let's decide the order.
- You come here.
- I'll go there. You come here.
- Yes.
I'll sit next to you.
- All right.
- I'll go first.
- He can't do it.
- Okay.
A bolt.
(A bolt)
- Out of the blue.
- What? It's out of the blue.
(Quiet)
(A bolt out of the blue)
- He's...
- It's "out of the blue."
I was confused.
I couldn't think of it suddenly.
I want to dropkick him.
- In the back.
- What did you do?
- I couldn't think of it.
- It's "out of the blue."
How can you get it wrong?
Why couldn't I think of it suddenly?
You failed at the first attempt.
Jae Suk, you sit here.
- He must be crazy.
- Seriously.
It was so easy.
This is the basic.
My goodness.
- I couldn't think of it.
- Here I go.
Let's do this.
Little strokes...
(Little strokes...)
- Fell great oaks.
- That's it.
- Gosh.
- Why did you...
(Little strokes fell great oaks.)
- Gosh.
- Why did you...
- You should think.
- I mean...
It doesn't come to your mind, right?
- Why did you...
- It takes time to load.
It was close.
- It takes time.
- This is driving me crazy.
Hey, you know proverbs, right?
- Focus.
- I know the basic ones,
but I get confused
when I'm given a fancy one.
"Fancy."
Not the fancy one.
I know "A bolt out of the blue."
You should give him
what he knows, Bo Pil.
- That's the basic.
- A bolt out of the blue.
We've never given you
a difficult one.
- That's the basic.
- Not the difficult one.
Count three.
- Go.
- It's very easy.
It makes you even more nervous.
(Se Chan who said he would be fine
as long as it's not a difficult one)
A leopard cannot...
change its habit.
- Change its spots.
(A leopard cannot change its habit?)
It's "spots," not "habit."
- Change its spots.
I thought it was "habit."
(A leopard cannot...)
(So Min made the same mistake
last time.)
(Empty Heads' same wrong answer)
- You failed.
- Gosh.
- "Its habit."
- For real?
- Let's start from here.
- Hey.
- He said "its habit."
Jong Kook, come here.
- I mean...
- That's not the problem.
- I'll go first.
- Everyone should guess it right.
Let's do it again.
- I'm upset.
- I'll go first. Let's do it over.
- He's upset.
- Let's go.
- My heart is beating fast.
- Get it together.
- We got this.
- Let's get 500 dollars.
This isn't a joke.
We're filming at Jong Kook's house.
(We're filming
at Jong Kook's house!)
- Yes.
- We didn't come to play.
Here I go.
Even a monkey...
(Even a monkey...)
Even a monkey can fall from a tree.
That was nice. That was easy.
- What? It's not easy.
- Let's go.
- When you have to answer...
- It's good.
I'm fine
with this level of difficulty.
Like draws...
- To like.
- That's right.
Gosh.
That's right, So Min.
- Let's go.
- Give me something like this.
Why did you give me a difficult one?
- I feel dizzy.
- Don't give me a difficult one.
No, I won't.
- You should relax.
- Okay.
- You can't think when nervous.
- Right.
It's an easy one.
Why would you be nervous?
Both were very easy.
I know.
- Here I go.
- Be quiet.
It's nothing.
Of course.
Hunger is...
(Hunger is...)
- The...
- The best sauce.
(Timeout again)
The best sauce.
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm sorry.
- Seriously...
I suddenly couldn't think of it.
Even I knew it.
- Knew what?
- What on earth...
- is he doing?
- I knew it.
- You couldn't think of it either.
- Why do you think so?
Honestly...
You honestly didn't know, right?
- I thought it was "for frogs."
- He must be crazy.
"For frogs?"
- I thought "for frogs."
- Why did you give me a hard one?
That was easy. Even I knew.
Hunger is the best sauce.
Give us two more chances.
It's because I'm sorry to Jong Kook.
- He said yes.
- But...
- I got chances.
- But it's ridiculous.
I'll go first.
- Go.
- Here I go.
This is nothing.
It is the tail...
- Wagging the dog.
- Yes.
- It's easy.
- If he got it wrong...
- Good.
- I almost said something else.
It will become a controversy.
Go.
- Let's go.
- He's nervous.
He's nervous.
Bite...
(Bite...)
- Your house?
- The bullet!
(He suddenly thought
of "Bite your house.")
- The bullet.
- Why would it be "your house?"
Did he do it on purpose?
Did you think
"your house" was better?
I couldn't think of it.
Did you do it on purpose?
You did it on purpose.
- I couldn't think of it.
- He wouldn't do it on purpose.
- Don't lie.
I couldn't think of it.
Jong Kook, you go first.
- You try it.
- It doesn't...
- make sense.
- You try it.
- But it doesn't make sense.
- I couldn't think of it suddenly.
I knew it was "the bullet."
He didn't get it wrong so far.
Good.
- I'll get it together this time.
- Get it together.
- I'll do it. Okay.
- Please do so.
- Here I go.
- Yes.
(The owner of the house who
was full of confidence debuted.)
All noise and...
- No side dish.
- Incorrect.
- Hey.
- It's "substance."
No substance.
- Hey.
- No substance.
I told you.
Hey.
- Won't you do it properly?
- He gave me a difficult one.
- It's a hard one.
- He suddenly gave me a hard one.
This one is hard. So Min, come here.
- So Min got it wrong as well.
- All of a sudden...
She just said "substance."
It's "no substance."
Let's do it again.
We have one more chance.
- The last one.
- No substance.
- You used all your chances,
- So Min.
- but I'll let it slide.
- Just one more time.
- Let's do it just one more time.
- Try it.
It isn't easy.
It was hard.
- It was all hard.
- I said it was not easy.
It's difficult to think
of the words that come next.
Why do you think I said
"Bite your house?"
- Try it.
- Starting from here.
Give me an easy one this time.
Experience is...
(Experience is...)
- Hey.
- Incorrect.
- It's "the best teacher."
- Experience is the best...
- The best teacher.
(He was so confident.)
What's wrong with you? It was easy.
Why did he give me the one
I didn't know?
It's not that you didn't know.
Come out.
- Come out.
Let's do it again.
Jae Suk should go there.
We'll make a dream team.
- I should be in.
- Yes.
I'll be in.
- "Bite the bullet, the best..."
- Suk Jin.
Is this a dream team?
He suddenly gave me
the one I didn't know.
We'll try with a dream team.
Do you get how good I was earlier?
I mean...
He kept giving others short ones.
But he gave me a long one.
- Look. "All noise" was long.
- Yes.
- The "experience" one was long too.
- What?
Give me something like
"Bite the bullet." Something simple.
Or give us four-character idioms.
- Four-character idioms.
No. It's more difficult.
- So if I give you two characters...
Say the first two.
He said
he would give us the last two.
The one you suggested is harder.
It gives you a mental breakdown.
No. Give me the first two.
Give us the last two.
"The relation between friends."
- No.
- "The partnership between friends."
- "The relation between friends."
- It's "Faith should reign over."
- "Faith should reign over."
"Faith should reign
over the relation between friends."
- Here I go.
- Yes. It's four-character idioms.
- Will you give us the last 2?
- I'll say the last 2 characters.
Okay. Good.
That feeds you.
- Bite the hand that feeds you.
- Yes.
I know this one.
- I know this one.
- Isn't it much better?
- We have a good chance.
- I know it.
Do it lightly, roughly. Relax.
- Talk.
- Sweet.
- I know it.
- Let's go.
- Oh, no.
- Old Man.
You know old sayings.
He learned it at a village school.
Yes.
I learned it at a village school.
Talker.
- Faith should reign over.
- It's "smooth."
(Incorrect)
(Faith should reign
over the talker.)
- It's "smooth talker."
- "Smooth talker."
- Incorrect.
- It's over.
It's a relief that it was over
before my turn.
This is weird.
It's a relief that he got it wrong
before my turn.
This is...
It's "smooth talker," Se Chan.
- I've heard of it.
- "He's a smooth talker."
You should give us three chances.
- Give us three chances.
- Just once.
The last one. Come here, So Min.
Starting from So Min...
- Four-character idioms are...
- Yes. Start from So Min.
- We did four-character idioms once.
- Start from So Min.
- I'll start from here.
- Okay.
"Smooth talker." Gosh.
If you three guess it right,
we'll do it too no matter what.
- No matter what.
- I'll take it slow.
- It was because I was in a hurry.
- We know many idioms.
- We learned them in childhood.
- Yes.
- Here I go.
- It's simple.
Strong outside.
- Soft inside.
- Good.
By the skin of his teeth.
(By the skin of his teeth.)
- By the skin of his teeth?
- It's "He escaped death."
(Jong Kook failed again.)
- Hey.
- "He escaped death."
- Escaped, death.
This is the only thing
I didn't know.
It's "He escaped death
by the skin of his teeth."
- "He escaped death."
- For real.
Even I knew it.
"He escaped death
by the skin of his teeth."
Let's do this with the four of us.
- Was it an idiom?
- "He escaped death."
"He escaped death
by the skin of his teeth."
He's unexpectedly bad.
Unexpectedly bad.
I'm not lying.
I knew everything except for this.
We have the last chance.
Gosh, I can't tell him off
because it's his house.
- Should we start from here?
- Yes.
We have one last chance.
Buddy.
A bosom.
- I knew it.
- A bosom buddy.
What? You know it
because you heard my answer.
Vow.
(Vow.)
Horse...
- Isn't it "wedding vow?"
- "Wedding."
(Horse?)
He made a wedding vow
and still got it wrong.
- What's with "horse?"
- You made a wedding vow.
What's with "horse?"
It's so strange. I know
all the idioms given to others.
I know "wedding vow."
- You...
- I couldn't think of it.
- What's with "horse?"
- I know the idioms given to others.
- "Horse vow?"
- This is strange.
- What's with "horse?"
This is hard.
I gave you ten chances. You failed.
Goodness gracious.
- We can't do it.
- This isn't easy.
I wanted to give the money
to Jong Kook.
Can you give us one more chance?
You know we all got it wrong
at least once, right?
- Yes.
- Oh, no.
What if I guess five questions right
by myself for 500 dollars?
- You?
- Five questions by myself.
- Five questions.
- Why are you so confident?
- Let's go.
- I'll go.
Didn't you get many questions wrong?
Let's go. Cheer me up.
- You got this.
- You can do it.
- Four-character idioms only?
Four-character idioms only. Okay.
Give him five questions in a row.
Let's see how many he gets wrong.
There's no penalty
for the wrong answer though.
What?
I'll let you slap me in the face.
Okay.
By who? Hyo Im?
(Hyo Im, the main writer?)
- Okay.
- That's good.
Getting slapped in the face
by Hyo Im.
- That's good.
- It'd be comfortable for Hyo Im...
- when she's not on camera.
- Film her arm only.
- It's to make her comfortable.
- Yes.
It's a penalty.
- Here I go.
- It's stressing me out.
(It's stressing her out
in the meantime.)
- A hard place.
- Between a rock and a hard place.
- It's good.
- Well done.
The second question.
Into rage.
Into rage?
- It's that one.
- Incorrect.
- "Fly."
- It's "fly into rage."
- Incorrect.
- "Fly."
(Everyone flew "into rage.")
Even I knew it. "Fly into rage."
Hey.
It's "Fly into rage."
You got the really easy one wrong.
- I'll get slapped.
- Go ahead.
I will get slapped
behind the camera.
It's okay if we only hear the sound.
Hyo Im, come here.
- Slap him properly.
- He needs to get slapped.
For your anonymity,
- we will use a tight shot.
- Use a tight shot.
- Hyo Im, slap him properly.
- Slap me.
- Slap him hard.
- Only your hand will appear.
You are carrying out a penalty.
I asked for this.
Don't feel guilty.
- Slap him twice.
- Oh, no.
(A light slap)
- You slapped too gently.
- She slapped too gently.
- Hyo Im, you slapped too gently.
- You slapped too gently.
- Come on.
- Hyo Im,
- you should have done this.
- Slap me harder.
- Slap him harder.
- Do it, Hyo Im.
- Carry out the penalty properly.
- Slap him hard.
That wasn't bad.
- She doesn't have much strength.
- Okay.
- Let me try it. I will go first.
- Five questions.
- The house owner will go first.
It should be a hard slap.
- I will make up for my mistake.
- Okay.
All the easy questions are gone.
Why can't I remember anything
when I am answering the questions?
Let me relax first. Hold on.
- Relax.
- I will relax.
- This is nothing.
- The first question.
- Let's say that you are answering.
- That's a good idea.
The first question.
- The better.
- The more, the better.
- Okay.
- That was an easy one.
The second question.
Are the best.
Local products are the best.
- That was a hard one.
- I know.
- You are answering.
- Good.
- Can't you do better?
- His mental control is incredible.
Think that I am answering.
- The third question.
- I think he will succeed.
Can't be hidden.
Talent can't be hidden.
- Talent can't be hidden.
- Okay.
I didn't hear it.
- I swear I didn't hear it.
- He swears.
- I didn't say anything.
I swear it.
- I heard it too.
- Punish me if it's a lie.
- You can bet your future, right?
- I didn't hear anything.
- It was a difficult one.
- He knows the idiom.
- I swear it.
I understand, but you get a warning.
- Okay.
- Seriously.
- We didn't hear it.
I swear I didn't hear it.
He swears.
- He usually doesn't do that.
- Right now,
- Jae Suk is answering.
- Okay.
- Only 2 questions remain. Let's go.
- Only 2 questions remain.
(Two questions remain.)
Of visitors.
- A constant stream of visitors.
- Good.
- It was easy.
- Give him an easy one.
One question remains.
(Will Jong Kook be able to succeed?)
No gain.
- No pain, no gain.
- Yes!
(No pain, no gain.)
- You got 500 dollars.
The answers come easily...
when you think they are
someone else's questions.
- Good job.
- I could succeed...
- because I expanded the realm.
- Good job.
- You sweated so much.
- Feel his palm.
Jong Kook sweated so much.
Hey, my palms...
He sweated so much.
Suk Jin should go next.
(Suk Jin gives it a try
for additional 500 dollars!)
Jong Kook.
- I am sorry. I will cross my legs.
- Think widely.
- Let's say we aren't filming.
- That's a good idea.
- The first question.
- Okay.
- High horse.
- Beating a dead horse.
(Incorrect)
Oh, it's
"Getting on your high horse."
- High horse.
- Beating a dead horse.
(Getting on your high horse)
Oh, it's
"Getting on your high horse."
(He proudly yelled,
"Beating a dead horse.")
For goodness' sake.
- Come on.
- I mean...
Who will do it?
- Hyo Im?
- Get slapped.
I thought it was
"Beating a dead horse."
- You made it confusing.
- It's a different idiom.
Why did you give a different idiom?
For a second,
- I was like, "What?"
- Getting on your high horse.
- "Why did Bo Pil say..."
- I said it.
- "the latter words?"
- Beating a dead horse.
The answer was
"Getting on your high horse."
I thought you made a mistake.
- Hurry up.
- Do it.
- It's okay, Hyo In. Slap me.
- Slap him.
Do it.
(He doesn't need
to be slapped again.)
That was good, Hyo In.
(The satisfactory slap
makes the customer happy.)
Hey.
- That was fun.
- That was good.
- Say that you are okay.
- What?
Say that you are okay.
I'm okay.
She slapped me hard.
- It's nice.
- It was what we wanted.
- Getting slapped by the crew.
- It's nice, right?
- You know,
- We should do it often.
I thought you made a mistake.
You said, "High horse..."
and I said, "Beating a dead horse."
Why don't we make So Min answer
three questions?
- I will do it for a finger flick.
- A finger flick.
- Who will carry out the penalty?
- Se Chan.
No.
I won't do this.
I will do this instead.
- No.
- Then it won't hurt much.
I want...
the camera director to do it.
Really?
- He can be scary.
- Okay.
Hit her hard.
Otherwise, it won't be funny.
Let's begin.
Okay. I am not answering.
- You are answering.
- Se Chan is answering.
You are answering, So Min. It's you.
Focus. It's you.
- Focus.
- The first question.
Focus. It's you.
- It will be great if you succeed.
- Answer right away.
- That's right.
- Focus.
- Stop it.
- Focus. It's you.
- It's you, So Min.
- Come on.
- The first question.
- Okay.
Sit up straight.
The dumps.
(Hesitating)
- Incorrect.
- Down in the dumps.
Down in the dumps.
- For goodness' sake.
- So Min, it was a hard one.
- Down in the dumps.
- It wasn't a hard one.
It was a hard one.
I didn't know the answer either.
We are currently down in the dumps.
What? Do you think you failed
because of me?
What did I do?
- It was an easy one.
- Come on.
(The owner of the house loves
watching people receive penalties.)
For goodness' sake.
Only your hand will appear
in the shot.
Okay.
(Yes!)
(The older members
smile from ear to ear.)
I told you that I would do it.
Hurry up and say that you are okay.
- I am okay.
- You are okay, right?
- It's okay
- I am okay.
- Everything will be fine
- That was great.
- Down in the dumps.
Down in the dumps.
- Did your chest turn sweaty?
- Where?
- It's sweat.
- I sweated.
- He was nervous.
He sweated because of the idioms.
The idioms made Jong Kook sweat.
I relaxed my body,
but this area was tense.
You wouldn't need to do
aerobic exercise today.
- Idioms can replace it.
- Seriously.
Idioms can replace aerobic exercise.
I thought you were relaxed.
- It's no joke.
- Only your face relaxed.
- Only my face.
- His palms were so sweaty.
So sweaty.
My palms were sweaty.
- Se Chan, give it a try.
- Three questions.
- Give it a try.
- I will get slapped.
- Ah Reum will do it.
- That's a good idea.
- She is the type to go crazy.
- Seriously.
She is the type to go crazy.
- Ah Reum is a bit crazy.
- That's right.
(She is known to be a crazy writer.)
Go slowly.
- Give me the ones I have heard of.
- It's your question. Focus.
- The ones I have heard of.
- Let's begin.
- Open your ears like this.
- The first question.
All right.
Like son.
Run about like son.
(Run about like son)
Like father, like son.
(The comedian who specializes
in idioms made people laugh again.)
- Hey, what was that?
- Like father, like son.
- It's "Run about in confusion."
- Run about in confusion.
My goodness.
- Like father, like son.
- Se Chan.
- It was the easiest one.
- Hey.
Why did you do that?
Why did you give such an easy one?
- It was the easiest one.
- Get slapped.
I knew the answer.
- When it isn't my question...
- Slap hard.
(Slapping)
I am okay.
- "Run about like son" was funny.
- All right. Let's wait for food.
- That was funny.
- Run about like son.
You got 500 dollars.
- All right.
- We did well.
That was funny. Thank goodness.
- My stress level went up again.
- Let's see.
(So Min)
Mine went up, right?
Mine went up.
Shall we have a quiz
so that it skyrockets?
Mine is 77 again.
Yours is so high.
- Look. It's 77.
- Why do you get so stressed out?
Mine is 41.
- Mine is 58.
- Why is mine so high? It's 77.
Isn't it wrong?
I am under constant stress.
It's correct.
You are in the situation
that puts you under constant stress.
Look at the color
of Jong Kook's clothes.
- They are so dull.
- They are so dark.
All of them are black and gray.
- He can do that...
- I live alone.
- because he lives alone.
- It's convenient.
You rarely discard things.
I rarely discard things.
That's why I don't buy things.
- You don't discard people either.
- No, I don't.
Why do you keep doing that
to Jong Kook?
- Why do you keep doing that?
- It's not like that.
- Hey.
- Seriously.
Why do you keep doing that?
Why are you showing interest
in Jong Kook?
- I was just asking.
- Do you think he is yours?
- No.
- You think all men are yours.
Are you struggling with work
these days?
- Are you?
- So Min is ridiculous.
You keep testing Jong Kook.
If you aren't careful,
bloody fights will break out
among the cast members.
I was just asking.
Se Chan, do you discard people?
Why would I discard people?
I don't do that.
For goodness' sake.
You do that.
You discarded Se Chan.
You discarded him.
- You discarded him.
- She did that right away.
(They can do anything to be funny.)
- Gosh, So Min.
- How about you?
I don't discard people.
Suk Jin, stay out of this.
I mean...
- Suk Jin, stay out of this.
- Suk Jin.
The moment you butt in,
this entire bit will get edited out.
Don't be like that.
- Stay out of this.
- Don't do that.
- Why would I butt in?
- They are here.
They are here.
- Open the door.
- For goodness' sake.
- Did they open the door?
- Open the door.
- Welcome back.
- What took you so long?
- They brought back coffee.
- Was the cafe far away?
- It's so damp.
It's damp outside.
- Is it hot?
- It's like a sauna.
- Thank you.
Thank you. We will enjoy it.
- Great.
You bought a lot.
- What is this?
- Good job.
My goodness.
I am exhausted.
- My legs hurt.
- I am exhausted too.
Gosh, my shin.
(His legs became weak in one day.)
Going outside
increased my stress level.
- Really?
- It's no joke outside.
- It's so hot.
- Is it that hot outside?
- We exercised too.
- That's right.
- We did squats.
- You are right.
That's right.
Think about how healthy you would be
if you do that much every day.
Think about it.
Being outside was better.
Seriously.
- They acquired 500 dollars.
- We played a game.
- What did you do?
- Haha.
- You would have never succeeded.
Why? What was the game?
- It was hard.
- Idioms and proverbs.
- It was really hard.
- It's true.
There's no way you succeeded.
You sat out, right?
- I participated.
- Do you know any proverbs?
- What do you know?
- What?
Proverbs that are common knowledge.
- It's so hot outside.
- Is it that hot?
- It's humid.
- It's very humid.
It's the rainy season.
I am going to Jeju Island
during the rainy season.
It will begin raining there tonight.
(Suk Jin will go to Jeju Island
when it's raining heavily.)
I didn't think of that
when I planned the vacation.
(Uninterested)
- Good job.
- It will rain the day I arrive.
- That's nice. It suits you.
- My goodness.
You are trying to stress him out.
Which places will you visit
on Jeju Island?
On Jeju Island?
I will just stay in a hotel.
Then you should stay here.
What's the use of going there?
I see that you have begun.
Seriously.
(He pretends to be unfazed.)
Think about it.
Suk Jin is flustered.
I won't get stressed out.
- Think about it.
- I know it's your strategy.
I won't get stressed out.
- I mean...
- Suk Jin makes this gesture...
- when it's an emergency.
- I won't get stressed out.
- It has begun.
- Still...
- There are nice hotels here.
But the atmosphere
is different there.
- Let's begin the next mission.
- Okay.
In the next mission,
a single decision
will bring delight or frustration.
It's the Perfect Touch.
The Perfect Touch.
All members will receive
a Pirate Roulette.
What then?
- Insert as many swords as you want.
- It will be hard.
The team needs to insert
a total of 25 swords.
Okay. I got it.
- All right.
- Insert 3 to 4 swords.
Let's relax and enjoy the game.
We earned some money anyway.
- Insert 3 to 4 swords.
- Yes.
We earned some money.
- I don't have high expectations.
- I can insert ten swords.
If you think the pirate will pop up,
leave it to the next person.
- All right.
- The next person can take over.
But the moment a pirate pops up,
- it's over.
- Okay.
Let's not blame anyone who fails.
We won't do that.
Don't blame anyone.
Okay.
Let's not blame anyone who fails.
Let's not do that.
Why don't we insert one sword each?
- Yes.
- Go.
There you go.
Why did you put on sunglasses?
They were laying around.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
- While you were gone...
- Hold on.
- I am not trying to start trouble.
- Okay.
So Min kept showing interest
in Jong Kook.
I will insert two swords.
(She receives the news.)
- I can keep going, right?
- Hey, don't change the subject.
- I will insert another one.
- Don't change the subject.
- Insert three swords.
- She is holding a sword.
- Will you be okay?
- Hurry up.
- Hey.
- Stop.
- Three swords.
- Are you going to be like that?
- Good job.
- I am done.
- You changed the subject.
Okay. I get it now.
- Shall I start?
- Yes.
Someone needs to insert
three more swords.
It doesn't pop up that easily.
Why do I think
this slot will make it pop up?
- Then choose another slot.
- The next one.
Don't do it. You have a good hunch.
- Choose the next slot.
- Which one? This one?
- Yes.
- What if it's this one?
It might be this one.
Then go to the other side.
I will insert it into the slot
I originally chose.
(Remaining number)
- It was a safe one.
- One more?
- But...
- I am done.
Really?
Although Jong Kook has
muscular arms, he goes...
(Trembling)
"What should I do?"
- His palms get sweaty.
- I felt like it would pop up.
- His chest gets sweaty.
No blaming others.
For goodness' sake.
I inserted it. I am done.
(Remaining number)
- Everyone is timid.
- Ji Hyo, insert some swords.
- Ji Hyo, insert more swords.
- I think it will pop up.
- Again?
- Insert more swords, Se Chan.
- I am done.
- But...
- My goodness.
- Good job.
- Stop now, Ji Hyo.
- Stop now.
- Hey.
- Stop now, Ji Hyo.
Okay.
(She inserted 3 swords.)
Why do I feel like it would pop up?
Please.
- Stop.
Let's make a round first.
- Someone like me...
- I am glad you stopped.
(Remaining number)
Isn't it the one behind?
(Jae Suk succeeded
to insert one sword.)
Shall I stop?
How many slots are there? Eight?
What's the remaining number now?
Three.
- Three.
- Insert all the swords.
- Hold on. All the swords?
- Yes.
How many swords will you insert?
(The remaining number is 14.)
- All the swords?
- How many swords will you insert?
Hey.
- Jae Suk.
- You failed.
- How many swords will you insert?
- Hey.
(A pirate escaped.)
(The mission ends
in the speed of light.)
For goodness' sake.
- Why did you do that?
- I told you to stop.
Why did you do that?
The first two attempts were good.
It ended so quickly.
- I mean...
- Why did you keep going?
- You should have asked us.
- The first two attempts were good.
Why did you act on your own?
I thought the third attempt
would be the same.
You were too confident.
- I inserted four swords.
- You failed.
I thought the third attempt
would be the same.
- Five swords.
- No blaming others.
You should have asked us.
All right. You failed
to acquire 500 dollars.
Let's move on to the next mission.
- Jae Suk.
- For goodness' sake.
Whatever.
This place is so stressful.
This is a pit.
We have to get out.
Let's do the escape room.
- That's the only hope.
- We have to get out.
I want to go home.
I want to hurry up and leave.
- I am stressed out.
- Seriously.
For the first time ever,
I want to go home and babysit.
- It's time for the last mission.
- Okay.
Let's do it.
- When I give you a word,
- A word?
change the 1st letter
of the 1st and 2nd syllables...
in three seconds.
- What do you mean?
- Let me give you an example.
If the word is Yoo Jae Suk,
say, "Ju Yae Seok."
- This is hard.
- Can we use any words?
- No.
- I will give you a word.
- Y and J got switched.
- The first letters.
- Yes.
- This is hard.
- If it's Ji Suk Jin,
- Yang Se Chan.
the answer is See Jeok Jin.
- Kang Je Chan.
- Sang...
- Sang.
- Y and S.
- You follow the order.
(Switch the first letters
of the first 2 syllables.)
- Let me tell you this in advance.
- Sang Ye Chan.
I can't do this.
- Try it.
- Sang Ye Chan.
- Try it for Song Ji Hyo.
- Song Ji Hyo.
- Jong Si Hyo.
- Ji Suk Jin.
Let's begin. Only 4 out of 7 people
need to succeed.
That's good.
- Who wants to go first?
- That end.
Let's stay calm.
- All right.
Only four people need to succeed.
- It's time for aerobic exercise.
- Stay calm.
- Jong Kook.
- He will do aerobic exercise.
(It's time for Jong Kook
to do aerobic exercise.)
- It will be like aerobic exercise.
- Se Chan.
- Give Jong Kook a towel.
- He is sweating already.
- Stay calm.
- Let's begin.
This is like aerobic exercise
for him.
Who will go first?
- We will start from this end.
- Okay.
Rhinoceros.
(Rhinoceros)
Nhiroceros.
- That's correct.
- Nhiroceros is correct.
- You did well.
You are good at things
that don't require knowledge.
Seriously.
This is a matter of association.
- A matter of what?
- Association.
You did well, So Min.
Let's go.
- Here it comes.
- Don't say it quickly. Go slowly.
Kang Ho Dong.
Hang Kong Hok Dong.
(Incorrect)
Hang Ko Dong.
- One person succeeded so far.
- This is hard.
This requires imagination.
- Let's begin.
- Then it's "Ttaengkkong bug."
No, it isn't.
Susaek Station.
(Susaek Station)
- Sosaek... No.
- It's the same.
- It's just Susaek Station.
- Susaek Station.
- Sosaek... No.
- It's the same.
(It's just Susaek Station!)
- It's Susaek Station.
- Susaek Station.
It's just Susaek Station.
Are you stupid?
That fool.
(He laughs due to embarrassment.)
- You didn't have to change it.
- It's just Susaek Station.
S and S.
- Se Chan.
- I ended up going,
"Sosaek..."
- Se Chan.
- S and S.
It's okay.
Just grow up into a nice man.
- Se Chan.
- I also thought, "Susaek?"
"What is it?"
Susaek Station. That's right.
The first letters are the same.
- Gosh.
- This is impossible.
Is it Ji Hyo's turn?
- I am ready.
- All right.
Okay.
- Do well.
- Im Kkeok Jeong.
- Kkeok Im Jeong.
- Incorrect.
The second part is Kim.
- Kim.
- Ikeok Kim Jeong.
She said it so seriously.
- Kim.
- Kim...
All three of us need to succeed.
- That was funny.
- Go.
- Let's do this, married men.
- Focus.
- Married men!
Focus.
Here it comes.
Swallowtail butterfly.
(Swallowtail butterfly)
- It's over.
- Lwalsowtail butterfly.
- Incorrect.
- Come on.
- It's too late.
- Lwalsowtail butterfly.
- Let me off this once.
- Incorrect.
- Come on. It's too late.
- Lwalsowtail butterfly.
- Incorrect.
- It's a bezzer-butter.
- It was too late.
- You mean "A buzzer-beater."
"A bezzer-butter?"
- Even I got it right.
- A buzzer-beater.
The first attempt failed.
- Haha will begin now.
- It's the second attempt.
- I will give you three attempts.
- Jae Suk needs to try it.
It's hard when you actually do it.
That's right.
Jo Biden.
Three, two...
- Bo Biden.
- Incorrect.
- Jiden.
- Bo Jiden.
- This one was easy.
- I know.
- Bo Jiden.
- For goodness' sake.
- Let's see how well you do.
- Watch.
- It's hard when you actually do it.
I will succeed right away.
Let's begin.
- Jeong Yak Yong.
- What?
Jeong Yak...
(Jeong Yak Yong)
(What?)
Don't do that.
- All right.
- You are buying time.
- Why did you answer?
- All right. I will do it properly.
- Why did you go, "What?"
- "What?"
- Why did you do that?
- Hey.
It's Yeong Jak Yong.
It's late.
Let's start over.
- All right.
- You need to answer right away.
- All right. Don't worry.
- He did it to buy time.
Don't worry.
Ji Hyo, you should study.
- I am studying now.
- Here it comes.
Bring it on.
Han Seok Kyu.
Han Seok Kyu. Well...
Incorrect.
(Han Seok Kyu!)
(Well...)
- San...
- San Heok Kyu.
You said "incorrect" too quickly.
You used up time by talking.
- You said it too quickly.
- San Heok Kyu.
- For goodness' sake.
- Okay. Did we fail?
- Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
Fried shrimp.
Two, one.
Sried fried.
- Incorrect.
- "Sried fried?"
- Sried fhrimp.
- It was an easy one.
Song Ji Hyo.
- Go.
- Two...
Jong So...
- Jong So Hyo.
- Incorrect.
- This is hard.
- Three-syllable words are easy.
- Incorrect.
This game is hard.
- This game is hard.
- They stress us out...
and measure our stress levels.
It's annoying.
It's difficult.
It's at 79.
This is getting stressful.
- This is stressful.
- This is difficult.
- It's hard.
- This game gives me so much stress.
- It's...
- All missions are over.
- I have the final result.
- Okay.
The person with the biggest
difference doesn't place last.
- That's not how it works.
- No.
It seems So Min had a lot of stress.
- First, it's Jae Suk.
- Yes.
- You were at 40 in the beginning.
- At 40.
- You dropped to 41.
- In the end,
you were at 42.
Okay.
- You're on the list.
Forty means there's barely anything.
- Next is Suk Jin.
- You still went up.
You were at 36. In the end,
it was at 63.
- That's high.
- How can you escape?
The fact you thought
you could escape...
Haha. You started at 56.
It ended at 61.
(Haha becomes a penalty candidate.)
- You're also on the list.
- I knew it.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
- You started at 42.
- At 42.
- It ended at 52.
- That's high.
- She was under a lot of stress.
- It's the four of us.
You started at 45.
- It was low.
Forty eight.
It ended at 43.
(Se Chan avoids the penalty.)
- That was close.
- No stress.
So Min. You started at 48.
- Eighty six.
- Fifty two.
It ended at 47.
(So Min avoids the penalty.)
(So Min and Se Chan avoid
the penalty.)
- You dropped?
- She dropped.
So, these four are up
for the penalty.
- Okay.
- Good.
This is too much.
It'll be one of you four.
- Gosh. Excuse me.
- It's always me.
- You should give them out.
- Jong Kook. You distribute them.
- Okay.
- You should distribute them.
I had a penalty recently.
- I know.
- But he doesn't know.
- Right.
- He doesn't know what it is.
- You don't know, do you?
- No.
Go.
Here.
Gosh.
Thank you in advance, Jong Kook.
- You bet.
- Thank you, Jong Kook.
Thank you in advance, Jong Kook.
You bet, Jae Suk.
- Shall we open it one by one?
- Okay.
- Let's open it one by one.
Go.
- Just relax.
- One, two, three.
(If it says penalty, the person
has to receive the penalty.)
No, it's not her.
- You should do it.
- No, it's not her.
- It's not her.
- See? It's not her.
- It wasn't Ji Hyo.
- Gosh.
Right?
- I hope it's Suk Jin.
- He's going to Jeju Island.
Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin also avoids the penalty.)
Not again.
- It's them again.
- You should switch.
- It's "How Do You Play?"
- It's these two again.
- Jae Suk.
- I'm not switching.
(They remained to the end again.)
- Jae Suk.
- I'm not switching.
- There must be something.
- One.
You should switch.
- No.
- There must be something.
It's always those two.
I was right.
(Jae Suk gets the penalty.)
(Jae Suk gets the penalty again.)
(Everyone is laughing.)
I had no idea.
- He didn't know.
- I didn't know.
Jae Suk got the penalty
two weeks in a row.
He's getting the penalty every time.
That's amazing.
How is this possible?
You should get an exorcism.
- Jae Suk.
- You should do that.
Before I announce the penalty,
here's the housewarming party gift
you won.
Congratulations.
- He did it.
- I'm not sure if I deserve it.
You deserve it.
It's not easy to film at home.
- Thank you.
- Not everyone...
- reveals their house.
- Right.
- This means a lot.
We'll donate the rest
to a good place.
Here's today's penalty.
You were under
a lot of stress today.
To relieve your stress,
you have to sing alone
in the coin karaoke.
(Sing three songs
in the coin karaoke alone.)
(He gets to go
to the coin karaoke alone.)
- Bye.
Goodbye.
(Other guests get ready to go home.)
(Jae Suk happens
to hate it so much.)
I don't know if I deserve this gift.
(Coin karaoke?)
Jae Suk.
I'll take that for 50 dollars.
(Jae Suk.
I'll take that for 50 dollars.)
(She suggests trading the penalty.)
I'll do that for 50 dollars.
So Min.
Good. I'll pay you.
- For 50 dollars.
- Fifty?
- Fifty.
- Really?
- For fifty.
- Hang on. Sixty?
- So Min. Raise the price.
- Fifty.
- Call 100.
You should call 100. It's Jae Suk.
- Sixty.
- Sixty. Okay.
- You'll do it?
- Yes.
Thank you so much.
I hate singing alone in the karaoke.
- I love it.
- Really?
This is great.
So Min. This is great.
I'll send you 60 dollars now.
I'll allow that trade
only for today.
- Okay.
Now, that's all for
Jong Kook's housewarming party.
- What should I sing?
- Thank you.
- It was successful.
That was neat.
Thank you, So Min.
I'll give you 60 dollars now.
- Of course. It's fun.
- Good work.
- First,
I'll sing Fin.K.L.
(To start with)
I don't know recent songs.
Fin.K.L and...
I actually prefer ballad.
So I'm going to sing mostly ballad.
Come in. It's so spacious
for a coin karaoke.
Then I'll start.
(Then I'll start.)
It's Cameraman Bong Jo's request.
(Her cameraman requested "Dash.")
(Getting ready to dance)
I used to know this dance,
but I forgot now.
(Come on.)
(The cheesy girl's
extraordinary dance)
(The ghost wave)
(She ignores the tone and beat.)
There's only Young Chul's version.
This is really fun.
You should jump with me.
(Ring)
(Forced to dance)
(She enjoys the beat alone.)
(Bouncing)
(I'm your girl.)
(The retro style dancer
dominates the small room.)
(It's all heated up.)
(I'm your girl.)
(The dance balladeer mixes air
in her voice.)
(I want to seduce you tonight.)
(So Min already sang
more than three songs.)
(She adds emotions that
no one told her to do.)
(The production crew is flustered
as it gets long.)
(Balladeer Jeon forgot
about going home.)
(Some crew end up joining
Jeon So Min Show.)
Say, I'm a fool.
- I'm a fool
- Okay.
Se Chan!
(Se Chan!)
This song is for Se Chan.
("Pride" by Fin.K.L)
(A song for a foolish man who
doesn't understand the girl's heart)
(As So Min isn't likely to stop...)
Where are you going?
Keep filming me.
(The penalty deputy enjoyed
the penalty so much.)
That's so high.
What should I sing next?
Something fast.
Our encounter
(To X Generation Running Man...)
(and the old man KCM,)
(MZ Generation pays a visit.)
(Park Cho Rong, Yoon Bo Mi)
(Mirani)
(A class on MZ's hip...)
(to overcome the generation gap)
(Learn...)
(the hip gesture.)
(You look like you're cold, So Min.)
(Enjoy...)
(the hip restaurants.)
(Will we...)
(be able to become hip?)
I'm getting sick of you.
It's funny because that's so lowly.
(At that moment)
(You'd even eat poo
if people say it's hip.)
It's more shocking
when the AI says it.
(Will you conquer the hip...)
(or be conquered by it?)
(War of Spoon)