(The 4-week-long journey
of Whatever Penalty Project)
(Week 1)
(Grim Reaper Ji Hyo was out.)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo
received penalty stickers.)
(Week 2)
(In the roulette race,)
(Haha lost 4 times
beating all the odds.)
(Week 3)
(Se Chan was targeted by
the tough girls...)
(and received penalty stickers.)
(Week 4)
(After last week's race,)
(Se Chan got the most stickers,
and Jae Suk got exempted.)
(Se Chan will get the penalty,
and Jae Suk will be exempted.)
What is this skull?
I'm feeling at ease now.
Jong Kook, I'm feeling at ease.
- You'll be going anyway.
- I'll go anyway.
Jae Suk must be relaxed too.
- He's not going.
- Actually...
- He seems to be in a good mood.
- These five must be nervous.
It's unbelievable
that he got exempted.
- I know.
- Which one is the closest?
We can't go to Yeosu.
- Yeosu is...
- Yeosu is too far.
I heard this episode would be short.
- Well...
- Should we talk less?
Our show usually starts at 5 p.m.
But why does this episode
start at 4:50 p.m. today?
(It's for the new TV show,
"Sing For Gold")
- All of a sudden?
- Talk less.
Why do we have to finish at 6 p.m.?
- Does it end at 6 p.m.?
- What?
Hey, at this rate, we will end up
shooting short clips.
(At this rate, we will end up
shooting short clips.)
- That's too short.
- Are we doing the reels?
- Is it only one minute long?
- It ends right away.
People would want to know why.
The end.
We need to explain why.
I know.
- For the next 4 weeks...
- It's for 4 weeks.
- For 4 weeks.
- We will start at 4:50 p.m.
- Please keep that in mind.
- All right.
Will we have our pay cut
because it's shorter?
- No way.
- That's impossible.
We made a promise.
Thank you.
(Making a bow)
- We should thank them.
- Sure.
Thank you so much.
Before we decide the penalty
and the member to receive it today,
I will give you a last chance...
to get rid of the worst penalty
that you want to avoid.
If all of you
succeed in the mission,
you get to get rid
of one penalty you want.
I think the upgraded
water slide jump...
- is not so bad.
- I like that.
- You can do that.
- I like the water jump.
No. I'm scared.
But the sky bridge... Gosh, I'm...
I don't mind going to Yeosu.
But it's the last day
of the Chuseok holidays.
- It will be horrible.
- It will be a long way back.
- Then Se Chan and...
- Okay.
the other member
to get the penalty will decide.
Can I get rid of a few?
You should do that.
Se Chan, what is it
you want to get rid of?
- The window.
- First, I want...
- Get rid of the window.
- Actually, cleaning the window...
- It's too scary.
- It's about safety,
- Right.
- So I want to get rid of it.
- That's a good one.
- There's no way he can do that.
You should get rid
of the sky-glider too.
I will. Which one?
If the wind rises, you'll die.
I don't want to do anything
that can kill me.
- Get rid of this.
- Why do you keep saying that?
- You will get a bruise.
- The sky-glider is too scary.
- Right. This is...
- Do you know...
- which one is the least horrible?
- What is it?
- Becoming a diver on Jeju Island.
- The diver thing.
Right. Jeju Island.
- It's not so bad.
- But you have to get on a plane.
But you can get seasick
when you dive.
- It is hard.
- You can get nauseated.
- It's difficult.
- And you should wear the lead.
- I can't go down the water.
- You feel nauseated.
Then there's nothing you can do.
I'm not going.
How many penalties can we remove?
- Up to three penalties.
- Three?
There will be three missions.
You can remove one at a time.
- We will get rid of one each?
- We have to succeed.
- Okay.
- We can work together...
- as a team, right?
- Yes.
- This is what we can do.
- We try hard.
- We're good at this.
- Let's do this.
- This is our thing.
The first mission is...
your favorite game,
- drawing on sketchbooks.
- Okay.
(Whatever Penalty Project Mission 1:
Drawing Game)
- Okay.
- Sketchbook!
This is the upgraded version.
It's called Running Man
One-line Drawing.
- One-line drawing?
- One line?
- Draw without lifting the pen.
- Yes. It has the same rules.
But you have to draw without
lifting the pen from the paper...
and pass it over to the next member.
- Okay.
- It will be really fun.
You're given five seconds each.
If you lift your pen within
five seconds, your turn is up.
- Okay.
- Got it.
We will have
a lot of fun doing this.
We will probably lift the pen
and pretend nothing happened.
You should get 4 questions
out of 7 right to succeed.
- Okay.
Who will answer?
- It's not difficult.
- It's either Jae Suk or...
I'm good at it.
It's not difficult to draw
without lifting the pen.
- You know that, right?
- I'll answer first.
We should split the paper in half
for Chinese idioms.
- Okay.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
- Let's hear the category first.
- What's the category?
- What is it?
The category is food.
- Food.
- Okay.
- It's food.
It must be something complicated.
- Is this where you will answer?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Is this where you give an answer?
- Jae Suk will do it.
- Jae Suk will answer.
There must be jjajangmyeon
or kimchi jjigae.
- Don't worry.
- I bet this will be difficult.
It's difficult to draw food.
It's ambiguous.
- It's hard.
- We should show if it's spicy.
That's a good idea.
- Draw a fire.
- A fire? That sounds good.
- Fire.
- Fire means spicy.
- That's for spicy.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk, look that way.
You know he wouldn't
go against the rules.
- I never break the rules.
- I know.
You get five seconds.
Start. Five.
(The first question)
(Janchi guksu)
- Four.
- Four. Three.
Two. One.
Pass it over.
It's food.
(They were told to draw without
lifting the pen 1 minute ago.)
(Janchi guksu)
- Four. Three.
- Do it slowly.
Two. One.
- Pass it over.
- Okay.
It looks good.
- What?
- Five. Four.
Three. Two. One.
We need to describe
the first two syllables.
Five. Four. Three.
Two. One.
(Describe the first two syllables.)
Describe the first two syllables.
- Four. Three.
- Go ahead and do it.
(Whistling)
You can't lift the pen.
- What are you doing?
- Gosh.
- I'm sorry.
- What's with you?
- Hey, Haha.
- Okay.
- You're right.
- Don't erase it completely.
I'm sorry. I was confused.
- I'm really sorry. I'll draw again.
- Erase it.
- I erased it.
- You just need to apologize.
- My goodness.
- Erase it.
- You're not an amateur.
- This is ridiculous.
You can't write that down.
- I guess I was so desperate.
- Draw an anchovy.
I'm really sorry.
Okay. Let's say it was a practice.
- I'll draw again.
- What are you doing?
You committed a foul,
so you lost one chance.
- Why?
- No, that's not right.
- That can't be right.
- No.
No, this is...
- I'm really sorry.
- The question is...
I'm sorry, but I need
the production crew to come up...
with words
that have unique features.
We're not supposed
to make a random guess.
- All right. This time...
- Let's do this then.
Since we both are at fault,
- let's say it doesn't count.
- Right.
It was too...
You should try drawing janchi guksu.
It is featureless.
We should split the paper in half.
- On the left...
- Split it in half.
On one side,
describe the first syllables.
- And on the other side...
- Draw the rest of the syllables.
If it's pork kimchi jjigae,
draw pork on one side,
- and kimchi jjigae on another.
- Let's do that.
We can give it a try.
- Okay.
- Got it? Split it in half.
- I'll get it right anyway.
- We can do that.
- Split in half.
- Ready.
Don't worry. I'll get it right.
- Split in half, okay?
- Okay.
(Galbi dumpling)
- You shouldn't lift the pen.
- You lifted it again.
- Your turn is up.
- You lifted the pen.
(He split the paper in half,
and it's over.)
- Gosh, he's...
- I'll just draw this.
- You should keep drawing.
- I just split it in half.
- I shouldn't lift it.
- Four.
Three. Two. One.
- What?
- Hey.
(What's that?)
- What was that?
- This is...
- It's a plate.
- I guess she drew a plate.
- Five. Four. Three.
- What did you do?
(Galbi dumpling)
(Ji Hyo is trying to draw galbi.)
- Draw the right one instead.
- Two. One.
Darn it.
- Draw the right one instead.
- Two. One.
- Pass it over.
- Darn it.
Hey, what did you do?
- Five. Four. Three.
- Gosh, look at her.
- We messed up.
- Two. One. Pass it over.
(It finally looks
like a decent drawing.)
I'll recognize it right away.
Just draw.
- Draw the right one.
- Don't worry and do it.
- One. Pass it over.
- Don't lift it.
(He lifts it again.)
- I didn't lift it.
- Don't lift the pen from the paper.
- Four. Three.
- Draw dumplings.
- Draw it again.
- Dumplings.
Two. One. You lifted it.
- My gosh.
- You're so bad at this.
What's that? Is that a wooden shoe?
- What's wrong with you?
- This looks...
just like the thing
we ate in the waiting room today.
- This looks like what we just ate.
- You can't say that.
- It looks the same.
- Why not?
- I mean...
- The thing next to the noodles.
- Isn't it food?
- It smells different.
- It's food, isn't it?
- The category is food.
When I look at this...
When you talked
about stock prices earlier...
Don't give him a hint.
What we ate in the waiting room.
- That's a big hint.
- I enjoyed it a lot.
- I'll guess it from the drawing.
- I ate two pieces.
We're not amateurs. We're pros.
- Jae Suk is...
- This is the tea kettle...
- No.
- Jae Suk, think carefully.
I don't think it's a tea kettle.
We split it in half.
- No.
- So these two.
That's right. We split it
in half for a reason.
- What do you think each means?
- What is that?
- The bottom one...
- I think this is ramyeon.
- No.
- No?
I think this is ramyeon.
- No.
- No?
(That's not it.)
- Hang on.
- Look at the right one.
Something's on a plate.
(Look at the right one.
Something's on a plate.)
- On a plate...
- Well...
- It's a shoe.
- Mapo...
- Shoe?
- Five.
- In Mapo...
- Four.
- Three.
- When I first ate it...
Dumplings.
- No, wait.
- All right.
Boiled dumplings.
- Wait.
- Boiled dumplings.
- Give me that.
- My gosh.
- That's not it.
- Darn it.
The first one is galbi.
- How can this be galbi?
- It's ribs.
- Ribs.
- We drew ribs.
I can't draw.
Should I give an answer?
It's hard to draw
without lifting a pen.
I'll answer.
- It's difficult not to lift a pen.
- I think I should give an answer.
Dumplings...
- We will change the category now.
- Isn't this better?
- What?
- Isn't it better this way?
- It's the name of a TV show.
- A name of a TV show?
- Suk Jin.
- From the old ones.
- I know a lot of TV shows.
- Hey, that's good.
How would we draw a TV show?
Se Chan, remember
we will split it in half.
Let's split it.
That would be better.
But it's difficult to draw it
with one line.
Why don't we just draw
one syllable at a time?
One syllable at a time.
- Really? Then I'll just draw lines.
- Ready.
- You don't have to.
- I don't?
- We will split it without a line.
- Start.
Don't lift the pen.
Gosh, this is too difficult.
("Young Power, Open Up Your Heart")
(It's a show where students shout
what they want to say on a rooftop.)
Gosh, this is...
- Gosh, this is too difficult.
- Five.
- Four.
- Gosh, this is...
- Is it still on air?
- Suk Jin.
- No.
- It's an old show.
- Pass it over.
- How would I draw this? Hang on.
- What's that?
- What do I do?
- Five. Four.
- This is...
- You lifted the pen.
- You can't lift it.
("Young Power, Open Up Your Heart")
- Good.
- Five.
(She drew a person on a rooftop.)
You lifted the pen.
- Gosh, you're being too strict.
- It's...
so hard not to lift it.
- Gosh, you're being too strict.
- It's...
so hard not to lift it.
Three. Two. One.
Do you remember the show?
I do know what it is.
- I bet Se Chan knows.
- That's right.
- No, stop drawing.
- Two. One.
("Young Power, Open Up Your Heart")
- You shouldn't draw more.
- What do I do?
- Five. Four.
- Just erase it.
What's that buttocks-looking thing?
- What is it?
- Stop drawing.
- Stop.
- What are you doing?
Why did you draw that?
Now, guess what the show is.
I think he will recognize it.
Just look
at the first one carefully.
- It's just a drawing.
- It's a TV show.
He might not know
the name of the show.
- You watched it back in school.
- It's an old TV show.
- Was that when you were little?
- So Min, sit.
- Was it when you were little?
It's Pan Yoo Geol.
Just stay still.
Don't let them find fault with us.
Do you not know this show?
It was an entertainment show.
Why did you sit there?
I should've sat there.
You know the answer.
That's not it. You're supposed
to give the correct answer.
You know Pan Yoo Geol.
Then you should know the answer.
You have to get it from Pan Yoo Geol.
Young people like you
can figure out the name.
- But you...
- Wasn't that when you were little?
Just open your heart.
I drew two dots here.
Hey, you fool.
He's young, but he has no power.
It's not like we draw
"Stop Right There."
(Oh, right!)
- You get five seconds. Five.
- All right.
(He pretends he figured it out
himself after hearing all that.)
- You get five seconds. Five.
- All right.
He's opening his heart here.
"Young Power, Open Up Your Heart."
("Young Power, Open Up Your Heart")
(The producer reluctantly
accepts the answer.)
Good.
- Nice.
- Well done.
- Pan!
- Yoo!
- Geol!
It was when
you were students, right?
- Pan Yoo Geol.
- He's about our age.
He said, "He's young,
but he has no power."
"He's young, but he has no power."
I was talking to myself.
You didn't hear that, did you?
- Why did you say that?
- For that,
you can just give
Seok Sam a penalty.
- No. He didn't hear me.
- Give him one penalty sticker.
- Give him one sticker.
- Give him the skull.
He will receive one sticker.
You can't give me
a penalty sticker just like that.
This is really serious.
Nice. We can do this.
- So you got one question right.
- Okay.
- This is another TV show.
- Jeon So Min.
- Do you want to give it a try?
- Okay.
"I like you."
- I really liked the show.
- He knows a lot of TV shows.
I know a lot of TV shows.
- All right.
- Ready.
Jae Suk, you know it, right?
Start.
("Law of the Jungle")
- Gosh, this is...
- This is easy.
Pass it over.
- Why did you not draw anything?
- What did you do?
(He used up the time
shaking his hand.)
(Seok Sam's pen is useless.)
- Gosh, he's unbelievable.
- Is he a spy or what?
- Three. Two. One.
- Pass it over.
- What's that?
- What did you do?
- Look at it carefully.
- Stop it.
Five. Four. Three.
- This is an easy one.
- Two. One. Pass it over.
- It's done.
- That's enough.
Five. Four. Three. Two. One.
Pass it over.
That's nice. You drew a good one.
- Five.
- That's nice. You drew a good one.
- I can...
- You lifted the pen.
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
- You did.
Fine. I get it.
- All right. You do it.
- You...
Four. Three. Two.
- I'll get it. Don't worry.
- It's done.
- This is done.
- You have to get it right.
- You will get it.
- You know what it is, right?
This looks like
"The Fishermen and the City."
For SBS, it's really...
- You know it.
- Stop it.
It's the main beneficiary.
(He openly tells Jae Suk
that it's an SBS show.)
- SBS.
- You know it.
- So it's an SBS show.
- It's the main beneficiary.
It's "The Fishermen and the City,"
but it's not SBS.
You can't say that
because it's from another company.
There are trees.
- You can't give him a hint.
- Trees.
Look at the trees.
This is a palm tree.
(Surprised)
A palm tree...
- I think you are amazing.
- Of course.
- I'm complimenting him.
- This is a mountain.
(He's an amazing cheater.)
- A palm tree...
- He should get it by now. Wait.
He should get it by now. Wait.
- He should know that.
- Oh, right.
- This is...
- Did you figure it out?
- I can recognize it right away.
- I bet he knows.
- You know?
- That's it.
(An SBS show, a palm tree,
and a mountain?)
This is "Law of Jungle."
("Law of Jungle!")
(They got 2 questions right
in a row with all sorts of fouls.)
This is so much fun.
- Why don't we...
- It's really fun.
- My gosh.
- A palm tree and a mountain.
- This is Byung Man.
- Right.
- Now it's a song name.
- So Min, do you want to try it?
So Min, do you want
to give an answer?
I don't think I can do it.
If I don't get it right,
- will you get mad at me?
- You have to get it right.
- Just sit there.
- She can't answer idioms.
- Hey.
- What?
- Why?
- Let So Min give it a try.
If you can't do this, stay seated.
We have to get rid of a penalty.
- If you can't do this, don't try.
- I'll draw.
- I'll answer.
- We have to do this.
- He knows a lot of songs too.
- Okay. I'll do it.
Jae Suk, it's a title of a song.
Start.
("Playing With Fire")
- This is easy.
- It's easy.
- Three. Two. One.
- Are you done?
- Pass it over.
- Gosh. Please.
- Come on.
- Please.
- One. Pass it over.
- You can't draw there.
You can't draw there.
Five. Four. Three. Two. One.
Pass it over.
- No. That's enough.
- Stop it.
- Five. Four. Three.
- You can stop it.
Two. One. Pass it over.
You should put an explosive device
on the pens next time.
So it will explode
once they lift the pen.
Three. Two. One.
- They never listen to you.
- Pass it over.
- Stop drawing.
- But they never stop.
Or it should give an electric shock.
Stop drawing.
- It should give an electric shock.
- Stop drawing.
- My goodness.
They don't stop
even if you say that.
Take a look. This is...
- What did you draw?
- You can do this.
I think you can get it.
- You can get it.
- Danger.
- Attention?
- You get five seconds.
Wait. Why would you start
counting five seconds so soon?
Why did she draw it on the right?
This isn't a fire. What is this?
- This isn't a fire. What is this?
- Yes.
This is a fire.
Jae Suk.
On the left...
- It should be on the left.
- This is an old song, right?
- Yes.
- It's an old song.
- Jae Suk.
- "Fire?"
That's not it.
I didn't think it was "Fire."
- Is that your answer?
- No.
- The fire should be on the left.
- "Fire" is...
- It should be on the left.
- I didn't think so.
Is it "Fire" by BTS?
- No.
- I didn't think so.
I didn't think that was the song.
- You will pee.
- Five.
- You'll wet your bed.
- He's enjoying the fire.
- On the left...
It's dangerous.
- No, think differently.
- It's hot, so he can't get close.
- It's your nickname.
- Something different.
- I'm a prankster.
- That's what Suk Jin likes.
(Fire! Prankster!)
- Suk Jin...
- That's what Suk Jin likes.
"Playing With Fire?"
"Playing With Fire."
(Gosh, he got it right.)
- "Playing With Fire."
- He's quick-witted.
- Playing with fire
- BLACKPINK.
- He's quick-witted.
- Only pranksters can get it.
Are we playing charades?
"Playing With Fire." Okay.
- "Playing With Fire."
- Jae Suk.
So it's not like
strength versus strength.
No, it's not.
I was surprised at the last minute.
Is it "Twist Drama?"
Amazing.
This is a TV show, right?
What's the thing on the left?
- Hey.
- Oh, right.
Just stay quiet.
- I thought you were a tutor.
- Leave him alone.
- You sound like a tutor.
- Jae Suk.
From head to toe, hot issue
- "Family Outing."
- Okay.
(Committing all sorts of fouls,
they got the last question right.)
- How did you get it?
- My goodness.
That's where I first met Ji Hyo.
So the drawing game is over.
- Why is it over?
- We won't do it ever again.
- This is so fun. Why not?
- Why aren't we doing it again?
- This is so much fun. Why not?
- Hyung In is...
- This is our favorite game.
- Hyung In is not that decisive.
- Why?
- Like I said,
you should put an explosive unit
on the pen for a one-line drawing.
All right.
Or at least it gives
an electric shock.
You answered 5 questions out of 7.
So you succeeded.
We are good.
You can decide on one penalty
that you want to get rid of.
- Can I get rid of one first?
- Okay.
- You do it.
- I'll be doing it anyway.
I'll be going anyway,
so I want to remove one.
You do it.
- The unicycle.
- Alluvial gold mining.
Get rid of the sky-glider.
- You can't go to Gangwon Province.
- What I hate the most is...
- either the window cleaning...
- Okay.
- or alluvial gold mining.
- All right.
- I like alluvial gold mining.
- Remove alluvial gold mining.
Get rid of the window thing.
You might die.
- Get rid of one.
- All right.
- I'll get rid of the window.
- Okay.
(He deletes cleaning the windows
of the SBS building.)
All right. He got rid
of the window cleaning.
I should go somewhere else.
Who will be going?
This mission is...
a game where
you should adjust to new rules.
- It's called Landmine Kungkungtta.
- What's that?
You will play
the Kingkungtta game in turn.
But you're not supposed to say
three-syllable words.
- What does that mean?
- I see.
- A word with 1, 2, or 4 syllables?
- You'll play the word chain game...
- A one-syllable word won't work.
- Right. That's not allowed.
- A word with 2 syllables?
- A word with 2, 4, or 5 syllables.
- Ramyeon, kungkungtta
- Kungkungtta
- Wedding... Oh, right.
- Wedding veil doesn't work.
How about "noodles?"
Then you can say...
Smell of feet
You fail
if you say a three-syllable word.
You must go back and forth twice
to complete the mission.
- It sounds difficult.
- Indeed.
Should we say a 2-syllable word
and a 4-syllable word in turns?
- No, it doesn't matter.
- Oh, I see.
As long as you don't say
a three-syllable word.
- It's difficult. Let's do this.
- Let's go.
- Then I'll give you the first word.
- Who goes first? So Min?
- Ready. Set. Go.
- So Min will go first.
- Kung, kung, kung
(They'll have 4 rounds.
The 1st round begins.)
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta
Air purifier, kungkungtta
Train, kungkungtta
(Air purifier, train)
Now, let's get the car fixed
- You could've said "garage."
- Or "road."
Now, let's get the car fixed
(Now, let's get the car fixed?)
- Or "ticket."
- Right.
- A two-syllable word is allowed.
- Suk Jin.
- Let us start over.
- Hold on. Suk Jin didn't...
- He didn't understand the rule.
- What is he doing?
- You got confused, right?
- It's tricky.
- Did you do that on purpose?
- I was confused.
We can say two-syllable words
consecutively.
- "Garage" works too, right?
- Let's get the car fixed
"Garage" works, right?
- You had a lot of options.
- "Garage."
- Being the first to go is easier.
- Shall we start with Se Chan?
- Let's go in the other way.
- Okay.
- We're good at this game.
- Can we switch our seats?
- Let's go.
- It's okay.
- You've got this.
- Jae Suk, make sure to do well.
- Don't you worry.
- I'll go first.
- It was hard for me. That's why.
- I've played this game before.
- It's easy. Right.
- I've played it many times before.
- The middle seat is the best.
- This game is easy.
- Let's begin.
Ready. Set. Go.
- Kung, kung, kung
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta
- Kung, kung, kung, kung
Scarecrow, kungkungtta
Fertilizer, kungkungtta
Lately, kungkungtta
- What... Gosh, you.
- What?
- Hey.
- The third person...
(Lately, kungkungtta)
(He said a difficult word
and caused the team to fail.)
- Why would you pick that word?
- Gosh.
You could've said "cook."
You see, it sounds similar to "pee."
- "Pee."
- "Pee?" Hey, let's just...
- Let's just send him home.
- "Pee."
You said you had played this game
many times before!
- Then why did you do that?
- "Pee."
What word could he have said?
Jong Kook, there's "luunch."
"Luunch."
You could've said "luunch."
There was a word you could've said.
- Let's move on.
- "Luunch."
- "Luunch?"
Gosh, seriously.
- "Luunch vaalue meal."
- "Vaalue meal."
- Jae Suk, that was terrible.
- All right. I heard you.
Hey, switch seats with someone
if you can't do it.
All right. Don't worry.
I'll do better next time.
- Let's move on.
- I've played it many times before.
- Then why are you so bad at it?
- Let's do this.
Hey, I have a lot of experience.
Let's just say two-syllable words.
- Let's do that. That'd be easier.
- That'd be easier.
- Also...
- What word did you say?
- "Fertilizer."
- "Fertilizer?"
- You picked a difficult word.
- That's a hard one.
But there are a lot of Korean words
that start with "yo."
- Right. Such as "chamber pot."
- There are so many such words.
- I'm to blame. Ready. Set. Go.
- Gosh.
- Kung, kung, kung
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta
- Kung, kung, kung, kung
Cherry tomato, kungkungtta
Toto, kungkungtta
(Cherry tomato, toto)
(Toto?)
- Why?
- "Toto" is acceptable.
- "Toto."
Some people call
"Saturday Night Music Show..."
- "Toto."
- "Toto" is acceptable.
- No.
- Buying Sports Toto is legal.
- Jong Kook is right.
- It's an English word.
- It's a lottery.
You can find the word "Toto"
in a dictionary. It's a noun.
There's a rock band called TOTO.
- They're internationally famous.
- That's right.
- I'm sure you can find it.
- Sports Toto isn't acceptable.
- You won't accept this either?
- No.
- Fine. Then...
- Look it up.
- You can find it in a dictionary.
- A proper noun is not acceptable?
It's not in a dictionary.
- No.
- It's a proper noun.
- It's a foreign word.
- It's not acceptable.
- Is a foreign word not allowed?
- You should've told us...
- it wasn't allowed, Hyung In.
- Haha, we didn't know.
- Hyung In didn't...
- She didn't tell us that.
- For example, "toji" as in "land."
- She didn't tell us...
- a foreign word wasn't allowed.
- Foreign words commonly used...
- in Korea are allowed.
- I see. Now, we know.
(I see. Now, we know.)
- Okay.
- We didn't know that.
I'm sorry for getting upset with you.
I didn't know that rule either.
- Both of us are at fault, right?
- Hey.
Haha, you should stop using
foreign words.
- Both she and I are at fault.
- Okay.
- He... Gosh.
- Did you apologize to her?
Who wants to go first? Does anyone
want to switch seats with me?
- He said he was good at this game.
- I'll go first. Come here.
- Okay.
- I'll go first.
It's hard to be the first to go.
- He's so bad at this.
- I shouldn't sit here.
- Sorry?
- This seat is like a minefield.
- That's the hardest position.
- It's even harder.
- Come here and sit down.
- It's hard to be the second to go.
- You should sit here.
- Me?
- You sit here. I can't do it.
- Shall I sit here?
- This is good.
- I'll go first.
- Let's take it easy and go slow.
- I'll pull it off. Okay. Got it.
- We don't need to rush.
- Let's do it slowly.
- We've got this!
- It's up to us.
- Right. We can decide the speed.
- We're not competing.
- Right.
- Exactly.
- Ready. Set. Go.
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta
- Kung, kung, kung, kung
Hyena, kungkungtta
- Butterfly, kungkungtta
- Good.
Emergency, kungkungtta
Reserve, kungkungtta
(Hyena, butterfly, emergency,
reserve)
Biru, kungkungtta
"Biru?"
- What's "biru?"
- "Biru?"
"Biru?"
(Everyone pauses
as they hear a strange word.)
- "Biru?"
- As in "pitiful?"
- "Nama biru!"
- Hey.
"Nama biru!"
(Nama biru is the Japanese word
for "draft beer.")
"Nama biru!"
Hey.
- "Biru."
- "Biru" as in "beer?"
(Se Chan must've craved draft beer.)
- Foreign words are not allowed.
- It's not allowed.
- That's a foreign word.
- Right. She said it wasn't allowed.
- I'm sorry.
- You could've said "bidet."
- Or "fertilizer."
- Hey.
- Or "soap."
- "Bidet."
- Ji Hyo said it intensely.
- Right.
- You said it so intensely.
- Okay.
- You could've said "soap."
She said it like this. "Reserve!"
- My gosh.
- This is the final round.
- Okay. Let's do this. Stay alert.
- Okay. Let's go.
Let's keep it together.
- Don't speak intensely or fast.
- Okay.
- We've got this.
- Speak gently.
- I'll do that.
- Ready. Go.
(The final round begins.)
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta
- Kung, kung, kung, kung
- Please maintain a moderate speed.
- Got it.
Seagull, kungkungtta
Train, kungkungtta
Street, kungkungtta
- Road, kungkungtta
- Kungkungtta
(Seagull, train, street, road)
- Lo Hee, kungkungtta
- Kungkungtta
- Hee Soo
- Lo Hee is a name.
(Lo Hee?)
(Speaking urgently)
- Lo Hee.
- Lo Hee is famous.
- Let's keep going.
- That's not acceptable.
- Whom are you referring to?
- Whose daughter is Lo Hee?
- Jung Jun Ha's...
- It's not...
- Jun Ha's son is Lo Ha.
- No.
- Lo Hee.
- The daughter of Eugene of S.E.S.
- She's Eugene's daughter.
- Right.
- She's famous.
- I guess you don't know her.
- A person's name is allowed.
- Eugene must be upset.
- You can't keep going on like this.
- Then you could say any name.
You could say a random name
and say it's your cousin's name.
- No. Lo Hee is famous.
- They're not celebrities.
- She's famous enough.
- Wouldn't SOHEE be accepted either?
- Lo Hee is a celebrity too.
- Right. She's a celebrity.
When we played this game before,
"Im Chang Jung" was allowed.
- Yes, it was allowed.
- Celebrities' names are allowed.
- Why?
- Both of you are at fault, right?
- Right.
- Go and apologize to her.
- And shake her hand.
- Let's start over again.
- Make up with her.
- I think we should laugh it off.
- A word that starts with "lo..."
- Lo Hee.
- We're good now.
- There are a lot of them.
Let's say the names of stars
they would know.
- Let's start from "Lo Hee."
- Okay.
- Good.
- "Lo Ee" or "Lo Hee?"
- "Hee."
- It's "Lo Hee."
- You don't even know her name.
- That's not true.
- Ready...
- Wait. What did you say?
- Kung, kung, kung
- Lo Hee
- Kungkungtta
- Hope, kungkungtta
- Good.
The dead, kungkungtta
- Seat, kungkungtta
- Okay.
Ribbon, kungkungtta
- Glue, kungkungtta
- That's good.
Drum, kungkungtta
Rum, kungkungtta
(They're almost done
with the first lap.)
Injection, kungkungtta
Love, kungkungtta
Seedling, kungkungtta
Type, kungkungtta
Ryu Jin, kungkungtta
- Why?
- Ryu Jin, kungkungtta
- He...
("Ryu Jin" is not acceptable.)
- Ryu Jin is famous.
- Why?
- Let's keep going.
- Move on.
- Why?
- It's acceptable.
- Lo Hee is okay, but Ryu Jin isn't?
- Hey.
- It can cause controversy.
- "Ryu Jin?"
- Hey.
- I'm not doing this.
- Hey, Ryu Jin is...
Hey, Ryu Jin is a famous actor.
- He's an actor.
- "Ryu Jin" should be accepted.
Okay. Then...
- Let us start over again.
- Okay.
You failed to complete the mission
Landmine Kungkungtta.
- We failed?
- What a shame.
Yes, and you also failed
to delete a penalty.
- I need to delete more penalties.
- All right. Fair enough.
They have no choice.
They already let us off many times.
We'll begin the last mission now.
Please bring the set.
Okay.
What game are we going to play?
Let's pull it off.
Let's go!
What is it? I see velcro on it.
Will we throw something?
The long jump?
- Maybe.
- I think we all have to be in it.
We can see how good your teamwork is
through this mission.
- It's We Are One Heart, One Body.
- What game is it?
You'll put on socks
with velcro on them...
and take turns running and jumping
at the starting line.
You must land inside
the yellow lines on the square.
If all seven members hold out
for five seconds in it, you succeed.
- It's very small.
- I guess it's important...
to land on the right spot
so that we can all stand in the box.
- Those who can jump far go first.
- We can move around in it, right?
- You can't because of the velcro.
- We can't?
Please put on these socks first.
Your hands must not be on the floor
for more than three seconds.
- Three seconds?
- Yes.
The girls should go last.
Yes.
You only get three attempts.
- Three.
- We will succeed in it.
- We will do it in one go.
- All right.
- Don't worry.
- We don't need three attempts.
- I will go to a corner.
- We are good at this.
- Shall we give you one attempt?
- Okay.
- No, there is no need.
- Don't be so strict.
(No.)
There is no need to do that.
Also, you should use some money.
Don't use tape
for something like this.
Things should explode
if we go outside the tape.
Why do you like explosion so much
these days?
Do you want to blow everything up?
- Blow everything up.
- Things should explode.
If your hands touch the floor,
you need to get up in three seconds.
- Okay.
- Other people can count.
- Jae Suk, you are light. Go first.
- We can do that.
Where should I land?
Here. Land like this.
- It will be hard.
- It won't be easy.
The right foot should fall here.
- For goodness' sake.
(He planted his sock.)
- Gosh.
(Farmer Ji gets criticized.)
I did it for the team.
Hold on.
You and I should stand on the sides.
- Okay.
- Someone can come in the middle...
- and position his legs.
- Let's do that.
- Let's try it.
- Se Chan can do that.
- I will go to the middle.
- Okay.
- Here I go.
- Go first.
- Go.
- Go to the side.
- You will stand at the end, right?
- Of course.
- Stand at the end.
- Don't step on the starting line.
- We won't step on it.
- Go easy on us.
- We aren't professional athletes.
- We won't step on it.
- Hyung In.
- Set up explosives from now on.
- That's right.
- Then things will blow up!
For goodness' sake.
Set them up under the feet.
- Set up mines.
- We would receive electric shocks.
- That's right.
If we go out the designated area...
All right, Jae Suk.
- You did well.
- I did well, right?
- It's good.
Can't you... Jae Suk.
Can't you turn like this?
- Of course I can.
- You can, right?
- Good.
- Good. There you go.
- Shall I go?
- Okay.
- Hold him.
- Hold him if he trips.
- Here I go.
- I will hold you.
- Come on.
Here I go.
- My goodness. Good job.
- Good job.
(Jae Suk and Jong Kook landed
on either end.)
- Good.
- Come in as much as you can.
Come in as much as you can.
- Position yourself in the middle.
- You can do it.
Do you want me to jump like this?
- No.
- Here.
- Shall I try it?
- Yes. I don't understand.
How will you do it?
Explain it to us.
- I will fly into the air...
- That sounds cool.
and spin like this.
- The triple axel.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- I will fly into the air.
- Okay. Good.
- Okay.
- That sounds cool.
- Good.
- Hey.
- I will jump high.
- Will you put your feet at the end?
- Yes.
- Go as far as you can.
In that case, fall into our arms...
and stand in a corner.
That would be for the best, right?
- Here I go.
- We will catch you in the air.
Why don't So Min do it
since she is light?
- No. Haha should go next.
- I am not light.
- Go ahead.
- Just come. It's okay.
Kid.
Fall into their arms.
- Yes. You did it.
- There you go.
(Staggering)
- You jumped well.
- Fall into their arms. Yes.
- There you go.
(Haha landed nicely.)
- You fell into their arms.
- He jumped well.
- He can't turn around.
- Face the front.
- It's okay. Hold me.
- There is room.
- There is room indeed.
How should I do it?
Hold on. Instead of Se Chan,
- Suk Jin should go next.
- Should I go next?
- Okay.
- Are you nervous?
You need to hold Suk Jin.
- Boom!
- Jump far, okay?
You are cool.
(He suddenly takes off his glasses.)
You look like Bruce Lee!
(You look like Bruce Lee!)
Lim Ha Ryong, come on.
Bruce Ji.
He won't be able to go far.
- Enter this way.
- After that stunt...
(Bruce Ji flew into the air.)
He did it.
Oh, no.
- My goodness.
- For goodness' sake.
After that stunt...
(Bruce Ji's flying kick...)
(makes the human tower crumble.)
- Hey.
- Come on.
You should have stood up.
Why did you push us?
You should have supported me.
- I held out for a long time.
- For goodness' sake.
- Seriously.
- Gosh.
- I held out for a long time.
That's mine.
- Isn't it mine?
- It's mine. That's yours.
- Gosh.
- Seriously.
- I held out for a long time.
- This is so disappointing.
- You should have stood up.
- You know,
- this is hard.
- This is hard.
- I will go first this time.
- Okay, Jong Kook.
(They begin the second attempt
right away.)
- Gosh.
- Jong Kook.
- You got it.
- I got it.
Put your feet here.
Please make sure
he continues to lift his heels.
- It was the perfect landing.
- For goodness' sake.
We aren't like that.
- I did it.
- You did it.
It begins once he climbs
on someone's back.
- You did it.
- I did it.
- Good.
- He went in.
- That's incredible.
- He did it.
- You got this.
- Okay.
(They even pull off
a difficult technique.)
- How did we do that?
- He did it.
- Unbelievable.
- Good.
- That was incredible.
- How did you do that?
- You startled me.
- Come on.
- Don't move your feet.
- Ji Hyo and So Min, come here.
- This is bad.
Guys, jump at once. I am exhausted.
- Come on.
- Practically hug us.
(Only Ji Hyo remains.)
- Are we done?
- We are almost done.
We are about to tip over.
- Move out of the way.
- I am about to tip over.
(At that moment!)
We are tipping over.
(His heels touched the floor
outside the line.)
- We are tipping over.
- Se Chan's feet...
touched the floor.
- Gosh.
Where?
- Se Chan.
- Hey.
You should have stood on tiptoes.
- You should have stood on tiptoes.
- But...
you pushed me too much.
Suk Jin didn't jump right.
If you are the 5th or 6th one,
you can't jump far.
You know,
- you should jump...
- There is no space.
and land here as much as you can.
- You are right.
- Here?
We were so close.
How are we supposed to do this?
- I figured out a way.
- We should stand like this, right?
You can go over the line
and come back, right?
Of course. You just need to do it
in three seconds.
- It works, right?
- We will allow that.
Okay. Then we can use that method.
Yes. It's simple.
- Three seconds.
- Don't you need to run up?
Of course I don't.
- You should run up.
- It's okay.
I have iron strength,
- so it's okay.
- Forget about your iron strength.
- This is our last chance.
- There is no need for a runup.
- Is this our last chance?
- This is our last chance.
- I don't want you to regret it...
- after blowing up this chance.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
- Here I go.
All right.
- Step on the ground and come back.
- Good, right?
- There you go.
- He did it.
(He takes a step forward.)
- There you go.
- He did it.
- That was neat.
- This time,
- it's Jong Kook's turn.
- Good.
My one foot can go out, right?
- One foot.
- My left foot will go inside.
Let's begin. Here I go.
There you go.
Good. The foot
should come back inside.
- There you go.
- That's exactly right.
- Nice.
- Good.
(What?)
(They show a poker face
even though his both feet moved.)
- Nice.
- I almost messed it up.
- Good job.
- Nice.
- Will you go next?
- You should go to the center.
- You did well earlier.
- Okay.
- I will go next.
- Come on in.
Do it the same way. There you go.
- You did it right. There you go.
- Do it the same way. There you go.
(Jae Suk's sock comes off.)
- There you go.
- You did it right.
(Glancing around)
- There you go.
- Don't fall down.
Why is the velcro here?
My foot is here.
(Even the velcro is
at a weird place.)
- How strange.
- Your foot is here.
(The 7-member fraud ring
became even more shameless.)
We did it, right?
- It's a mess.
- Put on your sock.
- Put it on my foot.
- His sock came off.
- All right.
You should have sewed it on.
- I will put it on your foot.
- It's the production crew's fault.
- That's right.
- The sock should have stuck...
- to the square.
- That's right.
- Jae Suk, I will go to you.
- Okay.
I will step with this foot
and this foot.
- Okay. Here I go.
- We almost messed it up.
- There you go.
- One, two...
- Good.
- Okay.
- Should I go that way?
- Come on.
Do the same. Go over the line
and bring one foot back inside.
(It's Suk Jin's turn.)
Suk Jin, your feet are taking up
too much space.
- There you go.
- Put it on the other foot.
- All right.
- There you go.
- Come this way.
- Make some space.
You should put on the socks.
Come on.
- There you go.
- So Min.
(Success)
- We are about to tip over.
(So Min needs to enter the square
for them to remove 1 penalty.)
- Just put your feet inside.
- So Min.
Here she comes.
- Did she come in?
- Yes.
(She came in.)
- She came in.
- Okay. We are about to tip over.
Three, two, one.
Success.
(Success!)
We did it.
This is Running Man.
Did you see that?
Idol singers, bring it on.
You can't do this.
Why do you always challenge
the idol singers?
- Idol singers.
- Yes.
Good.
This is
a middle-aged man's high five.
- My goodness.
- Good.
- We did it.
- I can't believe we did it.
- My goodness.
- We did it.
It was electrifying.
- I can't believe we did it.
- This is Running Man.
- It was hard.
- It was fun.
This is the taste of Running Man.
The production crew never asks us
to do the impossible.
- That's right.
- I can't believe we did it.
Discuss among yourselves
and cross off a penalty.
- Which one should we erase?
- Sky glider.
- Okay. Let's erase it.
- I want to erase the water jump.
- This one?
No. The water jump is better.
The water jump is better.
Why? The water jump is a bit...
- We can't do this.
- We will keep alluvial gold mining?
- We will keep it.
- Let's erase this.
- Let's erase it.
- I want to erase the water jump.
- The water jump is better.
- We will get bruises.
- As for the water jump,
- it will end in 30 seconds.
- We will get bruises.
That's right. It ends in an instant.
You just go down the slide.
- That's right.
- Really?
- Yes.
- That's the penalty.
- I see.
- You go down the slide...
- which sends you up in the air.
- Yes.
It's easy.
- It's easy.
- We should keep the water jump.
- Erase this.
- Okay.
You erased the sky glider.
- Alluvial gold mining.
Even if we film for 3 hours,
3 minutes of it will be aired.
That's right.
Are we spinning a roulette?
No. It's another method
that chooses a random penalty.
A random penalty? Please.
What's that?
(What's the method
that isn't a roulette?)
- Diving experience...
- What's that?
(A mysterious and huge device
appears.)
They made something.
- My goodness.
- It must be a bomb.
- A bomb is entering.
- Will it explode?
My goodness.
Will a ball...
Will a ball spin and come down?
- What? There is another one.
- Will a ball spin and come down?
- Why are there two?
- What?
- The penalty and the member.
To pick the penalty
and the penalty taker,
we had special funnels made.
Throw the balls with the penalties
and penalty takers...
into the funnels.
- We throw them inside.
- Then they will spin inside.
Wait for all the balls to go in.
Once you remove the sticker,
you'll find out who will receive
which penalty.
(The result will be revealed
after all the balls drop.)
It's the ball
that lands here, right?
(The sticker marks the spot.)
I'm a nervous wreck.
I'd rather die than do this.
- I think it'll be Haha.
- Me too.
Right?
You're getting the feeling too.
- Yes, Haha.
- This feeling means it's Haha.
(Nervous)
Then...
Will four balls
have my name on them?
- No, just one.
- Just the one.
- Just one?
- It is as random as it gets.
(It's the same probability
for all members.)
Are you really going to drop it?
I shouldn't be the one
to drop my ball.
- But...
- We should mix it up.
Only that way
will we throw it faster.
(For it to be fair, they will throw
someone else's ball.)
(Sighing)
We'll see which penalty
you'll be receiving first.
- Who will throw the ball?
- This is intense.
I wonder what will get chosen.
The air bicycle
seems like the best option.
I think it'll be the water jump.
I'm fine with everything
except that.
Let's go to Jeju Island.
- Don't let it be the water jump.
- Look.
Jeju Island is the best option.
I agree.
- Shall we?
- Let's do this.
- Do we start with the penalty?
- The penalty.
One.
Two.
- Three.
- Let's do this.
(They throw the balls.)
- Three.
- Let's do this.
(All the balls made it inside.)
Which one will it be?
(Which penalty will be chosen?)
I wonder what it'll be.
Se Chan is already up
for the penalty.
Let's reveal what the penalty is.
Please remove...
Please remove the sticker.
(The penalty will be revealed.)
We must be able to see through it.
(He slowly removes the sticker.)
Alluvial gold mining
is at the very top.
What a relief.
(It isn't alluvial gold mining
at least.)
Here we go.
- Where...
- What a relief.
- It's not the diving program.
- Okay.
- This is the worst.
Jeju is out.
Just don't let it be Yeosu.
(It'll be either the sky bridge,
the unicycle, or the water jump.)
(What will the penalty be?)
- What on earth?
- The sky bridge?
- Is it that?
- That's easy enough.
- What on earth?
- The sky bridge?
You will be walking the sky bridge
and getting on the swing.
What?
Sky bridge and air swing.
What is this?
In Yeosu?
(The extreme activities
will take place in Yeosu.)
(It's the penalty
they all wanted to avoid.)
I can't get on it.
- Me neither.
- Are we headed to Yeosu?
(A long road trip
with a scary penalty)
What?
- Shouldn't it be the bottom one?
- In Yeosu?
Must we go to Yeosu?
Will we get a harness?
It's terrifying.
The harness and rope...
We might fall off the cliff.
What?
The ground is beneath you,
but then it's not.
It'll be like stepping off a cliff.
- But...
- Hold on.
Could one not return from this?
Of course. No one
has even come back from it.
- Before...
- Where did he go?
In some countries,
someone got on the swing,
but only the swing swung back.
- Don't say that.
- It's true.
That's why it's called "air" swing.
Air swing, gosh.
Let's now see
who will receive the penalty.
(The most important moment
of the day)
You will throw someone else's ball.
Someone else's ball.
- We'll throw on three.
- But if we take someone else's...
Luck will decide.
- I...
- Haha, should I throw yours?
- Shall we?
- I'm good.
All right.
(They're all ready
to throw their balls.)
I'll be throwing Haha's.
(I'll be throwing Haha's.)
- One...
- Be the first to throw.
Haha...
One.
Two.
Three.
It'll be Haha.
We'll now see
who will also receive the penalty.
(The big reveal)
As long as it's not me.
- Let it be Haha.
- Haha.
- Why me?
- I want you to accompany me.
- Why me though?
- Because I'm fond of you.
- Let it be Haha.
- This is intense.
- Yeosu...
- Take your time, guys.
Of course.
- Why wouldn't we?
- The one at the top is safe.
- Right.
- The square could be at the top.
All right.
Please remove the sticker.
We should see where the square is.
- Here we go.
- Show me my name!
(Which member will be the first
to be safe from the penalty?)
- Jeon So Min.
- Haha.
- Suk Jin.
- Jeon So Min.
- Haha.
- Whose name is it?
It's Haha.
- Yes!
- He's safe.
- But Haha...
- Nice.
- I thought it'd be him.
- Could it be me?
Is it really my name?
- Where is it?
- Haha, you're safe.
This is so annoying.
You had his ball, right?
- Yes, I threw his.
- I think it's going to be me.
I think it's going to be me.
Thank you so much.
- It's Ji Hyo's name.
- Ji Hyo's safe.
Ji Hyo, I'm the one
who threw your ball.
- Thank you so much.
- No problem.
- Leave them.
- It's 1 out of 4 now.
- Right now?
- No, 1 out of 3.
Jong Kook, Suk Jin, or So Min.
- I can't believe it isn't me.
- Who threw my ball?
- I don't know.
- I threw Suk Jin's.
- I threw yours.
- Hold on a second.
- Wait, we're there.
- This is the one.
- Who's at the bottom?
- Show who's at the bottom.
- The bottom.
Please let it be me.
- Jeon So Min.
- It's good to be at the bottom.
Whoever this is got lucky.
- Ji...
- It's a good thing.
Whoever this is got lucky.
- Ji...
- It's a good thing.
- It's "Ji."
- Ji!
(Ji Suk Jin!)
- I'm safe!
- Who's left?
So Min and Jong Kook.
- So Min or Jong Kook.
- I told her earlier...
that I had a feeling
it was going to be her.
(It'll be either
So Min or Jong Kook.)
No, from the bottom.
- No, the top.
- Let's see who it is.
This person
will receive the penalty.
Kim or...
- This is intense.
- Two.
- Jeon?
- This is killing me.
Three.
Jeon.
(Jeon So Min)
(Jeon So Min
will receive the penalty.)
(No way...)
I knew it.
(Jong Kook survives.)
You're a sweet couple, aren't you?
She's following you there.
Those two.
- Something's pulling them together.
- Who threw her ball?
It was me.
- Suk Jin, you're the best.
- I threw her ball.
I had a feeling
it was going to be her.
She's really unlucky.
She gets caught every single time.
- I know.
- Still,
- you'll be going with Se Chan.
- That's right.
You're lucky it's me.
I'll be there for you.
Seems reliable, doesn't he?
But before he got
on the Nevis Swing...
I know.
- That was him.
- I'm doomed.
Don't worry...
The four-week long penalty project
has now come to an end.
Se Chan and So Min,
we'll see you two in Yeosu
for filming.
- Sure.
- Good job, everyone.
- Good job.
Why do we need so many people
for this unpleasant event?
This is wrong.
I'm suddenly finding this hilarious.
(They made
a long-distance trip to Yeosu.)
Are we at Yeosu Airport?
(They seem dispirited.)
- Hello.
Let us film the opening.
Don't walk but run. Running Man!
(The youngest members
of Running Man)
- To be honest...
- Over here.
- Our masks.
- We should take them off.
It didn't seem real...
until I finally landed here.
I heard it was going to rain though.
Wouldn't it cancel all activities?
What if we slipped and fell?
(They get their hopes up.)
Would you rather
come back some other time?
What? Why would we come back?
I want it to end today.
I'll break my leg
if that's what it takes.
It's been a while
since we left Seoul,
and now you're here in Yeosu.
We call it "the youngest were going
to receive the penalty anyway."
(The youngest were going
to receive the penalty anyway.)
I guess you're right.
One of the members
were particularly thrilled...
by the fact that you two were
receiving the penalty.
He sent you a gift.
(A special gift
for the two youngest members)
(The Yang Se Chan Car enters)
It's the Yang Se Chan edition.
Are you kidding me?
- This...
- Are we bragging about...
being in Yeosu?
- My gosh.
- What is all this?
No way.
You ordered a convertible, right?
(The red convertible
will take them to their location.)
I haven't been
in a convertible before.
No way. What are you doing?
I'm getting the door. Hold on.
You're making me uncomfortable.
(Smiling)
This is uncomfortable.
Do you know how it opens?
- Of course.
- This is uncomfortable.
There's an umbrella.
(The driver for the day
is well-mannered.)
- All right.
- A convertible.
It's my first time being in one.
And it's red.
They got one in red of all colors.
What on earth?
There's a lot going on.
Fasten your seat belt.
- Let's go.
- Off we go.
(They are off
to receive their penalty.)
Goodness.
(Laughing hysterically)
Wait. Is this even a penalty?
(The tour begins with an aerial shot
that can't be seen on Running Man.)
- This is embarrassing.
- What?
This is embarrassing.
It's embarrassing to be in one.
- They're all looking.
- Hello.
Oh, no.
- What do we do?
- It's funny...
because this is supposed
to be a secret.
But we were seen
by just about everyone.
Hello.
This is so embarrassing.
I'm embarrassed every time we stop.
They all acknowledge us.
The people of Yeosu are nice.
What if they think
we're here on a trip?
Shouldn't we tell them
that it's for a show?
- Tell them.
- Hello.
- Hi, we're filming.
- We're filming for a show.
We're not here on a trip.
Yes, I can see the camera.
RIght.
Thank you.
Can you turn
"Yeosu Night Sea" for me?
Right now?
- When we're downtown?
- It's better this way.
Better here than the expressway.
It's playing.
Good.
(They force the hype
by playing an obvious song.)
Yeosu, we're here!
(They force the hype
by playing an obvious song.)
- Yeosu night sea
(A red light)
Please keep going.
It's embarrassing when we stop.
Aren't there
a lot of traffic lights on the way?
I'm so embarrassed.
(They're making a good content
for the show without being asked.)
This itself is a punishment.
(They didn't go far,
but it's red light again.)
I hope we don't get caught by
a traffic light. It's embarrassing.
- We came to receive a punishment.
- I see.
He didn't even ask.
You said you wouldn't say it.
The air is clean here in Yeosu.
It's Yeosu, isn't it?
This is crazy. Come here, So Min.
Why are we going up so high?
Gosh.
Why are we going up high?
- Over there.
- Is it that one?
It's crazy. I can't walk on it.
- Don't lie.
- Don't lie. I seriously can't walk.
No. What's this?
(A scary sky bridge at 100m high)
What if we fall?
- What's this?
- How can I cross it?
What's this?
(Passing the wood section)
I can't do it.
I think I'll stop in the middle.
How can I go back?
Will they come to save me?
No. What's this?
What if we fall?
What's this?
How can I cross it?
Get off.
(The cart stopped
in front of the sky bridge.)
- Thank you.
- Is it really this one?
Let's see if there's
safety equipment under it.
- I mean...
- Get off.
- I can't do it.
There's nothing beside it.
This is a footbridge.
Don't go.
Please.
Wait for me.
(She wants to have even
one more person to stay with them.)
I...
Come here. So Min.
I feel so sick. What should I do?
Is there a net on the ground?
No. There's nothing.
And it's so long.
So Min, I don't think this is right.
Can we get in there to cross it?
No. We must walk.
There's no net under it?
What's this?
I...
This is no joke, So Min.
This is the finale of the four-week
Whatever Penalty Project.
You arrived at the penalty place.
(She announced a penalty
with a bright voice.)
So Min, you should stop her.
Stop her from going ham.
You picked it yourselves last week.
The penalty you will receive...
is crossing the sky bridge
and getting on an air swing.
(Whatever Penalty Project penalty
list: 1. Sky bridge and air swing)
Do we not get to choose one of them?
- It was both.
- I think...
I can get on the swing. But...
Let's cross the sky bridge first.
Some people might have fun
with this.
But I'm afraid of heights.
- Me too.
- It's serious for me.
Why is there no one
who is crossing it before us?
We don't know if it's safe
because there's no one.
No. We tried it earlier.
The Assistant Director tried it.
Who?
Jong Seo.
- The youngest?
- Jong Seo?
Why can I not see him?
Where did he go?
- Jong Seo.
- Is he under the sea?
- He's not here.
Jong Seo.
(Jong Seo disappeared.)
Where is he?
Hurry up
and bring him in front of us.
Let us see if he's okay.
Can he speak properly?
- Where is he?
- Can he walk with both legs?
(Coincidentally, the youngest
producer disappeared after that.)
He's coming.
- He's here. Try walking.
- Jong Seo.
- Try walking. Can you walk?
- They're not your legs.
- Right?
- You can walk, right?
Did you do it? How was it?
If you're delusional,
you'll feel
like you'll lose your mind.
You will wonder
why it's made of wood.
(The sky bridge makes you
think all sorts of thoughts.)
It won't randomly break
in the middle...
like "Squid Game," right?
Right?
This doesn't make sense.
(After playing a game,
So Min decided to take the lead.)
(So Min in the lead
wears the safety gear first.)
I'm so sensitive right now.
I'm sensitive about everything.
It bothers me.
This is crazy. Come here, So Min.
I really can't go.
(It's an open sea in the front.)
What if I fall on that pine tree?
I don't think I can't do it.
There's no net.
This doesn't make sense. Why...
There won't be many people
who will do this.
(They should walk with their legs
without handrails or handles.)
(Shocked)
So Min, go.
(So Min is wearing a safety gear
and has to go now.)
I'm sorry. I need some time.
I'm really sorry.
Go quickly.
(She can't easily take a step.)
I didn't know
when I saw it from there.
- But now that I'm here...
- Here is...
I hate that there's nothing.
I can see the rocks and the sea.
- Look.
- Sir, let's say I shook and fell.
This will protect me.
But how can I come up here again?
Will you come to me?
You should get up by yourself
in the middle.
I should get up by myself?
Does this make sense?
It's even windy.
Can you go first?
- Please take the lead just once.
- Why?
Se Chan, can't you go first?
What are you going to do for me?
Anything.
No. You should go first today. Go.
Just once.
(Her colleague is strict
when he's scared.)
I don't think I can go either.
(Upset)
- The wind is so...
- Is this scarier than the swing?
It's so windy.
- Go.
- My gosh.
It's so windy.
(The first step)
This is driving me crazy.
Once you start moving,
it will start.
Start. Go.
- You've done it.
- I'm going crazy.
What should I do?
You should look down.
No, I mean...
It's so windy.
What should I do?
I really can't do it.
(Her hands and feet are shaking.)
Oh, my goodness.
(She got to the second block.)
You're done. You can move
from one block to another.
Take a step forward.
- Go.
- Am I smiling?
- I'm crying.
- Take a step forward.
Take a step forward.
- This makes me dizzy.
- What should I do?
Wait.
What do I do?
I'm in trouble.
Yes.
People do this for an experience.
Oh, gosh. What should I do?
(So Min tries to calm herself down
by talking to herself.)
What should I do?
Se Chan. Hold on. Wait.
Wait. This is...
This is the hardest part.
(Laughing)
Things will become weird if you cry.
Just go quickly.
I'm trying not to cry,
but the tears keep falling.
You can air it if I smile
while the tears are falling down.
Right. Because you can
get teary-eyed...
- Right?
- because of the sea wind.
The viewers won't say anything
about it.
You can't say "Save me."
Or "I can't do this" while crying.
I'm sorry.
I'm being a nuisance, right?
But I'm so scared.
I'm really afraid of heights.
So MIn, think like this.
That you will get ten dollars
every time you step on the block.
That's right. That's 20 dollars.
(My goodness.)
That's 20 dollars.
(Her fellow penalty receiver
encourages her in a weird way.)
I'm scared. What should I do?
I'm smiling though.
I'm so scared. What do I do?
(Dizzy)
("Squid Game" soundtrack)
- What should I do?
- You're doing good.
It's so fun.
I'm having a lot of fun.
What should I do? I'm in trouble.
It'll be fine if I just pass this.
I can do it once I pass this.
It's very windy.
(Moving forward against the wind)
You're done. Okay.
I'll go soon.
It's fine.
My gosh.
(But she still has a long way.)
You...
The wind.
(The wind is getting stronger.)
- Oh, no.
- It's so windy.
It's not windy in the middle.
So Min, he said
it's not windy in the middle.
- It's better to get there quickly.
- It's so windy. What should I do?
- Oh, my.
What should I do?
Gosh, what should I do?
(She has to fight the wind that
shakes her entire body.)
Gosh, what should I do?
Oh, my. I almost went
without the belt.
(He almost left the world
thanks to the sea wind.)
Put it on me beforehand.
I almost went without the belt.
(She's crying and smiling
at the same time.)
(Crying)
This is fun. I'm so excited.
(The effect of her self-hypnosis
is getting weak.)
- Take it slow.
- This is no joke.
Take it slow.
(Se Chan, the second one to go,
is also ready.)
This is no joke.
(He can only sigh at that height.)
Don't look down.
- Don't talk to me.
- Don't look down.
I said don't talk to me.
- Don't talk to me.
- It's vibrating.
(He slowly goes forward
with shaky legs.)
Done. Go.
Take light steps.
I can feel the vibration.
- Oh, my goodness.
- It's shaking.
- What should I do?
- So Min, it's so windy here.
- Just a moment.
- Go quickly.
Hurry up and get to the middle.
Wait.
- Hold on. I'm straining my legs.
- It's scary here.
(They can feel the strong wind
under their feet.)
It's windy.
It's very windy.
(They can clearly feel
the vibration of the sky bridge.)
I think this got loose.
Is this okay?
- I think it got loose.
- It's okay.
(The gear is fine,
but she feels nervous.)
I'm not joking. It feels like
I'm not wearing it. Is this okay?
It's loose.
(He can't answer.)
Oh, my goodness.
Hold on. Wind, stop blowing.
Wind, stop blowing. I said, stop!
(She's not even scared now.
She's furious.)
Just keep going.
(Just like that, a battle
against the wind has started.)
Gosh, it's so windy here.
Hey, hurry up.
One, two, one... It's so windy here!
It's so windy here! Gosh!
Whatever. One, two. Gosh, the wind!
Wind, stop blowing!
So Min, let's hurry up. It's scary.
- No. Stop shaking it.
- So Min.
No, don't shake it. What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Gosh, it feels strange.
What's with this screw?
- It feels strange here.
- It's strange.
Are you sure this is fine?
(This is strange.)
- This is strange.
- Oh, no.
I think the screw here is loose.
So Min,
Follow me quietly.
I think it'll be better to go fast.
- No, I can't go fast.
- It's scarier to stay here.
Can I go back?
(Can I go back?)
Hey, mister! Can I go back?
I want to finish crossing it
at once.
I want to go fast,
but because of her, I can't.
I'm afraid the steel would erode
if we stand here for too long.
(A creative scaredy-cat)
Hey, look at this!
One, two.
Oh, no. There are glass steps ahead.
What do we do? It's made of glass.
No, just go fast. I don't think
we should stay here for long.
It's made of glass!
- Where?
- The steps here are made of glass.
- Which one?
- The steps! They're glass.
They won't break.
Why don't you come running?
Go ahead and try it.
(Hiccupping)
Hey, it's shaking! It's windy here!
Hey, look!
(The scaredy-cat
can't get it together.)
Hurry up.
(Sighing)
Gosh, what do I do?
(So Min has stepped
on the glass step.)
It's glass! Gosh, whatever!
(She tries to get through it
by not looking down.)
It's glass!
(She crosses the glass section.)
Gosh, they were made of glass.
One, two.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan was behind
following So Min.)
- Gosh, what's this? Is this glass?
- It's glass.
It's glass!
I told you that there were
steps made of glass.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
- Gosh, what do I do?
- Step on them gently.
- Gosh, it's glass.
- The wind is so strong.
(He timidly steps on them
as he's afraid they might break.)
- Hey!
- Gosh.
(He's lost it.)
This is so scary!
Gosh, I want to fart.
Excuse me, I'll go.
- Don't fart.
- I did.
I'll kill you if you do.
Don't do it.
It's so windy here!
Wind, stop blowing!
- It's so windy! Oh, no.
- I grabbed it wrong.
- I'm grabbing it wrong.
- It's so windy.
Gosh, we're in trouble. The wind.
- I'm going.
- I'm so dizzy.
- I'm...
- Go!
- I'm going.
- One,
- two, one, two.
- Two, one, two.
(One, two!)
- Two.
- Let me fart.
We're almost there.
I have to fart.
Gosh, I want to fart.
One, two.
Gosh, I just...
One... I think this part is shaking.
What do I do? I'm a bit dizzy.
What's wrong with this?
Gosh, I'm nauseous. What do I do?
(Wait, this is...)
This is... We're almost there.
I'm almost done.
I'm here now. I'm done.
(So Min finishes
crossing the bridge.)
(Succeeds in crossing the sky bridge
after crying her eyes out)
It's so scary. It's seriously scary.
One, two. I got this. Two...
I got this.
(Se Chan finishes
crossing the bridge.)
- Why do people do this?
- It's so scary.
It was so scary.
Look how sweaty I am.
I know. Look how much
you're sweating.
Don't take it off.
We have another one.
- What?
- You need to get on the swing too.
Gosh, seriously...
(They're only half way done.)
- I'm exhausted.
- Can't we use a chance card?
I'm exhausted. I'm mentally drained.
(An extreme air swing is waiting
for the exhausted scaredy-cats.)
Can you carry me? My legs feel weak.
So Min, the seat on the right
is scarier.
- You sit on the right.
- No.
Hurry. Then let's play a game
to decide.
- Gosh.
- Let's play a game.
- I'm just kidding.
This side is less scary.
Lean far back.
- Right?
- Gosh.
You can start.
Should I just keep my eyes closed?
- Hey, what is this?
- Should I just keep my eyes closed?
(The swing is going up?)
- Hey, what is this?
Should I keep my eyes closed?
How does it work?
Does it keep going up?
I don't know.
- Oh, no.
- At least with this,
I don't have to move.
But how does it work?
Because we don't know...
- how this works...
- The director.
Look at the director. She's tiny.
- My, stop moving.
- Oh, no. Gosh.
It should stop moving already.
Stop. Why does it keep going up?
I think it should stop moving.
What's wrong with this?
It should stop...
(She has a bad feeling about it.)
How far up will it go? Stop!
Stop!
I think it's going to be scary.
We'll be fine if we don't look.
I won't look.
What's going on?
It's shaking. Oh, gosh.
What's wrong with this thing?
(What's wrong with this thing?
Stop!)
Stop!
Oh, please... Stop!
Stop it!
(The extreme air swing
starts moving in earnest.)
(A thrilling swing)
- Gosh, I'm nauseous.
- Hey!
- Sir!
(The Yeosu sea unfolds below them.)
(The two wax figures have frozen.)
(His face has aged
because of the sea breeze.)
(And she can't even open her eyes
after crying her eyes out.)
- Gosh, I'm nauseous.
- Sir, stop!
Stop! It's going to break!
It's okay. We can do this.
- We can do this.
- Gosh, my back hurts.
(The scaredy-cats can't even
keep their eyes open.)
(They probably couldn't see
the Yeosu sea at all.)
It's so scary!
(They probably couldn't see
the Yeosu sea at all.)
So Min!
I want to go home!
So Min, we're done with our penalty!
I won't get any penalty anymore!
Gosh, stop!
Ji Suk Jin, out!
Yoo Jae Suk, out!
Gosh, I'm nauseous.
- I'm nauseous too. Hang in there.
- I'm nauseous.
I think it's broken!
- Look at the sky.
- Sir!
- It's going down!
(The purpose of a journey...)
(is in its process,)
(not the goal.)
(The trip to Gangwon Province
they've been looking forward to)
(They're going to enjoy the trip
with even better weather.)
It's fall now.
It's so pretty here.
(While they're enjoying their
free time with the mood of fall...)
Guys!
(A while ago...)
(The members are faced
with two buttons.)
(Random trip where the choices they
make result in different courses)
(There's a course where they get to
jump into the Hantan River.)
(This is so relaxing.)
(Whereas the other members
are enjoying paradise.)
(While some of them are shooting
a race,)
(some are playing hide-and-seek
with their imaginary lovers.)
(You never know what will happen
on this trip until it's over.)
(Who will go back home
with the most impactful memories?)
(Go? Stop?)