This place is so pretty.
The floor is covered
with artificial turf.
This is so lovely. It's pretty.
When I see artificial turf...
What's so pretty?
- Do you want to play soccer?
- This is pretty.
- There's a boxing game machine.
- Hello.
- A boxing game machine.
This place is so pretty.
- This is...
- I should put my weight on it.
(While Seok Sam shows off
his weak power...)
(Doing a photoshoot alone)
- What is she doing now?
- My gosh.
- She can't help it.
- You know there's a camera.
That means they want me to do this.
- My gosh.
- I guess you're right.
This is embarrassing.
- But she's...
- Take a look at this.
(The May issue of Frog Magazine)
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hug me
Hello.
- Then do this.
- Hello.
One, two, and go.
- What is this?
- One, two, and go.
- Good.
- She's exercising...
- with her father-in-law.
- Take a look at this.
- It shows scores.
- Look at this.
Someone already tried this.
- What's that?
- I guess we have guests.
Right. Three guests.
Samseong-dong Nuclear Punch,
954 points. That's high.
- Banpo-dong Cyanide.
- Cyanide.
- "Is Jong Kook strong?"
The person who wrote this
will get a good scolding.
And there's Baby.
(Someone left a trace
provoking the members.)
There's Banpo-dong Cyanide.
Who is Baby?
- What's this?
- The one who wrote cyanide...
- must be funny.
- Exactly.
- Someone funny.
- Someone who likes to make jokes.
This one must be someone
who likes to make people laugh.
- It must be a comedian.
- You should give it a try.
It will be amazing if Jong Kook
gets a lower score than me.
If my score is higher
than Jong Kook's,
that means I'm strong, right?
I think so.
- Why don't you give it a try?
- Who?
"Those with a powerful punch
may try this and check the score."
- Who wants to go first?
- Do you want me to try?
Jamwon-dong Honey Punch goes first.
Jamwon-dong Honey Punch.
- Jamwon-dong Honey Punch.
- Suyu-ri Honey Punch.
- Honey Punch.
- Suyu-ri Honey Punch goes first.
Let's say Jamwon-dong Hellraiser.
- No. Jamwon-dong...
- Hellraiser.
- You're number four.
- It's an old movie.
- This is too low.
- All right. Suyu-ri.
- Isn't it too low?
Suyu-ri Honey Punch.
I should put my weight on this.
Sweet Fist.
- I'll go like this.
- Your punch tastes sweet.
Here I go.
All right. Jamwon-dong Honey Punch.
- Oh, dear.
- Gosh.
- Seriously...
- That's too weak.
- You are healthy.
- I missed it.
- That's too weak.
- I hit the corner of it.
That was weak, but it's 800 points.
- What is it, 800 points?
- It should be a lot lower.
- It's 800.
- I touched the corner.
- Let me try it again.
- This is very generous.
Hang on.
He's been practicing it. He is...
- Haha recently started boxing.
- He's into boxing.
MMA.
- Right. You should try it.
- You can do this.
- He says...
- No. You do it.
He says he has a powerful punch.
That's what the coach said.
- What?
- My punch might kill someone.
- Okay. Go ahead and try it.
- Just do it.
Mapo... Mapo One-Month Punch,
you do it.
What's One-Month Punch?
- You started boxing a month ago.
- It's been a month.
Why would you say that?
I want something cool.
Your nickname is One Month.
I'm Sleep Punch.
You're Hip Punch.
- You like to be hip. Hip Punch.
- It's Hip Punch.
- Can I use both hands?
- Mapo Hip Punch.
- Hip Punch.
- That doesn't matter.
He's been doing MMA.
- Good.
- You look hip. Nice.
- Go ahead and do it.
- Look at him.
- Just do it.
- All right.
- Gosh, look at that.
- Look at his steps.
That's cute.
You're wearing baggy pants.
- What?
- It's like he's wearing a diaper.
- He's wearing a diaper.
- That's unique.
- It looks like a diaper.
- He's wearing a diaper.
- I need to warm up before...
- It's a diaper.
- My gosh.
- That was really weak.
It was loud though.
- It's 874.
- Is that it?
Ji Hyo must be stronger than that.
What's Ji Hyo's nickname?
What do you want?
- I like Sleep Hip Punch.
- I...
Mapo Homebody.
Homebody?
- Mapo Homebody?
- Mapo Homebody.
- Homebody Punch.
It says Homebody Jeoktoma.
Homebody Jeoktoma?
- Homebody Jeoktoma.
- She wrote Homebody Jeoktoma.
She's Jeoktoma, but she doesn't run.
She never goes out of her house.
She never goes out. She's home.
Homebody Jeoktoma.
- Come on.
- Gosh.
- That's as weak as Suk Jin's.
- Don't pretend to be weak.
You'd get Suk Jin's score.
- It's 732.
- Why are you pretending to be weak?
What's my nickname?
Do you have any ideas?
You live in Yongsan, right?
What about Yongsan Tutu?
You look like Tutu.
- Really?
- Yongsan Frog.
- I'll go with Yongsan Frog.
Go. That looks good, So Min.
You should grab a marker pen.
- Yongsan Frog.
- You might get hurt.
- You'll get 300 points.
- Yongsan Frog, go.
Ribbit.
- Ribbit.
- My gosh.
(She throws a strong punch
with all her energy.)
- That was loud.
- You got it right.
- It was powerful.
- I'm sure it's high.
- It's out.
- It's 841.
(841 points)
(Yongsan Frog: 841 points)
- I got 800.
- It's higher than Suk Jin's.
- Let me try it again.
- No.
- I hit...
- You get to try only once.
- I touched the corner of it.
- It's over.
- My score is too low.
- It's my turn.
Jae Suk.
Hang on. You're Apgujeong...
- Apgujeong...
- Apgujeong Ugly Face.
- Apgujeong Idiot.
- Apgujeong Yoda.
- Idiot.
- Baby Octopus.
Apgujeong Baby Octopus.
- Hey.
- Apgujeong Baby Octopus?
- Apgu... Apgujeong Minion.
- Snout Thumbtack.
- Apgu... What?
Snout Thumbtack?
What about Apgujeong Smashed Face?
Apgujeong Smashed Face.
- Smashed Face?
- Smashed Face
- Apgujeong Smashed Face.
- That sounds great.
- Smashed Face.
- I like it.
- Apgujeong Smashed Face?
- Nice.
- I like Smashed Face.
- That sounds great.
What about Face Doctor?
- It sounds intense.
- Okay.
I'll get you a great nickname.
Apgujeong Smashed Face.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- I love Yongsan Frog.
- Gosh.
- It must be high.
- That was nice.
- He used both hands.
I hit it right.
- He put his weight on it.
- It must be high.
- This is about his pride.
- It's 939.
- My gosh.
- That's high.
- It's 939.
- You're second place.
- That was so close.
- Let me try.
- You did well.
- You're second place.
- It went well.
- Banpo-dong Cyanide is doomed.
- Look at that.
- How could it be so high?
What do you mean?
It's lower than before.
It's 700, Suk Jin.
Let me try.
This is strange.
It's my turn.
I can do better than this.
- That's so close.
- I should show them something.
- This is...
- Se Chan is strong.
- Seriously...
- Here comes Itaewon Boombastic.
- The truth is...
- He's quite heavy.
- Good.
- He must be strong.
Bang.
(How strong is Se Chan's punch?)
My goodness. Excuse me.
(The prankster is back.)
- Excuse me.
- That's nice.
- Why?
- Mr. Smashed Face, move over.
Be careful.
You shouldn't have worn that.
- That's right.
- Now he can't do it right.
It must bother him.
He can't do it right.
(Groaning)
- Excuse me!
- He can't do it right.
- Just do it.
- Mr. Smashed Face!
- Punch it.
- It can be dangerous.
- Okay. Just punch it.
- It was going well.
- Okay.
- Go ahead and do it.
- This is thrilling.
- My gosh.
- Do it again.
It will be about 300.
Gosh, Jae Suk. That wasn't good.
- It did affect him.
- That was good. Why?
- It's 926.
- That's high.
I want to try it again.
- I want to punch it again.
- What's Jong Kook's name?
- Secret Jjujju?
- Go with Jjujju.
Gosh, this is...
This is about his pride.
- Not really.
- All right.
- It's not about my pride.
- What's Jong Kook's nickname?
- Secret Jjujju.
- It can't be Secret Jjujju.
It should be Jjijji.
- Secret Jjijji.
- It sounds too small.
- Muscular pig.
- Should I punch it like this?
- What about Eun Hye Punch?
- Darn it.
(What about Eun Hye Punch?)
- I like Eun Hye Punch.
- I mean, Blessed Punch.
It means Blessed Punch.
- What's wrong?
- Don't do it.
- You're being sensitive.
- He's...
- I'm not sensitive.
- What...
- He's just unbelievable.
- Eun Hye Punch?
Blessed Punch.
Why do you have to say that?
- Your punch is blessed.
- Exactly.
- That's different.
- Go with Eun Hye Punch.
- He's honored.
- What?
- Glory Punch.
- Exactly.
- I mean...
- Glory Kim.
- My gosh.
- Why do you have to...
It doesn't have to be Eun Hye.
It means blessed.
- Eun Hye Punch.
- Glory Punch.
- Isn't that nice?
- He's strange.
- Glory Punch.
I like Eun Hye Punch.
- I can't understand him.
- Good. Eun Hye Punch.
- This is...
- This is romantic.
(Swinging)
- Great. Look at that.
The main character appears last.
You go like this.
- This is the ending.
- All right.
Jong Kook, you are legally
throwing a punch today.
It has to be higher than 954.
- This is...
- He's doing this legally.
- My goodness.
- Oh, dear.
I wonder how...
(Thump)
- Good.
- He looks like King Kong.
I don't think it's high.
It must be high. It's 961.
- My gosh.
- He's first place.
(He wins 1st place.)
- He's number one.
- He's first place.
- I want to do it again.
- Me too.
- Those who want to try again...
- Me.
(Give me two dollars.)
- Give me two dollars.
- Why?
- I will wire the money.
- Pay two dollars.
- I will.
- I'll wire the money.
- Pay it now.
- I'll pay.
- Bring the money.
- I will pay.
- This is ridiculous.
Can you pay for me?
- I'll pay.
- Pay 10 dollars for 5 people.
- I'll pay 10 dollars.
- Give me 10 dollars.
I'll pay ten dollars. Here.
(He puts his glasses in
as a pledge.)
Is it the pledge?
- I'll pay. My gosh.
- Okay.
All right. This will be
your new record.
- Okay. I'll go with this.
- Okay.
- I have to do this right.
- You have only one chance.
I bet this will be lower.
- I have to do this right.
I want more than 900 points.
- It's over.
- Oh, no.
It's over.
- It's 196.
- Oh, dear.
- Hey!
- It's 196.
I want to try it again.
Suk Jin, try it again.
Take off your clothes.
- One more try.
- Try it again.
- Try again. Take this off.
- Pay the money.
- You have only one chance.
- You can do this.
You get only one chance.
All right.
We have the results
of the Decisive Punch.
And we have the ranking on the wall.
The three people
with the lowest scores will...
- choose their captains.
- Captains?
Yes. You can choose
one of the blue names.
- Those three?
- Yes.
- Captain?
- I see.
All right. I will...
- Which one do you want?
- Which one?
- Samseong-dong Nuclear Punch.
- Okay.
- Nuclear Punch sounds good.
- Samseong-dong Nuclear Punch.
- Next.
- Jeoktoma.
I will...
choose the one
who said "Is Jong Kook strong?"
- Okay.
- I see.
You should choose Baby.
No, I want the strongest one.
- Nuclear Punch?
- Nuclear Punch.
Nuclear Punch.
Here. Is Jong Kook strong?
I should show him how strong I am.
All right. You're done
choosing your teams.
- So let's bring in the captains.
- Okay.
The three guests with decisive
punches, please come on out.
Who are they?
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
Hey.
- Baby?
(The ghost who follows Kim Go Eun
around in "Guardian")
(She's a scene-stealer
with her distinctive acting.)
(Park Gyeong Hye showed impressive
acting in "Escape from Mogadishu".)
(He was Park Bo Gum's friend
in "Record of Youth".)
(Actor Byeon Woo Seok also showed
great acting in a historical drama.)
- Hello.
- Oh, hello.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Baby?
- Hey.
- Is he Woo Jae?
- What?
- Is he Yoon Seok?
- It's Woo Jae.
- Hey.
- Woo Jae.
(Joo Woo Jae,
the paper doll shows up.)
It's Woo Jae.
We finally meet.
- Hello.
- It's so good to see you.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- What's your name?
- Nice to meet you.
You're Nuclear Punch. All right.
- Is that you?
- Is Jong Kook strong?
- You said that?
- Hey, you are...
The production crew...
It's just a nickname.
Write down your nicknames.
And we will decide the ranking.
I'll go with "Is Jong Kook Strong?"
Is Jong Kook Strong?
It has to be like that.
Hey, you are...
The production crew...
- It's just a nickname.
- Come here.
Come here. You're a guest.
Why are you here again?
Are you here as a manager or what?
- Why did you come?
- For "The Manager?"
- He's with me.
- Model...
- Woo Jae, is your jacket rusty?
- What?
- A rusty jacket?
- This is...
Woo Jae...
- was here before.
- Right.
We don't have to introduce him.
Actually, Woo Jae is...
You should at least introduce me.
- I must say we made him popular.
- That's true.
- We made him popular.
- Sure.
- It's true we made you famous.
- Isn't that true?
- We made Woo Jae famous.
- Right.
- You have to admit it.
- Is that right?
- You got more followers, right?
- After I was on this show,
- a lot of people asked me.
- What?
"Are you sure
you were a fashion model?"
I don't want to explain the details,
so I just say no.
I see.
Woo Jae, are you
close to other models?
What are you good at?
Do you have a group chat room?
I'm the bond
who glues them together.
He's like a comedian
in the world of models.
Exactly. Now I get it.
- He's like Kwang Soo.
- He's Kwang Soo.
- People would believe it.
- A comedian of actors.
We haven't talked about Kwang Soo
in a while.
- This is how tall people look.
- Right.
- Exactly.
- He's really tall.
- Right. He's really tall.
- He looks so cool.
Wait. So Min is...
So Min is stepping forward again.
- So Min.
- Stay right here.
- You can stand here.
- She weighs in again.
So Min was...
- She usually stays here.
- She took a step forward.
But she was standing here today.
- She has that smile again.
- Stand here.
- That smile. Look.
Stand there.
- It's all right.
- It's not like that.
You can stay here.
Don't be like that.
It makes him uncomfortable.
You are very tall.
- She's taller than you thought.
- Right.
She has that smile again.
I can tell you one thing for sure.
She's not interested in Woo Jae.
It's not Woo Jae.
- It's not Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae, it's nice to see you!
- It's definitely not Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae is...
So Min looks excited again.
The three guests have
something in common.
- What?
- They are close friends.
- Really?
- Yes.
And they each have a decisive punch.
- I see.
- Like what?
As you know, Gyeong Hye has done...
a lot of dramas and movies.
- She's a scene-stealer.
- She was on "Guardian".
- That's right.
- She was a scene-stealer.
- You know "Guardian".
- She was in the drama.
Woo Seok also has a decisive punch.
- What is it?
- He was on "Record of Youth".
"Record of Youth".
I loved the drama.
Thank you.
- Right.
- Park Bo Gum's friend.
Woo Jae also has a decisive punch.
- It's Running Man.
- Running Man.
It's Running Man.
Woo Jae's major work is Running Man.
- It's Running Man.
- We raised you.
- I must have something good.
- Woo Jae has done...
many TV shows and fashion shows,
- It's not "Love Naggers".
- but his major work is...
Did you do some research on me?
- We did.
- What made you famous...
- It's us who made you famous.
- We did our research.
- I see.
- First,
let's talk about Gyeong Hye.
- This is your first time here.
- Right.
How are you feeling?
Thank you so much
for having me here.
I really love this show.
Is your nickname Baby?
- Yes.
- Why?
I just want to look cute.
- You're cute.
- You've lovely.
- Gyeong Hye.
Is there anyone whom you look like?
- No.
- Not at all?
Actually, there's one,
but I can't tell you.
- Just tell us.
- Who is it?
- From a distance, at a glance...
- At a slight glance...
- It's for us to judge.
I'm so nervous
that I forgot the name.
- Benedict Cumberbatch?
- No.
It's not him.
- I'm excited.
- By the way,
you act like Park Na Rae.
That's right.
(They look alike in a way.)
- I love Na Rae. I'm a fan.
- Oh, dear.
- She looks a little like her.
- I'm a big fan.
And we have Byeon Woo Seok
from "Record of Youth".
- He's handsome.
- He looks great.
He's really good-looking.
All I can see is the back
of So Min's head now.
She never looks back.
- My gosh.
- Anyway, Woo Seok,
what did people say when you told
them you'd be on Running Man?
Did you ask Woo Jae anything?
I was a little nervous,
so I asked Woo Jae.
I thought he'd tell me what to do...
- And give you advice?
- and give me advice.
But he didn't say anything.
- "Just be yourself."
- How would I give you advice...
when I don't know what to do?
Woo Jae doesn't know
what to do here.
- That's what I heard.
- I couldn't say anything last time.
They are really mean
toward outsiders.
I watched...
the official YouTube channel of SBS.
They uploaded a video of me.
It shows how mean
you guys were to me.
- Hey, that's love.
- I was on the thumbnail.
- We did it out of love.
- That means we care about you.
- I was on the thumbnail.
- It means we care.
How could you...
I mean I was flattered.
- I loved it.
- We weren't being mean.
I found it friendly.
Your major work is Running Man.
- Honestly.
- Sure. It's Running Han.
- Okay.
- All right.
- He's...
- He is good-looking.
- They all say that.
- You must be popular.
You are popular
with girls, aren't you?
- Not really.
- Seriously?
Is that because of your personality?
- My personality?
- Yes.
- I have a pretty good personality.
- I see.
"A pretty good personality?"
He's humorous.
- We don't usually say that.
- He's so funny.
"A pretty good personality."
He's really funny.
(His words make her
laugh her head off.)
She even stomps her feet.
Look how she responds.
- What's with her?
- He's so funny.
- He's the best.
- She's really annoying.
She even stomps her feet.
Look how she responds.
- Hey.
- Look at her.
Take a look at Woo Seok's shoulders.
A bag would never
slide down his shoulders.
- I hate it.
- I want to have his shoulders.
He's got broad shoulders.
- I want to live with his body.
- They're broad.
Woo Jae's shoulders aren't
that broad for his height.
It's like Woo Jae
doesn't have shoulders.
- What?
- You've got no shoulders.
- And he has flat buttocks.
- That's right.
There you go again.
I don't have anything.
- Woo Jae looks so pale today.
- What I have...
Did you not sleep last night?
- Woo Jae looks so pale today.
- What I have...
Did you not sleep last night?
Now she's one of them. I mean...
- Did you get some sleep?
- They're like twin buildings.
While he's complete,
- Woo Jae only has pillars.
- Poor construction.
Why does your skin
look so horrible today?
- His face...
- He looks off-color.
Hey, you look sick.
- You should get a liver test.
- Seriously, you look awful.
- Did you rehearse this or what?
- No.
- You're sick, aren't you?
- We're serious.
- Just go ahead and cry.
- We're saying this for your sake.
If you're sick, you can go home.
It's all right.
I'll go home later.
You will soon get jaundice.
- That's enough.
- It's so...
- You went too far with it.
- His face is...
I got a lot of diseases
because of him.
Woo Jae, you'll get sick.
- He looks awful.
- He needs to get more calcium.
- You...
- He probably has a liver problem.
- What?
- Just play along with him.
- Come here.
- I'm not sick.
- Let me tell you about the race.
Today, we have three guests...
who left a deep impression on
viewers with their decisive punches.
So this is called
The Decisive Punch Race.
- I see.
- Punch.
Collecting bread stickers
is popular these days.
- Right.
- That's true.
- The seal stickers.
We made special stickers for you.
And we put them...
- in the bread package randomly.
- Really?
We have 300 packages of bread today.
- That's a lot.
- We have 300 packages?
And there are
ten different kinds of stickers.
Each team will win bread
after a mission.
The team that collects all ten kinds
of stickers wins the race.
(The team that collects all ten
kinds of stickers wins the race.)
(Winner)
Make sure your team collects
the ten different kinds of stickers.
I'll give you the Runningdex.
- Runningdex?
- We have the Runningdex.
- What's that?
- This is like the Pokedex?
We will do this.
- All right, Woo Jae.
- My strategy worked.
I see. You provoked me.
I knew Jong Kook
would pick this nickname.
(He got Jong Kook
for his team as he planned.)
- Are we a team of 4?
- We are 4.
This is awkward.
Don't tease me.
- But the team...
- Yes?
- that has Suk Jin always loses.
- That's not true.
- Don't worry.
- We have Jae Suk.
- You have me.
- Can I talk casually to you?
Sure. Please.
- Can I do the same?
- Of course.
Look at So Min.
She's not working.
What?
- Do you like cheesy girls?
- Sorry?
- Very much so.
- I see.
(Really?)
(The cheesy girl is smiling
from ear to ear.)
- That's great.
- She's elated.
- Your hair looks nice today.
- Finally, this day has come.
- Tuck your hair behind your ears.
- It looks pretty.
- Try to look pretty.
- There you go.
- Her hair looks great.
- She looks so happy.
- She's unbelievably consistent.
- Are you happy?
- He's good with words too.
- He made her day.
She's smiling so happily.
- The two of them don't seem...
- Not at all.
I'll do everything I can
to make it happen.
I'll try to make it romantic
somehow.
We'll be like a comedy duo.
I don't know why,
but she reminds me of Na Rae.
- She looks like her from afar.
- We're like a comedy duo.
- A comedy duo.
- I'll do my best to play Cupid.
She feels like one of us.
They look great together.
Now, each team will choose bread.
Based on the teams' average scores,
the team in 1st place gets 7,
- We get 7.
- the team in 2nd place gets 5,
and the team in 3rd place gets 3.
The team
with the highest average score is...
(Which team got the highest score
and will get 7 pieces of bread?)
The team
with the highest average score is...
- I bet it's us.
- Team Gyeong Hye.
(Team Gyeong Hye with an average score
of 894 points placed 1st.)
- How?
- We got the highest score.
- Team Woo Jae placed second.
- This is exciting.
- We placed second?
- Yes.
- He and I got similar scores.
- We...
Yes. Your team placed second.
- We placed 2nd.
- And Team Woo Seok placed 3rd.
- Why are we in 3rd place?
- You placed 3rd.
I really wanted to have that bread.
- Let's eat some bread.
- Oh, my.
- It's real bread.
- It looks delicious.
I see a sticker on each of them.
This is fascinating.
- We'll start with the winning team.
- Okay. Go ahead.
You can choose
seven pieces from them.
- Seven pieces?
- Come, Baby. Pick our bread.
I like this one.
This is my favorite.
- Pick one.
- Okay.
I like the red bean flavor.
Take out the stickers
and reveal them right away.
- Right now?
- Okay.
What could it be?
- Which one did you get?
- It looks delicious.
It's not good to pick
the same image. What is it?
(What could be the 1st Runningmon
they picked?)
(Team Gyeong Hye will reveal
their Runningmon stickers.)
It's hard to get a good one.
(They got 2 Woojaemon stickers.)
- Is it our turn?
- I want soboro bread.
Is it Woojaemon?
- You can pick three pieces.
- It's Jaeseokmon.
Oh, good.
(Team Gyeong Hye got
Jaeseokmon and Woojaemon.)
I got another Jaeseokmon sticker. Darn.
I got a Jihyomon sticker.
Jihyomon? We got three so far.
Hey, I got a different one.
- I got Sominmon.
- It's Sominmon.
(They've found Sominmon as well.)
- What is it?
- I got this one.
- I see an orange color.
- Then what about...
- It's Jongkookmon.
We've collected
five different stickers.
(Team Gyeong Hye has collected
5 stickers so far.)
It's Jihyomon. Darn it.
(They already have Jihyomon.)
- That's right.
- My, this is awesome.
(Team Gyeong Hye got 5 stickers.
What about Team Woo Seok?)
- Hey, I got a different one.
- What?
- I...
- It's Sominmon.
I picked myself.
- It's Jaeseokmon.
- Sominmon.
- I'm the only one left.
- We picked ourselves.
- Woo Seok, what did you get?
- Oh, it's Gyeonghyemon.
- Gyeonghyemon.
- Okay.
We got all different stickers.
- Put them in the almanac.
- Okay.
Sominmon.
- Which one is it? Is it Locust?
- It's Jaeseokmon.
Jaeseokmon.
Gosh, it's Jaeseokmon. Darn.
- Wait. What is this?
- What is it?
- This one is Jaeseokmon too.
- What is it? I don't see the name.
- What is this?
- I like bread.
- It's Woojaemon.
- This one is Sechanmon.
- Woo Jae is a mantis.
- Woo Jae, you are...
- I'm a mantis?
- We picked different stickers.
That's a relief.
We didn't pick the same one, right?
They're all different.
Check that one too.
We'll begin the first mission
after you change your clothes.
- Okay.
- Got it.
(So Min is
sitting far away from Woo Seok.)
So Min, sit here.
- It's okay. Please sit there.
- I want to sit here.
- I'm comfortable here too.
- Come on.
- Stop it, Suk Jin.
- Come and sit here.
- You guys...
- Why don't you sit there?
You guys always ruin everything.
- Just mind your own business.
- I can't believe you.
- I really want to...
- Mind your own business, will you?
I want to lean back here.
There's no backrest here.
- Please just leave me alone.
- I want to lean back.
You're telling us to leave you be,
but you asked him about his age.
- He has long arms and legs.
- How old are you, Woo Seok?
- How old are you?
- I'm 32.
- I was born in 1991.
- You're older than I thought.
What did you say?
What do you mean by that?
- You two don't have a big age gap?
- I think that's the case.
- So Min.
- "You're older than I thought."
Well, that's what Jong Kook thinks.
- Did she try to impress him?
- Yes.
- No.
- I see. Okay.
Do you have a girlfriend?
- Right?
- No, I don't.
Of course, he says
he doesn't have a girlfriend.
- What is it?
- He doesn't have a girlfriend.
- It was so funny.
- That's none of my business.
(Smiling)
My gosh. He won't stop it.
Please let me focus on my work.
If you keep going on like this...
I'm just messing with you.
Hey, I'm just joking around.
- I can do that.
- That'd be great.
- I'm just joking around.
- Okay.
I told him
that I was just joking around.
(Suk Jin told So Min right away.)
Hey, by the way, So Min,
why not Woo Jae?
- Woo Jae...
- I think he's attractive.
- Of course, he's fabulous.
- There's no man like him.
- But if you're this skinny,
- Yes?
you should have a health check-up
as soon as possible.
- Woo Jae, that could be a sign.
- You should have a check-up.
- I think...
- You look pale today.
- That could be a sign.
- you have a gallbladder problem.
- They said my makeup looks good.
- It's either your gallbladder...
Or you can apply some BB cream.
- His face looks grayish, right?
- Right, he looks...
Woo Jae, let us know
if you don't feel well.
- You might be calcium deficient.
- Your skin looks rough.
- Maybe he's right.
- Woo Jae, you got dark circles.
- Well... I'm healthy.
- He had dark circles last time too.
- I don't get sick often.
- Did he?
- We'll begin the first mission.
- Okay.
Lately, there's been much debate
over many topics...
such as perilla leaf
and padded jackets.
That's true.
The first mission where you will
debate over new topics is...
I Even Thought of a Tragic End.
(The 1st mission of the race:
I Even Thought of a Tragic End)
It's a line from
"Guardian: The Lonely and Great God."
- We love debating.
- It's a line from the drama.
- Oh, right.
- "It'll be a tragic end."
After sharing your opinions
on one topic,
each of you will decide
if you think it's okay or not,
- and raise the signboard.
- We'll talk about the topic, right?
The staff members will hear
your opinions and make a conclusion.
- I see.
- Only the members...
with the same conclusion as
the majority of us will get points.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- That's great.
We'll give you the first topic.
After that, you will come up with
topics to debate over.
The first topic is...
Could you reveal it, please?
(The 1st topic will be revealed.)
One, two, three.
(My lover met my friend secretly
to prepare a party for me.)
- "My lover met..."
- "My lover met my friend..."
"to prepare our one-year dating
anniversary party." No.
(My lover met my friend secretly
for a month...)
(to prepare our 1 year dating
anniversary party.)
- That's not okay.
- It's okay.
- Here you go.
- I think it's okay.
- It's okay.
- No. Unacceptable.
- No.
- That's nonsense.
- They met for a month.
No.
(Thinking)
To prepare a party?
I hate the idea already.
- Don't think from your perspective.
- I hate surprises.
A few times would be understandable.
But a month is not acceptable.
- Something can happen.
- A month?
- A month is too long.
- Not just one day?
It must be a very big party.
A month is not acceptable.
- They'd rehearse everything. No.
- Of course.
- I'll explain the situation.
- Okay.
It may change our thoughts.
"On the one-year dating anniversary
with my boyfriend,"
"my boyfriend invited me
to a luxury hotel."
He booked a hotel room?
A hotel?
"I opened the door with excitement."
"The room was decorated
in a way that I like."
"My boyfriend showed up with a gift
saying he wanted to surprise me."
"When I was tearing up,
my friend showed up..."
"with a cake with candles on it
to congratulate us."
- Her friend shouldn't be there.
- That's ridiculous.
(The friend showed up with a cake.)
- She shouldn't be there.
- That's ridiculous.
- Her friend shouldn't be there.
- Why would they be in a hotel room?
- Why would they be there together?
- Calm down.
- Isn't that a little inappropriate?
- That's ridiculous.
- Both of them are weird.
- Hold on.
Let me read the rest.
- Gosh, seriously.
- "It turns out the two of them..."
"have been contacting each other
over the past month..."
- "to prepare the party secretly."
- Nonsense.
This is unacceptable.
- This is too much.
- There must be another reason.
If they met just one day,
it would be so nice.
- Exactly. It'd be nice.
- That's right.
- But for a month...
- Why would it take so long?
- A month is long enough...
- But they didn't meet every day.
for a man and a woman
to get attached to each other.
- It's totally unacceptable.
- A month is too long...
based on what most people would
think about it.
- A month is too long.
- That's too much.
- But they wouldn't talk every day.
- How big could a party be?
They would meet once a week,
- four times in that month.
- No, I don't think so.
- They'd meet every day.
- They spent a month.
- A month is too long.
- They could fall in love.
- It's not a really big party.
- Think about it.
Can't you see what will happen
after that?
He'll call her friend and say,
"Thank you for your help.
My girlfriend loved it."
"I'd like to treat you
to a nice meal."
- With his girlfriend too.
- Right.
- That's not right.
- If they prepared it for a month,
one of them would end up crying.
One of them would cry
after the party. Don't you think so?
It seems that no one here
trusts other people.
(It seems that no one here
trusts other people.)
- I mean...
- What did you just say about us?
We don't trust others?
- We do trust other people.
- You're too naive.
- That's right.
- You should trust them.
I understand
they had good intentions,
- but a month is too long.
- You'll know when you find the one.
Hang on. This shows
our different relationship statuses.
- The anxious ones talk a lot.
- It's not acceptable.
They shouldn't meet up
without letting her know.
Absolutely not.
- That's not okay.
- It's not okay.
- You see, he spent a month...
- Exactly. I agree.
- preparing it for his girlfriend.
- Yes.
- He did it for his girlfriend.
- Right.
- So I think it's understandable.
- But...
- I think it is.
- Do you think it's good for her?
- He did it...
- Then...
- Woo Seok, imagine this.
- Oh, I guess...
it's because he's handsome.
- It's because he's handsome.
- Let's say...
- That's why he's confident.
- Suk Jin, don't say that.
- It's true.
Clearly, you don't know
how a debate works. Just be quiet.
He told him to be quiet.
He told him to be quiet
during a debate.
- Gosh.
- You should listen to others too.
You're the only one who's talking.
I'm trying to ask Woo Seok
a question.
I'm going to give him a situation.
Let's say you have a girlfriend.
She meets your best friend...
- Like Woo Jae?
- She meets Woo Jae...
It's okay if it's Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae is not a good example.
- I would understand.
(He wouldn't even worry about them.)
- Think of someone attractive.
- Someone popular.
Okay. It's not Woo Jae.
- I'll think of someone else.
- Someone else but Woo Jae.
- Hey.
- Think of someone more handsome.
- I'm irresistible.
- Someone else but Woo Jae.
- You could lose your girlfriend.
How about him? The popular...
How about Park Bo Gum?
They co-starred in a drama.
No, not Bo Gum. What was his name?
- Who?
- It can be me.
- Nam Joo Hyuk.
- Not you. Right, Joo Hyuk.
- Nam Joo Hyuk?
- Yes, Joo Hyuk.
- Nam Joo Hyuk again?
- Joo Hyuk.
- Nam Joo Hyuk. Good.
- He and Joo Hyuk seem close.
- Joo Hyuk is popular.
- I saw them at the gym.
- Please leave Nam Joo Hyuk...
- and Jang Ki Yong out.
- Joo Hyuk...
- You're tearing up...
- It's Joo Hyuk.
- as your girlfriend surprises you.
- See? It's weird.
- Then Joo Hyun suddenly shows up.
- Right.
"Congratulations, Woo Seok.
I helped her prepare this party."
- How would you feel?
- All day long.
They're wearing comfortable clothes.
It wouldn't be so easy...
What kind of clothes?
- Very comfortable...
- They're wearing pajamas.
- They're wearing pajamas?
- Yes.
(Pajamas?)
Why would they be wearing pajamas?
- Isn't that over the top?
- They're wearing pajamas?
- They're wearing casual outfits.
- A bathrobe.
- They're wearing...
- Revealing clothes.
- bathrobes.
- They're wearing revealing clothes.
- Joo Hyuk is wearing a bathrobe?
- Yes.
And then Joo Hyuk tells you,
"Hey, your girlfriend did more work
than I did."
(Hey, your girlfriend did more work
than I did.)
- That's not okay.
- I would be so upset.
- That would...
make Woo Seok the third wheel.
I would feel like
I'm the third wheel.
- But still...
- Would you be okay with that?
- But it's Joo Hyuk.
- Would it be okay?
- He has so much pride.
- But it's Joo Hyuk.
I think he's simply
very understanding.
- To be honest...
- Think more about it.
- Woo Seok is amazing.
- Let's give him time to think.
What about you, Woo Jae?
- He's more of an expert than me.
- What do you think?
- Imagine the situation.
- Woo Jae, be honest with us.
- Don't lie to us.
- Woo Jae, how would you feel?
- Did Woo Seok say it's okay?
- Yes.
I think it's okay.
- That's his inferiority complex.
- Why?
- You don't think it's okay.
- That's his inferiority complex.
- Who's my friend?
- Well...
- Joo Hyuk.
- It's Nam Joo Hyuk.
Please stop talking about him.
Jong Kook,
I won't bring Yoon Eun Hye up.
That's not the same.
What are you talking about?
What if it's Woo Seok?
How many of us think it's okay?
I don't think I can understand that.
- Of course, you can't accept it.
- It's because...
- I think it might be okay.
- It doesn't matter...
who my friend is.
They've been meeting for a month...
- at a hotel.
- That's right.
They met at a hotel.
And imagine what could happen.
- It's just crazy.
- They wouldn't write it down.
- They would rehearse it.
- Yes.
- "Can you walk toward me?"
- Exactly.
- "I'll stand here."
- Yes.
- They would rehearse it.
- Of course.
You know how actors immerse
themselves in their characters...
- while acting, right?
- Right. It's not acceptable.
- I think...
- I think Ji Hyo would understand.
- No.
- Really?
- During the month,
- Right.
my boyfriend and my friend...
- would talk a lot on the phone.
- Right.
- They would share...
- They'd talk a lot together.
- their feelings.
- A month is too long.
I think that one of them would
develop feelings for the other.
- "How should I kiss her?"
- That's right.
- "Should I tilt my head this way?"
- Exactly.
- No way.
- They wouldn't go that far.
- I don't think so.
- No way.
They could do that.
I'm just saying
that it could happen.
- Definitely.
- No way.
But they would talk about me
the whole time.
So I think it'd be okay.
- No.
- That's exactly what I think.
- It's okay.
- Would you be okay with it?
I'd be totally okay with it.
- Are you serious?
- Hold on.
- Hey, do you really think so?
- You'd be okay with it?
- Or is it because Woo Seok said so?
- No.
- Woo Seok, do you think it's okay?
- She'd never be okay with it.
I don't think you'd be okay with it.
- My friend just helped him...
- She'd never be.
- show his love for me.
- But do you think...
- that they really need a month?
- Five hours would be enough.
Even a set for "Let's Go! Dream Team"
can be built in a week.
Even by a bunch of nobodies.
So I haven't seen my girlfriend
in a month?
- No.
- You met her.
- She met him while dating you.
- Right.
That's even worse.
She met him secretly and met me too.
- No.
- But Woo Jae...
- This is what I hate about this.
- You see...
On such a happy day,
he made me...
- have negative thoughts.
- Exactly.
- That's wrong.
- I agree. That's the key point.
- Exactly.
- I'm sorry, but stop being angry.
- It makes me so angry.
- But I think...
- Why are you so angry?
- You see...
- Let's say you walk into the room.
- Yes.
And you see Suk Jin...
behind your girlfriend.
Would you be angry?
- Wouldn't that be okay?
- Suk Jin helped your girlfriend.
I wouldn't be angry
if it was Suk Jin.
- I wouldn't be upset if it's you.
- If it's Suk Jin...
I wouldn't be angry if it's him.
- I'd be okay with it if it's you.
- Right.
There are three people here
that wouldn't make me upset.
- You wouldn't be angry.
- You, Jae Suk, and Suk Jin.
I think it depends on
who the friend is.
- Even if...
- I'd be happy if he does it for me.
Even if Suk Jin shows up topless,
I wouldn't feel anything.
That would be totally fine with me.
- Honestly, I wouldn't be upset.
- Of course.
- If it's Suk Jin...
- Right?
I wouldn't be upset
if it's Se Chan either.
I guess we've come to a conclusion.
- Yes.
- We've come to a conclusion.
- Now please...
- Shall we raise the board now?
- Each of you, decide individually.
- Each of us?
Okay. Ready. One, two, three.
- It's not okay.
- You said it was okay.
- Three.
(Everyone thinks
that it's not okay.)
(So Min and Woo Seok were convinced
in the end.)
- Why... And Woo Seok too?
- I changed my mind.
I mean,
I think that a month is too long.
- Exactly. It's too long.
- I think it's too much.
- Everyone thinks it's not okay.
- Yes.
The majority of the staff members
concluded that it was okay.
- So all of you got a point.
- Yes.
And Team Woo Seok is taking the lead
because they have four members.
- Okay.
- Good. Okay.
- I see. That's how this works.
- I'm glad she changed her mind.
We can catch up.
Now, we'll begin the second round.
You will come up with
a debatable situation...
- Should we write on the board?
- just like this.
- Oh, like that?
- I see.
It'd be helpful if you guys could
share your experiences.
Would a true story work too?
(Would a true story work too?)
- Of course.
- Do you have an idea?
A story just popped into my head.
- So Min is like a dating expert.
- Because of this,
I had a really big fight
with my ex-boyfriend.
- Tell us.
- All right.
- What happened? Tell us.
- I'll just tell you.
It happened when I was in my 20s.
One night,
my boyfriend said...
that he was hanging out
with his female friend.
- Go on.
- And...
my boyfriend didn't have a car
back then.
Was he alone with her?
- No, with a group of friends.
- I see.
Since they were going the same way,
his female friend gave him a ride.
And my boyfriend said
he would pick me up...
and drive me home on the way
because it was getting late.
So I said, "Okay."
I knew his female friend too.
I had met her once or twice,
and he'd told me about her a lot.
My boyfriend and his female friend
came to pick me up.
- He sat in the passenger seat.
- Right.
His female friend drove,
and I sat in the back seat.
I lived in Ilsan back then,
- and he lived in Sangam-dong.
- Okay.
- When we arrived at my house,
- Yes.
I expected my boyfriend
to get out of the car.
- But he didn't get out.
- I see.
- That's weird.
- Then he said...
(So Min's boyfriend said goodbye
to her while sitting in the car.)
- "So Min, go home safely."
- Yes.
- He went home in that car.
- It wouldn't have been a problem...
if he had sat in the passenger seat
on the way to his house.
- But it wasn't like that.
- Yes.
They switched the seats
so he could drive.
And his female friend...
(So Min's boyfriend suddenly moved
to the driving seat.)
- That's upsetting.
- His female friend...
- sat next to him...
- That's...
- in the passenger seat.
- That's ridiculous.
- She sat in the passenger seat.
- My gosh.
- Isn't that too weird?
- That's...
- In the passenger seat.
- That's ridiculous.
- She sat in the passenger seat.
- Are you...
- Are you sure...
- I was... Yes?
- Are you sure you two were dating?
- It's understandable.
Yes. My gosh.
I just thought...
- Of course, they were together.
- It wasn't like that.
- Maybe they were a couple, and...
- Then why didn't he drive before?
- I don't understand.
- Exactly.
- So... That's not all.
- That's...
I was so upset,
but I didn't let it show.
I wondered if I was overreacting
because they acted...
- as if it had been a normal thing.
- It's weird. I would've been upset.
I pondered on it that night,
and talked to him the next day.
- "Honestly, it made me upset."
- Right.
- "Why did you have to..."
- Of course.
- His answer must've mattered.
- "Why did you drive her car?"
Yes, I asked him why he drove.
He said that he didn't go home...
because he was going to pick up
her birthday gift for him.
He stopped by her office...
before going home to pick that up.
- I asked why he drove her car.
- Exactly.
He said, "I asked her to let me
drive because I wanted to."
- He wanted to drive her car?
- Why?
He wanted to drive her car...
- It must've been a nice car.
- Well...
- I guess so.
- That's understandable.
- That's what he said.
- That's...
- understandable.
- "Don't get the wrong idea."
"But you should've gotten out
of her car with me,"
- "and taken a bus or a taxi."
- He lived near your house.
"I understand that you went home
in her car."
"But why would you drive her car?"
- Right.
- "It made me upset."
But he couldn't understand me.
So Min, were you close
to his female friend?
No, I just heard a lot about her.
- I only saw her a couple of times.
- I don't understand his friend.
- Maybe his friend was...
- The fact that he came...
- in her car to pick you up...
- That's weird.
He should've switched the seats
after getting out of the apartment.
- If he wanted to hide it.
- No.
- No. That's not good.
- Isn't hiding it even weirder?
- That's even worse.
- That's not what I mean.
- What I'm saying is...
that even if he wanted to drive,
- Then you wouldn't have known.
- he shouldn't have done it...
- while you were watching him.
- No, that's even worse.
I usually don't feel this way,
but I think I would be upset.
- Right?
- Why?
The fact
that they switched the seats...
- would bother me for some reason.
- Of course.
Think about it.
We should all try to think
in So Min's shoes.
- Of course, it would bother me.
- Imagine how you would feel.
You thank him for giving you a ride.
Then turn around to go home,
and your girlfriend...
- switches the seats and drives.
- Exactly.
What if her male friend is Suk Jin?
- It would be okay.
- What if it's Suk Jin?
(Everything would be okay
if it were Seok Sam.)
I knew it.
Why would it be okay if it's me?
- It depends on the person.
- That hurts.
- Yes.
- What's wrong with me?
- Anything would be okay, right?
I wouldn't worry if it was him.
- I wouldn't worry.
- Why?
- It's always the subtle nuance.
- It's hard to say.
It's a gray area.
It's not an absolute dealbreaker.
Tell us something more serious.
It happened more than ten years ago,
but it still hurts.
- Really?
- Is she crying?
- She's crying.
- Don't cry.
- You should let it go.
- What? I'm not crying, Woo Seok.
- Oh, I see.
Woo Seok just...
(Woo Seok's words helped her
get over it.)
- He was her boyfriend.
- If there was something going on...
between them,
they wouldn't have picked you up.
That's exactly what he said.
- They wouldn't have picked you up.
- Right.
You see, it's strange
that people always lie...
that their opposite-sex friends are
same-sex friends to their partners.
- To prevent any trouble.
- It's pointless...
- to ask about them.
- I heard...
that they can never be friends
unless they're attracted to...
each other by more than 70 percent.
They don't keep each other around.
- It affects your friendship.
- They don't keep each other around.
- Well, that's...
- Only then,
- That's not necessarily true.
- a man and a woman can be friends.
Also, in dramas like "Propose",
the lead characters
who are best friends...
- Ryu Si Won and Kim Hee Seon...
- You watched too many dramas.
- That's not true.
- They become lovers.
- It's a drama.
- Hey.
Think about me and Song Eun I.
We've been friends for 30 years.
I believe that a man and a woman
can never be friends.
- I think it's possible.
- It's possible.
- I don't think so.
- No, it's not.
- It's possible.
- I also think...
- I think it's possible.
- I don't think it's possible.
- It's possible.
- Let's debate this.
(So they began a new debate.)
- It's possible.
- No. Let's debate this.
- Okay. This is our new topic.
- A man and a woman can be friends.
Hold on.
You should be able to take a shower
with your opposite-sex friend.
- Hey!
- What did you say?
- Why?
- Come on.
(Hold on. You should be able to
take a shower with your friend.)
(Disgusted)
- How can anyone do that?
- That's ridiculous.
If she's your friend,
you can shower with her.
That's too much.
- No, I can't do that. Come on.
- That's nonsense.
- You know I'm right.
- I agree.
You should have no interest in her
in a romantic way...
- if she's your friend.
- Still, I can't do that.
- There should be no reaction.
- If your female friend...
(Indifferent)
- Right. But...
- What?
(A common sight at a small sauna)
You know I'm right.
You should be able to do that.
- If you really are just friends.
- No.
Are you sick?
Take a break if you are.
How about this, then?
There have been
many controversies...
such as the perilla leaf debate
and the shrimp debate.
The most recent one is
your boyfriend zipping up...
- a friend's jacket on a cold day.
- A long padded jacket.
Of course that shouldn't be done.
Why would one go that far?
- Of course.
- That's crossing the line.
But what if...
someone in front of you...
was stuck?
Even so...
- What if the zipper's stuck?
- You can help in that case.
- You can help with that.
- The act itself...
is too warm.
You only do that
for your own girlfriend.
Gosh, listen up.
- Only if the girlfriend allows it.
- Let me conclude this.
- This really turns into a debate.
- Listen up.
- Over here.
- Listen up!
- I...
- Let me conclude this.
Seriously?
Why are you arguing over this?
- Over here.
- Listen up!
Here's the thing with the zipper.
- It shouldn't be done.
- Let's say that...
someone is having trouble
zipping up his or her jacket.
It's weird to
lend a hand right away.
What if that person asks?
But what if the zipper was stuck...
and even my girlfriend
is trying to help her?
And my girlfriend
couldn't help it either.
- Only then...
- Of course you can help with that.
- That scenario is okay.
- But that's an exception.
- That much is allowed.
- Of course it is.
What about this?
She's trying to zip up her jacket
and her nose is running.
"It's darn cold!"
"It's so cold."
- My girlfriend didn't see it.
- You still shouldn't.
I'm the only one who sees her...
and her nose is running.
- "It's so cold."
- No way.
- No?
- Why not?
- With the perilla leaf,
the nuance is everything.
Holding it gently...
- could be an issue.
- The perilla leaf?
No one will be able to eat it
if she can't get hers!
We're only helping her eat
so that we can as well.
- But the padded jacket...
- You're right, Jong Kook.
- She's preventing us from eating.
- He's right.
But zipping up someone's jacket...
My helping her
is for the greater good.
Who cares if she zips up
her padded jacket?
- The padded jack is not okay.
- Right.
We can't go
for second rounds of drinks...
until she zips up her jacket!
She can just wrap it around herself.
- But her nose is running!
- Like this.
Hold on a second.
Gyeong Hye, what do you think?
This is what happens
when you zip up a coat.
Watch this.
It starts from down here...
- and they end up face to face.
- Exactly.
(An unexpected eye contact)
- You're right.
- What about this, then?
- How about this?
- This.
Like this.
- Here.
- Down to up.
In that case...
Her hair can get caught...
and problems like that
will only make things awkward.
Can you pull the zipper down?
- That's weirder.
- Unzipping the jacket.
Unzipping...
Unzipping is weirder.
- Unzipping...
- Unzipping the jacket?
- No way.
- What if...
What if the zipper gets stuck?
- No way.
- Woo Seok, what do you think?
- Well...
- After you unzip it...
It's all about
not making eye contact.
- Exactly.
- That's not what matters.
- Without looking?
- Like this.
- Must you go to such lengths?
- That's weirder.
- Is it?
- Well...
- You see...
- It's like this.
This is where you stop
when zipping it up.
It shouldn't reach the stop.
- You just match the teeth for her?
- Yes, the teeth.
All you need to do
is align the teeth for her.
- That...
- That's a wise solution.
Right? All you need to do
is align the teeth for her.
- There's no need to zip it all up.
- Exactly.
She's not that important, you know.
- Then the conclusion...
- I have something to ask.
- Go ahead.
- What if...
my boyfriend...
is good friends...
- with one of my female friends.
- Right.
- Let's say that she moved.
- Okay.
Did he help him with the boxes?
- He must've hung the curtains.
- Yes, the curtains!
- Is he insane?
- Are you kidding me?
(The boyfriend hung the curtains
for her female friend.)
Gyeong Hye, that's insane!
What if this happened?
(He shows his soft belly.)
This is more than okay.
- Just a second.
- This is okay.
(His squishy belly
gets him the okay sign.)
- It's okay as long as it's you.
- Hold on.
- You're fine.
- There's no issue with you.
- You're good to go.
- Wasn't that charming though?
- You're good.
- It's okay if that guy is you.
- As long as it's me?
- I heard...
that women find men charming
when they help with such things.
- But...
- Call a handyman over instead.
- That's just wrong.
- Of course.
Hanging my own curtains
is a nuisance.
Exactly.
I can hang the curtains
for my girlfriend,
but for my girlfriend's friend?
That's absurd.
What if that boyfriend...
is the crafty type?
I'd allow it in that case.
- If he's a professional handyman?
- Yes.
He should at least
tell his girlfriend though.
- As long as he's paid.
- Right.
When he leaves...
(As long as he's paid)
- As long as he's paid.
- "That'll be 120 dollars."
- Then that's more than okay.
- "Is it 100 dollars?"
(It's fine if he gets paid for it.)
- Good.
- That's fine.
- But...
- Nicely said.
A professional handyman.
What should we vote for first?
- The curtain debate?
- Yes, the curtain.
- Let's vote first.
- The curtain debate.
- Yes, the curtain.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Not okay!
- It's not okay.
- No way.
- Not okay.
- It's just weird.
- What about the driving debate?
- I need a conclusion.
- The driving?
Can we end this?
I'm too exhausted to continue.
- I mean...
- All right!
Only speak if you've been
in a relationship before.
Then sit. Marriage...
That came out wrong.
- Then...
- I meant, conclusion.
Can you be friends
with someone of the opposite gender?
- What?
- Friends of the opposite gender.
It's a fundamental question.
- Is it possible or not?
- Possible or not?
Of course it is.
Hold on a second.
What have we been doing so far?
Just hurry up with it.
- Let's get this over with.
- The friend thing.
- Can you be friends or not?
- Yes or no?
- Can you be friends?
- I think you can.
In 1, 2, 3.
- No way.
- Yes, you can.
- Are you serious?
- Yes, you can be friends.
Two, three.
- No way.
- Yes, you can.
- Yes, you can be friends.
- Are you serious?
Let's hear from the staff next.
- Of course.
- You're okay with it?
Of course it's okay.
That concludes your first game.
In first place is Team Woo Seok.
- Us?
- Really?
- They have more on their team.
- Exactly.
In second place is Team Gyeong Hye.
(2nd place: Team Gyeong Hye)
And in third place is Team Woo Jae.
(3rd place: Team Woo Jae)
Why do I finish last
every time I'm on the show?
What's wrong with me?
Shall we get started?
The winning team may select seven.
- Seven?
- Really?
- We should pick the others.
- The cream bun.
(Team Woo Seok)
- Sominmon.
- Another Sominmon?
- Yes, a Sominmon.
- Do we already have one?
- Yes, from earlier.
(Team Woo Seok)
I have the Hahamon sticker.
And I have Jihyomon.
Your exterior is all rocks.
Check it out.
- Rocks.
- Rocks?
Woo Seok, did you open yours?
- Not yet.
- Am I a rock golem?
- We need what we don't have.
- Another Jaeseokmon.
You should keep this for now.
- And the Sominmon.
- I have Woojaemon.
- We don't have that.
- What about Jongkookmon?
- We don't have that either.
- We don't have it.
And Hahamon? Hey, we're almost done.
- I think we have them all.
- We have seven.
Isn't this something we don't have?
Wooseokmon, Jongkookmon,
Seokjinmon, Hahamon,
Jihyomon, and Sominmon.
(Team Woo Jae)
Darn it. We have another Woojaemon.
But this will be of help.
- Why are there so many of them?
- It'll be of help.
It's another Woojaemon.
(This team is also frustrated
by Woojaemon.)
Woojaemon, Jaeseokmon, Sominmon.
- We don't have it.
- Jaeseokmon.
We don't have Sechanmon.
You'll now relocate,
play another game,
and also have lunch.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
This bun's quite good.
Let's go.
- Do we sit with our team?
- Yes, please.
So Min should sit with him.
It's fine, Jong Kook.
- You're over here.
- Sit there.
- Do we have designated seats?
- How natural did that seem?
They only sat in the order
they got on the bus.
(So Min sits next to Woo Seok
thanks to the cheeky matchmakers.)
It's only a coincidence.
Cheeky, aren't you?
- Put your seatbelt on.
- Now, I'm the one uncomfortable.
I thought you were
helping me with it.
Here I am sitting next to them.
- This?
- I thought you were helping.
- This goes over there.
- It startled me, you see.
- Are you doing it for me?
- No, this one's mine.
- Se Chan's not that considerate.
- I was just doing mine,
but she thought I was doing hers.
This calls for a debate too.
Yes, the belt debate.
What about this, then?
A female friend of mine
is sitting next to my boyfriend...
and he did this
after hitting the breaks.
- That?
- Goodness.
The arm shouldn't shoot out.
Maybe only this much.
How about this?
Like this. Just with the elbows.
Wouldn't this be allowed?
Yes, that's fine.
Isn't that okay?
This is more than okay.
- This is perfectly fine.
- Right?
The debate won't end.
- Here's a good one.
- What is it?
- His friend...
- It happened for real.
A good friend of mine...
did this for my ex-girlfriend...
and my fist shot out.
Did you actually punch him?
No, more like this.
- Like this?
- Even if it was for fun...
He should've
mentioned it to you instead.
- "There's something on her."
- He could've told her directly.
"You have something on here."
- Of course.
- There are some people...
who act before thinking.
- But it's none of your business.
- Woo Jae,
- that...
- You must be sick again.
Face the front, will you?
It's an eyesore.
(He passes out
from the harsh words.)
- It's an eyesore.
- Why do it for her?
CPR is allowed, right?
- It's a crisis.
- When the boyfriend is there?
Not you though.
It's a no for smokers.
- Of course.
- Would you allow it though?
You'll faint while performing CPR.
The one receiving it
might be against it.
So Min's never been the one
to sit in the corner.
You're not as talkative
as you usually are.
It's to flirt with Woo Seok,
of course.
- So Min...
- So that's where you are!
She hasn't sat behind me in a while.
- But...
- Yes?
You don't seem
like the older woman though.
- Woo Jae seems jealous.
- Me?
- Even Se Chan gets chosen more.
- Right.
I'm way more charming than he is.
- Back in the day...
- Yes, on "Love Me Actually."
Woo Jae's great,
but he's not exactly charming.
Yes, there's nothing
special about him.
- That's his problem.
- Exactly.
- That's harsh.
- How can we interpret this?
- You're great as a friend, but...
- He's very approachable.
- Yes, he's approachable.
- However...
It's why people like us adore him.
- We love you, you know.
- Right.
It's why we adore you.
If I were a woman,
I wouldn't date you.
I've been up against him, remember?
When?
He isn't charming at all.
I know for sure.
I'll beat him every time.
- He lost to Se Chan.
- That's right.
- He was crushed.
- Is the air conditioner on?
Switch it off.
It'll only make you sicker.
Calcium is what you need right now.
You need calcium.
Can we get a blanket for him?
- But Woo Jae...
- He needs one.
Just so you know,
Se Chan is super charming.
- Se Chan is...
- Se Chan is super charming.
Really? How so?
- Se Chan's eyes are really pretty.
- It's my first time seeing him.
- With a mask on, he's...
- Oh, gosh!
She was so startled.
- Se Chan's eyes are really pretty.
- It's my first time seeing him.
- With a mask on, he's...
- Oh, gosh!
(His face made her jump.)
- She was so startled.
- Se Chan was looking at her...
- like this when she turned.
- I know.
- Gyeong Hye.
- What's wrong, Gyeong Hye?
I'm the shy type, that's why.
- I'm the shy type.
- His eyes are really pretty.
And he's really sweet.
So Min really likes Se Chan.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Then why don't you date him?
- We've been on the same show.
- So I know what his charms are.
- What are they?
Women approach him very easily,
and they're at ease.
But it turns out...
- But he's mean?
- But he's manly?
that he's different
from the image they know him of.
You can't let your guard down.
That's what they fall for.
Once they fall for his charms,
there's no turning back?
There's no turning back.
- Right. He doesn't allow it.
- That's right.
Let me tell you what it is.
Se Chan has limits too.
He can't cut them off.
- Got it?
- That's exactly right.
- I do have limits.
- You do.
There are limits
he just can't overcome.
Woo Seok, what's your MBTI type?
- What was mine again?
- It's ESFJ.
- Yours?
- No, Woo Seok's.
- He's ESFJ?
- You know his MBTI type too?
- You remember that?
- He's very caring.
What's yours, Woo Jae?
Mine is ISTP.
Yours is ISTJ, right?
I'm not sure. I tried it once,
and the result was the same as his.
No, you and I got the same result.
- What's yours?
- Where did I...
Mine is INFJ.
- INFJ?
- We got the same result.
- What was mine again?
Can you please listen to Ji Hyo?
- Ji Hyo said you got the same one.
- Ours is the same.
- I know that. It's not like...
- Do I...
Do I have to remember
these things too?
That's not it.
(Do I have to remember
these things too?)
That's not it.
It's not that.
Ji Hyo is making a character...
- for herself now.
- I can't remember!
(Ji Hyo has been enjoying
playing couples...)
(since the pepper incident.)
I can't remember.
- That was sudden.
- I should get it tested.
- I'm a fan of that couple.
- I should try it.
- Right?
- That couple.
You can be their fan because
they're not a real couple.
- It's for the show.
- They have the possibility though.
- That's right.
- With So Min and Se Chan,
no one thinks they can become
a real couple.
No, they have their own storyline
that they still have a chance...
- to become a couple.
- That's right.
Is that an objective view?
- Of course.
- I see.
Why are your eyes so scary?
- I was just looking at you.
- He seems so flustered.
- Is that so?
- You pick on Woo Jae a lot.
- That's not true.
- He likes Woo Jae.
- That's because he likes him.
Because he reminds me...
- of the tall guy we used to have.
- It's been long, so...
- The tall guy?
- It's been a while since...
He likes tall guys.
I like him.
I like guys who are clumsy.
This is what I think.
I think it'd be better...
if you don't hope
for Jong Kook and Ji Hyo...
to become a real couple.
But you never know.
They could be dating right now.
- But Jong Kook...
- Come on!
- I told you.
- If they're actually dating,
we can't tease them like this.
I'll buy them a big-screen TV
and a fridge if they get married.
- Come on.
- I'm sorry,
but just don't come to the wedding.
- He won't invite Suk Jin.
- Just in case...
- I'm rooting for you two.
- Even if you don't invite him,
he'll go to your wedding.
(Even if you don't invite him,
he'll go to your wedding.)
(Attendee of every event,
he tried going to Son Ye Jin's wedding.)
He attends every event.
When did I become that?
Dear viewers,
don't be too surprised...
even when Suk Jin
attends one of your family events.
- It's in trend.
- It's just that...
- he likes attending events.
- That's right.
- He likes to attend events.
- He loves to party.
The next mission is familiar
to the members of Running Man.
It's a game where you can win
if you come up with a good strategy.
It's Strategic Floating Mat Battle
with Bread at Stake.
You'll start on your team's mat.
The scores will be given
in the order of teams...
that survived the longest.
So the team that falls in the water
first gets one point,
the 2nd team gets 2 points,
and the winner gets 3 points.
There will be four rounds in total.
There will be 1 round of 1-1-1,
2 rounds of 2-2-2,
and 3 rounds of 3-3-3.
But Jong Kook's team is too strong.
Let's just win second place.
I'll tell you the first players
for the 1-1-1 game.
It's Se Chan versus Woo Seok
versus Woo Jae.
(Woo Jae versus Woo Seok
versus Se Chan)
Let's go!
(Jumping)
- Let's go!
- You can do it!
- I think our team will lose.
Woo Jae, show us your jump again.
(The mantis shows off his jump.)
- That's so cool.
- Woo Seok, try jumping too.
- This?
(Woo Seok also shows off
his long legs.)
- He's good.
- He's so light.
They look cooler
because they have long legs.
- They jump so well.
- Woo Jae is exhausted.
- Se Chan, you should try it too.
- They're both so tall.
- He's exhausted.
- To be standing...
between these two...
(The little kid from Dongducheon
is going up against the tall guys.)
All right. Let's give it a shot.
Oh, no. They must be really nervous.
So this is how it feels.
Everyone, the long-awaited
1-1-1 game will start now.
Let's go!
Woo Jae! It won't kill you!
- Gosh, Woo Jae.
- Hey!
- Hey, that's enough!
- That's not it.
- Stop it already.
- It won't kill you!
- You'll run out of energy.
- I wanted to act like...
I was working hard.
Gosh, seriously.
Woo Seok!
- Show them.
- Don't make a move hastily.
I'll watch them first.
Use every move you can.
Se Chan, let's go!
(Unlike the two,
Ssaebssaeb is experienced.)
Gosh, that squid.
Get ready.
- Se Chan, you look especially...
- It's going to be fun.
You stand out so much.
- I'm the visual member here.
- Yes, you are.
You stand out the most.
I'm going to play
really dirty today. Watch me.
Bo Pil, I'm going to beat them up
to a pulp.
Get ready.
(The game starts.)
- All right.
- What's with his body proportion?
Se Chan is really strong.
I'll go to you.
- I'll go to you.
- No, you have to be careful.
You might fall while trying to
go over to another mat.
- Think carefully when you do.
- Woo Jae.
Don't fall in vain.
While trying to jump over...
- That's threatening.
- Look at Se Chan.
Se Chan is the target.
Look how Woo Jae is acting up.
Here comes the mantis.
Don't bully me!
Don't bully me, you guys!
What? Look at these guys.
You need to be strong to play this,
but you need to use the mat well.
- It's all about timing.
- Of course.
- It doesn't move forward.
- It will.
Then come to me.
- Woo Seok, you should row it.
- Right. You should do that.
- Row it.
- Okay.
It'll move if you row it.
You should row on this side.
- You should row on this side.
- What are you doing?
If you row from there,
it'll come to this side.
- Yes, that's how you should do it.
- Woo Seok, you might get attacked.
Woo Jae might suddenly
pull your hand or something.
If he does, I'll push him off.
Only Se Chan is far away
from the two. How strange.
I know. What's wrong with you?
- Oh, they joined forces.
- Come at me.
We can't beat Se Chan 1-on-1.
- Then let's really go on his mat.
- Okay, let's.
(Se Chan with strong bones
is their common enemy.)
It's moving.
You'll use up all your strength.
Look at Woo Jae.
Woo Jae will use up
all his strength.
Woo Jae, you might use
all your strength.
- They got it.
- They went pretty far.
(Se Chan is cornered.)
- Se Chan is cornered!
- They went far.
- Se Chan, you're not cornered.
- I'm good.
Woo Seok, let's just
jump onto his mat.
- You have to go quickly.
- Okay.
Great. That's great, Se Chan.
Where are you going?
(Only Woo Jae ends up
going toward Se Chan's mat.)
They got it. They're 1-on-1 now.
- Where are you going?
- Go! Attack him!
(Se Chan went over
to Woo Jae's mat.)
He went over.
Woo Seok will...
(He tries to escape but fails.)
(Go away!)
- All right.
We have one man down.
- You fool.
- It went as we all expected.
Oh, no...
(The end of Pushover Joo
had no twist.)
- You fool.
- Woo Jae, please move.
Thank you, Woo Jae!
That little...
- Woo Jae!
- What's wrong with him?
- My gosh, that guy...
- He didn't even get to attack.
What did he just do?
I have no idea!
- Push him.
- What were you thinking?
- Hey.
- Time to show how good you are.
You'll be punished for this.
- Woo Seok!
- It's 1-on-1.
Time to show how good you are.
Woo Seok, you just have to
fight him head-on.
There's no other way.
- Come at me.
- Woo Jae, push their mats.
That's it. That's enough.
- They're going at each other.
- Attack.
- Great. Go!
- He came over.
That's it.
Grab him!
Oh, no!
Be careful, Woo Seok!
Woo Seok! Be careful!
(Se Chan fails to read the room
and does his best to win.)
He's trying so hard to win.
Woo Seok works out every day.
Oh, really?
Woo Seok won't lose to him.
My gosh.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- My gosh!
- He's so strong!
- Woo Seok won't lose to him.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- Se Chan is so harsh.
(Se Chan got Woo Seok!)
Se Chan is so harsh.
(Surprised)
(Throwing)
He's so harsh.
(Squid with
superhuman strength wins.)
(Shouting)
That was...
Woo Seok!
Are knee strikes allowed?
- Are they allowed?
- Sorry.
He got hit by Se Chan's knee!
Se Chan hit Woo Seok with his knee.
- He got hit by Se Chan's knee!
- He hit Woo Seok with his knee.
How dare you
strike him with your knee?
Why that little...
I think it's better...
that I got eliminated early
than to be out pathetically.
- You looked most pathetic.
Is that so?
- You were so good.
- Did you hear So Min though?
It was like he was
cheering for her boyfriend.
She went, "Se Chan is so harsh!"
You can't kick his face
with your knee!
- Are knee strikes allowed?
- How dare you?
- Good job!
- It's all right.
- They won the first round.
- Let's go.
- Is it our turn?
- Let's go!
I'll give you another chance.
Don't you get eliminated again.
- Those two are playing?
- Woo Jae is playing? Great!
I have a shot at winning with them.
(Laughing out of embarrassment)
(Doing slapstick comedy
all by herself)
I just...
(Startled)
(Her friend joins in
for slapstick comedy.)
I can't stand up.
Be careful.
- Oh, no!
- Hey.
- Be careful.
- We have a chance at winning!
Let's go!
I am Jong Kook here.
Be careful, So Min.
(Bring it on!)
What are you, the Avengers?
You can beat them
once you get on their mat.
(The members of Group 2
are all playful.)
So Min has no will to win.
She's just there to make it funny.
Go!
How should we play this?
Why are you putting on airs?
He got it.
Woo Jae is good at rowing!
(Woo Jae finally found his talent.)
He's Row Woo Jae.
Because his arms are long...
Woo Jae can row!
- Row Woo Jae.
- Come here.
- Go over!
- Woo Jae, go over on their mat.
- Just go already.
- Where should we go to?
(Right then, Seok Sam's
expression changes.)
- Let's attack them!
- You went over already?
Why did you go over?
Why did he go over on their mat?
Go over on their mat, So Min!
So Min, you must go over
on that mat!
Get So Min!
(Haha attacks So Min
while So Min is hesitating.)
So Min! Come over!
- So Min is out.
- Oh, no!
So Min is out.
Gosh, those two...
Haha, help me!
- I'm coming.
- You need to go over.
(Gyeong Hye joins
the battlefield as well.)
Hey, push the mat to me!
(Ji Hyo and Suk Jin
are eliminated.)
All right.
Ji Hyo, you're out.
Woo Jae! Give it a try.
You can do it!
- Play fair!
- Take his pants off.
- Woo Jae.
I'm so sorry, Woo Jae!
(Floundering)
Woo Jae!
- Woo Jae!
- What's with Woo Jae?
(Woo Jae gets eliminated
after floundering pitifully.)
At least we won second place,
Woo Jae.
(Gyeong Hye, the dark horse,
eliminated 3 players on her own.)
We won second place, Woo Jae.
- We won second place?
- We did.
- Who is playing next?
- The next 2-2-2 match.
Let's start right away.
Please get ready.
I think we should win the next one.
(Panting)
Hey! Seaweed, hurry over.
- What is it?
- You're playing next.
- You're playing with me.
- Again?
- Woo Jae is playing again?
Won't he take a break?
(A 2-2-2 match)
- We should get rid of them first.
- Okay.
- We'll drag you down with you.
- We'll drag you down.
We'll drag down
the ones who attack us first.
Okay.
- They're our target.
- Hey, Jae Suk.
We must win this time.
- We must get rid of them first.
- We must win this time.
- Jong Kook, give us a chance.
- Of course.
- So you can attack them?
- Yes.
- That's not allowed.
- Let's fight 1-on-1.
We must get rid of them first.
(Confessing all of a sudden)
- I've always been your fan.
- Hey.
- I'm serious.
- Why would you say that now?
- Well...
- We've been here for so long.
- He's...
- I didn't have a chance to tell.
He's from Anyang.
- You're from Anyang?
- Jong Kook, I'm from Anyang.
(Jong Kook, I'm from Anyang.)
- Why would you share that now?
- That's right!
- I didn't have a chance to tell.
- Where in Anyang?
- Are you really from Anyang?
- No, I'm from Ilsan.
What are you doing?
(Meanwhile, the seaweed passed out
on the mat.)
Give us a chance to attack them.
- So you're from Anyang?
- Yes.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
- What are you doing?
- Come at us.
(Approaching)
(Se Chan ends up
making a move first.)
I'll push you down right away.
Why that little...
Why is he doing the leg dance?
What's with him?
(Doing the leg dance)
Your pants might fall.
Be careful, Woo Jae.
- Come at us.
- This is so fun!
- Let's do it.
- Come on over.
Come at us!
Let's jump over.
- Bring it on!
- Let's jump over.
There are waves, so... Oh, gosh.
Look at Woo Jae! He's...
There are waves, so...
(Whoosh)
(Row Woo Jae is here again.)
- He's rowing again.
- My gosh.
He rows so well!
- Row Woo Jae!
- I thought you had a motor on.
This is so nerve-racking.
We'll get really high viewer
ratings this week, don't you think?
This week's viewer ratings
will be soaring.
A battle between men.
Those chickens.
(Shouting)
(Shouting back)
(Glancing)
(Shouting)
(Darn it.)
- Darn it.
- No!
- Gosh, that stings.
- Nice!
What was that?
- Jae Suk...
- Hold on.
- It was a mistake.
- No, you're out.
- You're out.
- It was a mistake.
- No. Hey!
- You're out.
- I was just playing around.
- That was...
- You can't play around!
- I was just playing around.
- But it was funny.
- I made a mistake.
- But you slipped.
- He's out.
But I was just playing around.
- It was so funny though.
- It was a funny scene.
I'm so sorry. I just played around.
I made a mistake.
Then you should just
get a water slap.
- Okay, I'll take that.
- Give him a water slap.
- Get a water slap.
- Okay.
- I'll do it.
- All right. I'll get a water slap.
- Come here.
- Everyone.
I was just playing around.
- We'll go to you.
- It's a water slap.
- Okay.
- Let's splash water on him.
- All right.
- Let's do it.
- Here it comes. In 1, 2.
- A water slap.
- Three.
(Splash, slapping)
- A water slap!
- That's right.
- Water.
- Slap.
- Boombastic!
- Okay.
Okay, fine.
- We can do this.
I'm sorry about that.
- We have to go.
- Oh, gosh.
(He falls into the water again.)
- Come on, Jae Suk.
- No, that doesn't count.
What do you mean?
- It doesn't count.
- What was that?
- That was...
- It doesn't count.
What do you mean?
(No!)
- It doesn't count.
- He was clearly out.
How many times will you
fall into the water?
- We weren't playing.
- What was that?
- You're out.
- We weren't playing.
I was just playing around.
- I was just playing around.
- Come on.
- He didn't say we could begin.
- Get a water slap from Jong Kook.
- Get a water slap from Woo Jae.
- From Jong Kook?
I'll get a water slap
from Jong Kook.
I was just playing around.
He's so playful.
You know how excited I get
when I see water.
- A water slap.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They just slapped him twice.)
- All right!
- All right.
- There will be no more exceptions.
- No more.
I won't play around anymore.
He's so playful.
Why are you so playful today?
- You're not even good at it.
- He's so excited.
- I'm just so excited to see water.
- All right.
We got them.
(The race starts again
with Se Chan's attack.)
Haha, you must come over!
Haha!
(His cowardly brother
pretends not to have seen him.)
Haha, you must come over!
He's out.
- He's out.
- What was that, Haha?
It was too far.
Can you come over first?
- Jong Kook, I'll help you.
- Come here.
- I'll help you. Give me a chance.
Take me as your hostage.
- How will he throw Haha?
- You can do it!
Haha!
(The little martial artist
holds out against the tiger.)
(Grunting)
That's it.
- The power of a dad.
- I can't tell who's going to win.
The challenge of a dad!
Jong Kook is smiling!
- He's having fun. He's enjoying it.
- He's enjoying the game.
- No!
- Look at Haha's muffin top.
- Hey.
- Look at his muffin top.
No!
Look at his muffin top.
- Okay!
- Hey.
No!
(A flip-over)
(Darn it!)
(He can feel pain in that area.)
- Well done.
- Haha.
- We got this.
- Look at Woo Jae.
(Team Woo Seok approaches
Row Woo Jae.)
Attack the only man standing!
Go! Go over!
Woo Jae.
(They try to attack Woo Jae
who's all by himself.)
- Woo Jae!
- Go over!
They're on. Okay, push them now!
Push them off!
Wait.
Push him.
Jong Kook can't go over.
- Push him.
- This won't work! Darn it!
(This won't work! Darn it!)
(Splash)
Nice. We did it.
He missed it.
(He gets eliminated
in an absurd way.)
Did you see how short
Jong Kook's legs were?
We won!
Wait!
(Pushover Joo is
left all alone again.)
- Wait!
- We did it.
Please let me stand.
- Let me stand, at least.
- No can do.
- Please let me just stand up.
- No.
(The floundering seaweed
gets eliminated.)
- We did it.
- All right.
Woo Seok and Jae Suk win.
- We did it.
- We won.
You have short legs
It's the long-awaited 3-3-3 game.
- It's the 3-3-3 game.
- All right.
Woo Jae.
(Woo Jae.)
You must play.
- Woo Jae!
- Come on up here!
- Woo Jae! Your pants fell off.
- He didn't take a single break.
Woo Jae needs to keep playing.
- What? Why?
- Your pants fell off.
Oh, gosh. Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Everyone! Woo Jae's pants fell off,
but he doesn't know!
It's okay.
The final winning team
is Team Woo Jae.
(Team Woo Jae wins 1st place.)
The team in second place...
Oh, right.
There's a second-place winner.
It's Team Gyeong Hye.
Team Woo Seok is in third place.
- What's the penalty?
- You'll choose your bread now.
We don't know what the penalty is.
The 1st-place team
will pick 7 pieces of bread.
The 2nd-place team will pick 5,
- and 3rd place will pick 3.
- We'll pick 3?
We need Suk Jin's sticker and mine.
Oh, please...
(Team Gyeong Hye)
It's Jihyomon.
- What? Do we have her sticker?
- We do.
We don't have your sticker
and Gyeong Hye's sticker.
- It's your sticker!
- We got it!
This is great.
(Team Gyeong Hye)
- Please.
- It's my sticker!
- All right!
It's Sominmon again. We got enough.
All right.
(Team Woo Seok)
Which stickers do we need?
- It's what we don't have.
- We got Wooseokmon.
- We got you.
- It's you.
- We got it.
- This one is Wooseokmon too.
- Okay.
- It's you again.
- It's me again.
- We are getting multiple stickers.
We need to stop getting it.
- We don't have you.
- We need Seokjinmon and Sechanmon.
- Which stickers do we need?
- What?
Which stickers do we need?
We only got Woojaemon.
(They only got two Woojaemons.)
- Aren't there too many Woojaemons?
- Seriously.
It's like a dud.
- How many did you add?
- We didn't do that.
It's Seokjinmon.
- Hey.
- Okay.
- Seokjinmon.
- All right.
The next mission will give you
the last chance to catch...
the missing monsters for Runningdex.
It's the One Last Punch.
Stickers are hidden
throughout the broadcasting station.
You simply need to find them
and complete the Runningdex.
The race ends
as soon as a team completes it.
- I see.
- We need two more.
- You have overlapping stickers.
- Yes.
You can use those stickers
to purchase elimination tickets...
- to eliminate other members.
- How many?
(You need elimination tickets
to take off the name tag.)
You can use overlapping stickers
to purchase elimination tickets.
However, the price is different
for each member...
and it will be decided
by other teams.
Let me give you an example.
The total price
for each team is 12 stickers.
Let's say Jong Kook decides
that it will be one for Gyeong Hye,
one for Haha, and ten for Se Chan.
Once he makes that decision,
Se Chan needs ten stickers
to purchase an elimination ticket.
(Decide on the price
for each member!)
Understood? Decide on the price
within the total of 12 stickers.
That's what we need to purchase
an elimination ticket.
If you eliminate a member
who was carrying a Runningdex,
you can take off one sticker
you want.
(You can take off one sticker
you want.)
You can't take it.
You can simply eliminate it.
Now, each team will move...
and decide on
the elimination ticket price.
Team Jong Kook will decide on
Team Jae Suk's prices.
Team Jae Suk will decide on
this team's prices.
- Then this team will decide on...
- Team Jong Kook's prices?
The total price is 12 stickers.
Let's make Se Chan pay 12 stickers.
- No, that's the total.
- That's the total.
Why don't we make it
seven for Se Chan,
four for Haha,
and one for Gyeong Hye?
- Shall we do that?
- Let's do that.
Four for me, seven for you,
- and one for Gyeong Hye.
- Seven?
- It will be hard for me.
- We will need to help Gyeong Hye.
You should take these stickers
so that you can eliminate someone.
- Me?
- Of course.
You just need four stickers.
I will hold on to 1 sticker.
I will collect 6 more stickers...
so that I can eliminate someone.
Runningdex is what's important.
Who should carry it?
Gyeong Hye should.
- Me? What if I get eliminated?
- What if she gets eliminated?
Should I protect it?
What do you think?
Wouldn't that be better?
- Me?
- What?
(Did you just say
that you will protect me?)
- I am not sure.
- Haha.
Did you hear what she said?
Upon hearing my words,
she asked me if I would protect her.
I will protect the Runningdex.
- What are you talking about?
Gyeong Hye,
I will protect the Runningdex.
Didn't you see us earlier?
- We ditched you earlier.
- We have a business relationship.
You should carry it.
- You should carry it.
- I will carry it.
I will run away well.
- Okay.
- All right.
We should make Jong Kook pay
the most.
Let's go with 10 for Jong Kook
and 1 for the rest.
- That isn't surprising at all.
- They are too much.
- There is no twist whatsoever.
That's no fun.
We need Haha's, mine, and So Min's.
- Three.
- We just need three more.
- Haha, Ji Hyo, So Min.
- Ji Hyo, So Min, Haha.
Ji Hyo, So Min, Haha.
We could lose a sticker,
so...
It's okay to lose Woojaemon
like crazy.
I have four more.
Woojaemon, the mantis...
You should look for the stickers...
we can use to purchase
an elimination ticket.
- So we will look for the stickers.
- Let's make it obvious.
I will run.
You should keep running.
We can get eliminated like crazy.
One thing is certain.
You need my help.
(You need my help.)
- Sure.
- My help.
- You said that earlier too.
- Ji Hyo.
This isn't a laughing matter.
- I can do this.
- Sure.
You have long arms.
I have a long reach.
Come here. You have long arms.
But your long arms are useless
when you can't move.
Don't you agree?
Woo Jae used up his strength.
Woo Jae, your long arms are useless.
This won't do.
- He is my team, right?
- Yes.
- That's good.
- Your long arms are useless.
- I can attack suddenly like this.
- Right.
I could have ripped off
the name tag.
I would have succeeded
had I moved a bit more.
Let's make it 1 for So Min
and 3 for the rest.
The same price
for Jae Suk and Woo Seok.
- So 4, 4, 3, and 1.
- Let's do that.
Why is my price one sticker?
How come Suk Jin's price is
three stickers?
- They are serious about this.
- They think I am strong.
How come Suk Jin's price is
three stickers?
I watched Woo Seok play games.
He doesn't have much strength.
You are pretty clumsy.
You need know-how
for Name Tag Elimination.
Can I try ripping off the name tag?
- Rip it off.
Don't do it so shyly.
You need to do it roughly.
- I will do it roughly.
- Why don't we have a face-off?
- Go ahead.
- Go ahead. Have a 1-on-1 match.
- Put down your bag.
- Let's try it.
What if I win?
- Then you win.
- You should win.
Go.
- Hold on.
- Come on.
- You need skills.
- Yes. You need skills.
- See?
- See, Woo Seok?
- He has no skills.
- Listen.
Listen, Woo Seok.
- Listen to me.
- But...
- What are you doing?
- I will show you how it's done.
- It ripped.
When you meet an opponent,
- do this.
- Do you grab the clothes?
- No. Don't grab the clothes.
- I have beaten other people.
With one hand, push the shoulder.
Actually, you shouldn't push it.
Pull it.
- I see.
- Then rip off the name tag.
Have you done that before?
(Incredulous)
(She got caught teaching a skill
she has never used.)
- You don't have time for that.
- Stand strong.
Woo Seok,
you don't have time for that.
- Stand strong.
- Here.
Just grab the person
and rip it off right away.
- Okay. Stand strong.
- Stand strong.
- Pull.
Have you done that before?
- Okay.
- Okay?
Woo Seok, weren't you
a bit surprised?
Yes, a bit.
- It's harder than it seems.
- It's just that...
- my body is still tense.
- That's right.
We have done this for over 12 years.
You got pulled over very easily.
Suk Jin, stop it.
Give it a rest.
- It's not like that.
- Do you think you are better?
- For goodness' sake.
- Woo Seok.
- Jae Suk, he is enjoying himself.
- Why are you so weak?
- Seriously.
- You got pulled over very easily.
He hasn't done this in a while.
I will take on Woo Jae.
- Okay.
- I will take on Woo Jae.
- Can I try again?
- Okay.
Grab this part.
- Then the top...
- The name tag comes closer to you.
You can do that.
Grab the shoulder first.
- Okay. Then I pull.
- Grab the shoulder first.
There you go.
- I get it now.
- You get it now, right?
Here she comes.
(He practices with So Min too.)
You got it now, right?
- Ripping it off gives me thrills.
- It does, right?
I haven't had that experience once
in the past five years.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I haven't had it.
- You have that experience today.
- Okay.
- I will help you.
- Hurry up and buy it.
- I will buy an elimination ticket.
- Me too.
- Buy So Min one.
I will take out
the person I run into.
(Haha purchases
an elimination ticket.)
It hurts my pride that my price is
four stickers. Okay.
I will eliminate someone.
- The race will begin.
- Let's go.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
The race starts.
Let's go.
(The first team to complete
the Runningdex will win!)
I need to find the stickers.
(Team Woo Seok needs to find
2 more stickers...)
I need to find
as many stickers as possible.
(to complete the Runningdex.)
(Woo Seok looks very excited.)
How far can we go?
Are we using the entire building?
(Woo Seok navigates the building
with his long legs.)
I found one.
(He found a Runningmon sticker.)
Already?
Who is it? Open it.
If it's a new one, we can't use it
to purchase an elimination ticket.
- We don't have it. It's new.
- Don't we have Sechanmon?
Make sure
no one rips off your name tag.
Then they will take away a sticker.
- They will take away a sticker.
- Yes. That will happen.
- Sechanmon.
- Sechanmon. Then we just need...
- Seokjinmon.
- Right.
- I found a sticker.
- Did you?
I found a sticker.
It was a new sticker,
- so we just need one more.
- Really?
- We just need Seokjinmon.
- Okay.
That's good.
They might be hiding.
We just need one more.
We just need your sticker.
- Really?
- Will the race end if we find it?
Yes. It will end.
What? It's Haha.
- Haha is over there.
- Jae Suk.
- What?
- Did you find something?
No.
(On guard)
Who can rip off name tags?
- You?
- It's obvious.
Haha can rip off name tags, right?
I bet Haha can rip off name tags.
(They don't know
who has an elimination ticket.)
My price is one sticker, so...
- What?
- Come here.
My price is one sticker.
It put me in a good mood.
- We should look for more stickers.
- You are right.
There is no need for a scuffle.
What? Ji Hyo,
what are you doing here?
(They find Ji Hyo
who is by herself.)
- I am looking for stickers.
- Let's take off your name tag.
- Come on.
- Give me that.
Give me that.
- Hold on. All right.
Will you give it to us
or get eliminated?
I will give it to you.
- Give it to us.
- Get lost.
How dare you...
(Ripping off)
Woo Seok, sorry.
(Woo Seok's name tag
gets ripped off instantly.)
Woo Seok, sorry.
- Woo Seok is out.
- She ripped it off.
- Just like that?
I will purchase one.
(Gyeong Hye purchased
an elimination ticket.)
(When they were having a standoff,
she waited quietly behind Haha.)
Ji Hyo.
(When their attention was
on Ji Hyo,)
(she came out
and looked for a chance.)
Now is my chance.
Will you give it to us
or get eliminated?
(Woo Seok had his back turned.)
(She ripped off his sticker
right away.)
Woo Seok, sorry.
- Woo Seok is out.
- She ripped it off.
- Just like that?
I can't believe it.
- Hey.
- I can't believe it.
Woo Seok.
- Gyeong Hye, you are good.
- You are really good.
I ripped it off too early on, didn't I?
- It's okay.
- Don't worry about that.
- I am sorry.
- Woo Seok, you practiced so hard.
Why didn't you notice Gyeong Hye?
You should have ripped off
a Running Man member's name tag.
This is driving me crazy.
(Woo Seok got eliminated
in 1 minute and 38 seconds.)
(He took after his teacher, Suk Jin,
and got eliminated early on.)
Let's remove a sticker.
- Will he get screen time in prison?
- No.
No? Oh, no.
- Woo Seok.
- You eliminated a guest.
Good job, Gyeong Hye.
- Good job.
- The strap broke.
She becomes really competitive.
(When it comes to a match,
she disregards the friendship.)
Hold on. I feel so bad.
What is he going to do?
He was carrying the Runningdex.
You can take off one sticker.
Were you carrying the Runningdex?
- This is so annoying.
- One sticker.
- Oh, no.
- Take it off.
- Gyeong Hye, what have you done?
- We will take off Sechanmon.
You eliminated
Woo Seok's screen time.
- This is driving me crazy.
- What am I going to do?
Viewers must be watching
in order to see Woo Seok.
- What am I going to do?
- One of them will carry it, right?
(Gyeong Hye still feels bad.)
What have I done?
For goodness' sake.
I will get going now.
At prison...
Good luck.
All right.
(He feels disappointed
as he heads to prison.)
So this is how it feels.
Woo Seok, why are you out?
Who ripped off your name tag?
So Min. Gyeong Hye did.
My goodness. Gyeong Hye?
Oh, no.
I practiced.
Oh, no. It's too...
Why did it have to be Gyeong Hye?
Is there a revival ticket?
Is there?
I want to revive Woo Seok
in exchange for my life.
Is there no such thing?
Oh, no. Once you go to prison...
- I don't want to go.
- I will follow you. Hang in there.
- Okay.
- I will follow you to prison.
- Wait.
(She will follow him
to the netherworld.)
Gyeong Hye?
I will have my revenge.
I will rip off
Gyeong Hye's name tag.
(Ji Hyo averts the crisis
and runs away.)
Everyone is so scary.
Gosh.
(Jong Kook is hiding
with the Runningdex.)
Do they go around
as a group like that?
Is that allowed?
(He spots Team Woo Seok in a group.)
That makes no sense.
Let's go.
(He goes back into hiding.)
- We need to eliminate Se Chan.
- We need to eliminate him.
- Jong Kook.
- We can't give them more time.
- Hurry up.
We are doing pretty well.
We have good teamwork.
Gyeong Hye has a fighting spirit.
It came off again.
- What?
- Check up on Jae Suk's microphone.
- I need it fixed.
- It keeps coming off.
(Jae Suk has a problem
with the audio system.)
We will take a look at it.
The screen came off.
(Suk Jin and So Min keep going
without Jae Suk.)
Suk Jin's stickers are pretty rare.
All right.
There they are.
Jong Kook is coming.
Once we find Se Chan...
They are the same team.
Let's go.
(He retreats.)
- Why are you running away?
- Where are you going?
- It's so nice to see him run away.
- We must be intimidating.
- Rip it off when I grab him.
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk is looking
for Suk Jin and So Min.)
Where did Suk Jin and So Min go?
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk is looking
for Suk Jin and So Min.)
Where did they go?
How could they run off
by themselves?
Where is Jae Suk?
We need to find him.
It's dangerous to be by ourselves.
- It's dangerous.
- We need to travel as a group.
Where is Jae Suk?
Shall we call him?
This is...
Oh, no.
This makes my heart ache.
Wasn't there a snack bar here?
It disappeared.
When did it disappear?
What's wrong?
- This makes my heart ache.
- Why?
I made so many memories
at the snack bar.
What are you talking about?
This isn't the time to do that.
It's not like that.
There was a snack bar here.
- You startled me.
- We went in through here.
We found many hints here.
- That's right.
- There was a chair here.
There used to be a snack bar.
- We found a hint on the laptop.
- That's right. There was a table.
Han Na and I looked at each other...
- like this.
- That's right.
- We did that.
- You were wary of each other.
- That's right.
- "Come here. Come inside."
We went inside and...
It's blocked off now.
- Oh, no.
- The snack bar was on this side.
- And...
- the chair was here.
- It used to be empty.
Ice cream container was here.
- We had to solve a quiz here...
- Snacks were here.
- for an elimination ticket.
- That's right.
(While Suk Jin and So Min
are absorbed in the past,)
(this man
is desperately calling them.)
Where are they?
(Seriously.)
(At that moment)
There he is.
Haha, there he is.
Jae Suk is coming.
There he is.
(Jae Suk got spotted
while walking around alone.)
- Where?
- Jae Suk is coming.
Gyeong Hye.
(Team Gyeong Hye won't miss
this chance.)
Hide there.
Come here.
(Se Chan approaches Jae Suk.)
Se Chan.
What are you up to?
You hid Haha, didn't you?
You underestimate me.
Why would I do that and lure you in?
Let's have a conversation.
Where are my team members?
Suk Jin, what should we do?
Things changed so much.
- They didn't change.
- Why didn't you change at all?
They didn't change.
You didn't change either.
Compared to five years ago,
you didn't change at all.
You are still the same.
(Smiling from ear to ear)
Let's keep saying nice things
to each other.
You become stronger
and healthier every year.
(The 2 of them have no idea
what's happening.)
(He senses that he is in trouble.)
For goodness' sake.
Let's take a stroll.
- Come here.
- What?
Let's take a stroll.
I won't walk all the way there.
Grab him!
(Haha and Gyeong Hye
begin to gang up on him.)
Grab him!
(Jae Suk needs to fight
against 3 people.)
Gyeong Hye is like a thug.
(Team Gyeong Hye
attacks vigorously.)
Gyeong Hye, take it off.
- Gyeong Hye.
- There you go.
Gyeong Hye is like a thug.
- Jae Suk is out.
- This is...
Hey.
Where were you guys?
This is...
(The two of them finally appear.)
Why did you walk around alone?
Do you have the Runningdex?
I can't believe him.
Where were you?
We would have saved him
if you weren't absorbed in memories.
- It's her fault.
- I got eliminated.
She was absorbed in memories.
It isn't my fault.
Why is he using me as an excuse?
I shouldn't have trusted them.
Jae Suk?
When did he get eliminated?
They are fast.
- Is there one?
- Yes.
Let's open it.
Why are there so many of them?
I have five Woojaemons now.
Is this Woojaemon?
This is Woojaemon.
Why are there so many of yours?
Are you going to make me
a common man?
Woojaemon is so common.
Is there one?
Jihyomon.
Is it Jihyomon?
- Gosh.
- It's Woojaemon.
- How many are there?
- Woo Jae.
It's your sticker.
Did you hide about 200 Woojaemons?
We keep finding his stickers.
There are only Woojaemons.
- There are only Woojaemons.
- There are so many of them.
Seriously.
There are only Woojaemons.
This is making me look like
a common man.
- That hurts.
- Suk Jin is out.
- We might win if we stay still.
- Really?
Who is eliminating everyone?
That means the pink team is out.
The pink team is over.
(A moment ago)
It's me.
I got her.
- Can you rip off name tags?
- So Min is out.
Get Suk Jin.
- What?
- I ripped it off.
- All members are out.
- We eliminated all of them.
(Team Woo Seok is out.)
Did you have to go that far?
You didn't know, did you?
- Gyeong Hye, you are the best.
- You are incredible.
She is a killer.
I am so frustrated.
You shouldn't have gotten
eliminated.
I would have done well with you.
Seriously.
(Team Woo Seok started at the top
and ended up at the bottom.)
- This is good.
- Team Pink got wiped out.
We will win.
At this point,
- it will be hard for us to lose.
- Se Chan and...
Will you be able to beat Jong Kook?
- Of course.
- Yes.
It will be hard for Jong Kook
to collect ten stickers.
(Both teams focus on
collecting Runningmon stickers.)
It's Jong Kook again.
It's Se Chan again.
Gosh, Yang Se Chan.
(Jong Kook found a sticker as well.)
It's Haha.
It's a sticker we don't have.
This is great.
Haha.
This must be why
people collect such stickers.
How about you?
Did you get Ji Hyo or So Min?
- No.
I just found Haha.
- We need Ji Hyo and So Min.
- I just found Haha.
- It's here.
- You startled me.
- Where?
(Team Gyeong Hye
finds Runningmon stickers as well.)
What is it?
(They need
Seokjinmon and Wooseokmon.)
Hold on.
- Is it Woo Jae?
- It's Wooseokmon.
- We got this.
- Come here.
(Team Gyeong Hye got
1 more Runningmon sticker.)
- Haha.
- Woo Jae went that way.
Haha, come here.
We just need one more.
Show it to the camera.
Seokjinmon.
Let's do this.
- If they find it first,
- It will be bad.
- we won't get to use our strength.
- Let's take them on.
How many stickers do you have?
I have about five more.
Hold on to them.
- I have 7.
- You have 7?
Hold on.
Then give me four.
Then we can eliminate one person.
(Jong Kook purchases
an elimination ticket.)
- Ten stickers.
- All right.
- We can do this together.
- Relax.
- Either one of us...
- can rip off name tags.
- That's right.
- My gait changed.
- You can relax now.
You can relax now.
- Do I look relaxed?
- Yes, you do.
Woo Jae, you look relaxed.
There it is.
Where? My goodness.
Please.
If it's Seokjinmon, we will win.
- Suk Jin.
- I hope it's Seokjinmon.
Please let it be Seokjinmon.
Please.
- It's Jong Kook.
- Gosh.
All right.
Once I grab someone,
rip off the name tag.
You just need to rip it off quickly, okay?
Jong Kook can't eliminate us.
He doesn't have ten stickers.
(Team Gyeong Hye hides
in a corner of the building.)
This is driving me crazy
because we just need one more.
We just need one more.
- One more.
- We don't have time to do that.
- We should eliminate someone.
- They only need to find one more.
- Really? Then we should hurry.
- Yes.
So I heard.
Where could it be?
Okay.
- Did you find one?
- Please.
(Team Gyeong Hye
found another sticker!)
It's over once we get Seokjinmon.
(Team Gyeong Hye
found another sticker!)
It's over once we get Seokjinmon.
Please.
- Yes!
- Why?
We found it. This is amazing.
(They managed to find Seokjinmon.)
Hurry.
(Team Gyeong Hye is done
collecting all the stickers.)
Let's hurry.
- What?
Darn it. Seriously, is it over?
I guess they found them all.
We were about to get them. My gosh.
- We stranded Jong Kook.
- Right.
We got rid of Team Pink's name tags.
This is the best.
(Team Gyeong Hye wins the race.)
My gosh. Our teamwork was perfect.
We've completed it.
Let's pretend this is glaring.
- Start.
- Oh gosh!
(Team Gyeong Hye)
- Well played.
- You are really good.
(The 3 winners have won the prize.)
- Thank you.
- I just started enjoying tea.
(We thank Woo Jae, Gyeong Hye,
and Woo Seok for their appearance.)
(Let's forget about age and fight.)
(I don't drink,
but I need some alcohol today.)
(The two towns have grudges
that are about to come to a head.)
(That's when they receive...)
(a mysterious message.)
(Two pairs of arch enemies show up.)
(Cho Jun Hyun, Cho Jun Ho,
Yoo Ri, Hyoyeon)
(There can't be two suns
in the sky.)
(How dare you get smart with me?)
(Act like a senior if you are one.)
(Don't let your enemy know
about your embarrassing secret.)
(Yoo Ri hasn't studied for a while.)
You'd make a good idol artist.
(They don't care about ethics.)
(They have nothing to lose
with this battle.)
Stop it.
(The end of the conflict?)
(Or the beginning
of the eternal war?)
(Which town will be
the winner of the battle?)
(Enemy Cha-Cha-Cha)