(The Republic of Korea)
(Seoul)
(Busan)
(Incheon)
(Jeju Island, Ulsan)
(Daegu, Daejeon, Gwangju)
(The miniature of the eight special
and metropolitan cities in Korea)
(The Running National Map)
(Following Gwangju and Incheon
where various foods are gathered,)
(there are leisure facilities
including a chair...)
(and a swimming pool
in Seoul and Busan.)
(You can buy all these lands
from Running Real Estate.)
(Welcome to Running World.)
- Oh, my.
- Why?
- What's going on?
- What's this?
(They're surprised
by the grand studio.)
- What is it?
- It's Busan.
Is it Busan-themed today?
- No, there's Seoul too.
- Busan?
There's no Jeju Metropolis?
- Busan.
- There's Jeju Metropolis too.
- Haha.
- Ulsan.
- What's with today's setting?
- Suk Jin will like this.
Haha.
- What's this?
- Haha.
- Real estate.
- You need to find Jeju Metropolis.
Hurry and find it.
Find Jeju Metropolitan City.
- Hurry and find it.
- As soon as I entered...
- Try finding it.
- There are many cities.
- Suk Jin.
- What's going on today?
I'm not sure what it is,
but it looks exciting.
- It's what you like. Real estate.
- Why?
For me...
- Oh!
- Is it a competition?
This is my life.
I've never succeeded in it though.
- This theme today...
- You know, right?
Se Chan, Jong Kook, and I did
a similar show.
Right.
- We know this. But...
- Real estate?
- Whenever we get the information...
- Oh, gosh.
- Right.
- Woljeong-ri in Jeju Island?
If you invested,
how would it turn out?
- At Jeju Island?
- Yes.
- I won't be here.
- Seriously?
- If you invested?
- It's now over thousands of times.
- Isn't it like twentyfold?
- That doesn't make sense.
- Jong Kook.
It's now 86 times higher.
- That's right.
- Was it 86 times?
- Woljeong-ri rose 86 times higher.
- Eighty-six times.
(Anyway, they're here as a result
of not buying property back then.)
- Woljeong-ri?
- It's only cash for me.
Cash.
- He makes me frustrated.
- Only cash for me.
- He never invests.
- Yes.
I don't know about these.
Near Jong Kook's apartment,
there's a rumor that
a jangdokdae is buried underground.
- There's cash in it.
- A bunch of cash is in it.
- Yes.
- Under the floor.
He goes there every month...
- It's your mission.
- and digs up.
Try digging.
So I'm carefully
looking around that area.
- Yes.
- He's so sure of keeping cash.
I have no assets.
If Suk Jin listened to me,
- He won't be here?
- You wouldn't have seen me.
He would have enjoyed his life.
I'm a proactive investor type.
Such wealth can lead to
loss of health.
- But Suk Jin...
- There's no mercy.
- But you know that about him...
- You're right.
- Be positive.
- I agree.
- For Suk Jin, he...
- What?
never listens to people...
who stayed with him for a long time.
- But by chance,
- Random person.
if he meets a man at the airport...
- An old gentleman.
- A new person.
the conversation he heard
while the elevator door closed.
- An old gentleman.
- He listens well to these people.
(It activates Seok Sam's
gullible tendency.)
I lost so much after listening to
the president of Korean Association.
That happens.
- It's weird. It happens to me too.
- Why are we like that?
- I experienced it too.
- We can't help it.
I don't know why.
- I've never invested.
- Yes.
But I listened to one person's
advice and invested.
- But I got doomed.
- Right?
Seriously. That happens.
- Jong Kook's style is...
- I blew up so much money.
- mostly not listening to others.
- For real.
But he loses everything
through his close friend.
- In one go.
Mine was huge.
Honestly, people like Ji Hyo...
is great to be cheated on.
No, you're the best.
(No, you're the best.)
You little...
- He really hit him.
- I didn't think he would.
- Ji Hyo...
For today...
Some might have done this before.
- Yes.
- It's an upgraded hopscotch.
I wanted to do this.
- The immersion is no joke.
- We've done it a long time ago.
I think I've done this before.
- You tried when you were a guest.
- Yes, as a guest.
(The first hopscotch special
on episode 281)
(The first hopscotch was
full of slapsticks.)
(Se Chan was a guest for the second
hopscotch special on episode 321.)
- Yes, you were a guest.
- I was...
- a team with you.
- You were...
in a team with me.
You could be a member
because I took care of you.
- Because you did well that day.
- Suk Jin...
- Don't say that.
- You didn't matter.
- That's how you succeeded.
- No way.
- I did nothing.
- I'll tell you the facts.
You never made anyone succeed...
and no one succeeded because of you.
- You and I think differently.
- You...
are the only one
who was raised by us.
- Only you.
- You only raised Hyun Woo.
His wife raised Hyun Woo
all by herself.
He raised no one.
- Do you know about my family?
- Of course.
You always went to a cyber cafe.
That's a long time ago.
- It's an old story.
- I...
So I was worried and I asked,
"Don't you need to
take care of Hyun Woo?"
- He said, "He will..."
- He'll grow on his own.
- "grow on his own."
- Grow himself.
- Of course.
- Right. They grow by themselves.
Currently, at the back,
there are provinces
of metropolitan cities.
They are metropolitan cities
of Running Man.
- Jeju Island is there too.
- Jeju Metropolitan City.
Jeju Metropolis is there.
- So there are a total of 70 lands.
- Oh, my.
- Yes.
- That's a lot.
One mat is equivalent to one land.
You'll be able to purchase land
within your budget.
There are good and
bad factors in the land.
- Oh, in the land.
- But these are...
not real and all randomly chosen.
- Is it random?
- Yes.
It's just imaginary.
- It's imaginary.
- That's better.
That makes it fair.
Land prices rise and fall depending
on the good and bad factors.
Every hour from 12 p.m. until the end,
we'll give you the profits.
Some lands will have good factors...
so they'll make you
profit every hour.
But some will have bad factors
and take your money instead.
- We can't know in advance.
- But Gangnam is a must.
There are more lands
with good factors.
- Yes.
- Okay.
After you earn your money
through a mission,
you'll buy lands.
Then you'll only be able to live
within your lands.
- It's small. The land is small.
- Right.
After that,
we'll calculate your profits.
- I see.
- If you earn 30, we'll give you 30.
Each empty land is 100 dollars.
- Okay.
- Oh, my gosh.
If you're taking away from others,
it'll be 150 dollars.
- A hundred and fifty dollars.
- Yes.
If you pay ten dollars,
you can see the land information.
(When the land is purchased
through an intermediary office)
But you can have a deal
amongst yourselves.
You can negotiate
to purchase the land for 50 dollars.
If you step on others' lands,
you need to pay
ten dollars as a toll.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Today's penalty and prize
work like this.
Excluding the richest two,
we'll choose randomly
among the five members.
- Oh, seriously.
- Among five of us?
We're going to cash out...
the land you have at the end
of the day for the rankings.
So it's important for you
to have many good lands.
Okay.
- Only the first and second matter.
- No use from the third.
I need to be the first
or the second.
We should see these carefully.
One has a chair.
- One has food.
- I want the land with food.
I should buy accordingly.
I have to be at Incheon Seo-gu...
- to eat.
- Yes.
We need both Incheon Seo-gu
and Gwangju Nam-gu to eat.
- You want to sleep?
- Then Busan area isn't good.
It's a path to the bathroom.
- I need to rest.
- Jong Kook.
Even the bathroom?
We need to buy Busan
to go to the bathroom.
- We need to pay to go?
- Seriously?
We can't exempt you from it.
- To go, you need to step on it.
- Seriously?
If you step on others' land,
you have to pay ten dollars for toll.
- Ten dollars?
- Please give me a chamber pot.
I'll just secrete in the water.
If you want to change your clothes
if they get wet,
- Do we need to buy?
- we prepared them.
- Is it prepared?
- Oh, there's a place to change.
- You can see it on your right.
- For real?
You can only change to those.
Or you can decide not to change.
- First, I need to eat.
- This land can earn the most money.
- Incheon and Gwangju.
- I want that.
It's not bad to receive tolls
for the bathroom.
I think that land will bring
the most profit.
- Right. The most profitable land.
- But how many times...
- will we visit the bathroom?
- Right?
We'll go only once.
- Shall I make them eat first?
- If I can't, I'll just...
excuse myself.
- At where?
- Behind the plants.
- I don't know.
- Urinating on the street.
- It's okay.
- I don't know.
In the pot...
- Inside the fitting room.
- Inside there...
I'll just excuse myself.
- We prepared a pool just in case.
- What?
- You can use the pool too.
- Right.
Yes, we can use the pool.
We'll start the mission
for you to earn...
- the first investing money.
- Yes.
- We need to earn money.
- The first earning is vital.
What is it? There's another game?
We'll start the mission for you
to earn the investing money.
- We can buy land with this.
- This mission is...
beneficial for real estate investors
who know well about geography.
Geography?
The mission is called
Going to Seoul, Daejeon, Daegu, and Busan.
- What?
- Okay.
The seven cards in front
are written...
- with starting points in Korea.
- Starting points.
Choose one card
and from your starting point,
search your destination.
According to the taxi fares,
we'll pay you from highest to lowest.
- That's nice.
- Oh, gosh.
- This is...
- I should know the geography.
- Is this random?
- Yes.
- The starting points are different.
- It's random.
- So it's random.
- Yes.
- We should know the geography.
- Shall we go one by one?
- Who will start first?
- Haha can start first.
- Shall I go first?
- Yes.
- I know geography well.
- You know a lot.
- I know the roads.
- He drives a lot.
- Because I...
- You know about the whole nation?
- Of course.
- Yes?
I know most places.
(Thinking hard)
- Do I just take it? I pick it?
- I know most places.
(Which starting point
did Haha choose?)
- The starting point.
- Let's see.
Mount Mudeung at Gwangju.
- It's far.
- I don't know where that is.
- They have delicious meat.
- It's far.
You need to choose a destination
with the highest taxi fare.
- Okay.
- I see.
(Next is Jong Kook's
starting point.)
- It's here.
- That's so good.
You hit the jackpot.
Daejeon Expo.
(Daejeon Expo Park)
The middle area is bad.
- Are you Daejeon?
- Where did you pick?
- Daejeon Expo.
- You're done.
Then you're...
Just choose Seoul
as your destination.
- Choose Seoul.
- It's difficult.
- Sokcho.
- You may choose your destination.
Yours is fine.
- Is it?
- It's nice.
- Busan Haeundae Beach.
- It's good.
- This is good.
Mine is South Chungcheong Province,
Kkotji Beach at Anmyeon.
You can go there by taxi.
Because at Gyeonggi...
- By taxi.
- Okay!
I got Dongducheon City Hall.
- Dongducheon.
- It's my neighborhood!
Why does that matter?
You need to write the destination.
- What?
- Jong Kook and I got the worst.
You need to write the destination.
I can go to Busan or Jeolla Province
since they're far.
- Then I need to go like this.
- Go like this.
Write your own destinations.
Daejeon is about here.
- It's the furthest like this.
- By taxi?
- I can write wherever I want?
- Yes.
Like this.
Anywhere, right?
- What is in this area?
- Write the exact location.
What places are there in this area?
It's best if you write Yangyang.
- What are you talking about?
- Yangyang.
I know that it's close by.
- You know that?
- Yangyang is right here.
- This is very far.
- Show me.
From Dongducheon...
I shouldn't let you know.
(The kid from Dongducheon already
wrote his destination.)
The area
where Ttangkkeut Village is located.
- What was the name? Hahoe?
- You can choose any place.
- It's Hanam.
- No, that's not it. Ha...
- Hadong.
- It doesn't matter.
(Is Ttangkkeut Village located in
South Gyeongsang Province, Hadong?)
I'm sorry about the noise.
(She's bad at
the geography of Korea.)
To be honest,
those who picked Busan...
or Dongducheon got so lucky.
- Why? Are you belittling the areas?
- South Chungcheong Province is...
I'm not belittling the areas.
You know exactly where it is.
- "Are you belittling the areas?"
- And they're in the northern part.
Why would you belittle the areas?
Dongducheon is a nice place.
- We always...
- I'm saying it's a good thing.
- attack one another like this.
- Exactly.
You know that, right?
I must say, we always...
We always attack one another
like this.
- I'm saying you're at an advantage.
- "Are you belittling the area?"
(The Running Man style of dissing)
- I'm dumbfounded.
- "Are you looking down on me?"
Please tell us your destinations.
Haha, where is your destination?
- Okay.
- Hwacheon-gun Office.
Next.
I picked Haenam-gun Office.
- Haenam-gun Office? Okay.
- Yes.
- That's far, indeed.
- Oh, my.
- He picked Haenam-gun Office.
- Next.
- Seok Sam.
- Me? I picked Homigot in Pohang.
(Departure point: Daejeon Expo Park,
Destination: Homigot in Pohang)
- Pohang is far from there.
- Indeed.
- Next.
- Hadong...
A parking lot
in Ttangkkeut Village in Hadong.
She wrote the wrong name.
A parking lot in Ttangkkeut Village
in Hadong?
- It's in Haenam, not in Hadong.
- It's not in Hadong.
- It's in Haenam.
- Isn't it in Hadong?
- Look. Hadong is...
Hadong is
in South Gyeongsang Province.
- This is why...
- I get it. This is why...
- you told me not to tell her.
- That's right.
You didn't tell me intentionally,
right?
Ttangkkeut Village is located in
Haenam.
- Next.
- I picked Eurwangni Beach.
- From Haeundae Beach.
- You picked a perfect place.
- To Eurwangni Beach.
- That's very far.
- Yes, indeed.
- Next up is Ji Hyo.
I'm going to a night sea cart bar
in Yeosu.
- What?
- Isn't that the name of a bar?
- Pardon me?
- I think...
- You can go with it.
- that Ji Hyo...
- It must be close by.
- She just wanted to go there.
From Kkotji Beach on Anmyeon Island
in South Chungcheong Province...
- to a cart bar in Yeosu.
- She just wanted to go there.
- I picked...
- From South Chungcheong Province...
Sagewood Country Club
in Gyeongdo, Yeosu.
- It's located in Gyeongdo, Yeosu.
- Is it a country club?
It's located
on the edge of the island.
- On the edge of the island.
- Really?
- Okay. Let's go.
- Let's go!
- It'll be Jae Suk or Se Chan.
Haha, please show your board
to the camera.
(From Mount Mudeung in Gwangju
to Hwacheon-gun Office)
It's actually Hwacheon-gun Office.
- Oh, my. It's coming up.
- My gosh.
- How much would it cost?
- I don't know the name of the area.
- I can't see it.
- Which area is there?
- It's 436.01 dollars.
- How much?
- How many kilometers?
- It's over 430 dollars?
- It's really far.
- Oh, my.
It wasn't a bad choice, right?
Look. It goes all the way south.
- Oh, that's where I should go.
- Right?
Next. Jong Kook, please show us.
I picked Haenam-gun Office.
(From SBS Prism Tower
to Haenam-gun Office)
- That's far.
- It's on the edge.
- He picked the farthest place.
- It's 356.91 dollars.
- Haha wins.
I got a higher number.
(Jong Kook's taxi fare:
356.91 dollars)
- I got a higher number.
- Why is that?
- The road conditions must be good.
- Yes, exactly.
Oh, the road conditions are better
on his route.
- There's the Seohaean Expressway.
- That's right.
That's the place I wanted to go to.
- Isn't it near the place?
- This is awesome.
The road conditions can... I see.
Next.
- Homigot in Pohang.
- It's near Busan.
Haha moved diagonally,
and Jong Kook moved straight.
- Pohang is that way. Yes.
- He picked a good place.
- It's far.
- It's not so far.
- It takes three hours.
It's 262.94 dollars.
- It's not so far.
- I'm relieved.
- It's close to his starting point.
Could I get no results?
Next, So Min's destination is...
There may be no results
for Ttangkkeut Village, Hadong.
- You should type "Hadong."
- It's not very far.
- I'll type "Hadong."
- Okay.
You should type something like
"Hadong-gun Office."
My old nickname was Hadong.
Hadong. That's right.
(The taxi fare: 803.09 dollars)
It's 803.09 dollars.
- I'm surprised.
- It's over 800 dollars?
(It's 803.09 dollars!)
- It's 803.09 dollars.
- What? Are you sure?
- Really?
Hang on. You wrote
"Ttangkkeut Village," right?
And "Hadong."
- But she wrote the wrong name.
- Try Ttangkkeut Village.
- Ttangkkeut Village.
- That shouldn't be accepted.
- But you all accepted it.
- Hadong is at the southern end too.
- She's out.
- What are you talking about?
- This is unacceptable.
- My gosh.
Guys, let me off, please.
Then how about we give her
half of it to be fair?
- Okay.
- I'll take half of it.
- That sounds fair.
- Her fare is 400 dollars.
You picked the right place.
Hadong is very far.
- Indeed. It's over 800 dollars.
- Right.
- It's on the edge.
- If it was Ttangkkeut Village...
(From Haeundae Beach
to Eurwangni Beach)
Eurwangni Beach.
My, I see
the road conditions have improved.
- Exactly.
- Any place from Seoul...
It's 573.47 dollars.
- How much?
- It's over 570 dollars.
(It's 573.47 dollars!)
- It's over 570 dollars?
- You did well.
- It's far.
- The road conditions must be good.
You're currently in the first place.
It's over 570 dollars. Nice.
- A cart bar in Yeosu.
- It doesn't look too far...
- from Ji Hyo's starting point.
- It's really far.
I guess the distance isn't all
when it comes to taxi fares.
- You're right.
- The distance is quite long.
- It's 588.27 dollars.
- What?
- My gosh. What?
- It's five hundred...
(It's 588.27 dollars!)
Now, Ji Hyo won
by a difference of 15 dollars.
- Oh, my.
- But how come it costs more...
- for a shorter distance?
- Because of the road conditions.
Because the road conditions are
better on my route.
Did she take a deluxe taxi?
- It costs too much.
- Ji Hyo, you did a great job.
Let's move on to the last member.
Let's go to Sagewood Country Club
in Gyeongdo, Yeosu.
I think
it's far from his starting point.
It's 512.35 dollars.
- It's not that much.
- It's a lot.
- The road conditions must be good.
- Right. That must be the reason.
- It makes a big difference.
- As a result,
Ji Hyo placed first.
- She did an amazing job.
- No way.
- She didn't know where it was.
- Ji Hyo is really incredible.
- She didn't even know that.
- That's true.
She's so smart.
- Jae Suk placed second.
- My goodness.
- Se Chan placed third.
- All right.
- Haha placed fourth.
- Oh, my.
So Min placed fifth.
Jong Kook placed 6th,
and Suk Jin placed 7th.
I thought that Jong Kook would be...
- Hang on a second.
- Didn't we all laugh at them?
Her taxi fare was reduced by half.
- Yes, her fare is 400 dollars.
- That's why it's 400 dollars.
- It was over 800 dollars.
- It's because...
- My destination is...
- in the middle.
- there isn't a direct route...
- to So Min's destination.
- That's right.
- This is fun.
- It's over.
As a result of the game,
the winner gets 790 dollars.
And... You can come and receive it.
- I bet she'll buy a lot.
- She'll buy a lot of properties.
- Oh, boy. I think...
- We still have a chance to win.
Right. We have a chance to win.
How much do I get?
- Do I get 590 dollars?
- I get 690 dollars?
Now, you'll purchase...
- your first property.
- Yes.
The winner gets to
make a purchase first.
As you must know,
you can't purchase...
any of the properties she bought
in this round.
Let's move to the other set
and begin.
I'm really bad at investing.
(The members will officially begin
investing.)
(Current time: 11 a.m.,
Everything about this game is fictitious.)
Which area should I buy?
We should get the food first.
- Absolutely.
- Yes, we should get the food first.
But Ji Hyo will buy those areas.
Which area should we buy, Ji Hyo?
I have so little money.
I should buy this area to ally with
Ji Hyo and to get food.
(The profitable property that draws
the investors' attention is...)
Then I should buy the fridge
in the middle.
Right, you should.
Oh, my goodness.
- Oh, my.
- It's nice.
- I see chicken breast too.
- There's a lot of food in here.
- I'll have ice cream.
- I just need to have one meal.
Hey, there's frozen food too.
- Look at the crunchy fried chicken.
- Oh, my.
- This is it.
- Exactly.
- It must be more profitable.
- Ji Hyo will buy them all.
- How much is Seo-gu, Gwangju?
- It's 100 dollars.
- I see.
I can use the toilet now, right?
- No.
- No, you can't.
(- I can use the toilet now, right?
- No!)
- I knew it.
- Oh, gosh.
I wish I could go to the restroom
before we begin the game.
Now, please make your purchase
starting with Ji Hyo.
I have a question.
Can another member buy the land
that I've purchased?
In the next round.
They can't do that in this round.
I see. Then I'd like to...
(Ji Hyo gets to choose the land
to purchase as the winner.)
My, look at the chicken breast.
There are chicken breast
and everything.
- But Ji Hyo will buy these areas.
- How much is Nam-gu?
Ji Hyo can't buy any more than...
(Ji Hyo is thinking hard.)
(Seo-gu, Incheon!)
Seo-gu, Incheon.
I'd like to purchase that area.
(She chose Seo-gu, Incheon, that's
in front of the snack table.)
We'll give you the land certificate.
(Land Certificate, Seo-gu, Incheon)
What?
(The value increases
as a dragon appears in the area.)
(The information on the certificate:
1. The cause of value changes)
(2. The profit from value changes
at hours)
(This property makes 200 dollars
every hour.)
And Dongdaemun-gu, Seoul.
Dongdaemun-gu, Seoul.
Dong-gu, Nam-gu,
and Suyeong-gu, Busan.
Hey, Jae Suk.
- She didn't buy it.
- This is...
- What?
- She bought those areas.
Why did she buy those areas?
I think it's because of the toilet.
Jae Suk, I think it's best
to buy the area in the middle.
- We should buy Buk-gu, Gwangju.
- Absolutely.
I'll buy these six areas.
(Jae Suk, who placed 2nd
with 690 dollars, is up.)
- This is the total amount.
- Okay.
(He bought all the areas around
the snack table and the fridge.)
(He checks the land certificates
as well.)
(Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju,
The value increases every hour.)
(Nam-gu, Gwangju,
Great. It's nice.
- Did you make your purchase?
- My, these properties...
- They're tasty, right?
- They're tasty.
(Yangcheon-gu, Seoul,
The value increases every hour.)
This is great. I struck gold.
(Seo-gu, Gwangju,
The value decreases every hour.)
Darn.
(The value of Seo-gu, Gwangju,
drops sharply.)
Gosh, seriously.
Darn it. This is not good.
Did you buy all of them, Jae Suk?
- Yes, I did.
- That's cool.
- Who's next?
- I didn't know it'd be like this.
- I'm next.
- I didn't go to the restroom.
You need to go to the restroom now?
Why now?
Had you told me about the rules...
- You can buy Seo-gu, Busan.
- Pardon?
- What did you say?
- You can buy the area at the end.
(Seo-gu, Busan, is the toll gate
to the restroom.)
- Jae Suk, is this your land?
- Yes.
(Meanwhile,
Jae Suk New Town is being built.)
- I can't even go near it.
- He practically owns the fridge.
- I'm in trouble.
- I'll be hungry all day long.
He's like the owner of a snack bar.
I'm worried. What do I do?
- We can't go there.
- The only thing...
that Ji Hyo doesn't have is
access to the toilet.
- Jae Suk, you bought a lot.
- Of course. I bought six areas.
You can say
that you can't come near the fridge.
- Why did you buy only these areas?
- Also,
- I can move around the grass field.
- Yes.
- I can move this far. Sorry?
- Is it a common area?
- Oh, it's a common area.
- Yes. So I bought all these areas.
- Good for you.
- Right?
I can use this bed too.
I have food to eat
and a place to sleep.
I can go for a walk too.
- You can't use the toilet.
- What?
I can take care of that
behind the fridge.
I'll do it behind the fridge
like this.
(He'll actively use the blind spot.)
- Is it possible?
- Of course, it is.
- I can't see you.
- Right?
- And I have this.
- He says he can do that.
He says it's possible.
- It's so funny that he says so.
- We need it to cook.
- I might have to use it.
- We'll need that pot.
- That's nonsense.
- What?
Now, shall I eat some food?
Let me see.
I want to eat ramyeon, Ji Hyo.
Shall I give you ramyeon?
I'd like to purchase
Gangdong-gu, Seoul,
Jungnang-gu, Seoul, Jeju Island,
Seo-gu, Daegu,
- and Namdong-gu, Incheon.
- Seo-gu, Daegu?
- Yes.
- It's 580 dollars.
(He focuses on Jae Suk New Town
and the hydropower resources.)
If you give me
the land certificates...
(He receives the land certificates
of the areas he purchased.)
(Jungnang-gu, Seoul,
The value increases every hour.)
This is nice.
(Seo-gu, Daegu,
The value increases every hour.)
Good. I bought good land.
Shall I heat up some dumplings?
Shall I heat up some dumplings
using this microwave oven?
- Ramyeon goes well with dumplings.
- Right.
- What goes well with dumplings?
- Ramyeon.
Or for now
I'll have a cup of iced Americano
with ice cubes
I'm not jealous. You'll need to
use the toilet if you drink it.
Please leave my property
I can come to the common area
as well.
- That's right.
- How do you...
- Oh, my. You bought these areas.
- I can order some food here.
- Yes, that's right.
- You can go from here...
- and jump to this area.
- Yes.
- But you can't reach the fridge.
- No, he can't.
- I can take food out of it.
- How?
I'll show you later.
- Will you do it like this?
- Enjoy watching it.
(The fridge expressway will be open
later on.)
Okay. It's done.
Has it begun?
- Those who bought land have.
- The property owners have.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
Wait. First...
I'll bring some food.
(Se Chan is getting ready to move.)
What are you doing?
Good. It's so cool.
My, it's good.
- This is my land.
- He's upset.
- It's so nice.
- Don't put your feet in there.
I was going to drink the water
when I got thirsty.
(The water source is contaminated by
the thoughtless citizen.)
Why would you put your feet
in there?
It's so nice.
I've made my decision.
Give me a second.
Here's 400 dollars.
Thank you.
(He receives the land certificates.)
All right.
(Haha goes to an area
near Jae Suk New Town.)
Hello, sir.
- Hello.
- I've moved next door to you.
(The little neighbor came for food.)
- It's nice to meet you.
- You too. I hope we get along well.
- Oh, you're drinking something.
- Yes.
Jae Suk, can I get one too?
- What?
- Give me one of that, please.
- Salad.
- Hey.
- Please.
- What...
That was so smooth.
(Pumping)
Hey.
(Attacking with a water gun)
Give me a portion of salad now.
My gosh. I'm speechless.
(Here I come!)
Will you give me a salad or not?
You might get soaked
from head to toe.
- Hey, are you...
- Or you can enjoy the water park.
- Are you serious?
- Come on.
- Will you keep going on like this?
- Don't come near me.
- This has a long range.
- I'll never give you any food...
- if you keep acting like this.
- You'll never give me any food?
- No way.
- "No way?"
"No way?"
- It's fun to watch.
- Hey...
I'll never give you any food.
I'd rather get soaked.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- Yes. I don't mind.
- I'd rather get soaked.
- It's not too late. Say, "Stop."
- Say, "Stop."
- I'd rather get soaked.
- I'll never give you any food.
- Give me just one.
- No way.
- "No way?"
Then I won't let you eat either.
Drink some water instead.
- Didn't you put your feet in it?
- Yes, I did.
Yes, I put my feet in it.
I chose the right areas.
Gosh, those punks.
I checked out the properties
before I came here.
I'd like to purchase
these three areas.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Yongsan-gu, Seoul...
- These three areas?
- Yes.
I think that the value of Yongsan-gu
will increase.
Here's your land certificate.
It will increase by 300 dollars.
Oh, it has the information I need.
(Yongsan-gu, Seoul,
The value increases every hour.)
Thank you.
I have water.
- Water?
- Are the white areas yours?
Yes, I'm wearing a white shirt.
- I think I chose the wrong area.
- Oh, it matches the color.
I won't be seen.
So Min, did you make a purchase?
(The chair blocks her.)
- I made a mistake. I'm invisible.
- Did you make a purchase?
- Jong Kook, I bought Yongsan-gu.
- Yes.
The chair you're sitting on
blocks me.
- Jong Kook, you're up.
- Is it my turn?
All right.
Since I don't have much money...
Wait.
I have to give up on
either food or toilet.
(Food versus toilet)
I'll give up on food.
I'd like to purchase
Yeongdo-gu, Busan.
I think I'll have to stay here
if I buy Yeongdo-gu, Busan.
- He bought the toilet pass.
- I'll have to stay here.
My gosh.
(He starts living in one spot,
Yeongdo-gu, Busan.)
- I picked the wrong areas.
- The last member, please come.
- Sorry, but I'll use the toilet.
- Okay.
- Can you go to the toilet?
- Yes.
- Of course, I can.
- I guess you can jump.
- Of course, I can do it.
- Wait.
- Between the two options,
- Oh, gosh.
I chose the toilet
and gave up on the food.
That's my land.
Jong Kook, pay me ten dollars.
- Jong Kook.
- Can't I step on here either?
- No, you can't.
- I see. Okay.
- Hey, just give me ten dollars...
- Okay.
(He jumped.)
Did he pull it off?
No one else but Jong Kook can
jump that far.
Dong-gu, Ulsan.
- Ulsan?
- Yes.
Is there anything I should know
about Dong-gu, Ulsan?
- Here's the land certificate.
- Okay.
Is there anything special
about the area?
(The value increases at noon
and decreases after that.)
(I picked a good one.)
At noon... Wait.
It goes down after that.
After I get 200 dollars at noon?
Can't I move to another area?
- You should sell it to someone.
- I should sell it.
Try to make the area
look profitable.
Really? How should I do that?
Try your best to make them believe
it's a profitable property.
Right. To sell the property?
- Can I sell it?
- Make them want to buy it.
(He begins playing the game
with an awkward exclamation.)
It's nice.
Hey, at least I picked a good area.
I can move to the common area.
I can jump over there as well.
- And here...
- You just stepped on Buk-gu, Ulsan.
You have to pay ten dollars.
- What?
- You stepped on the area.
Gosh. Buk-gu, Ulsan...
(He's been fined ten dollars.)
What's wrong with Suk Jin?
I didn't step on it.
(He failed to promote his property
and ended up spending money.)
- Gosh. You're too strict.
- It's delicious.
- I'm back!
- Oh, gosh.
(I'm back!)
- I'm back!
- Oh, gosh.
(The gym lover in Busan goes
in and out of the toilet loudly.)
My gosh. Why would he... Okay.
Fine. Keep it strict.
- Suk Jin, do you have only 1 area?
- Yes, I have 1 area.
- I skipped breakfast this morning.
- I had breakfast.
From here...
But you see...
Suk Jin, you bought a good area.
(He stole Jae Suk's coffee
successfully.)
What is he doing?
It has the water
that I put my feet in.
You're lying.
(His next target is the fridge.)
Suk Jin, you can't do that.
- Hey, you can't do that.
- Move.
Why?
- You can't do that.
- Why can't I?
- Of course, you can't do that.
- Let's help each other out.
- You have to pay ten dollars.
- I see.
That's too much.
I'll give you anything you want
if you give me ten dollars.
(At that moment, Se Chan shoots
his water gun at something.)
(Suk Jin's land)
Don't you think
that he's acting like a thug?
- Gosh, Hey.
- You can't sit on it now.
- Stay standing all day long.
- That's not the problem.
- It's slippery.
- Right. Okay.
- Suk Jin.
- He can't go back to his land.
- You'd better stay there.
- Where?
- On the grass field.
- No.
We can't steal one another's
land certificate, right?
- That's not allowed.
- Okay.
(Seok Sam's goal is
to move to Incheon...)
(where he can get resources easily.)
Wait. It's time.
Jung-gu, Seoul.
(Suk Jin fell.)
- Jung-gu, Seoul.
- What did he do?
- What's his problem?
- Suk Jin, pay ten dollars.
Hey!
Darn it!
Why are you trying to lie down
during a shoot?
Oh, that's what he wanted?
(Biting)
Who wants to drink water?
(A cookie made him happy.)
You have to pay ten dollars.
(He's trying to get more food
with his arm shaking.)
- He's so cute.
- Indeed.
Then... Since we have
made a reservation...
- But I don't have any eggs.
- Water is ours, Haha.
Haha, take this water gun.
We should stop him.
- How can you steal my coffee too?
- Stop stealing food.
- Why would you steal my coffee...
- What's wrong with you?
(He shoots to help Ji Hyo.)
- Wait. Don't move.
- Why would you steal my coffee?
(Laughing)
- No.
- What's wrong with you?
- You're unbelievable.
- Stop it.
- Suk Jin, give Ji Hyo ten dollars.
- No.
- He didn't pay me either.
- You stepped on my land.
- No, I didn't step on it.
I feel like
I'm watching the show at home.
- What did you say?
- That's funny.
- I feel like...
- What did you say?
- I feel like I'm watching TV.
- What are you doing there?
Why are you slacking off?
There's nothing I can do.
The only thing he can do is
use the toilet.
- I can only jump to the toilet.
- How will you cook it?
Well...
(The phone bell rings.)
- That's the phone.
- Hold on.
(Why on earth is the phone ringing?)
Hello?
(Others are bewildered,
but Jae Suk seems calm.)
Got it. Just a moment.
What is it?
I know what it was.
(What is he doing with the gourd?)
- What is that?
- What are you doing?
- Darn it!
- Throw it down hard.
- Well...
- Is this a personal mission?
- What?
- Is it a mission?
- Yes.
That must be it.
Maybe the price will go up.
Yes, that must be it.
(Back when Jae Suk
purchased his land)
(Seo-gu, Gwangju:
An unidentified beast appears.)
(Can be negated by breaking a gourd
with the head every hour)
(A piece of information was written
on the land certificate.)
(Some unfavorable conditions
can be negated.)
(Can be negated by breaking a gourd
with the head every hour)
(Unlike some lands with conditions
that can't be negated,)
(some lands have ways
to stabilize the price.)
(The owners will receive a call
as a reminder.)
I know what it was.
(He tries to negate
the negative effect.)
- What are you doing?
- Throw it down hard.
(If he does this, he can negate
the negative effect at noon.)
- Maybe the price will go up.
- Yes, that must be it.
- Darn it.
- Once more. You've got it.
(He broke the gourd.)
(Can be negated by breaking a gourd
with the head every hour)
Gosh, that hurts.
(He negated the effect.)
(Meanwhile, Suk Jin
tries to escape.)
This...
(Grunting)
(A sliding show)
It's slippery because of
the water I sprayed.
Jae Suk, one is enough.
What was with the one-man show?
- Darn you brats.
- Gosh, that hurts.
Pay up, Suk Jin.
You owe them and us
ten dollars each.
- Give me my ten dollars.
- Sure.
The phone is ringing again.
Why aren't I getting a phone call?
- Is there a phone in here?
- Is there a phone?
Do we all have phones?
- He must've bought one.
- Hello?
- Can you buy phones?
- How can you buy phones?
- Is there one in our briefcases?
- Got it.
Maybe it's only offered
to those in the top three.
Or maybe the top two.
Don't we get phones too?
What are you doing?
This must lead to a price jump.
The rest of us don't have phones.
It must be given to the top two.
Is it offered to those...
who bought land
with favorable conditions?
Why don't we join forces
and make ourselves some ramyeon?
- Then...
- Good idea.
Gather some money as payment, then.
- What?
- Gather some money as payment.
We'll provide the water.
You should include us too
since we can provide the water.
I'm selling this for five dollars.
Three dollars.
- Two dollars.
- One dollar.
How about 70 cents?
Is this how it's going to be?
- Hurry.
- Sell it for 50 cents.
Okay, 50 cents.
I'll definitely buy that.
- Okay.
- Us three should eat together.
This is all that I can do.
You...
It doesn't get me
in the mood though.
Why are you shaking that?
This is all that I can do.
I'll lose muscle at this rate.
Sitting all day will do that to me.
Get your lottery tickets!
- Get your lottery tickets.
- Lottery tickets?
Get your lottery tickets.
(The lottery ticket vendor
from Chungcheong Province)
- How much is it?
- It's...
ten dollars per ticket.
- I'll buy one.
- I'll buy one too.
- What is that?
- We have no choice.
Those who don't have assets
need to gamble with the lottery.
- What?
- What is that?
- These are lottery tickets.
- I'll take one!
- Lottery tickets?
- I'll take one.
- Each of you...
- I'll take three.
- Lottery tickets?
- I'll take one.
I'll take three.
- What?
- Ten dollars.
What on earth?
- He spilled his coffee.
- I'll take one.
- What?
- He spilled his coffee.
- Darn it!
- Gosh.
- Unbelievable.
Can someone give me a towel?
I'm selling paper towels!
(Unfortunately, paper towels
are in Gwangju.)
I'm selling paper towels!
- How much is it?
- Ten dollars.
- That'll be ten dollars.
Ten dollars? I'll take it all.
- I can't give you all of it.
- I need it to wipe this all up.
I'll offer you this much.
After all I did to get the coffee?
- That much for ten dollars?
- Yes.
That much for ten dollars?
It's not enough.
I'll give you what you need.
- The prize money is 200 dollars.
- Wait, 200 dollars?
- I'll take one. How much is it?
- Wait, 200 dollars per ticket?
- I'll choose mine.
- No, ten dollars per ticket.
I'll buy a ticket too.
- You can only buy one.
- Ten dollars.
- This...
- Here you go.
Here.
- There's a 1 in 4 chance.
- You can only buy one.
- Sorry?
- There's a 1 in 4 chance.
- A 1 in 4 chance?
- That's not too bad.
I hope I win the prize money.
The winning ticket will have
three of the same faces.
Three of the same faces.
Sounds good.
(They dream of turning
their lives around.)
Darn it.
- Mine's a dud.
- Can I buy one more?
- Can I?
- Jong Kook.
- Mine's a dud.
- Here I go.
- Jong Kook...
- I have the money to buy more.
Suk Jin, darn it.
- Darn, that was close.
- Mine's a dud.
- Darn it.
- Yes!
So Min, I won the prize
with three of your faces.
- What?
- No way.
- Unbelievable.
- You won the prize?
This is the worst.
Only the rich
get richer in this world.
- Good for you.
- Nothing's working for me.
How can only the rich
get richer in this world?
- Haha, you!
- Only Ji Hyo won the prize.
The ticket vendor will be back.
- Mine's a dud.
- No way.
- Ji Hyo.
- Did you really win the prize?
- Yes, with So Min's faces.
- Lucky you.
Why is she the only one
who is lucky among us?
It's done!
- Let's eat it with kimchi.
- Sure.
Here you go.
- This...
- This looks good.
(Suk Jin is still
cleaning up the coffee.)
Just look at this mess.
Why did you spill coffee there?
I didn't even get to take a sip.
(Slurping)
Just a second.
Should we make another?
The ramyeon is to die for.
Gosh, this is delicious.
It's even better
because we're outdoors.
Ramyeon tastes the best
when outdoors.
Yes, outdoors.
Those darn brats.
(Those darn brats.)
Did you cuss them out?
What? Well, I couldn't help myself.
Why did you cuss at us?
What's so wrong
with cursing the rich?
- The rich?
- You should've been smart...
with your investments.
A well exploded on my property.
I bought the wrong kind of land.
Water got pumped up
from below the surface.
Let's ride it out, Suk Jin.
Jong Kook.
- Let's ride it out.
- We should join forces.
- I can't take it anymore.
- I know.
The towels are over here.
You can buy some from Jong Kook.
- Really?
- He has towels.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Jong Kook, can you hand me
a towel? You and I should...
- My head's spinning.
- What's wrong?
What's wrong? What is it?
I stood up too quickly.
- Was it due to all the labor?
- Yes.
- Can I have one?
- I feel for you.
Right? Can I have a towel, then?
You should offer me
something in exchange.
What would you like to have?
Bring me whatever you have.
- Okay.
- I'll accept anything.
Jong Kook, here.
(So Min throws him
a triangular gimbap.)
So Min, no way. My gosh.
Jong Kook, that's for you.
I'll give you this
in exchange for So Min's good deed.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You wanted a towel.
- Right. Thanks.
I see we've split up into groups.
- Right, you three are a team now.
- Right.
Things are cozy enough
for them as well.
I'm glad you've found
a way to survive.
So Min, I felt your love just now.
I'm going to make myself at home.
You, me, and So Min should team up.
Right, we should.
If only you were situated
around here.
If I get too annoyed,
I'll buy the land in the center...
and throw things as if
this were "Squid Game."
- Like this.
- That you should.
Ramyeon is the best
when there is barely enough.
It tastes better
when eaten as a group of four.
- Of course.
- Right?
Having money sure is good.
It's now time for you
to receive your first payments.
Okay.
Bring in the status board.
(Who earned the most money
from the land they had?)
Why did Jong Kook lose money?
(The status board is revealed.)
(Land Appraisal at noon)
(Favorable, Unfavorable)
(Jong Kook's total profits at 12 p.m.)
Jong Kook lost money.
- Haha, you earned a lot.
- I earned 200 dollars.
- Suk Jin too.
- This is how valuable...
my land is.
(Suk Jin's total profits at 12 p.m.)
- Hold on a second.
- I can buy two more.
I should purchase more.
It's all about investing now.
- In total...
- So Min earned 400 dollars.
(So Min's total profits at 12 p.m.)
I earned a lot from my land.
What did you purchase? Oh, Yongsan.
In total, my profit is 300 dollars.
You can purchase four more.
(They turn their focus to So Min.)
You'll receive your money
according to the status board.
Thank you. Can I purchase
land from others now?
Where should I buy next?
I can't jump over Jong Kook
to go to the bathroom.
- Darn it.
- If you can jump two at a time...
If you can jump two at a time,
- pay Ji Hyo ten dollars.
- And?
I'll let you pass for free.
- And then jump from here.
- I have a question.
Can I buy someone else's land
if I want to?
You can get that done
during the purchase phase.
However, the price
will be 150 dollars.
- One hundred fifty dollars?
- To purchase land owned by others?
- That's right.
- But we can buy whatever we want.
- Exactly.
- Which land should I buy?
So Min, you bought two lands,
didn't you?
I bought three.
Yongsan and...
- So Min got 400 dollars worth.
- Yes.
- It's favorable.
- Right.
So even if I buy So Min's land
for 150 dollars,
- I'll have 50 dollars more later.
- You'll have more.
So I must buy two lands of hers.
The same goes for Suk Jin's land.
What does he have?
Oh, you should buy Suk Jin's land.
You'll get extra 50 dollars
no matter what.
(The price of Dong-gu, Ulsan, will
plunge unlike their expectations.)
You'll get extra 50 dollars
no matter what.
- It must be favorable. Yes.
- Yes.
Please. I only have this one.
- Pardon?
- It's 50 dollars.
What about 50 dollars?
- You should give it to me. Yes.
- I should give it to you?
If the price goes down,
- should I pay?
- Yes.
It's my land.
It's actually a tax.
Really?
When someone buys our land,
will I get the money?
- No, it's not like that.
- Gosh, what's this?
Are you a communist or what?
- You pay taxes for everything.
- When someone buys my land,
- shouldn't I get the money?
- What?
- Who takes it then?
- Who takes it?
- Us.
- It's not reasonable.
- You should give it to him.
- Hey.
What kind of country is this?
We bought the land.
- It belongs to the country.
- Then...
- it's better not to buy it.
- Right.
- Tell them.
- Then...
- Hear me out.
- It doesn't make sense.
We built the infrastructure
for you to eat and sleep.
- Infrastructure?
- Come on.
- This is...
- Does it make sense?
The one who sold it
should get the money.
- It's like we...
- We can pay taxes.
- A real estate transfer tax.
We can pay a transfer tax.
If I sell it for 150 dollars,
I can pay 50 dollars.
- I mean...
- You're right.
You can trade yourselves then.
- Can we?
- You can do it yourselves.
Without us, the real estate agency.
- If we do it ourselves...
- Without commission?
(They can trade
without the real estate agency.)
Won't you be arrested
if you trade without paying taxes?
- Jong Kook.
- Without commission?
Jong Kook.
I'll buy your land for 100 dollars.
Do you want to buy my land?
- Will you give me 100 dollars?
- Yes.
- That'd be great.
- That's why. Sell it to me.
- I'll buy it.
- It sounds good.
- Really?
- I want to buy that land.
Okay. If you buy it for 100 dollars,
I can buy another land.
I'll buy it for 100 dollars.
(Dong-gu, Ulsan: 200 dollars up
at 12 p.m., 300 dollars down at 1 p.m.)
(It's getting close to 1 p.m. now.)
(Suk Jin needs to sell his land
quickly.)
For your information,
it's 150 dollars with the agency.
But I'll sell it for 120 dollars.
If you're going to buy it...
I should get it for 120 dollars.
How about 130 dollars?
I'll get it for 120 dollars.
- You should give me 130 dollars.
- Suk Jin.
- I'll buy it for 130 dollars.
- Okay. 130 dollars.
- How about 140 dollars?
- For 140 dollars?
I say 150 dollars.
No more than that.
- For 150 dollars?
- For 150 dollars.
It's better to buy it
with the agency then.
- I'm not buying it.
- Because he will...
I should pay the agency
for nothing then.
That's better. It's better for him
to buy it from them.
I know. That's why
he wants to sell it to me.
- But I don't know why.
- Sell it to me.
Why do you want to buy that land?
(Killing the mood)
Because it will go up
by 200 dollars.
There are so many unexplored lands.
There are a lot of good factors.
Why would you want to buy it
when there are many good factors?
It's because I know
I will gain from the land.
You should buy this kind of land
for 50 dollars.
- There are other lands.
- I know.
- Buy something else then.
- I'll pay 50 dollars.
You should give me
the original price at least.
I can't.
They will take it then.
- I won't buy it.
- They will take it.
There's an order here.
- All right.
- Okay.
It's better to sell it and get money
than to be taken away from me.
I think I should buy the land
to block people from the restroom.
It's 7 of us, right?
I'm 6th place again.
What's wrong?
- Are you 6th?
- I'm 5th.
What's wrong with us today?
This is weird.
I'm one rank higher than you.
(Bitter)
Wait. But it's...
Didn't you give them out?
I should pick them.
Why did you give them out?
They asked me to do so.
But Myung Jae...
I'm sorry,
but don't we have to pick this?
- Myung Jae gave these out.
- Even if it's just 100 dollars...
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- Myung Jae gave these out.
- That's true.
- We should pick them.
- Hey.
Lee Myung Jae.
- No. Why?
- We should do it again.
- Why?
- Right. Because Myung Jae...
- We should pick them ourselves.
- Yes.
I'm fine with doing it again.
Mine isn't that good.
- Let's do it again.
- Myung Jae...
- I don't...
- Those who want to do it again,
do it again.
(Then those who want to do it again,
do it again!)
(1st place will step out of it.)
- I mean...
- What is your rank?
- I'm first.
- What's your rank?
- Myung Jae...
- I'm not doing it again.
- You guys can switch.
I'm first.
- No.
- I can buy the land, right?
Okay, I got it.
- Myung Jae.
- Darn it.
Come over here and cook something.
Eat.
It's all yours.
Come over to the fridge and eat.
- So Min, give me 100 dollars then.
- Okay.
- You can give me the land deed.
We're going to trade now. Can I go?
You can go when it's for a trade.
- Is it okay?
- He said it's okay.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for 100 dollars.
- I should've not bought it.
- A hundred dollars is still good.
What did you say?
If they don't go to the restroom...
They should go to the restroom.
How can I have five people who want
to use the restroom every hour?
That's...
I heard it's on sale.
- How about 50 dollars?
- I want 100 dollars.
A hundred is a little...
- Give 100 dollars to me.
- Because...
He has too little money anyway.
- I don't have money.
- I said no.
I got 200 dollars.
How about 40 dollars?
I can't sell it for 40 dollars.
- Okay, then.
- Because something good...
- will happen later.
- I should buy three lands.
Let's go with 40 dollars.
I'll give you 10 dollars later.
- Then bring 40 dollars.
- Yes.
Gosh, 40 dollars?
It's 40.
I'll trade right away.
(He's acting
until right before making the deal.)
Here's 40 dollars.
(The 40-dollar deal is made.)
We made a contract.
I should go down.
- This land.
- I should expand from here.
This is my land.
Give me the deed.
- Here it is.
- Thank you.
Darn it.
(Dong-gu, Ulsan: 200 dollars up
at 12 p.m., 300 dollars down at 1 p.m.)
(Laughing)
Why?
(So happy)
This became minus.
He sold the land.
(It will decrease
by 300 dollars per hour.)
I was so nervous and worried
that he might not buy it.
What did you say?
I finally sold that land.
You got a weird one, didn't you?
It must be minus.
- Make a deal, Jae Suk.
- We made a contract.
- I should expand from here.
- I think some lands...
- I should expand from here. Right.
- The price of some lands goes down.
There must be land
with an oil field.
- The land 1,000 dollars worth?
- I should find the golden land.
Excuse me.
Are you a gangster
around the neighborhood?
My land is sold.
- Is it sold?
- I don't have any place to stay.
I should buy one too.
I'll buy these.
Gwangjin-gu, Geumcheon-gu,
and Nam-gu.
Gwangjin-gu, Seoul.
Is it done?
- Oh, my gosh.
- I should buy it.
(He found the land
that is 400 dollars.)
- Me?
- Why?
- Oh, my.
- You must hit a jackpot.
- This is a jackpot.
(What is it?)
- Why is he overreacting?
- Oh, my gosh.
- Why?
- It's a jackpot.
Which land is it?
- Oh, my.
- How many did you get?
He's rich. A rich landowner.
Haha's land.
I guess there's something.
I got to move into this area.
(Jae Suk's overreaction
shakes the real estate world.)
- I picked good ones.
- Whose is it?
It's Jae Suk.
(Super excited
about extra 50 dollars)
(Geumcheon-gu, Seoul: 50 dollars up
by 12 p.m., 1 p.m., 2 p.m., 3 p.m.)
(He bought 3 and all 3 lands
have favorable conditions!)
This is amazing.
(It makes those in the lower ranks
feel deprived.)
- Where are you moving into?
- Yes?
- Sorry?
- Where are you moving into?
You can see it.
(The rich landowner got excited.)
(The middle-aged rich guy
loves this world so much.)
Is it that good?
He might be acting.
- It could be acting. We don't know.
- I picked good ones for now.
Jae Suk has too much land.
- Jae Suk's land...
- He's a rich landowner.
Gangnam-gu, Seocho-gu,
and Eunpyeong-gu.
That one is good.
I thought the land near the forest
would be obviously nice.
Honestly,
I'm buying the areas
I want to live in.
I'll get it.
I'm screwed. What should I do?
I'm in trouble.
I'm screwed. The price went down.
(Gangnam-gu, Seoul is unfavorable.)
This is bad. What do I do?
(Seocho-gu: 50 dollars up at 12 p.m.
and 1 p.m., 300 dollars down at 2 p.m.)
I'm in trouble.
I should sell Seocho-gu quickly.
This one is better. Eunpyeong-gu.
I shouldn't buy the areas in Seoul.
Thank you.
It's done. It's good.
I'll buy Gangseo-gu and Jung-gu.
What?
(Gangseo-gu, Seoul: 300 dollars down
at 12 p.m., 1 p.m., 2 p.m., and 3 p.m.)
(Even the virtual world
is affected by Suk Jin.)
Hey, Gangnam isn't popular here.
Mapo-gu, Songpa-gu,
and Haeundae-gu, Busan.
(He just bought the areas he likes
regardless of the conditions.)
(Haeundae-gu: 300 dollars down
at 12 p.m., 1 p.m., 2 p.m., and 3 p.m.)
(Songpa-gu: 100 dollars up at 12 p.m.,
1 p.m., 200 down at 2 p.m., 3 p.m.)
What? Why?
(Songpa-gu: 100 dollars up at 12 p.m.,
1 p.m., 200 down at 2 p.m., 3 p.m.)
Gosh.
Oh, no.
- Why?
- Jae Suk must've gotten good ones.
Yes. He bought some great ones.
- We should get his land.
- But...
Jae Suk is taking the lead.
Why does he have so much?
Because...
- He had some land at first.
- The price of the land increased.
You guys should know.
You should buy as much land
as possible to make money.
- Is that so?
- Think about it.
- It goes up by 200 or 300 dollars.
- Right. The price goes up.
But I don't have any land.
Even if you have cash,
it means nothing.
- But...
- You should buy land.
- The price goes down as well.
- I know.
I'm sorry, but you don't know what
it's like for those who got nothing.
- Have you ever not had any land?
- I don't have money to buy it.
- Have you...
- That's my land.
It's okay for now.
Have you ever had no land?
This is my land, mister.
The poor ones don't even have money
to buy land.
So that's why I'm telling you
that you should invest.
Yes, but I don't have money
to buy land.
- So...
- Give me some money then!
(Give me some money then!)
You should give me some money then.
You should've done better earlier.
Why did you do a bad job?
It's not because I did a bad job.
Is it something I can do well?
- Don't talk with him. Come here.
- You should've done well.
- My goodness.
- Let's go. You're fifth, right?
- I'm fifth.
- Buy land.
Goodness gracious.
He's saying that I should invest
when I'm worrying about surviving.
You can survive just with protein.
- Why are you complaining?
- My gosh.
Mister,
which area do you have over there?
- Are you going to buy it?
- Wait.
- Where?
- I'll just buy Seo-gu, Gwangju.
- Which land did you say?
- I should survive at least.
(Seo-gu, Gwangju?)
(Seo-gu, Gwangju
that Jong Kook chose is...)
(Seo-gu, Gwangju: 300 dollars down
at 12 p.m., 1 p.m., 2 p.m., and 3 p.m.)
(The only land
whose price will plummet)
(He tried to think of a way
to sell it.)
You're going to buy it?
- Seo-gu, Gwangju?
- It's...
You would have nowhere to go.
Forget it.
- Anyway, Jong Kook will...
- I can just give you 150 dollars.
Finally, the Squid Game has started.
(The Squid Game has started.)
- Why?
- Round two.
The Squid Game.
Someone will be eliminated and die.
Why would you want to buy
Seo-gu, Gwangju?
Excuse me?
I'm telling you.
Surviving is my priority.
- Did you buy it?
- Yes.
- I...
- Where?
Give me the land deed, sir.
- Give me Seo-gu.
- Gosh, this is...
Hurry up.
- Now I...
- My goodness.
don't have to worry about surviving.
This is the one for Seo-gu, Gwangju.
- But you should be careful.
- Why?
- It doesn't feel good.
(Seo-gu, Gwangju: 300 dollars down
at 12 p.m., 1 p.m., 2 p.m., and 3 p.m.)
The land doesn't feel good.
Okay.
He's helping me.
- Mister, it doesn't feel good.
- Yes.
So only the rich will be richer.
The poor will stay poor.
This is why...
ordinary people are just watching
others making money.
I guess you were very hungry.
I'll buy Jung-gu, Busan
and Yeongdeungpo-gu. The two.
I'll get them.
I should go to the restroom.
(He might have to pee quickly.
He bought the land near the restroom.)
Please be a jackpot.
Please be favorable.
I'm going to turn the tables
with a favorable land.
(Checking the deed
after a deep breath)
After going up once,
it will keep going down.
(The price will plunge again later.)
(Jung-gu: 200 dollars up at 12 p.m.,
1 p.m., 400 down at 2 p.m., 3 p.m.)
Jung-gu, Busan.
(He needs to sell it quickly again.)
(Jung-gu: 200 dollars up at 12 p.m.,
1 p.m., 400 down at 2 p.m., 3 p.m.)
Can I take it back?
It's past 12, right?
I'll go crazy after that.
Gosh.
(On top of that, the price
of Yeongdeungpo-gu doesn't change.)
For real?
This is annoying.
How can I sell it? I don't think
I can sell it as I sold one earlier.
This is terrible.
I want to go to the restroom though.
When I have to go...
I can't go to the restroom.
It's my turn.
I can't go
because I don't have money.
I can go to the bathroom now.
- Ji Hyo, I'll pay ten dollars.
- Yes?
- I can pass then.
- Yes.
Then...
I signed a memorandum of understanding
with Jong Kook, so... Wait.
Did someone buy this land?
(The owner of Yeongdo-gu, Busan
has changed.)
Who bought this area?
Who? Is it you?
- Why did you buy it?
- She bought it.
I paid a lot.
- For 150 dollars?
- No. For 100 dollars.
Geumcheon-gu, Seoul.
If so...
(He paid ten dollars to check
the information of Geumcheon-gu.)
I'll pay ten dollars
to use it first.
(The reason why Se Chan asks for
information about Jae Suk's land)
(Jae Suk was making a fuss
when buying the land.)
(Rich Jae Suk's land purchase
stirred up the people.)
(Jae Suk cheered 3 times
while checking 3 lands.)
(Se Chan was staring at Jae Suk
in the meantime.)
(He paid ten dollars
to check the information.)
This one?
This is about Geumcheon-gu?
(What?)
Why did he shout then?
It's nothing much.
(It's not as big as he thought.)
It's not a big deal.
Guys, if you give me
just ten dollars...
so that I can buy lottery tickets...
- I...
- If I win...
I'll get Jung-gu, Daegu.
Jung-gu, Ulsan.
The unfavorable factor will be gone.
Whose land?
Yes? It's over.
- It's over.
- Guys.
I really have to buy
lottery tickets.
- I have 20 dollars.
- Just give me 10 dollars.
- What?
- I'll pay back.
Dunk your head in there.
(The loan condition of Se Chan Bank
is quite unique.)
- What?
- Dunk your head in there.
Then I'll give you ten dollars.
- Will you give me ten dollars?
- Yes.
Dunk your head completely.
(Haha desperately needs ten dollars
as lottery is his only hope.)
You little punk.
Hold on.
(Screaming)
(A bald head shampoo show)
What? Is he doing a mission?
Hey.
The water will turn black as you
paint your head with a marker.
- He's doing a fun mission.
- I said I'd give you money later.
- Haha, when I get the lottery...
- Give it to me.
I don't know.
Is your mission to dunk your head?
(In "Running Man" world,
they fool others for ten dollars.)
Give ten dollars to me, you punk.
You said you would give me
ten dollars if I dunk my head.
And you really did it?
Hurry up. Give it to me.
I don't have money.
(So Min's phone is ringing
at that moment.)
Why does everyone have
a phone except for me?
- Hello.
- Bad news is coming.
Why do I not have a phone?
Does everyone have one?
I guess only some people have one.
I guess it's optional
depending on the land they have.
Depending on the land?
- It comes with the land.
- I see.
- I'm so full.
- What is she doing?
(Strike bodybuilding poses every
30 minutes to remove a bad factor.)
She did it earlier.
She did it while looking at me.
(Strike bodybuilding poses every
30 minutes to remove a bad factor.)
What is that?
- What is that?
- I don't know.
You're good, So Min.
She's good.
It seems she's done it many times.
(He suddenly gets up.)
Can you not use the air fryer?
It must work.
Can I use the air fryer too?
- Which one?
- Can I use the air fryer for this?
- Yes.
- Of course, you can.
Do you want to eat
crunchy fried chicken?
Yes.
What are you doing all of a sudden?
Why are you dancing?
For some reason.
It's convenient to use a microwave.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- There are two. Okay, I got it.
- I used it well.
- No, I won't change.
- You won't change?
- No.
- Yongsan-gu seems nice.
I'll sell it for 140 dollars.
What? I don't have 140 dollars.
I said, I don't have money.
What are you doing, Se Chan?
What are you doing?
Don't worry about me.
- What are you doing?
What is it?
- Get lost.
- What is it?
- Why?
- Don't mind me.
- What are you doing?
- Get lost.
I must do this.
(Shaking off the bad factor)
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
This is not a weird thing.
- Don't mind me.
- What are you doing?
It's not something weird. I'm done.
After some time,
the price will go up again.
Many people are saying that
they're not going to the restroom.
Don't turn the cameras off.
So Min bought all the land
we should pass to use the restroom.
She bought them all.
The restroom is meaningless.
You can pay me and go.
- What?
- Pay me and go to the bathroom.
Hold on.
So Min would be the most annoyed...
when I give Ji Hyo ten dollars...
and skip those three areas
to use the restroom.
- Right. If you get the middle one.
- Jae Suk.
I have Nam-gu, Busan,
so if I buy Dongnae-gu...
and give Ji Hyo ten dollars...
to skip those areas,
that'd be the best.
Where?
That will make So Min
annoyed the most.
Seriously.
Let's trade. The real estate.
Take my land...
- and give me one.
- How about 20 dollars?
Let's switch ones with good factors.
Then I'll show you Haeundae-gu.
- You've heard about Jung-gu, Busan?
- Yes.
It's a favorable area.
So I want to switch with a good one.
You'll get money
as soon as it becomes 1 p.m.
- Can I get money from your land?
- Mine is the same.
- Is it? Right away?
- Yes.
- Shall we switch then?
- Haeundae-gu?
- Yes.
Then I'll change Haeundae-gu
with mine.
- Switch then.
- Switch.
Exchange.
Yes. Thank you.
This isn't good or bad.
I'll...
(Haeundae-gu, Busan: 300 dollars down at
12 p.m., 1 p.m., 2 p.m., and 3 p.m.)
(The unfavorable blue land)
If it's a minus...
Can you lie?
You can't lie.
- Who?
- Hey.
What kind of land is this?
You shouldn't lie.
Gosh, this is...
- It's hilarious.
- Hello.
Why? What did they tell you to do?
Okay, I got it.
- What did they tell you to do?
- Oh, my.
(Suk Jin who was curious about
others' calls got the first call.)
- Come on. Let me see.
- I can't show you.
It must be hula.
What are you doing?
Does he have to do hula
because he got it from me?
That was mine.
What are you doing?
I can see your armpit hair.
This is annoying.
I'll give you 300 dollars
if you buy Haeundae-gu.
(Haeundae-gu is annoying
in many ways.)
I'll give it to you if you take it.
The welfare of this country...
- Come on.
- Darn it. I hate that.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
Go to the restroom
if you want to poop.
Stop, Se Chan. It's disgusting.
- Don't do that.
- Get lost.
- Are you twerking?
- Go over there, will you?
- Gosh.
- Hey.
- Why?
- Go over there.
Why? I should do this.
How dare you...
(Jong Kook who has Seo-gu, Gwangju
removed the bad factor as well.)
- What is it?
- I had to break the gourd.
Why do they have missions?
One of my lands
became a dumping ground.
Isn't this Nanji Island?
It became...
(The owner of the land started
throwing trash thoughtlessly.)
(Everyone mistook it
as a dumping ground.)
- Stop throwing trash in my land.
- I didn't make it like this.
- It was always like this.
- Hey.
Hey.
What are you doing?
- What's that?
- Why does she keep doing it?
- What is it?
- What is she doing?
She's good.
- Gosh.
- She's good though.
She is good.
- So Min.
- I hate that so much.
- So Min does it well.
- She is good.
- She must have done it before.
- She has the right expression.
It's 1 p.m.
(It's time for the second payout.)
The profits will be revealed.
The profits.
Let's see.
(Jae Suk's total profits at 1 p.m.:
80 dollars)
- I made 0 dollars.
- I made 0 dollars too.
(Jong Kook and Suk Jin
got rid of the bad factors.)
- How about me?
- You made 45 dollars.
It isn't half bad.
Haha has the best lands.
- So Min made a lot of money.
- Haha.
Before the purchase,
- you will have a mission.
- Okay.
Here comes the mission.
Will this decide the rankings?
Yes, this will decide the rankings.
- Good.
- You will receive money too.
- We will receive money too.
- Let's go.
- Please gather around.
- All right.
This isn't easy.
Don't you guys want to use
the restroom?
Suk Jin.
I am holding it in like crazy.
- I am waiting, but no one is going.
- No one is going.
- I will explain the rules.
- Okay.
It's a nice game for residents.
- What is it?
- Soap Water Steal the Chairs.
Soap Water Steal the Chairs.
- One of the residents will rule.
- Jong Kook.
Please make me 2nd or 3rd place.
- You know...
- Jong Kook.
Jong Kook can make that happen.
- That's incredible.
- If you make me first place,
I will give you
a land of your choice.
All right. Music, cue.
(Round 1 begins
with 7 people and 6 chairs.)
I am not sure about this.
- It won't be easy.
- We need to dance.
Suk Jin.
(Slipping)
- It's insane.
- Be careful.
Be careful.
(The soapy floor is more slippery
than they thought.)
Circle around.
The floor is so slippery.
- It's slippery.
- It's no joke.
It's so slippery.
Don't move the chairs in advance.
- Haha, don't do that.
- What are you doing?
(Singing)
(They hum and pretend to know
the recent song.)
- What's this song? It's nice.
- "Love Dive."
- Please be considerate of...
- This is mine.
- Okay.
- I sat down.
(Jong Kook, Haha)
I sat down.
(Ji Hyo is okay.)
All right.
I sat down.
(The rivals have met again.)
- I sat down.
- Sit down on the chair.
Sit down.
- He sat down.
- Suk Jin.
(The weakest members had
a fierce rival match.)
So Min is last place.
I am exhausted.
(Both of them are exhausted.)
- So Min.
- It went exactly as I predicted.
I could have stolen it,
but Suk Jin...
- It's hard.
- I will remove one chair.
- This is hard.
Circle around the chairs once more.
Music, cue.
- Let's go.
- This game isn't easy.
(There are five chairs.)
- It's "Tomboy."
- Tom!
Tomboy
It's "Tomboy."
(Whistling)
I sat down.
Tomboy
(Suk Jin goes against Haha
this time.)
You must be on the soapy floor
when you sit on the chair.
Who stole the chair?
(Haha grabs the chair.)
Suk Jin keeps being the target.
- I keep being the target.
- I feel bad for him.
(They make strange noises
as they play around.)
- They are happy.
- Hey.
- The neighbors get along well.
- They are happy.
- What a friendship.
Why don't we join forces...
and steal Ji Hyo's chair?
That's a good idea.
- Are you targeting Ji Hyo now?
- Let me take it.
- Let's go. I won't steal it.
- Let's go.
- Let go.
- Let's put it here.
- Give it to me.
- Okay.
- Let's put it in front of So Min.
We will get criticized
if we gang up on Ji Hyo.
Why don't we attack Jae Suk?
It's over once you sit on a chair.
That's nonsense, you punk.
Why are you swearing at me?
- Why are you swearing at me?
- Why are you angry?
Put yourself in my shoes.
I have no money or land.
I have nothing.
(A father's desperate cry)
- Shall we play a game?
- Rock-paper-scissors?
- Okay. For real.
- For real.
- I will give the chair...
to the winner.
- Okay.
- Give me the chair.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- I will do that.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's play Subtract One.
- Subtract One? Okay.
- Come on.
- Your butt...
- Rock-paper-scissors, subtract one
Rock-paper-scissors, subtract one
(My goodness.)
(Two scissors)
He played two scissors.
What?
What's up with Suk Jin?
(A father's surprise attack)
What?
What's up with Suk Jin?
I can't believe Suk Jin.
(Then he sits on the chair.)
- Haha is out.
- Am I out?
(Haha is out.)
I can't believe him.
- Suk Jin.
- Seriously.
- I think you will be criticized.
- It's okay.
That's life.
- Don't upload this on YouTube.
- That's life.
Don't upload this on YouTube.
Haha's fans, I am sorry.
I apologize.
Seongsan Elementary School, rise!
Now,
it's time to pick 5th place
with 4 chairs.
My goodness.
All right. Music, cue.
(Round 3 begins.)
(It's Jae Suk's favorite song,
"Kiss Kiss" by LABOUM.)
I will make your lips
Shine
(They dance
with tension in the air.)
He got the chair.
- You need to circle around.
- Circle around.
You need to circle around. Come on.
(It's their first time
seeing Suk Jin's passion.)
Come on.
(Slipping)
(The timing of the whistle
was against Suk Jin.)
What was that?
What are you doing?
Why are you grabbing my pants?
- What's up with Suk Jin?
- What are you doing?
- What's up with him?
- You punk.
You will understand
if you are poor like me.
(Kicking)
Suk Jin is working hard.
(My goodness.)
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Why?
- The chair is in my hand.
- For goodness' sake.
(He suggests rock-paper-scissors
as if he is being generous.)
- I can't believe him.
- I mean...
(He attacks after a pause.)
This middle-aged man is too much.
- Mister.
- For goodness' sake.
- He is a bully.
- What was that?
He is too much.
He stole the chair after asking
to play rock-paper-scissors.
He is too much.
- I am penniless. I am sorry.
- He is a bully.
It's okay. It was pretty good.
- It was pretty good.
- I agree.
- You won't get criticized for that.
- Right?
I am sorry,
but are you the judge
on what gets criticized?
- I think about...
- No!
- what the viewers will say.
- Good.
- He is a total bully.
- Okay.
Okay. I admit it. I am a bully.
Get ready.
Music, cue.
Ji Hyo, you are the target.
Be careful.
Let's go.
("Twist King" by Turbo)
I love it.
He is approaching me again.
You need to circle around.
(It's the perfect song
for dancing on the soapy floor.)
(Look over there.)
(An uninvited duo
crashed the dance floor.)
(They have fun
regardless of the game.)
All right.
(Whistling)
(Incredible speed)
(Freeze)
- That was...
- Are you serious?
- He is good.
- Jong Kook.
How does Suk Jin do that?
He is really good at this game.
Jong Kook, you are out.
Suk Jin showed a b-boying move.
His freeze was impressive.
(There is a reason why
he is so determined.)
I don't have any money.
I'm sorry, I must win.
I will win!
Did the price drop?
(His investment
faced hardship from the start.)
(Despite the younger members'
mistreatment and teasing,)
(Suk Jin waited for his big break.)
(Now is the only chance
to turn the tables.)
(Suk Jin becomes competitive
once or twice a year.)
(After 6 matches,)
(he becomes the last one standing.)
Suk Jin won!
- Seriously.
- He has incredible willpower.
For goodness' sake.
He deserved to win.
- He was determined.
- Good job.
Please congratulate him.
- Okay.
- I had nothing.
Now, go back to your land...
- or communal land.
- Let's go.
Here it is. It's communal land.
Shall I buy land now?
Suk Jin became rich
thanks to the game.
Suk Jin, you are rich.
Please show me Yongsan-gu.
I will give you ten dollars.
(Whispering)
(He checks information
on So Min's Yongsan-gu.)
Here it is.
Yongsan-gu.
(Yongsan-gu, Seoul: 300 dollars up
at 2 p.m., 300 dollars up at 3 p.m.)
I will buy this land.
Yes. I will give you 150 dollars.
(So Min's favorite place
gets demolished.)
Who bought my land?
Suk Jin?
Suk Jin, you suddenly bought
my land.
I could have sold it to you
for a cheaper price.
- Jung-gu.
- Jung-gu, Daegu?
- It's Se Chan's, right?
- Yes.
(He checks information
on Se Chan's Jung-gu, Daegu.)
I will buy Jung-gu.
(He purchases the land
upon checking the good factors.)
Jung-gu.
Why does Suk Jin look
so greedy today?
Today,
- he is showing his greedy side.
- He is being greedy today.
- He is showing his greedy side.
- Seriously.
Look at his back.
- Look at his back.
- Hey.
Suk Jin isn't listening to us.
Is Bupyeong-gu okay?
I will take chances.
I don't have much money.
I will buy it.
He is ambitious. He wants to win.
You know,
my power is coming out.
I wanted to go to the restroom
from the start,
but I am holding it in until now.
- I am holding it in until now.
- Suk Jin.
You are mistaken
if you think you are holding it in.
Your pants are pretty wet.
It doesn't show...
- because I rolled around.
- Your pants are pretty wet.
It doesn't show
because I rolled around.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- I see why you worked hard.
I see why you were determined
to survive until the end.
It's no wonder
things got more watery.
- I tried my best to hide it.
- I see.
Does anyone want to trade land
with Haeundae-gu?
- Haeundae-gu?
- Yes.
- Do you want to trade?
- Which land do you offer?
Do you have land in mind?
Do you want to trade Haeundae-gu
with Nam-gu?
Where is Nam-gu?
Is it right next to Haeundae-gu?
- It's right next to Haeundae-gu.
- Nam-gu, Daegu?
You should give me some more money.
It's good land.
Nam-gu is good land too.
- It doesn't bring in much money,
- Okay.
- but it's good land.
- Same here.
Give me 20 dollars.
I need money.
I only have 20 dollars right now.
If the price goes down,
I won't sit still.
The price won't go down.
- You have to promise me that.
- I promise you that.
- I don't have such lands.
- Are the numbers in red?
- They are in red.
Really?
Did the price fall for Nam-gu?
No. I made profits.
For goodness' sake.
Okay. Let's make the exchange.
I trust you.
Trust me. So it's...
- in Daegu.
- Nam-gu.
(They exchange Nam-gu, Daegu
and Haeundae-gu, Busan.)
Here. It's Haeundae-gu.
(Haeundae-gu, Busan:
300 dollars down at 2 p.m.)
I made 100 dollars.
(300 dollars down at 2 p.m. and 3 p.m.)
(Nam-gu, Daegu: 400 dollars down
at 2 p.m. and 3 p.m.)
For goodness' sake.
(400 dollars down?)
That little grasshopper.
I made 100 dollars.
(Suk Jin got tricked.)
A hundred dollars.
How could you be so evil?
(Jae Suk easily got rid
of a problematic land.)
I will go and purchase land.
Oh, there is a way
to get rid of bad factors.
- Where?
- Thank goodness.
- What?
- There is a way to get rid of it.
Can you get rid of bad factors?
I didn't know that.
(Hula dance to get rid of
bad factors.)
It's just minus 300 dollars.
- Let's cancel the trade.
- No way.
I didn't know it was possible
to get rid of bad factors.
It was right there.
- That's too much.
- The numbers are in the negative.
You lied too.
Your lie is much greater.
You reaped the benefits.
The price will begin to fall at 2 p.m.
At 2 p.m.? Now?
(The price will begin to fall now.)
I can't believe him.
I will go and purchase land.
It's the best.
(Earlier)
(Jong Kook won the lottery.)
(He visits the intermediary office
with cash.)
All right.
- Why didn't anyone buy Guro-gu?
- What? I didn't know.
I will go and look.
(Many lands are still unoccupied.)
(Glancing over)
Jung-gu, Ulsan. Buk-gu, Ulsan.
Buk-gu, Ulsan?
Buk-gu, Ulsan. Yes.
(Jong Kook chooses Buk-gu, Ulsan.)
Buk-gu, Ulsan.
(Buk-gu, Ulsan: 500 dollars up
at 2 p.m and 3 p.m.)
(500 dollars up)
My goodness.
(He purchased a jackpot land
by chance.)
This is...
(Buk-gu, Ulsan
shows the highest price.)
Hold on.
Hold on. How much do I have?
Should I buy something else?
Dong-gu, Daejeon, please.
(He purchases Dong-gu, Daejeon.)
(How is the price
for Dong-gu, Daejeon?)
- All right.
- Whatever.
(How is the price
for Dong-gu, Daejeon?)
(Dong-gu, Daejeon: 100 dollars down
at 2 p.m., 700 dollars up at 3 p.m.)
(700 dollars up?)
(He discovered
another jackpot land.)
This is my decisive move.
Guro-gu, please.
- Guro-gu, Seoul?
- Yes.
Let's take a look.
(Guro-gu, Seoul: 50 dollars down
at 2 p.m., 200 dollars up at 3 p.m.)
All right.
If I keep it until then,
I will get the original cost.
- Jong Kook, you have a call.
- Yes?
Is that so?
I am done.
Stop littering on my land.
I didn't litter. That's a landfill.
- It has always been that way.
- It looks like...
I won't be able to take
1st place or 2nd place.
I see my lands...
as I walk down now.
Where?
(Will Jong Kook be able
to come from behind?)
I can move a lot more now.
Who is it?
Hello. Jae Suk speaking.
Okay.
- It must be about Haeundae-gu.
- What's that?
(He begins the hula dance.)
Haeundae-gu
is definitely a cheerful place.
(He is getting rid of
the bad factors of Haeundae-gu.)
(He is in a good mood.)
Doing that gets rid of
the bad factors.
(Suk Jin didn't know that.)
Once I do this,
the numbers won't be in the negative
With the land I gave him,
Suk Jin will lose 300 dollars
He is so annoying.
Such is life
Suk Jin, don't criticize me
We lied to each other
So we can't say
one was better than the other
Jae Suk stepped on Jungnang-gu
multiple times while dancing.
All right. Pay up.
- Pay up.
- He stepped on it five times.
He stepped on Jungnang-gu
repeatedly.
- Who did that?
- You did.
You stepped on Jungnang-gu
as you danced.
- I was carrying out the mission.
- I saw it too.
It's still prohibited.
- That's right.
- Who owns Jungnang-gu?
- Me.
- Take ten dollars.
- Hey.
- For goodness' sake.
- The elders are talking.
- That's dirty.
- Why is your butt so wet?
- Stop it.
Ji Hyo, let me cross your land
for ten dollars.
Okay.
Get it from Se Chan.
Where are you going?
I am going to use the restroom.
You can't go from there.
Can you go from there?
I am going to find a way.
(Hammering)
What are you doing?
I am going to step on these nails.
It won't work.
Suk Jin, why are you being
so pessimistic?
(He begins to nail the wall.)
(Screaming)
For goodness' sake.
He has a condition.
He wants to go to a hospital.
If he isn't careful,
- he will skin his butt.
- He wants to go to a hospital.
- His body must be itching.
- Then Jong Kook's brother...
- will perform surgery.
- Just pay the toll.
Just pay the toll.
I can't use 20 dollars
to go to the restroom.
(He is frugal
despite having many lands.)
(He begins to break the wall.)
That works.
That's right. Try rock climbing.
Nail the wall.
Yes. Do it like Um Hong Gil.
Isn't it the first time
someone broke the wall on the show?
If he makes a path,
I will go out of business.
That's right. You will be dirt poor.
(He succeeds to climb up.)
- He is happy.
- I can't help but think,
"What am I doing?"
Hey, I hope you succeed.
He is basically paving a highway.
I can't let him do that.
I hope he falls.
- I hope he falls.
- Jae Suk is strong.
I just need one more.
(I just need one more.)
(Will he succeed in rock climbing?)
- I hope he falls.
- It will be funny.
Fall.
What is he doing?
- Did he succeed?
- What is he doing?
(He succeeded in rock climbing.)
Did he succeed?
- Yes.
- Did he succeed?
- He succeeded.
(He became the first person
to climb the set.)
Is he still hanging?
He succeeded.
- So Min.
- He is incredible.
- How will he return?
- You have to return.
How will you return?
You have to return.
So Min.
Let me use the restroom first.
(He will think afterward.)
Hold on.
(So Min brings a sheet.)
(She fills up the holes.)
(The landowner refuses
to stand there and do nothing.)
I feel so refreshed.
What are you doing?
- So Min.
- Yes?
Bye.
(So Min heads
to the intermediary office.)
She is as ridiculous as I am.
Why did she have to put a sheet
over the holes?
The unpurchased lands...
Is that Haha's land in Busan?
I want to purchase Seodaemun-gu.
- Seodaemun-gu.
- Yes.
- Gwangjin-gu, Seoul.
- So Min.
- Yes?
Hurry up and drop Jae Suk.
Hey.
Do it.
- Make him step on your land.
- Hey.
You can't do that.
I was purchasing lands.
- Push him. Now is your chance.
- Now is your chance.
Hey.
(He got caught right away.)
(The tragic climber who messed
with the wrong landowner)
- Hey.
- He will fall. Hang in there.
Gosh.
Counting 20 dollars,
30 dollars, 40 dollars...
- It's 40 dollars.
- Come on.
Three steps.
- Ten dollars.
- You took three steps.
- Three steps.
- So Min, take ten dollars.
- It's 30 dollars.
Pay 20 dollars
since you took 3 steps.
It would have been easier
to pay ten dollars each way.
You sweated for no reason.
My goodness.
Dongnae-gu, Busan.
- Dongnae-gu?
- Yes.
Buk-gu, Gwangju.
I will buy all three lands
in Daejeon.
I lost so much money.
Bo Pil, before you leave,
please make sure I don't look
overly greedy in this episode.
Suk Jin is
the epitome of greed today.
I think I look a bit greedy.
(It's time for the third payout.)
The totals are out.
(Jae Suk, Se Chan, Jong Kook,)
(Haha, Ji Hyo, So Min, Suk Jin)
- Se Chan has many good lands.
- The totals are out.
Me? Not really.
Jong Kook?
Jae Suk is 1st place.
He made 650 dollars.
He has a lot of land.
It's important to buy a lot of land.
I told you.
That's right.
Jae Suk has a lot of land.
Jong Kook has the best lands.
Jong Kook must have
a very profitable property.
I'll wait for the next round.
(He has two profitable areas.)
- It will increase by 500 dollars.
- I'll make more money next time.
Jong Kook's property?
If I get lucky,
I might place second.
(If he keeps his land,
he can turn the game around.)
Jong Kook has two areas
that will increase by 500 dollars.
- Those two areas.
- It's free, right?
- It'll go up by 500 dollars.
- I can step on...
- my own land.
- Does he have three areas?
The maximum amount is 500 dollars.
Does anyone have such areas?
- Jong Kook does.
- Jong Kook does?
- Jong Kook.
- It must be in Ulsan.
- I don't know which areas he has.
- You know the changes of Gwangju.
- Yes, I know.
The person who gets
Jong Kook's land.
I think I'll lose it
in the next round.
We have to get Jong Kook's land.
We have to find Jae Suk's land too.
(He must keep his land that will
make 700 dollars of profit.)
The member who wins this round
can turn the game around.
You have to roll it.
(As a result of a simple game
to make the final purchase...)
He threw it.
This is your final purchase.
(Suk Jin who won the mission will
make a purchase first.)
Well...
There's no property
without an owner.
Can I get information
on Buk-gu, Ulsan?
(Suk Jin gets information
on Jong Kook's land as expected.)
- Information on Buk-gu, Ulsan?
- Yes, please.
(But Buk-gu, Ulsan, is...)
(the property that will make
500 dollars of profit.)
(Awesome!)
I'll buy Buk-gu, Ulsan.
It's 150 dollars.
(Suk Jin who found the land at once
purchases it right away.)
My gosh. I hit the jackpot.
(Ripping off)
My gosh.
He bought my land right away.
(So Jong Kook lost
one of the profitable areas.)
Where else is yours?
Here.
(Suk Jin is asking about Jae Suk's land,
not about Jong Kook's.)
(The members didn't figure out about
the better property Jong Kook has.)
Is Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju, yours too?
(The members didn't figure out about
the better property Jong Kook has.)
Then...
What else does Jae Suk have?
Jae Suk's land.
The ones with "Yoo" on them.
Nam-gu, Ulsan.
- Nam-gu, Ulsan, please.
- Information on Nam-gu, Ulsan?
- Nam-gu, Ulsan.
- Are you done?
(Nam-gu, Ulsan, will make
400 dollars of profit.)
- I'll buy it.
- Okay.
Yes. I'll buy all the good ones.
It's 150 dollars? Here you go.
Look at him from behind.
He's being greedy.
He's being greedy
unlike his usual tendency.
Can I get information
on Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju?
- Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju?
- Yes.
(Gwangsan-gu, Gwangju:
100 dollars up at 3 p.m.)
I'll buy it.
(I'll buy it.)
Okay. I'll buy it.
(The value of Seongbuk-gu, Seoul,
will increase by 100 dollars.)
Okay.
(Happy)
(So the number of purple areas
decreases gradually.)
- He bought many of Jae Suk's.
- Exactly.
It's understandable because Jae Suk
had many profitable areas.
- Right.
- He made 600 dollars.
I can't buy the areas back.
- Right.
- Oh, that's right.
Can I get information on Jongno-gu?
Let's plant apple trees in Jongno
It's not so profitable,
but I'll buy it since I can make a profit.
Here you go.
I'll give you Dong-gu, Gwangju,
for 50 dollars.
- Thirty dollars.
- I'm not interested.
- He's being reckless.
- I'll give it to you for free.
(I'll give it to you for free.)
If you want to win the race,
buy Gangdong-gu, Seoul,
and Dong-gu, Gwangju.
The value of Gangdong-gu will
decrease by 200 dollars.
Why that little...
The value of Gangdong-gu will decrease
by 200 dollars.
These two areas are
the master keys to winning.
They're going to drop by
200 and 300 dollars.
That little...
(Upset)
(Jong Kook who lost
1 of his 2 profitable areas...)
I'm doomed.
Se Chan!
- It's ten dollars, right?
- Yes.
(He'll be ranked high
if he buys profitable land.)
Okay. Let's go.
- Can I check out Geumcheon-gu? Yes.
- Geumcheon-gu?
(He purchases information
on Jae Suk's land.)
Haha, you look great.
(But it won't make a big profit.)
- This is the final round.
- Then...
It'd be pointless to buy land
to make 50 dollars, right?
- It should be at least 200 dollars.
- Yes! I hit the jackpot!
- Only then I'll make enough profit.
- That's mine!
- I won't buy it.
- Give me that.
- I'll just leave.
- Are you done?
Yes.
Gosh. I lost too many of my areas.
(Next up is Jae Suk who lost
a lot of profitable areas.)
Can I get information on this area?
- Yangcheon-gu. I mean, Jungnang-gu.
- Okay.
And Seo-gu, Busan.
Gwangjin-gu as well, please.
(Then he bought all of the areas.)
Yes, I'll buy all three of them.
Would you like to buy
Jungnang-gu too?
Here's 450 dollars.
What should we do?
- Gosh. Twerking again?
- Not again.
- This must be the last time.
- I think it'll be different. Hello?
- Yes. Where? Got it.
- I hate the sight of it.
Because you bought new land?
- Did you buy another area?
- Gosh.
(He starts twerking again.)
- I was told to do this.
- I'm sick of it.
- He smells like fart.
- Hey!
- Gosh.
- I'm sick of seeing his butt.
- Seriously.
- What was that?
- I had no choice.
I had to do that in order to
avoid losing money. I'm sorry.
- Why did you show it to my face?
- Let's go!
Since this is the final round,
we'll change the rule for you.
The top 3 will survive,
and 2 of the bottom 4 will get a penalty.
- What?
- The top three will survive.
You see...
- I'd be upset if I place 3rd...
- I should be in the top 3.
- and get a penalty.
- That'd be unfair.
- I'd be upset.
- I'd be really upset too.
How do we decide the top two
at the end of the game?
Based on the money we have?
On top of the cash you have,
we'll tally the value of your land.
- A hundred dollars per area?
- Yes.
Let's check the result.
Everyone.
I'll announce the result.
(The final value of the investors'
land has been tallied.)
The first place is...
Jae Suk with
a total of 3,215 dollars.
(Jae Suk placed 1st
with 3,215 dollars.)
- Jae Suk won.
- He's rich with a lot of land.
And the 2nd and 3rd places
were neck and neck.
The 2nd and 3rd places?
But the member
who was in third place...
- dropped in the rankings.
- Really?
(The person in third place
dropped in the rankings.)
(The lucky person
who placed second safely is...)
With 2,550 dollars,
Jong Kook placed 2nd.
(Jong Kook placed second.)
- I pulled it off.
- That was unexpected.
I focused solely on basic needs.
(Jong Kook placed 2nd with 3 areas
and a total of 2,550 dollars.)
(The young man from Busan
turned his life around.)
- That's amazing.
- My, that's incredible.
The member
who could have gotten a penalty,
- but placed third and survived...
- Could it be me?
It must be Suk Jin.
I think I'm in third place
based on the money I have.
- Could it be So Min?
- I don't think it's me.
- I think it's Seok Sam.
- Oh, is it Suk Jin?
(The last person to be exempt from
the penalty is...)
It is...
Se Chan with 2,010 dollars.
- See?
- The ten dollars I got saved me.
(Se Chan placed 3rd with 12 areas
and a total of 2,010 dollars.)
- He gave me some money.
- Right.
And picked up bills from the floor.
- I'm dizzy.
- I...
I didn't expect Se Chan
to be in third place.
- Exactly.
- I'll go on.
So Min placed 4th,
and Ji Hyo placed 5th.
Suk Jin placed 6th,
and Haha placed 7th.
- Suk Jin...
(The greedy Suk Jin placed sixth?)
- But why did Suk Jin...
- Today...
- He made a lot of effort.
- For the effort he made...
- Me?
- He's ranked too low.
- I told you so.
- I'm ranked that low?
For the effort he made...
Haha, you were in third place,
but you suffered great losses...
in the final round.
- I told you not to buy the land.
- Why is Suk Jin ranked so low?
What went wrong, Suk Jin?
I mean,
there are some people like me.
People are different.
You're right.
Just as I planned...
- "Just as I planned?"
- You know...
I wanted to portray
that kind of person.
- A greedy man?
- Yes.
Anyway, today,
two of the bottom four will
get a penalty.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
- Let's go. Let's get it over with.
- This is the finale.
- This is the real finale.
- All right!
- What's the penalty?
- I'll explain to you.
It will wash your bad investments
cleanly.
- It's Random Soda Fountain.
- Oh, dear.
(Random Soda Fountain)
- Oh, gosh. It'll be sticky.
- Oh, dear.
There will be boxes
numbered from 1 to 4.
You can only see
the top of the bottles.
While looking at it,
you will drop gums...
that make soda blow up
at the same time.
Two of them will blow up...
- while the others won't.
- Right.
- You mean, with Mentos?
- Right. I get it.
Number two.
- I'll choose any number.
- Stand in front of your bottle.
- Let's go!
- Now, bite the Mentos.
(They're standing in front of
the bottles nervously.)
Drop them into the bottle
at the same time.
Do not lift your head up
after dropping them.
- Put your nose in it.
- Will it come up high?
- Ready. Get set.
- Lower.
(Who will be the unlucky two members
to get hit by the cola fountain?)
- Ready. Get set.
- Lower.
- This is Bo Pil's last penalty.
- Go.
(They all drop the bomb
at the same time.)
Put your face close to the bottle.
(So Min chose the cola fountain.)
Look at her.
(The soda shower cleans
your pores too.)
- Is it me?
- Suk Jin and Ji Hyo survived.
(Haha and So Min got the penalty.
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo survived.)
So Min, are you all right?
Suk Jin...
Hey, don't worry about others.
- It's important that we survived.
- It wasn't as intense as I thought.
- Good job, everyone.
- Thank you, Bo Pil.
- Bo Pil, thank you for everything.
- Thank you for your hard work.
(So the 12th summer of Running Man
is passing by.)
You did a great job.
- Ji Hyo is crying.
- You did such a wonderful job.
- Guys, Ji Hyo is crying.
- Great job.
(The amazing four-week project
will be revealed!)
(With a legendary penalty,)
(the Whatever Penalty Project
will begin!)
(For the next two weeks,)
(the members will carry out
penalties suggested by the viewers.)
(The first special
that no one anticipated is...)
(The Grim Reaper records
the life and death of humans.)
(They come to take those
who finished their lifespan.)
(The chase for life
that brings great horror!)
(Using lifespan as collateral...)
(The deal with spirits begins.)
(Ghostly War of Coins)