(A month before the World Cup match between Korea and Ghana)
(Someone showed up before the members.)
(The fake president of FIFA)
(He took office showing off his lame foot skills.)
(He suddenly started singing the World Cup song loudly.)
(Then he suggested watching the World Cup game together.)
(Everyone was lukewarm about the idea.)
- No. - Then I'll go.
Why would there be...
We should win today.
I hope we will win.
I'm excited about the cheering squad too.
The World Cup matches are so much fun.
There are a lot of things.
- We have all sorts of stuff. - We have ramyeon too.
This is non-alcoholic beer.
(All sorts of snacks including non-alcoholic beer are ready.)
(Ji Hyo is the first one to arrive.)
The manager looks like Kwang Soo.
- He looks like Kwang Soo, right? - Really?
(While she feels an affinity with the manager of Ghana...)
Kwang Soo.
(The little Red Devil arrives.)
- I'm really disappointed in you. - Why?
One of our production crew...
bet money on Ghana's victory.
- That's not one. - There are a lot.
- Not just one. - That's the problem.
- Go, Korea! - Do you want us to lose?
Hi.
- Se Chan. - Yes.
The Ghanian team has four goalkeepers.
- What? - Four keepers?
The four goalkeepers are taking photos together.
- Why are there four keepers? - The keepers?
He's here. The soccer king is here.
Who's here?
- Shutdolyi is here. Mr. Shutdolyi! - Hey.
(The soccer king of Anyang shows up.)
Hey! I'm here.
Nice.
Go, Korea!
(President Ji who arranged this meeting shows up.)
- He's a honeybee. - Go, Korea!
Are you a honeybee?
- A honeybee. - I got this from someone.
Ji Suk Jin.
My gosh.
(Everyone is present now including Jae Suk.)
Go, Korea!
Let's go!
Gue Sung! There's Gue Sung.
Why are you addressing him casually?
- I mean... - Do you know him?
He's the nation's beloved player.
He's so popular.
Gue Sung is the nation's beloved player.
President Ji of FIFA, put this one.
Okay. Thank you.
- The president of FIFA. - Yes.
Go, Korea!
This is nice.
That was really short.
He just did it once because of the cameras.
Just to show off.
You might get criticized.
What was her name? You look like Mina.
(You look like Mina from the 2002 World Cup.)
(Don't say anything and pick up the phone)
You look really hip.
Jung Woo Young and Hwang In Beom.
Suk Jin, you're wearing a knitted sweater.
It's red.
I'm just sitting here...
And the horns you're wearing are out of shape.
Actually, he came wearing hearts, not horns.
What? Are you going to pick up some girls or what?
- I think my stylist... - It's for picking up girls.
That's not for the Red Devils.
- Suk Jin. - Picking up a girl...
- at a bar. - I think my stylist hates me.
It has nothing to do with the World Cup.
- I found it strange when I got it. - What is this?
It looked strange.
It's a slow-motion replay of him.
Cho Gue Sung.
Cho Gue Sung used to be a center-back. A defender.
Really?
But he became a forward when he got into college.
He makes good headers.
- Nice. - He's good at it.
What? He's my boyfriend.
(Cho Gue Sung? He's my boyfriend.)
- Did you not know? - He's really popular.
- We're dating secretly. - Really?
In my heart.
If he scores a goal today... Seriously...
He'll be a star.
Well... He will buy an apartment in Hannam-dong...
and a Lamborghini.
Hannam-dong?
- Is he joining Running Man? - And he will join Running Man.
I hope he'll be here.
- He's handsome, right? - He really is.
He has a sexy face.
I bet Son Heung Min and Lee Jae Sung will score a goal each.
Lee Jae Sung isn't even in the starting lineup.
He's not in the starting lineup.
Will you at least check the lineup?
Who were you talking about?
Lee Jae Sung.
- But he's not in the lineup. - What's with him?
- In the second half. - That can happen.
Lee Kang In will definitely come in the second half.
We have to win.
- Gosh, that's scary. - I'm scared.
They look like sorcerers.
He looks amazing.
I'm somewhat overwhelmed.
He seems exhausted already.
He was on screen longer than he thought.
The screen wouldn't change.
- Hang on. - What do you want?
Do we have anything cool to drink?
Drink? Do we have anything to drink?
We have non-alcoholic beer and coke in the fridge.
Let me see.
Do we have any sandwiches or tender strips?
We have coke.
- I want this. - Jong Kook.
Thank you, Jae Suk.
- You're so kind. - Why?
He just gave this to me.
- Nonchalantly. - With a nonchalant air.
That's romantic.
It was romantic. The blood type B.
Why are you so touched?
What's with you?
We have 20 minutes left. This is crazy.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
What was that?
I'm really surprised.
What did you just do?
- Why? - He suddenly...
Jae Suk.
- What was that? - That was a little romantic.
- He's blushing. - Jae Suk.
That was romantic. Why did you do that?
What is he doing?
What's the matter with you?
It's romantic.
Why? I'm just eating.
This is a party. Everyone looks happy.
All right.
- Let's wait a little longer. - Suk Jin, you go.
I said 2 to 1. Why are they following me?
But you bet on Ghana's victory.
(Embarrassed)
People would believe that.
- You did say that. - That's ridiculous.
I'll make it different. I say 3 to 1.
- Three to one? - Yes.
- I'll go with 1 to 0. - Your guess is 1 to 0.
That sounds nice.
Se Chan, it will be more than 1 to 0.
I'm sure there will be a lot of goals.
You didn't even know today's starting lineup.
- It's not like that. - You didn't even check the lineup.
- This is more comfortable. - I do know the lineup.
Ghana has Kudus, the rising star of Ajax.
You should check Korea's lineup first.
Korea's lineup?
There's Cho Sung Gue...
- Cho Sung Gue? - That's Cho Gue Sung!
Cho Gue Sung.
Who is Cho Sung Gue? Is he a commentator?
You're the president here.
Can you cut this out for me?
- Hyung In, cut it out. - Cut it out for him.
- You should do that. - We should save Suk Jin.
(15 minutes before the match, Cho Gue Sung)
- There he is. - My gosh.
But for Korea...
- Not yet. - The number of cases of Group H...
Suk Jin, is this your first time watching a soccer game?
(Embarrassed)
It's not starting yet.
Do you know the rules?
- Stop it. - Is this your first time?
(Seok Sam's guardian angel is back.)
Stop what? I'm just asking.
What do you want me to stop?
Just look forward, you darn brat.
(Just look forward, you darn brat.)
(Seok Sam finally explodes.)
They will cut this out anyway.
(He keeps saying things that will be cut out.)
The chicken we ordered will arrive in 15 minutes.
We should eat.
We need two of you to come with us to pick it up.
- Two people? - Really?
Two of the members should go?
We will go.
- Don't worry. - Sure.
- All right. - I'll go.
- No. Later. - We should go later.
During the game.
- What? - During the game.
(The soccer king changes his mind immediately.)
Hey, you already said that, so you should keep your promise.
He's unbelievable.
- I see. - Should we decide now?
- It will arrive during the game? - We can't decide during the game,
so why don't we decide who will go now?
No, I'll go.
I think the game will go well when I'm not watching.
- No, Ji Hyo. - That's not true.
- Okay. That's a good idea. - I'm too nervous to watch it.
That's a good idea. We should respect the jinx.
- Do we lose when you watch? - When I watch it, we lose.
No, it's like...
- No, Ji Hyo. - We might lose.
- It's just... - Let's throw a dice.
The two members with the lowest numbers will go.
Why don't we let the one with the lowest member choose the other?
- That sounds good. - Let's not do that.
- Let the loser choose. - Why not?
You don't want to do anything.
- All right then. - Just don't do it.
The two members with the lowest numbers will go.
The two with the lowest numbers.
- Okay. - Don't choose.
- I know you will choose me. - I won't.
- Okay. - The losers will go.
- The losers will go. - Two people.
You need a high number.
(What will his number be?)
- Two. Okay. - It's two.
(Sighing)
He's really unlucky.
- He really is. - Gosh. Why am I so unlucky?
He's really bad at this.
I'll go next.
(Next up is Se Chan.)
It should be one. Then you two will go.
- It's four! Come on! - Gosh, that's not good.
- He's safe now. - I'm safe.
He won't go.
I think So Min will go.
- I don't want to go. - There should be two ones.
It has to be one.
There should be two ones.
- Two. - Two for two people.
(The current losers: Jae Suk and So Min)
For now, these two will go.
- You should get three. - What's wrong with you?
- I won't go if I get three. - What's with you?
- I won't go if I get 3. - Someone might get 1.
(He gets "one.")
He won't watch the game!
He won't get to watch it for five minutes!
Do the waves!
- Do the waves! - Can you believe this?
- You will go. - This is the worst.
- Can you believe this? - That's the worst.
- It's so funny. - How is this happening?
(After him...)
- Four. - How is this...
Haha, you should get one.
Jae Suk, if he gets one, you won't have to go.
- Right. Then I won't have to go. - He should get one.
(If Haha gets number 1 here, Jae Suk and So Min are safe.)
(What's Haha's number?)
It must be one!
(The descent of the Almighty of variety shows)
It's one!
Haha is going.
This is unbelievable.
- How could you get one? - It's so surprising.
- I'm safe. - Jae Suk.
- Okay. - Nice.
They will miss it for five minutes.
This is Running Man. Number two can survive.
- See you. - Are you all right?
It's starting now.
- Let's go. - Salute.
Darn it.
(The match finally begins.)
Let's go!
- We have to win. - Let's go!
- Long live our nation - Long live our nation
We will win. We can do this.
(Let's go!)
Let's go!
Go, Korea!
(Korea versus Ghana, the match begins.)
Here we go.
- Let's go! - It's begun.
So Min, did Cho Gue Sung call you before the game today?
With his heart. Telepathically.
So Min can't say he did.
People are watching.
Cho Gue Sung is really popular now.
- She might get criticized. - Right.
She doesn't want to be in trouble.
(Korea's offense)
It's Jeong Woo Yeong.
Kim Jin Su is on the right wing.
- A sharp pass. - Nice.
- Cross. - Yes!
Curl it.
- A sharp pass. - Nice.
Kwon Chang Hoon turns it. Shoot.
(The shot goes wide.)
- That was close. - We're really good.
- Nice. - That was a good one.
- There's a hole in Ghana's defense. - Our team is really good.
That was a brilliant pass.
If we keep pressuring them like that,
there will be holes in the rear defense.
They might try going for the rear.
That's what I just said.
This happens a lot.
They often say what I just said.
That happens to me too.
Ahn Jung Hwan does that.
(Korea's another counterattack)
- My gosh. - Good.
To the side. Good.
- There you go! - That's Son Heung Min.
- Go! - Son Heung Min dashes.
- Go! - Go, Son Heung Min!
- Nice. - Son Heung Min!
- It's a foul. - It's a foul.
(Korea gets a free kick in a good position.)
The chicken is here.
- Free kick. - You go.
- Suk Jin, you should go. - Go.
- I have to watch this. - Just go.
I should eat protein.
- Hurry and go. - Let me just watch this.
- We have to watch this. - Just this.
- Suk Jin. - Yes.
I'll go if you give me ten dollars.
Okay. Come here.
I'll wire the money.
- I'll send 20 dollars. - I'll wire the money.
Se Chan, I'll send 20 dollars.
I want 50 dollars.
- You should pay at least 50. - I want 50 dollars.
I'll go for 30 dollars.
You want 30? Deal.
Son Heung Min needs to be more aggressive now.
(Son Heung Min is ready for a free kick.)
I can't go.
Hey, I'm sending the money.
Suk Jin, I can't go. I have to watch this.
I'm sorry.
You said 30 dollars.
- I can't go. - The deliveryman is waiting...
- at the lobby now. - I'll go now.
I should go.
Hurry, So Min. I'll wire the money when you're back.
(They are forced to go and pick up the chicken.)
I didn't know I could hire someone with money.
Only with 40 dollars.
We have to hurry.
We should hurry.
For 40 dollars.
We practiced our set-piece play a lot.
(This is a crucial moment.)
Gosh, I can't stay seated.
I think this will be crazy.
- Kim Min Jae, go for a header! - Please.
Son Heung Min's cross.
- It's done. - It's a chance!
- My gosh. - Shoot!
- Shoot! - Don't hold it and just shoot.
- My gosh. - Who was that? Min Jae?
Shoot. Gosh, just shoot.
There will be another chance.
They're so good.
Take it slow. Pass it. Good.
Cross! That's right!
- They are really good. - They're doing a great job.
- They are good. - They really are.
That was great.
They are unbelievably good.
Gosh, that's impressive.
I feel bad that Jae Suk didn't see this.
(I feel bad that Jae Suk didn't see this.)
Things are going well.
- I hear something. - It's a chance! Shoot!
- Shoot! - Did they score? No?
I hear something. I think something happened.
First floor.
- They are so good. - They are amazing.
They are really good.
- It's in play. - Kim Min Jae!
- This is crazy. - The ball is in play.
It's a chance!
- I smell chicken. - I smell it too.
I smell the chicken.
(If a goal is made now, they're going to regret it forever.)
Thank you.
- Enjoy the food. - Thank you.
(They quickly take the chicken...)
(and walk fast.)
Hurry up.
They're coming.
- It was so fun, Jae Suk. - Really?
Thank you, Jae Suk.
- Thank you. - It was crazy.
- Was it? - What happened?
Try the most delicious chicken in the world.
This one?
It's so quick, right?
- One chicken for each of us. - They're going...
- to score a goal. - Good. It's from the same brand.
What happened?
- Is it a corner kick? - Let's go.
We can just take one. The two of us can share it.
(Eating)
Let's share it.
- Hold on. - Here.
It's delicious.
It's a long pass. Cho Gue Sung got it.
(Cho Gue Sung was elbowed at that moment!)
- He's hurt. - Who?
- No. - Who is it?
- Is it not Heung Min? - It's Cho Gue Sung.
He was elbowed.
Are you okay, So Min?
- Are you okay? Are you crying? - I'm fine.
All women will riot.
You don't know what to do?
(She can't react as she's scared of the aftermath.)
- If it blows up, So Min... - It's confusing.
She'll be ousted.
- Don't keep making me confused. - Okay.
Jordan Ayew.
Yes. Hwang In Beom cut it with a tackle.
(Hwang In Beom's foul grants Ghana a free kick chance.)
That was deep.
- It's dangerous. - Something like this is dangerous.
It's okay.
Block it.
The defenders should focus.
Kudus is getting ready to kick it with a left foot.
Jordan Ayew kicked it.
He kicks it one more time.
Korea allowed a goal.
(During the fierce fight in front of the goalpost, Korea allowed a goal.)
- No. - Hey.
Look at this.
- Things like this are dangerous. - I said it would be dangerous.
- It went in. - It's because I was watching.
No. But you get upset when you allow a goal like that, right?
You don't get so mad when they score because of their skills.
- But this was luck. - I told you. It goes in like that.
Something like this is dangerous.
- Now, when we push ahead... - They even check a shoulder seam.
- You don't know. - Semi-automated offside...
- was introduced at this event. - Was it offside?
Their bodies are in the front.
It kind of looks like offside as well.
- It's handball. - It's handball.
(it's handball!)
- It's handball. - Okay.
- Okay. - It's handball.
- The goal is invalid. - It's handball.
- The goal is invalid. - The goal is invalid.
- The goal is invalid. - It's considered handball...
in the Premier League.
- Yes. It's handball. - But I'm not sure about World Cup.
About the ball...
- They're checking. - Please.
(Checking)
- I got goosebumps. - It's handball.
- Please remove the score. - It's a relief.
It's handball. If the ball...
didn't hit the arm,
it would've gone in a different direction.
That's true.
Please.
- He must know it hit his hand. - He must know.
- He's not the one. - He's not?
(Embarrassed)
(Checking)
They approved the goal.
(But he approved the goal.)
- It's a goal? - What?
(It definitely hit the arm, but he approved it without checking VAR.)
- It's a goal? How? - It's handball.
He's not even watching the video?
- He should go and check. - It hit his hand.
- Let's forget about it. - Let's forget about it.
- Why does he not go and check? - Why does he not go and check?
I should send a direct message.
- Send a message. - This won't do.
You know that poop emoji, right?
- The poop and the skull. - Yes.
And something like a snake.
When we played against Togo before,
we allowed a goal first then we scored two goals.
- Yes. - Right.
- It has just started. - It's fun to turn the tables.
Right. Let's turn the tables.
The deity of variety shows won't stay still.
- Of course not. - Of course not.
There's still a lot of time left.
- We still got 15 minutes left. - If they stay calm,
they will definitely have a chance.
We'll definitely have a chance. But if we're not lucky...
You're just repeating what they're saying like a parrot.
Was I?
- It's just I'm thinking fast. - Is it?
If you're going to do this, you should sit on my shoulder.
Talk here.
- I'm sorry. - He kept repeating them.
I don't feel like laughing right now.
He passed it to the side. Gideon Mensah.
(Ghana keeps attacking.)
He's waiting, without crossing it.
It's Jordan Ayew. He kicked the ball.
- Look at this. - No. Don't give it to him.
(They allowed a goal for the second time.)
You shouldn't let him cross the ball.
This is a big mistake.
(They can't believe the opponent scored 2 goals in the first half.)
They can't crumble like this.
What should we do?
You got this.
- Let's score to make up for it. - Yes.
Why did they not acknowledge that it was a handball?
Let's turn the tables.
Let's cheer for them until the end.
We can do it. If we score just one goal, the mood will change.
- Right. - One goal can change the mood.
They need to turn the tables within the remaining time.
- Blocking. There you go. - Cho Gue Sung went for a header.
- The opposite side. Give it to him. - This...
They got it.
Son Heung Min.
He keeps the ball and goes for it again. Son Heung Min.
- He should've kicked it earlier. - He passes the ball first and...
(Kwon Chang Hoon's canon shot)
It was nice, Kwon Chang Hoon.
- It was nice. - Well done.
That was very good.
- It was nice. - Let's keep the energy.
- Let's go. - Let's seize a chance.
We can do it. Let's go.
It was nice.
I shouldn't watch it.
So that defenders won't gather around Son Heung Min.
Ji Hyo, go home then.
Why? What's the matter?
She thinks we're losing because she's watching.
- Active moves... - Yes.
My gastritis came back.
- Are you okay? - It hurts a lot because of stress.
This is so annoying.
We had so many corner kicks, but none of them...
- He's good. - This is so hard.
The ball was hit.
We have 45 minutes in the second half. It's fine.
(The first half ends 0 to 2 in the end.)
Okay. Let's get ready.
(It's half-time for the members as well.)
I should go to the bathroom.
First, let's remove all the negative energy.
Let's remove it.
- Let's empty it. - Let's set it up again.
Empty your body.
If you think you're unlucky, please go out.
- I'll go out. - All the negative energy...
- I'll go out too. - I think I should leave too.
We need to remove everything that is iffy.
Anyone who is unlucky.
- Erase them all. It's over. - Okay.
- Start over in the second half. - Okay.
- Yes. - Let's do it again.
Let's start in a good mood.
(Sighing)
(Solemn)
Everyone...
is a little devastated.
(No one is laughing at the Variety Show Department office.)
We need a drastic change.
This is not working.
Jong Kook, book a flight and go to Qatar.
- I should go. - You can't do this here.
- You should go. - I should go and talk to them.
- You should go. - This is...
This is a must.
Gosh.
I've been waiting for this day since two years ago.
Are you serious?
- Two years ago? - I've been waiting.
- When? - Waiting for the World Cup?
- Of course. - Two years ago?
I have been waiting for this day since the qualification.
That was before the final draw.
- My mom... - That was before the final draw.
- I... - It's so fake.
- I've been waiting. No. - Doesn't it sound too fake?
- I've been waiting. - That was before the final draw.
How did you know we would play against Ghana?
I've been waiting since I was in my mom's belly.
- One to zero? - After the second half begins,
- We should score quickly. - we should score quickly.
We should score quickly in the beginning.
If we score quickly, they should catch up.
- Let's score a goal in 15 minutes. - No. In 3 minutes.
It's our 2nd match. The 2nd half is starting now.
- Good luck. - This...
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- We can do it. - Let's go.
We can do it.
Let's go.
(They take it up a notch and cheer for the second half.)
- Good. - Yes.
Pressure them. Don't make them pass the ball.
- There you go. It's not a foul. - No. Just turn. Why?
- Turn. Why? - Nice.
Yes. That's how you pressure them.
You should score a goal.
You should give it to him.
Give it to Gue Sung when he cuts it. Why don't you give it to him?
- Jong Kook is very angry. - I mean...
- Because... - Take it.
They're too hesitant to kick.
They need to tell them to turn.
It's so frustrating.
(When they were losing smiles...)
It's fine.
They should make a bold move in a dangerous zone.
Try it. You're fast.
- He's bursting through them. - There you go.
It was so...
- Good. - That's...
That was too early.
(But he missed the opportunity.)
Cho Gue Sung followed Kudus to slow him down.
Don't dance.
"Don't dance."
It's too bad. It was so close.
I think they can score a goal if they have more confidence.
Yes. Kim Jin Su crosses the ball with his left foot.
- Goal. - Yes.
There you go.
- He did it! - Okay.
- Did he block it? - It's Cho Gue Sung.
(He blocked it?)
- He blocked it. - He blocked it?
Why did he block it?
He blocked it?
- He blocked it? - It would've definitely gone in.
- It was so close. - The way he crossed it was good.
Kim Jin Su should keep passing the ball.
It was a sharp cross.
And Cho Gue Sung kicked it.
He blocked it.
- Goalkeeper Ati-Zigi hit it away. - He blocked it.
It was close.
- It was close. It could've gone in. - He blocked it.
He really had to be there.
He can't read the room.
- Why did he block it? - The atmosphere is nice.
- It has come. - That's it.
- That's Cho Gue Sung's forte. - Things started to work for us.
- How come... - He spat on the ground.
Please.
(He's telling on him without a good reason in a childish manner.)
"He spat on the ground."
I was talking to the referee.
(While Little Cheerleader who is upset is nitpicking everything...)
I'm upset.
- Someone is coming out. - It's Lee Kang In.
- Lee Kang In. - Let's go.
- Kang In. - Nice.
Let's go, Kang In.
I guess Bento wants to win. He put in Lee Kang In so early.
Yes. Lee Kang In is a good choice.
- He did well. - You got this.
Good job.
- You got this. - He worked hard.
- Let's score just one goal. - His body looks light.
- Give it to Lee Kang In. - Give it to Lee Kang In.
Lee Kang In has enough space. It's not the time now.
(What?)
Hey. You're right.
Are you going to explain every little detail?
- You're right. - Will you explain everything?
I'm right. It's not the timing now.
He should've passed it to him when you told him to do so earlier.
- Yes. But it was late. - Okay.
- It's fine. - The pass is...
(At that moment)
- Kang In. - Nice.
- There you go. - There you go.
- Lamptey. - Lee Kang In took the ball.
(Lee Kang In made a chance.)
- Goal! - Goal!
He did it!
(It's finally a goal!)
My goodness.
He did it.
- I told you. - We scored a goal.
- He did it. - Lee Kang In.
- He did it. - He made it.
We did it.
We made it.
- We did it. - We did it.
We did it. I told you.
- Yes! - Yes!
(He's almost screaming.)
Look at Kang In.
(Excited)
(A precise cross)
(And an excellent header)
Kang In is good.
Kang In is the best.
Cho Gue Sung, go!
- That's what I'm talking about. - I told you.
- Now, it's good. - That's what I'm talking about.
- Lee Kang In. - That's what I'm talking about.
Lee Kang In was one step faster.
- Yes. - He did it.
Lee Kang In is definitely different.
His cross was so precise.
It was neat.
Send a direct message to him.
We'll score a goal in 15 minutes through the 2nd half.
- We should score a goal. - It's good.
- I told you it'd be Lee Kang In. - We'll score one more goal.
- Kang In. - No.
- It's Heung Min. - It's Son Heung Min.
(At that moment!)
- There you go. - Yes.
Lee Kang In and Hwang In Beom. Son Heung Min to the side.
Kim Jin Su kicked it. On the other side...
Yes.
(A consecutive goal in 3 minutes)
- Yes! - Okay!
(This is crazy.)
(The president's legs gave in.)
(The equalizer even made the Tiger cry.)
(They're making a fuss.)
(The thrilling goal makes them shiver.)
Let's go.
We did it.
- We did it. - Let's go.
(It's magic that makes everything look adorable.)
We did it. Okay.
- Okay. It's good. - I'm crying.
I'm crying.
- We did it. - I love you, Bento.
- Mr. Bento... We did it. - Mr. Bento.
Lee Kang In changed the atmosphere.
Bento made a great choice.
- Go, Korea! - Go, Korea!
(Go, Korea!)
Hey.
- Hey. - Oh, gosh.
- Okay. - Did you see that?
- They're not dancing. - Let's dance.
(Let's dance!)
Like that?
(The cheering battle where they receive a little and give a lot)
(Little Cheerleader is having fun only now.)
This is crazy.
- Lee Kang In completely changed it. - That's so cool.
I know. The atmosphere completely changed.
Today's game is so fun. How can it be so...
Why is it...
We got so much footage to air.
It's really amazing.
I told you. The deity of variety shows won't stay still.
- Right. - When we set up all of this.
This is so fun.
I teared up.
- Now, I... - Kook Jong was crying.
Yes. I'm about to get emotional.
- This is crazy. - Let's cross again.
- Gue Sung. - Let's go for a hat-trick.
You should give it to him.
There you go.
They definitely look intimidated.
- Three people are marking Gue Sung. - That's interesting.
- They're intimidated. - It's so interesting.
(At that moment)
(The ball crossed the halfway line.)
He blocked it. He kicks it.
- It's okay. - No.
(In the end, they allowed a go-ahead goal.)
(Disappointed)
My goodness.
- That's... - Did it go in?
The shot was...
I'm dumbstruck.
- What happened? - It's so...
You shouldn't let your guard down.
We can do it. It's fine.
- Let's do it. - It's okay. We have time.
- We can do it. - It's enough for two goals.
We can do it.
You got this.
It'd be amazing if we win after all this.
I guess they're dragging time.
But for the World Cup this time, even if they drag time...
- Later... - They will give them extra time.
I think they will give them at least ten minutes more.
- Yes. - The injury time.
I'm looking forward to Lee Kang In's free kick.
I'm going crazy.
Get ready to scream. It will go in.
Will it go in?
Lee Kang In.
(The Ghanaian goalkeeper blocked it again.)
- Nice. - His kick was very good.
(How can he...)
- It was a precise kick. - The kick was great.
- That was incredible. - Nice.
This is so...
- This game is really... - It's the best ever.
- This is so fun. - I'm going crazy.
- It's nerve-wracking. - But it's nerve-wracking.
It would be so nice if we win and have fun.
- It's nerve-wracking. - If we scored three goals...
It'd be amazing.
- Don't act up. - Be quiet.
(They're mad at innocent people as they're upset.)
So annoying.
I can't watch.
Let's score just one goal at 38 minutes.
- Why? Are you scared? - Yes.
My heart is beating so fast.
It's an emotional rollercoaster.
It's okay.
We still have a lot of time.
(She watches then shuts her eyes.)
It was close.
(Then she watches again.)
Look.
(Pale)
- So Min. - So Min.
- I'm so nervous. - Are you okay?
- I'm so nervous. - You're exhausted.
I'm so nervous. My heart is beating so fast.
I should think this is a rerun and watch it.
We won the game. And we're watching a rerun.
(They got a corner kick chance with 1 minute of extra time left.)
- The opponent is perplexed. - Yes.
- You got this. - You got this.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
Lee Kang In is so cool.
Seriously.
They got one minute left. But they might give them...
- Please. - more extra time. Lee Kang In.
A header.
- Just one more. - Kim Moon Hwan is following.
It's okay.
We still have time.
- Hwang In Beom to Na Sang Ho. - Let's go.
After the header, Na Sang Ho is following the ball.
It's out for now.
It's fine.
Sang Ho, we still have time.
- Let's do it. - Please.
(Yang Yeoguri is praying as well.)
Na Sang Ho.
- Son Heung Min. - Please.
- He got it. - Pass it.
He got it and heads it.
- There's no one. - Lee Kang In.
- Lee Kang In. - Kick it.
Shoot. It's out.
It was too strong.
(It's a pity.)
It was a good kick though.
- It was good. - It was good.
I'm so upset about that one goal earlier.
(The one that wasn't considered as handball)
We should block it and try one more time.
Yes.
(When the extra time is almost over)
- They're not going to finish it. - I think he's taking out a card.
- It won't be over like this, right? - No.
- He should go forward. - He should go forward.
He's going forward. Kwon Kyung Won. Is he going to kick it?
The ball hit him and went out. It's a corner kick.
(Sports caster Bae Seong Jae)
- What? - How can they...
- It's a corner kick. - Just one more goal.
- One last chance. - Just one more goal.
It's over?
(It's over?)
(The game suddenly ended before the corner kick chance.)
- What? - How can they end it...
before a corner kick?
Come on.
- They were lying down and stuff. - It was a corner kick.
The referee just ended the game.
(No matter how much they think about it, it's baffling.)
- Is he given a red card? What? - He gave Bento...
(He even gave Bento a red card.)
I'm speechless.
I don't understand the judgment.
They had a good chance.
(The game with Ghana ended before a corner kick chance,)
(but the players did their best.)
(The game with Ghana ended like this.)
(They're quiet as they're disappointed.)
How can he end it in the middle of it?
The final whistle is blown.
But they did a great job.
- Now, - Portugal should...
- win Uruguay, right? - Ghana should lose against Uruguay.
- Then... - Yes.
Portugal should win against Uruguay...
- early in the morning today. - They should win.
- That's right. - Then...
lastly, we should win...
- against Portugal. - Against Portugal.
- Then it's possible. - We can make it to the Round of 16.
Right. It's possible.
(And it really happened.)
It's the 1st time in 12 years.
The Asian Tigers made it to the Round of 16 again.
This is the Asian Tigers.
(President Ji's short clip)
(Let me make predictions.)
(We'll win against Uruguay 2 to 1.)
(We'll win against Ghana.)
(And we'll lose against Portugal.)
(Wrong or not, he hoped Korea would make it to the Round of 16.)
(The group viewing of the game where everyone was immersed is over.)
(The members gathered in Yeoui Island this time.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- There's a lot of beer. - It's a beer pub.
What is this? It's beer.
Are you sure we can drink this all?
- If you press this... - They're taking care of all this?
There are containers inside.
It's not an indirect advertisement.
(Writer)
Is it for all family members?
Not all family members.
- I love this place. - This place is so hip.
So Min got her hair dyed.
- Where? - She's NewJeans.
I thought you got ketchup on your hair.
What are you doing?
(A fake NewJeans member whose hair is the only thing that's hip)
- Red Devils. - Well...
So Min is obsessed with youth these days.
I thought you dipped your hair in yukgaejang.
Why are you saying that? She's our mascot.
Haha is my role model.
- Yes. You two are similar. - Why are you saying that suddenly?
Why are you picking on So Min?
- You must feel threatened. - She's still...
- She's still like a 20-year-old. - Yes, I feel threatened.
She even has earrings on.
- She has a fur beanie on. - Right.
- I went all the way today. - You look young.
- Exactly. - She looks younger than her age.
- Young So Min. - Nice.
- The MZ generation. - Don't you think...
the beanie should be pulled down?
- It should cover your ears. - Like so.
(Dragging down)
- Suk Jin, don't! - This looks more adorable.
- This is better. - Isn't this what you wanted?
- It's the hermit crab. - That's what you wanted.
- Doesn't she look cute? - Right.
- Isn't that a hermit crab? - You couldn't help yourself.
Don't ruin her NewJeans look.
- NewJeans! - Is there a number you like?
- Yes. - Of course.
- I have one. - Me too.
You'll all be given a sketchbook...
in which you'll write down...
the number that might bring you luck.
- Can it overlap? - Any number?
- It's all fine. - Really?
There isn't a number I particularly like.
Can others see it?
Which number should I write down?
(They all write down a number.)
- You like the lucky number three. - Right.
- Then I... - Three? What about you?
- One. - I like one as well.
- One and three. - Jae Suk must like one...
since he's also in first place.
- He likes the number one. - I like one and seven.
Eight has been the number for me since an early age.
My mom breathed it into me.
It's in our phone number too.
- There's always number eight. - One and seven.
I used to live in Unit 806, so eight is a familiar number.
- Unit 806? - I lived there for 20 years.
- Go with five. - That's a number I like.
- Really? - I like the number five.
I'll go with a number that hasn't been written down.
No one went with seven or four.
I'll go with the deadly four.
Go with seven. No one chose that number.
- Not fearing death is how you live. - Seven.
Go with seven.
- I will if that's what you want. - There you go.
- What's with him? - How sweet of him.
When did he become this nice?
- I'll go with seven. - How sweet of him.
- I'll do as Jae Suk says. - He's the sweetest.
- That's what I've been telling you. - Right.
If you're done, please show us the number you chose.
Sure thing.
- Here. - I'll go with nine.
One, three, seven,
- Five. - Five,
nine, eight, and eight.
Let me show you the meaning behind the number you chose.
- What is it? - I switched from three.
What could this be about?
They're giving us food!
(Food?)
The number must correspond with a different snack.
Is that tofu? It looks like one.
- It's a cake. - Isn't this coriander?
That I can't have.
I wrote down the number one.
(Number 1: Iced Americano)
- Lucky you. - I love bagels.
- All I get is coffee? - It's a bagel.
It's coriander.
- This is coriander. - Is this it?
What on earth?
- What's going on? - You were served the dessert...
that corresponds...
- with the number you chose. - Really?
The list was written beforehand.
Please go ahead and check what was served.
(The dessert varies depending on the number.)
- Iced Americano. - Iced tea with an extra shot.
- Coriander cake. - Mineral water.
- Coriander-ade. Seriously? - Coriander-ade?
Bagel's a good one. See what I mean?
- I'm glad I listened to you. - See?
- Orange ade. - Nine. Iced tea with an extra shot.
- Ice tea. - Suk Jin was served iced tea.
Iced tea with an extra shot.
We made pretty good choices though.
I don't mind coriander,
- but as a soft drink? - It's a first.
- Coriander ade. - Yes, coriander ade.
Hold on. Is this actually sold at cafes?
- Really? - Yes.
These were all bought from a dessert shop.
- No way. - The coriander is wilted.
I think the cake will taste nice.
(Visually, it isn't appealing.)
(She tries a bite.)
I think the cake will taste nice.
- Hold on. - Coriander ade?
It's not that bad.
You'll have to try it with the coriander to know for sure.
- It's weird though. - What on earth?
What am I tasting?
(It takes an acquired taste to enjoy the dessert.)
I don't think I can eat this.
Is this from a trending cafe?
I love them all.
I bet that's good.
That suits my palate.
I haven't tried any, but I love the cake.
- It suits my palate. - Because it's trendy?
The coriander cake is the worst.
Hold on. Let me try some.
- Do you eat coriander? - Can you stand it?
I...
- I don't go looking for it. - I didn't use to eat it,
but it's been growing on me recently.
Don't you think that's too much?
Try it.
You should have the leaves too.
Is it trendy?
It seems okay at first,
- but then... - It comes crashing.
- The more you savor it... - Exactly.
The sourness comes through.
- It's not bad. - Really?
- Try some. - I like coriander, but the smell...
- It gets bad at the end. - Exactly.
(It gets bad at the end.)
Exactly. It gets bad at the end.
At the very end...
- It gets bad at the end. - Yes, at the end.
It's okay at first, but it gets bad at the end.
I chose the wrong number.
Are you happy with the dessert you chose?
- Of course. - I'm happy with mine.
- I'm not that pleased. - Sure.
The number you wrote down...
will be your lucky number for the day.
- This number? - All day long?
Today, you'll compete...
- in the Lucky Number Race. - That sounds like fun.
How will it go?
As demonstrated, every choice will depend on your lucky number.
- Really? - That'll be five for me.
- I like races like this. - My number is three.
- You'll be split into two teams. - We have the same number.
- That means we're a team. - The race will end...
when you arrive at the final destination.
The first team to get there...
will be given an additional benefit.
Maybe I should've chosen a higher number.
The numbers you have will be your pool of lucky numbers.
One from the bag will be chosen randomly.
(A number for each team will be chosen randomly.)
- It'll be chosen randomly. - That's right.
Let's say one team chose the number three.
At a restaurant,
they'll only get to have the third item on the menu.
- Or... - So whatever it is...
If you get on a bus,
you must get off after three stops.
If you take a taxi, you must get off after three minutes.
- Like that... - That sounds like fun.
It doesn't sound easy though.
On your way to the final destination,
each team must complete two missions.
There are four missions to choose from,
but those chosen by the other team won't be available to you.
You can only travel by bus or cab today,
but you can't take a cab twice in a row.
You won't be given a specific meal time,
so feel free to eat at your discretion.
I'm glad I got to eat something.
There's no limit to the budget, so you may have whatever you want.
- Really? - Yes.
It won't be pleasing...
if we have to eat something we don't want.
- Not at Gimbap Heaven. - Gimbap Heaven!
- That's right. Gimbap Heaven. - At Gimbap Heaven...
Before you leave,
- you'll split into two teams. - Sure.
Since it's the World Cup, we'll decide by drawing names.
- Sure. - Sounds good.
(Running Man Draw Ceremony)
(The solemn process that'll play a huge factor in today's game.)
Good. Let's do this.
Here's someone who has...
- the authority to host this event. - Who is it?
It'll be our cameraman, Kang Chan Hee.
- Chan Hee. - It's General Kang.
He's been at this job since the 80s.
- Someone with high authority. - On shows that aired in the 80s,
his name appears at the bottom of the screen.
The legendary and wealthy Kang Chan Hee.
The wealthy Kang Chan Hee.
(He's called rich the second he enters.)
Kang Chan Hee.
Out of all the cameramen, he's the wealthiest.
- The one with neck pain. - He represents.
We'll choose one for Group A and one for Group B...
- and so on and so forth. - Sure thing.
Please choose a member that'll be placed in Group A.
(Drawing for Group A)
(It's as serious as it was during the World Cup drawing event.)
He's just going to choose one.
He's taking his time.
(Why is this nerve-wracking though?)
(He chose one!)
He's opening the ball just like they do at the World Cup.
- This is nerve-wracking. - It's not a ball with a number.
- There's something inside. - This is like the World Cup.
He's unfolding it.
Group A.
- Haha. - Haha.
Let's now see who's in Group B.
Since he's a cameraman,
I thought he'd show it to the camera,
but he let us see it first.
- You should get in on camera. - Exactly.
Why is he showing us first?
It startled me.
He's experienced enough to know better.
- Group B. - Let's see.
- The wealthy Kang Chan Hee. - Who will compete against Haha?
Who's in Group B?
- So Min. - Jeonsobari.
- The two hipsters. - Trendy versus trendy.
- What a bummer. - We'll see who's trendier.
The trend-setters.
They'll bring vibrant energy.
- We're back to Group A. - Group A.
- Good. - Who will be on Haha's team?
- Even dung... - Let it be me.
Haha and I will write history today.
(Group A: Ji Suk Jin)
- Let's write history. - Nice!
- Now for Group B. - Jae Suk.
I love it.
- They make a good team. - I agree.
I'm loving it.
- Right. - Good.
I guess it's my job...
to give the hipsters a reality check.
- The third member of Group A. - Group A.
- It can be anyone. - Let it be Ji Hyo.
- I think it's me. - Is it Ji Hyo?
Is it happening the way I want it to?
(Song Ji Hyo)
Suk Jin, what's going on?
Suk Jin, what's going on? What's with the predictions?
- No way! - He got it right again.
Has the AI Octopus replaced him?
This will be the last member for Group B.
- It's between me and Se Chan. - Let it be Se Chan.
Se Chan.
- Yang Ssaebssaeb! - Are you kidding me?
- Suk Jin, no way. - I see the future.
- Am I in Group A? - It was as I called it.
The groups have been drawn.
- Let's thank Mr. Kang for... - Thank you!
- Thank you. - Thanks, Chan Hee.
- The wealthy Kang Chan Hee. - Yes, the wealthy Mr. Kang.
Let me first inform you of your final destination.
- Where are we headed? - Apgujeong Rodeo Street.
- Apgujeong Rodeo Street? - Yes.
Apgujeong Rodeo Street?
- That's your neighborhood. - It's my neighborhood.
It's like we've already won.
- It's my neighborhood. - We're closing the show...
close to his home.
Your first means of transportation will be the bus.
- Right. - You will head...
to the Yeouido Transfer Center which is nearby.
- Sure. - Got it.
I haven't been on a bus in a while.
Me neither.
- Bus and then a cab. - Bus or cab.
- Riding a bus - We'll first take the bus.
- I haven't been here in a while... - But on the bus...
- So... - I know, right?
- We should get it out already. - We used to shoot a lot in Yeouido,
- since the TV stations are nearby. - That's right.
- It's been a while. - All of the TV stations were here.
- Of course. - It's a financial district.
Jong Kook, Jae Suk, me, and Haha...
- used to hang out in Yeouido. - Yes, we hung out here.
The TV stations were here.
You filmed a lot in Yeouido too, Ji Hyo.
- I did. - She must have been here a lot.
- It's been a while. - Yeouido.
- Seriously. - The sky is clear today.
It's been a while. It was supposed to rain a lot today.
- It's a relief. - It rained a little earlier.
It's perfect.
It's NewJeans.
(The fake NewJeans are back again.)
(Dancing)
So Min doesn't know.
So Min.
- She was side-eyeing. - She doesn't know.
You don't know "Hype Boy?"
Don't you know "Hype Boy?"
Is it a new song?
- He doesn't know. - It's been a while since release.
"Essential." Which song does that come from?
Essential?
(Essential?)
- What's "Essential?" - Amazing.
- I also know what that is. - "Attention."
- Don't you know "Hype Boy?" - I don't know.
Hype boy
(Hype boy)
- Hype boy - Hype boy
That's "My Boy."
This is how you dance to "Hype Boy."
(New Thing Boy)
I'm new, my glasses are new too
My pants are new too
This is so funny.
(Trendy songs are put to death as usual.)
Attention.
But So Min's beanie...
Isn't it cute?
He says it keeps coming off.
- He wants it down. - It might fall off.
It's climbing up your hair.
You acted like her boyfriend.
- It's like it's stuck on your hair. - Her boyfriend.
Pull your beanie down.
So Min is weird.
She says she doesn't like Se Chan, but she likes being cared by him.
It's weird.
Honestly, when Sae Ho came, Se Chan looked very handsome.
That day,
- Se Chan was glowing. - The day Sae Ho came?
Yeouido is really... Look at this building.
Was it not there when you were around?
- I'm a big fan. - I think it wasn't there.
- Pardon? - I'm a big fan.
Of Running Man?
- Thank you. - I subscribed to your channel.
You're subscribed to Jiseokjin World?
Of course.
He's a subscriber.
(His subscriber bravely came forward!)
Thank you.
- This is funny. - To Kim Jong Kook's too.
- Gym Jong Kook. - Gym Jong Kook.
His body says he's a Gym Jong Kook subscriber.
Your face looks like you're a Jiseokjin World subscriber.
Don't you have a nickname for your subscribers?
I don't.
- Thank you. Have a nice day! - Hold on.
When are we going to ride the bus?
It's Jidok? I thought you said Jidol.
- It's Jidok. - I thought the same.
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
(The major center where many buses in Seoul and Gyeonggi stop by)
- We'll split into two teams now. - Okay.
- Come here Hype Boy. - Hype Boy.
(They will split into two teams from here and begin the match.)
- We're the trend-setters. - That's right.
- Let's get moving. - Should we walk like this?
- We can eat whatever we want. - Yes.
- We should eat something nice. - Let's eat nice food.
- Like "The Tortoise and the Hare." - "The Tortoise and the Hare?"
Let's constantly move like the tortoise and then eat.
Are you hungry now?
- You're not hungry, right? - I'm not.
- That's right. What time is it now? - How about around twelve o'clock?
But you know the places in Apgujeong Rodeo Street.
Don't worry.
I know it very well. You don't have to worry.
The problem is that we can eat depending on what number...
- we pick. - That's right.
I know a good place there.
I don't think we should choose number one.
We should go somewhere with less dishes on the menu.
A single-menu restaurant?
That's right.
What do you want to eat today?
We're allowed to eat something expensive.
What's good to eat in the morning?
- We can eat anything. - Should we eat steak?
- In the morning? - Yes. Steak in the morning.
He always eats steak if he's not paying.
- You always eat that. - Bye.
- Lamb steak. - Bye!
- See you later! - See you!
- Bye! - See you later!
Where is this going?
It's going to Lotte World. To Samseong and Gangnam Station.
- Where? It's going to Gangnam? - This one.
- It's going to Gangnam Station. - Shall we get on this one?
- It's coming here. - We don't know how far we'll go.
Suk Jin.
- You're going to pick a number now. - Okay.
You'll immediately get on the bus with the number you pick.
- Okay. - I see.
So the route we're taking doesn't matter.
Okay. Got it.
- Really? - Really?
Our thoughts don't matter.
- What if we end up somewhere else? - We might do a tour around Seoul.
- Let's try it. - Let's pick one. Go first, So Min.
- Pick one, So Min. - You go first.
I'll look up the buses.
That doesn't matter.
- The number... - You have to use these numbers.
- Among those? - Just those?
- You can pick one. - Which one?
Number three.
(Team Suk Jin picks a number.)
I got it.
We have to ride a bus that includes this number?
What's this?
You have to ride a bus that includes eight,
- and get off at the eighth station. - Yes, at the eighth bus station.
Great.
- It's eight. - Eight?
I have a bad feeling about this.
- I think this one is good. - Let's see.
This one.
- Number eight. - Eight.
Eight.
Get on the bus that has eight when it arrives.
- But there are no buses with 8. - There's one. Bus 8000.
- Isn't that a wide-area bus? - We're in trouble.
What about Bus 6628?
- Bus 6628? - That works.
(Fortunately, there's a bus number that includes 8.)
So we have to get on this bus.
We can't ride this bus.
We have to go very far if we get on this bus.
- It's the red bus. - Shall we go to Mok-dong?
(There are wide-area buses that have 8 in their numbers.)
We can go this way to Yeouido Park.
- Are we going this way? - No.
- Is it going in this direction? - I think so.
This bus goes in this direction.
Then does it go in circles?
No.
Does the bus go around like this?
Is it a circulating bus?
(They're having difficulties already.)
- There's 8 here. Bus 8600. - There's Bus 88.
Bus 8600.
- Bus 8601. - It's going to the city hall.
Bus 8601.
- Bus 8500. - Let's see.
- One, two, three, four, five, six, - I should put my mask on.
seven, eight. It's Janggi Station.
It's going to Janggi Station?
- We can't go there. - Then we shouldn't get on this bus.
- Let's not ride this bus... - But we have to if it comes.
- We have to ride it if it comes. - That's the only bus here.
- Let's just ride the bus. - Yes.
There's nothing we can do.
It's Bus 8601.
- Bus 8601. - It goes to Mapo Station.
- We won this race. - Let's go to the second floor.
Let's go to the second floor.
Shall we? I've never ridden a double-decker bus.
A bus with eight in its number is approaching. You can get on it.
- We have to get on it? - We can't get on the bus we want.
We can't ride this one.
Isn't this a wide-area bus?
This is a wide-area bus.
Is it not?
But the bus route is a little...
Hello.
- Three people, please. - Three people, please.
- Three people? - Yes.
Do you want to go upstairs?
Upstairs? Should we go upstairs?
We have to get off at the eighth station.
- I've never ridden a double-decker. - Me too.
- Hello. - Hello.
The back doesn't have it.
- We have to put on the belt, right? - We don't know the direction.
You have to put on the belt everywhere.
We have to get off at the eighth station, right?
Yes.
- Eight stations? - I'll look at the map...
when the bus stops.
- This station... - Okay. Hold on.
(Is it heading to Seoul or the opposite direction?)
- This stop... - Okay. Hold on.
- is Mapo Station. - This is the first stop.
We reach Mapo Station within one stop.
We're at Mapo Station.
- This is great. - It's great.
- This is... - What will we eat, Ji Hyo?
This bus is going to Seoul Station.
Seoul Station is also nice.
- It's not bad. - Seoul Station is...
The area is nice. It has lots of good restaurants.
We can ride a taxi to the bus stop.
We can ride this...
- We can ride another bus there. - That's right.
Then ride another taxi.
Number eight is good. It's a great number.
- Eight is... - We picked a good number.
- Eight is a great number. - It's amazing.
(It really became a lucky number.)
- I've never ridden a double-decker. - Me too. It's high up here.
Where are we?
Us?
We should get off at the eighth stop.
We're at Yeouido Interchange.
What's the eighth stop?
Janggi High School?
Isn't that in Gimpo?
- Janggi-dong is in Gimpo. - We're in trouble.
(It's a bus heading to Gimpo.)
Why did we pick number eight?
I said number eight could be good.
- This is a red bus. - We're doomed.
Is this a wide-area bus?
If the bus takes the highway, we could end up in Gyeonggi-do.
It's past the rush hour, so there aren't many passengers.
Or else, there would have been many passengers.
- This is really... - We could go to Seoul Station.
- Seoul Station is good. - It's not bad.
It's way closer to Gangnam.
(Same number, same bus, but opposite fates of the two teams)
Where are we going now?
Does this bus not stop?
Why does it not stop?
- If it goes eight stops... - Where will we end up in?
We'll end up at the end of Gimpo.
Our PD is also flustered.
If the bus stopped at the stops, we wouldn't be going to Gimpo.
- That's right. - If we count the eight stops.
I took a wrong bus in Hongdae once, and I was in Gimpo after one stop.
Really? I guess it was a bus like this.
In my teenage years, I would ride buses a lot...
to calm my mind.
Back then, I got on a bus like this one.
- You did it on purpose. - I listened to music.
You listened to the mymy cassette player.
I listened to the mymy all day long.
(Today)
(At a place)
That's depressing.
(No one passed by)
(This sad song helped him breathe when he was going through puberty.)
- How much did you have then? - I listened to Lee Seung Chul.
- Two dollars. - That's sad.
Back in high school,
"Road" by god made me shed tears.
"Road."
- It was my birthday. Yes. - Where will this road take me?
I cried every time I listened to it. The lyrics were so fitting.
Now, we are traveling aimlessly.
- This is bad. - We are traveling aimlessly.
This is fun when you are dating someone.
- A bus trip. - You set off aimlessly.
- That's right. - "Let's run away."
(Eloping in a wide-area bus)
The family should be against the relationship then.
It should be a difficult love.
It can't be smooth.
On the second floor...
- of the empty bus, - The second floor.
- you will hold hands. - You will sit at the end.
That's right. You will sit at the end.
You would kiss your lover if there is no one around, right?
No. Instead...
(He suddenly asks a question about kissing.)
You would share earphones.
I think you would kiss your lover.
No.
If it's difficult love, you stare at each other sadly.
- Really? - Yes.
- There is no physical contact. - You would hold hands.
- You would hold hands. - Wouldn't you kiss though?
Jae Suk, why would you kiss on the bus?
It would be a peck on the forehead.
- A peck. - Yes. Then a peck on the nose.
Nose?
You should wet your lover's nose a little.
- It would smell like spit. - Not the nose.
Why would it smell like spit when it's only a peck?
- Se Chan has thick lips. - Yes, I do.
- Why are you thinking about him? - Seriously.
- For goodness' sake. - That's funny.
We finally arrived at the first bus stop.
This is driving me crazy.
- This is insane. - Where are we?
- Yeongdeungpo. - Dangsan Station.
- Dangsan. - Dangsan?
- We will end up in Gimpo. - This is bad.
At this rate, we will fall way behind.
I am sure the other team had complications too.
Of course.
We are passing the Mapo Bridge in a single stop.
Which stop is it? Is this the 3rd or the 4th stop?
Which stop is it?
We didn't hear the announcement yet. Here it comes.
- This stop is... - The third stop.
- Chungjeongno Station. - The third stop.
Chungjeongno Station. We are almost there.
- Chungjeongno Station. - We reached Chungjeongno Station.
- We are almost done. - I think things are going well.
- I think we made the right call. - I agree.
- Had we gotten off... - Yes.
Did "Mom's Diary" film the match against Uruguay?
- Yes. - When does it air?
I am not sure. I will have to ask.
- Don't you know? - I don't know.
"How Do You Play?" filmed the match against Uruguay.
- It aired. - Yes. It aired already.
Shouldn't you focus on your show?
It's good to have you back, Jong Kook.
I missed that kind of comment.
- It has been a while, right? - It just came out.
- I... - You forgot to be nice.
It just came out.
- I suppressed myself, - You couldn't change your ways.
but it just came out.
It came out since it was a habit. For goodness' sake.
It just came out.
I was annoyed by his words.
But I also felt glad.
- Seriously. - I felt the same.
- He is better that way. - I agree.
That was great.
We are at the City Hall.
The City Hall? Which stop is it?
This is the seventh stop.
The seventh stop? This is great.
There is a lot to eat here.
The seventh stop? Do we get off at the next stop?
- We get off at the next stop. - That sounds great.
I want a burger too.
- A burger? - Anything would be tasty.
Yes. We should eat something nutritious.
That sounds great.
It might be better to go to a snack food place.
Let's go to a nice restaurant. The production crew is paying.
- If we end up... - To be honest,
the production crew should buy us meat.
- But... - SBS should do that.
Ji Hyo suggested a snack food place because there would be...
- a long menu. - I mean...
We would be less likely to fail.
- That's right. - We wouldn't eat something bad.
What if we end up getting soju?
I would be thankful.
- No way. - I would be thankful.
That wouldn't count. We can't drink soju on the show.
- We can't drink soju. - You have to drink it.
- Really? - Yes. You have to drink it.
- Really? Would SBS be okay? - Yes.
- I... - We need to get ready to get off.
Let's eat here and take a cab...
to go to Hannam-dong.
Let's do that.
Eight minutes should be enough, right?
- Take the Namsan Third Tunnel. - This stop is...
- Chungjeongno Station. - Chungjeongno Station.
- The next station is... - We get off here, right?
Gongdeok Station.
- Don't we need to get off? - We need to get off.
- Let's wait by the door. - Let's go.
- Have a nice day. - Thank you.
- We are here. - Thank you.
- Didn't we pick the perfect number? - Sir, please hold on.
- Thank you. - We picked the perfect number.
Thank goodness we picked eight.
You can move, eat, or complete a mission.
- Shall we eat here? - Sure.
Let's go on an 8-minute taxi ride first.
Shall we do that? Let's eat there.
- We don't know this place. - Okay.
- Hold on. Where are we? - We need to cross the road.
Gangnam is that way.
- Wangsimni. You are right. - It's that way.
- Let's cross the road. - Let's cross the road.
- The crosswalk is over there. - It's over there.
Let's take a taxi here.
We will travel for eight minutes.
We won't have enough screen time. We are nearly done.
- It's okay. - Crew, would you be okay?
We are moving so fast. Would you be okay?
If we take a taxi back to the City Hall area,
there will be many buses that head to Gangnam.
That's right. The weather is perfect for the shoot.
- Look at that. - The light changed right away.
- What timing. - The light changed right away.
That was incredible.
- It changed right away. - We didn't even need to wait.
This is insane.
Wangsimni. Will we be able to hail a taxi?
- We need to go toward Gangnam. - We can ride it for eight minutes,
so let's ask the driver to get close to Gangnam.
- We need to get close to Gangnam. - Okay.
- Exactly 8 minutes. - Exactly 8 minutes.
We will set the timer on the phone.
- Really? - When eight minutes are up,
get off the taxi.
- It's here. - How will you follow us?
(A taxi passes by!)
It's here. Let's get in.
- Hello. - Hello.
- You can take the passenger seat. - Okay. Thank you.
Call us.
After eight minutes...
Get in.
- Set the timer. - I will set the timer.
Please go near Gangnam as much as possible.
Please go near Gangnam.
We need to take a bus afterward.
- You know... - This is Nanji Hangang Park.
Nanji Hangang Park. I thought this bus would stop.
- It isn't stopping at all. - It isn't stopping at all.
This bus is taking the Olympic-daero.
This is driving me crazy. What should we do?
- Hey, this is... - Jae Suk.
This bus isn't stopping at all.
This is driving me crazy.
What do we do now?
At Gimpo, we need to take the same bus back.
The round trip will take two hours.
- This is bad. - Our destination is Apgujeong,
but we are going in the opposite direction.
- This is bad. - We need to strategize well.
After we take the same bus back,
we can ride a taxi for eight minutes...
toward Apgujeong.
We can ride a taxi for eight minutes.
It isn't so bad since there is no traffic.
- I know. - It feels nice...
- since we are going fast. - That's right.
It feels nice since it isn't suffocating.
If I don't think of it as a shoot, it's very nice.
If I don't think of it as a game, it's very nice.
- It's a shoot. - It's a shoot.
Right.
I am riding a bus with you and Se Chan.
That's right.
Where are we going right now?
Jae Suk, isn't that a cruise ship?
What's that?
- Jae Suk, we need to go... - We are in Gimpo.
to Gangnam. But we are seeing ferries.
Hold on. Isn't that the outlet?
The outlet in Gimpo?
- You are right. - Hyundai Premium Outlet Gimpo.
Look outside the window.
(When they look outside the window)
It's pretty.
Where are we going?
Where are we? What is this place?
I am seeing barbed wire fences.
(It's a view they didn't expect to see today.)
Why does this always happen to me?
- You are unlucky. - I am serious.
I have no luck...
- in this kind of game. - Seriously.
- I am like that. - I am like that too.
And the two of us teamed up.
Seriously. I have no luck.
I wonder where Suk Jin's team went.
- Suk Jin's team... - I bet they are struggling too.
I know.
Sir, thank you much for your cooperation.
Thank you.
How far can we go in eight minutes?
In eight minutes, you can reach Myeongdong.
- Myeongdong. - Myeongdong.
There is a lot to eat in Myeongdong.
Myeongdong would be a good place.
It would be a good place indeed.
All right.
Now, 42 seconds remain.
Hello, sir. Do you know who I am?
Not really. I don't know.
It's okay.
You don't know who we are.
- The woman in the back is... - Who is she?
Kim... Song Ji Hyo.
Yes, I am. Hello.
All of you are famous.
Yes. You know who he is, right?
Who is he?
My goodness.
(Haha)
What could his name be?
Is he Haha?
- Yes. - You know.
Do you know the TV show, Running Man?
- I watch it often. - Do you watch it often?
It's on every time I turn on the TV.
Thank you.
- Where is that member? - Who?
- Yoo Jae Suk? - Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yoo Jae Suk. - He took a different vehicle.
He is in a different team.
I see. Is he in a different team?
- Yes. - Yes.
If you have any dissatisfaction regarding Jae Suk,
- please tell me. - That's a good one.
(Reporter Ji tries to get him to badmouth Jae Suk.)
That's a good one, Suk Jin.
- Regarding Jae Suk? - Yes.
Is there anything he should fix?
- There is nothing he should fix. - Okay.
How is he so popular when he isn't that handsome?
(The driver makes a loaded comment.)
- That was what we wanted to say. - That's a fact.
How is he so popular...
- when he isn't that handsome? - Seriously.
He made a funny comment.
Now, 6 minutes and 45 seconds have passed.
Eight minutes haven't passed yet.
Will we reach Myeongdong?
- Myeongdong. - Myeongdong Station.
- Myeongdong Station. - That would be the best.
This is bad.
- We should get off here. - It's over there.
- Please pull up here. - How much time remains?
Over there?
- Yes. - Fifty-eight, fifty-nine.
- Time's up. - Time's up.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Have a nice day. - Bye.
My goodness.
We are here.
Have a nice day.
Thank you.
- Film this. - We should wait here.
- The timer. - We got off exactly on time.
- It was perfect. - It counts, right?
(Suk Jin films things without being asked.)
This doesn't blink.
There are no staff members.
(The staff members are coming in a different vehicle.)
We should tell them that we are at the Shinsegae Department Store.
- I will call them. - Will you do that?
- My goodness. - This is funny.
- It's funny that they aren't here. - I know. They aren't here.
It's no wonder they gave us this camera.
I see a samgyetang restaurant,
but it's closed.
- I really want to eat samgyetang. - I am hungry.
- How about a Chinese restaurant? - A Chinese restaurant?
A Chinese restaurant would be nice.
- The 8th dish wouldn't be bad... - The 8th dish.
- at a Chinese restaurant. - It would be nice.
It wouldn't be bad. That's a good idea.
A Chinese restaurant.
Is the camera working?
- Yes. - How do I know? Is it working?
- Press this. - It's filming properly.
- Is it filming properly? - Let's film each other.
Right now...
(They agree to film each other.)
We are in front of the Shinsegae Department Store.
- We will totally win. - We got stranded.
Where should we go?
The staff members aren't here yet.
It's Haha.
- They should give us time. - It's Ji Hyo.
- It's Suk Jin. - People think we are being weird.
(People think we are being weird.)
- It's Suk Jin. - Seriously.
What should we do? Should we walk for a while?
(They play with the camera.)
There you go.
Which direction should we take?
- Is Gangnam that way? - It's that way.
- It's that way. - That way?
What happens if we take a bus here?
- There it is. - Does it go to Gangnam?
There is no eight.
- There is no eight. - Sorry.
- There is no eight. - Hold on.
- Where does this go? Cheongdam? - Apgujeong?
- It goes to Apgujeong Rodeo. - Apgujeong Rodeo.
- We need 1, 4, or 3. - We need 1, 4, or 3.
- One, four, or three. - It goes to Apgujeong Rodeo.
- Let's pick the number again. - But...
- it will be dangerous. - Here is the important thing.
- Why? - There are many buses...
which go that way.
We need to go over there so that we don't end up...
- in a different place. - Shall we do that?
- That's right. - Let's study the route.
- Listen. - Apgujeong Rodeo.
- It's not like that. - Here.
- You are right. - It isn't the solution.
- Listen. - Four or three.
- We just need to pick 1, 4, or 3. - Listen.
If we pick one.
- we get off after 1 stop. - We get off after 1 stop.
That's why we can't get on this bus.
We will need to get off...
- after 3 or 4 stops. - You are right.
- You are smart. - Thus,
- it's better to go over there. - Listen.
There is a Chinese restaurant across the street.
Shall we go to that Chinese restaurant?
- Let's go. Let's cross the road. - Let's eat.
- Let's eat. We are hungry. - Let's eat.
(They suddenly decide to eat.)
It's the stop.
- We are finally getting off. - We are getting off.
Let's get off.
Sir, have a nice day.
- Okay. - We finally got off.
We need to go over there.
Over there.
Where are we?
Gimpo.
Should we take a taxi or a bus?
- Let's take a taxi. - Let's travel for eight minutes.
Okay. Let's travel for eight minutes.
- Where are we? - Gimpo.
Let's do a mission.
- What would we do here? - What's here?
- A mission? - Let's do one.
- Let's do a mission. - A mission.
- Let's go inside. - Let's go.
We came a long way.
I feel like I am dreaming.
- We are suddenly in Gimpo. - You know,
I think I will remember the bus ride for a long time.
Where on earth are we?
Let's pick a mission.
(Team Jae Suk picks a mission.)
Go ahead.
- I won't pick it. - I will pick it.
- I can't do it. - I will pick it.
I am scared.
There are four. It's this one.
I don't know if we will be able to go to Apgujeong.
Here.
(Team Jae Suk decides to do one of the two missions.)
What is it?
- The mission. - The mission.
- "Get your eyelashes..." - "Get your eyelashes permed?"
(Mission 1: Get your eyelashes permed.)
You need to perm your own eyelashes.
- Do you mean our eyelashes? - Yes.
How do you do that?
You put on formula here...
- to get them permed. - Really?
- Then they get curled. - Once you do it,
- you will look annoying. - The eyelashes get curled.
Jae Suk.
When was it? A hairdresser permed my eyelashes one time...
since they were long.
- I thought I looked so annoying. - Afterward,
your eyelashes will look like this.
So Min looks cute,
but if you and I get them done...
- Eyelashes. - You will look like this.
- You will look like this. - My eyelashes will be curled.
Like this.
My eyelashes will be like this.
- Blink. - We need to do it on eight eyes.
- Since your number is eight, - Yes.
you need to do it on eight eyes.
There are only six eyes.
Shall we pick the number again?
Will you pick the number again?
Then we won't be able to go back.
- We need number eight. - You can pick it again.
Really?
It's raining. This is bad. What should we do?
- It's raining. - My goodness.
- Let's take cover. Come here. - What are we going to do?
- It's a rain shower. Run. - What are we going to do?
(The rain shower falls.)
Run!
- What are we going to do? - The bus stop.
(The sky is shedding tears on the unfortunate Team Jae Suk.)
(An unexpected race)
- Whose fault is this? - This is...
- Hey. - Who is the unlucky one?
- Is it you, Jae Suk? Is it you? - Hold on.
- This is bad. - It's raining so hard. Oh, no.
We don't even have an umbrella.
What are we going to do?
I didn't think it would rain, but it suddenly began to pour down.
Hey.
(Dazed)
We are in trouble today.
- What are we going to do? - It's raining hard.
- It's raining so hard. - How do we perm our eyelashes?
I will pick a new one.
Pick a new lucky number.
(Team Jae Suk picks a new lucky number.)
Are we picking a new number?
It will take too long to work on eight eyes.
- One would be the best option. - Let's work on one person.
- It's 1. - It's 1.
Who will get an eyelash perm?
- Me? - Your eyelashes are the longest.
- One person. - Sit down.
(They do the mission on Se Chan's one eye.)
- You know how to do it, right? - You have long eyelashes.
I have long eyelashes.
We don't have much time.
- We need to work fast and leave. - Let's work fast.
We need to work fast and leave.
All right.
- Close your eyes. - Okay.
I need to do this first.
- Keep tilting your head back. - This is hard.
I will apply this next.
- Jae Suk, is she doing it right? - I don't know.
- No! - What are you doing?
What are you doing?
What are you doing to my eyes?
- I stick the eyelashes on it. - That's right.
- My goodness. - If you open your eyes...
- It's not working. - I opened them slightly.
Is it working? I don't think it's working.
They are long. They are sticking.
- They are long. - This is suffocating.
No. Hang in there.
- Wait. - They are sticking.
- Let's stick them. - They are sticking.
- You know... - Do I look cute?
- Cute? - I will apply a coat. Wait.
I wouldn't say that you look cute.
- You look a bit annoying. - Right?
We don't have much time.
(Se Chan became annoying in no time.)
When will we complete the mission?
We have another mission,
- right? - So Min, when will this end?
Jae Suk, shall we go to the bus stop on the other side?
- Let's go. - You can do it on the bus.
- Let's go. - Can you go with your eyes closed?
- You can't open your eyes. - Okay.
- I can go. Ready? - Don't open your eyes.
You look annoying already.
- The crosswalk was over there. - I hope it doesn't fall off.
Come this way. Let's go.
(While Team Jae Suk is stranded in Gimpo)
- Let's walk a bit more. - Let's go.
Let's eat something tasty.
- That sounds great. - We are moving quite fast.
There are a lot of tasty restaurants here.
(There are a lot of tasty restaurants here!)
We have a lot of time.
That's right. Let's walk.
We don't walk much.
- When would we come to Myeongdong? - Seriously.
There is no way they will be faster than us.
- That's right. We did well. - We took the shortest route.
- Thank goodness we picked eight. - I know.
Thanks to that, we came here directly.
- Let's pick a restaurant. - A good restaurant.
- A samgyetang restaurant. - There is mala hot pot too.
Hello.
- There is a bulgogi restaurant. - Bulgogi.
- It looks nice. - How about this restaurant?
- How about bulgogi? - Let's eat it.
There is a galbi restaurant too.
No. The bulgogi restaurant...
- seems to have a lot on the menu. - Listen.
- There is a lot on the menu. - The bulgogi restaurant it is.
There is a lot on the menu.
- It seems that way. - There is a lot on the menu.
The eighth item could be...
- a mushroom dish. - That would be really annoying.
Let's go inside.
I hope we get the ribs.
- Japchae sounds delicious. - Ribs.
- That's right. - We didn't receive permission.
- We didn't receive permission. - Okay.
- Ask them. - I will ask them.
If they don't allow filming, it can't be helped.
Excuse me.
Would it be okay if we film while having a meal?
- You can't do it now. - We can't do it now. Okay.
- It isn't allowed. - It isn't allowed.
- It isn't allowed. - We can't do it now,
so we will go to a different restaurant.
(They run into an unexpected problem.)
Shall we go here?
That's a good idea.
- Here. - Let's go.
They have the Iberico pork neck.
This is a good restaurant.
Ask the owner.
Sir, do you allow filming in the restaurant?
- What do you want to film? - We want to film ourselves eating.
- You are Ji Suk Jin. - Yes.
- Go ahead. - Okay.
- Do you allow it? Thank you. - The restaurant is busy.
- Thank you. - Let's go to the end.
We need to eat the eighth item on the menu.
(What will be the 8th item on the menu?)
It depends on the menu.
- Not bad. - The menu from the owner.
The menu from the owner? Okay.
Sir, please give us the menu.
The menu. I am so nervous.
- I am so nervous. - I am thankful he allowed filming.
(Will number 8 bring them luck this time as well?)
Please let it be something nice.
Please.
- This restaurant... - Meat.
It might be meat.
- Korean beef. - It will make me go insane.
We picked a pretty good restaurant.
Wouldn't Korean beef be the first item?
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- You are Kim Jong Kook. - Yes.
Do we go from the very front page?
You will pick a page at random.
Really?
- At random? - Pick a page at the front.
The drinks are toward the end, so pick a page at the front.
- The front. - Yes. Pick a page at the front.
- Meat dishes are at the front. - Yes.
- Rice dishes are toward the end. - Rice dishes.
- Pick a page at the front. - Here I go.
(What kind of food will they get?)
(They get beef.)
- Beef. - Counting 1, 2...
- Gosh. - Gosh.
- Beef. - Counting 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6...
(What will be the 8th dish?)
Seven, eight.
- Beef tongue. - Beef tongue.
- It's okay. Beef tongue is nice. - Did I count right?
- Tongue. - Maybe we should go this way.
- Beef tongue. - It's okay. Beef tongue is nice.
- Did I count right? - Tongue.
- Did I count right? One, two... - Tongue.
Maybe we should go this way. One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven... We still get beef tongue.
How much can we eat?
- Beef tongue is tasty. - Beef tongue.
- It's expensive. It's 30 dollars. - Is it 30 dollars?
Beef tongue is a good choice.
- Beef tongue. - Ribs would have been nice.
- Beef ribs. - It's okay. Beef tongue is nice.
- Why are you so disappointed? - Do you like beef tongue?
I like beef tongue. It's tasty.
- It's tasty. Order four servings. - Four servings.
- Order four servings for now. - I am not used to that cut.
Had we gone one page further, we would have eaten japchae.
We would have eaten japchae.
- Let's be thankful for what we got. - Really?
- Let's go someplace else. - A dessert place.
- Let's go someplace else. - Before you eat...
- Since we are very close, - Seriously.
we feel relaxed.
Things are going so smoothly.
I shouldn't use all of my luck on this game.
- Use it on the Grand Award. - I know.
Shall I check the stock prices?
I should check KOSPI.
Maybe you have luck with everything but the stocks.
I am seeing a blue arrow.
- I think... - Minus one percent.
you have luck with everything but the stocks.
What's the point of eating meat? I am losing money here.
My goodness.
Suk Jin, what are you doing?
- Suk Jin. - I think you used up your luck.
- I think it's done. - I became unlucky again.
I suddenly dunked my phone in the sauce.
There is no beef tongue. We are out of it.
- Beef tongue. - They are out of beef tongue.
Really? What do we do in this situation?
- What do we do? - It can't be helped.
You are flustered too, right?
- We will eat the eighth item... - It will take a long time.
on the menu on the wall.
- Let's do that. - One, two, three, four...
- Five, six, seven, eight. - Pork and kimchi jeongol.
- Let's eat that. - Let's eat that.
- Pork and kimchi jeongol. - Let's eat that.
- Sir. - Four servings.
- Okay. - Haha and my YouTube channels...
are stagnant.
- I feel like I am dying. - Do you know how hard it is?
I am taking a break.
Did you stop filming new videos?
You should call people over and drink with them.
- You like to drink. - Seriously.
- These days, I can't drink. - You should do what you like.
Why not? Why can't you drink?
- It makes my body ache. - Really?
You are too young for that.
Look at Ji Hyo. She is still springy.
- How much can you drink these days? - His liver needs to recover.
- Me? - How much can you drink these days?
Sometimes, I get drunk after drinking four cans of beer.
- Really? But that's a lot. - Wouldn't anyone get drunk?
You mean the ones that cost 10 dollars for 4 cans, right?
That's a lot.
Those cans are this big.
- You mean the big cans, right? - The big cans.
- Wine. - I get drunk on those.
- Anyone would get drunk. - Who gets drunk on four cans?
Some people get drunk on one can of beer.
- What? - It depends on the alcohol type.
I got wasted after drinking 1,000ml of beer.
- My goodness. - I got wasted.
I used to drink 30 dollars worth of beer.
(12 cans of beer)
- You drank 12 cans of beer. - I drank 12 cans of beer.
- You are incredible. - You drank 12 cans of beer.
- What? - Seriously.
(The 8th item on the menu appears.)
It looks so appetizing.
- This place is amazing. - It's a proper meal.
We added a lot of meat.
(It's the kimchi jeongol with a lot of pork.)
Sir, my goodness.
Nice shot.
Thank you.
(Ji Hyo scoops out cooked kimchi for the others.)
It should be in the middle, right?
- There is a lot of pork. - My goodness.
The more you boil it, the tastier it gets.
We can keep on boiling it.
Please give me a lot of meat.
- Enjoy the food. - I am not faking it.
In a sense,
we are sightseeing while they are struggling.
- I know. - Right?
- They must be struggling. - Seriously.
- I bet they haven't eaten. - It's so tasty.
- Something like fish-shaped bun. - Fish-shaped bun...
or hotteok.
Why don't we go near Apgujeong and hang out?
- We can do that. - We can do that.
- Right? - Let's do the two missions.
We don't have enough time for anything else.
(While Team Suk Jin enjoys tasty lunch at Myeongdong)
But we can do the missions and eat dessert.
We aren't the only ones who are struggling, right?
They should get lost too.
We aren't the only ones who got lost, right?
- This is a disaster. - Do we need to be there by 2 p.m.?
That doesn't matter.
No?
We should have a cup of coffee.
- But... - We came all the way here.
We shouldn't leave Gimpo without doing anything.
Let's go to a cafe.
A cafe?
- Where will we find a cafe? - There has to be a cafe...
- somewhere. - How about a convenience store?
There are no cafes.
(Disappointed)
- What should we do? - Se Chan, I need to apply this.
Come here.
I can't believe it.
- Come here for a second. - This is...
Would it be okay if we sit here for a short while?
Thank you.
- Sit here. - Thank you.
- I want to eat something. - Sit down.
You can eat what's on the first shelf.
- What? - Did we pick number one?
- The first shelf? - Did my eyelashes get stuck?
Half of them are curled.
(The Camel Eyelashes Perm is nearing its end.)
This is suffocating.
So whether it's a fridge or not, it needs to be on the first shelf.
It's hard to pick an item on the first shelf.
(He can only pick an item on the 1st shelf.)
What I want isn't on the first shelf.
Here is a wet wipe.
- Hold on. - I will use an upward motion...
so that your eye doesn't sting.
Like this.
(My goodness.)
Use an upward motion.
There you go.
(He braved the stinging sensation to get his eyelashes permed.)
It's really uncomfortable.
- How is it? My eye stings. - They are a bit curled.
Hold on. I will use a cotton swab to remove the formula.
My eye stings. My eyelashes are curled, right?
- They are curled. - You completed the first mission.
Okay. Good.
- Let's hurry up and go to Seoul. - Let's go back.
(Glancing over)
I will carry it.
Do you want to ride it?
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Do you want to ride it to Seoul?
I thought it was new for a second.
- My goodness. - Jae Suk, let's hurry up and go.
- He wanted to take the scooter. - Jae Suk.
- Hey. - That would be theft.
You are frugal.
I am beginning to give up.
Seriously. What should we do?
He wanted to take the scooter.
Jae Suk, we need to hurry up and get out of Gimpo.
This is why they say that you struggle when you leave home.
(The unfortunate trio is struggling a lot.)
I have no luck when I play this kind of game.
You are filming Running Man.
Se Chan.
Hello.
- That's right. - Ma'am.
We were in Yeouido.
We were supposed to go to Apgujeong,
but we got on the wrong bus due to the mission.
- We got on the wrong bus. - We came all the way to Gimpo.
I will tell my friends that I saw celebrities.
Thank you.
- All of you are good-looking. - Thank you.
All of you are good-looking.
You are lying.
She is lying.
You should believe her words.
(Jae Suk is quick-witted in this sense.)
Seriously.
Thank you.
- Take care. - Thank you.
Bye.
Stay healthy.
I guess she watches the show. She knows all of us.
She knows all of us.
(Their lucky number is one.)
What?
Here it is. This is the bus.
(They found a bus stop after wandering around aimlessly.)
This is the bus we need to take.
Bus 8601.
That's right.
(The bus number contains 1.)
(Modam Village)
Let's go to Dangsan Station.
It will arrive seven minutes later.
This is the bus we need to take.
- It will arrive 7 minutes later. - It will arrive 7 minutes later.
Bus 8601 will arrive 7 minutes later.
We need to take Bus 8601.
- You see the number of empty seats. - Seven minutes.
(Seats)
(Bus 8601: 68 seats)
(Touching)
It isn't a touchscreen.
(Laughing)
To be honest, I had no expectations from the start.
I knew this would happen when I saw the team members.
We have been here...
for an hour.
We have been here for an hour.
Sit down, Se Chan.
- Yes? - What?
- I forgot to take a photo. - A photo.
That's a good idea. Come this way.
- Take a photo with us. - Take a photo with us.
- We had a conversation. - Come this way.
- We should take a photo together. - Stand in the middle.
- I don't know. - Come on.
- Let's take a selfie. - Let's do it together.
I wasn't going to be in the photo.
Come here.
Ma'am, where are you? There you are.
One, two, three.
(She makes a V-sign.)
Okay.
- Take care. - Bye.
That's quite nice.
- It slides out. - Yes.
It must be a new model.
Do you want to buy it?
It's...
Look at this.
I haven't seen anything like it. It slides out for the camera.
(Dropping)
You dropped the jelly.
It's okay if you eat it in three seconds.
(Blowing)
It's so fascinating.
This is an unexpected side of a big star like you.
- It's a wallet. - It's easy for taking photos.
- The phone case. - You can take photos like this.
There are so many new items these days.
It's old.
- I bought it three years ago. - He is like a middle-aged woman.
- Really? - Middle-aged woman Yoo.
- Take care. - Thank you.
(They finally say goodbye.)
How fascinating.
- He didn't even know... - It's convenient.
that he was dropping jelly.
He was crazy about the phone case. "What's this?"
Can we go back to Seoul? You need to focus.
It's the jelly you dropped.
It's here.
(At that moment)
- It's here. - We need to get on the bus.
Put on your mask.
(The bus they have been waiting for, Bus 8601 arrives.)
Hello.
(They will leave Gimpo after an hour.)
We need to pay.
(Dangsan Station is one stop away!)
Three people.
We need to go out and do the missions.
- The missions. - Shall we do them here or outside?
- Shall we pick one first? - Yes.
- Shall we do that? - I will pick a mission.
We don't have much time, so we need to hurry up.
If we keep wasting time...
That's right. We will end up running late.
- Who will pick it? - I will do it.
- Am I picking a mission? - Yes.
(Suk Jin picks the 1st mission.)
What's this?
- What is it? - I don't know.
There were 4 or 5 balls inside.
(They need to complete 2 missions to move to the ending location.)
Should we complete two missions?
- What is it? - What is it?
(What will be Team Suk Jin's first mission?)
Bowling?
(Bowling?)
I think that's what we did earlier.
The headbanging thing we did.
- That one? - Here...
You will go to a bowling alley.
- What? - And you will bowl with citizens.
- Really? - If you win as many times...
as the number, it's over.
- A real bowling game? - But the number is eight.
Are we going to a real bowling alley to play bowling?
- There's no twist. - I know.
Do you have ping-pong?
Where is a bowling alley? We should find one.
- Let's look for it. - A bowling alley near here.
There's one near the Dosan Park Intersection.
There's a bowling alley. It's 1.5km from here.
We should go to Gangnam anyway. Should we go there?
We can go there for the mission.
The one in Yongsan is farther.
The travel route is really good.
- It's perfect. - I know.
So we should go and play bowling with people there.
- With the citizens there. - With the citizens.
But people in the bowling alley...
- must be good at bowling. - There's one in Yongsan.
- They must be good. - People at the bowling alley?
- They should be good. - I haven't bowled for a long time.
- You don't know the average. - Let's go.
You don't know the average.
That doesn't matter even if you're good at it.
We can't bowl.
Let's go to the Myeongdong Catholic Cathedral first.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Is it done? - It's done.
- My gosh. - I'm tired.
I'm exhausted.
I didn't do anything special, but why am I tired already?
I'm so tired.
(They're exhausted already, but they're at the starting point.)
- Gosh. - Oh, dear.
What did we do for an hour and a half?
I don't know. The eyelash perm.
The eyelash perm, and at the convenience store...
- We ate at the convenience store. - We had a drink...
- and some jelly. - That's it.
- I told you. - For the next bus...
I should pick a good number. Gosh.
Then let's decide whether we take a bus or a taxi.
Okay. Let's do that.
There must be a bus to get there.
Is there a bus from Yeouido to Gangnam?
There are a lot.
We're on the Olympic Expressway again.
At least the bus won't stop on this road.
(Again on the Olympic Expressway)
- It feels better. - Right.
This is what I said before. It's like a hare and a tortoise.
We're tortoises now.
Right. The hare will take a nap...
- and lose the race. - Exactly. It falls behind.
We don't have much time.
(Team Jae Suk is determined to catch up with the hare.)
To catch the hare.
Gosh, we're in Seoul again.
- Gosh, we're back. - It's been hours.
It's been hours already.
- This looks delicious. - This is the place.
Look. They are eating beef noodles here.
- It sounds delicious. - There's mala soup.
That's macaroon.
- It sounds great. - Macaroon?
- Let's... - This place looks nice.
Is there a place that sells hotteok?
- Gosh, this is... - I have a craving for hotteok.
I want it too.
It will take a long time to bowl. We should probably hurry.
- We should hurry. - Right.
Bowling will take a long time.
There's a bus stop.
Where? I see.
- We should pick a good number. - Yes.
There's a bus stop.
We have to be careful here.
Gosh, there are buses that go everywhere.
- We might end up in trouble. - We should be careful.
- Do you want to go now? - We should go.
- Let's check the buses first. - Check the routes first.
We should complete number eight to go to Gangnam, right?
There's no bus that goes to Gangnam from here.
- There's no bus? - No bus to Gangnam?
(There's no bus to Gangnam?)
- We have number eight. - There's no bus.
There's no bus?
Hang on. If we pick number seven,
we will have to go to Suwon.
- No. - No, don't pick number seven.
No, this one is number seven.
We shouldn't pick number seven.
Don't pick number seven.
If we pick a wrong number here,
we will go very far.
- We have to pick number 4. - If we pick number 3...
- We shouldn't pick number three. - Right.
- We can't go to Bundang. - Right.
We might end up in Bundang.
Let's hurry.
Hang on. This is... Yeongdeungpo Han River Park.
How far can we go...
- We should've gone straight. - in only eight minutes.
So Min, hurry.
Hey, hurry and come.
So Min. Jae Suk, we should take a bus here.
Hurry.
(The fast hare, Team Suk Jin)
(Their fate changes only with a lucky number.)
(Where are we going?)
(Good luck finally visits Team Gimpo.)
(They have to win some points!)
(A perfect mission for them)
(Team Tortoise speeds up in excitement.)
(Team Hare should win a specific number of times.)
(Lady luck isn't on their side.)
(And they are against a strong bowler?)
(Are you kidding me?)
(The revolt of the tortoises)
(Who will Lady Luck be smiling on?)
(The Lucky Number Race)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)