It's rather cool today, right?
Yes. The heat let up.
It's cool and refreshing.
Hello
(A girl with black hair
shows up humming.)
I dyed my hair. What do you think?
(A girl with black hair
shows up humming.)
- I wanted to change my image.
- Hello.
Hello.
(Se Chan shows up
with the chirpings of cicada.)
As soon as I get here, the sound...
- I know. The cicada sings.
- It starts chirping.
Hello.
- Ji Hyo looks so cute today, right?
- Ji Hyo, what's with your outfit?
She looks lovely today.
A funky girl.
Why are you guys so skinny?
- She lost a lot of weight.
- I know.
Omicron.
What? Did you catch the omicron?
I caught the omicron.
- When?
What?
I thought she meant
that she just caught it.
So Min and I caught it together.
- What Ji Hyo got was the omicron.
- It was a long time ago.
You mean the thing
from a long time ago?
- Yes. When I was ill.
- I see. It was a long time ago.
- He keeps his distance.
- Okay.
- I can't believe So Min.
- Look at him.
- Why?
- They say they like the shirt...
- I wore earlier.
- It looked good.
- I like what you were wearing.
- Why did you get changed?
- No.
- It was pretty, right?
Jong Kook says
what I was wearing is better.
- Because of you...
- This is so banal.
You should ask Jae Suk.
This is a lot better.
He looked like
a retired chairman earlier.
This is weird. He looks
like an elementary kid.
- You looked younger earlier.
- Don't you think so?
- Now you look like Mr. Color Paper.
- I know.
- Mr. Booger.
- Actually,
the highlight of today is Jae Suk.
- Why?
- Jae Suk is...
dressed like a grandma.
Honestly, I tried to hold it back.
- I wanted him to wear it.
- Right?
- Why isn't he coming?
- He looks like a grandma.
I thought he was my grandma.
Don't let him get changed.
Grandma is finally coming.
- Grandma is here.
- He got changed.
- No.
- No, he didn't.
- Why would you say that?
- Forgetting
(They are ready
to greet the grandma politely.)
They said I looked
like a grandma, right?
I don't agree.
- Look at him.
- You look like a grandma.
- He thinks we're making fun of him.
- I don't agree.
- Mother.
- Grandma.
- What?
- Mother!
I don't care.
So Min mentioned it earlier,
but I didn't quite agree.
- On purpose...
- I'm not ashamed at all.
- A grandma's cardigan.
- You pretend to be fine, right?
- No.
- Do something with the pimple.
- So Min is upset.
- She failed to attack him.
- He doesn't want me to like it.
- So Min.
Are you wearing a towel?
That's what you wear
when you put your makeup on.
Honestly, this isn't the main theme.
- I...
- Why?
When I watched
"My Little Old Boy" yesterday...
- Why?
- What about it?
- Jong Kook?
- You were on the show shirtless.
- It's not like that.
- I couldn't believe it.
(Jong Kook took his shirt off
on "My Little Old Boy.")
(He was on the show shirtless
when he was just in a kids' pool.)
You take off your shirts
on every show, but not ours.
I was very disappointed.
He never does that on our show.
He shows his nipples on other shows.
- He's...
- All nipples.
What I liked about him was
that he had modest muscles.
I also had modest muscles that day.
He always tried to cover his body.
- But he took off his shirt there.
- But...
And he even put something
on his body.
- All over his body.
- Here's the thing.
I often take off my shirt
on my channel.
It's ironic that I never
take it off on other shows.
- Then take it off here.
- What about our show?
A lot of kids watch this show.
"My Little Old Boy" airs late at night.
Take off your shirt on our show too.
Why would I take it off?
He needs a reason.
- He doesn't need a reason.
- It's not like that.
What's wrong about taking off
a shirt at a swimming pool?
- Let's go to a swimming pool.
- It's strange to take it off here.
It was just
a small inground liner pool.
- Anyway, it was...
- He just had some water.
- All we need is water.
- I had to go into the water.
Then show
your lower body on our show.
Hey.
This show is for those above age 15.
What are you wearing?
- Haha.
- What's wrong with this?
- Why?
- You can't wear that here.
- What's that?
- What's wrong about this?
- What's wrong with you?
Have you not kissed at all?
Dream will be watching this.
Do you not mind it at all?
- What's wrong with this?
- This isn't just a kiss.
- Not just a kiss.
- We should blur it.
This is not right.
All our outfits are a mess.
- Doesn't he have another shirt?
- It's a mess.
- They are naked.
- This shirt is not right.
This is just fine.
- That's not fine.
- It's not right.
- Pull yourself together.
- We should blur it.
Get a grip.
Get me something.
- I'll do this.
- I need scissors. I'll cut it off.
- But we're...
- Young Jin!
We're being too strict
to one another now.
No, this is not acceptable.
This is just fine.
By the way, Ji Hyo's outfit
is the best I've seen this year.
- She looks lovely today.
- Ji Hyo is...
You can't wear a shirt
with skulls on it around Suk Jin.
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with that?
- He will soon become a skull.
- Me?
- What do I have to do with skulls?
- Hey.
You can't wear that
when you're with Suk Jin.
- Cover it.
- I have nothing to do with skulls.
- You should cover it.
- It's fine.
- He will soon become a skull.
- No.
- Pull yourself together.
- Right.
We never know who will die first.
- So Min.
- My goodness.
- So Min dyed her hair.
- That's right. I did.
I like your hair, So Min.
- Well done.
- I dyed my hair.
He does sound like a grandma
who nags a lot.
- I like her hair. What?
- Good.
There are a lot of grandmas
who are nice and kind.
Are you trying to belittle grandmas?
- That's a hasty generalization.
- Apologize.
- Hey! Get lost!
- Hey.
- Everything we say...
- Grandmas are...
Whatever we say, it's belittlement.
- Not all grandmas nag a lot.
- Seriously?
- My mom is a grandma too.
- Hey.
And my mom is a grandma too.
What about my mom?
She's a grandma too!
- Hey.
- And my mom nags a lot.
How could you say that
about grandmas in Korea?
(This is how the members
of Running Man attack each other.)
Today is Monday.
- We're being sensitive.
- Seriously...
- Se Chan looks good today.
- Why?
- He lost weight.
- Right.
- I lost 1kg.
- I knew it. I could tell.
When he loses weight,
his jaw area becomes slim.
Right. So my mouth
sticks out even more.
- I know.
- It's better when I'm fat.
We have some news to share.
- What is it?
- What?
For Korea's most
influential celebrity...
- Why would you say that?
- He was ranked number one.
- My goodness.
- It's Yoo Jae Suk.
- Number two is BTS.
- My gosh.
- Thank you.
- He's the most influential figure.
- I mean...
- I saw that too. He won...
over 70 percent.
I was greatly influenced by him.
Thank you. This is just...
Honestly,
I don't study others' faces,
but I do study his.
- Is it an influence?
- Yes, it is.
Jong Kook does.
He's the only celebrity...
- I walk on eggshells around.
- He does mind me.
Jong Kook does mind my feelings.
Look at me.
(Look at me.)
- This is what I do.
- He's 44.
I think this is just fine.
- Hey.
- Well done.
This is where you should put it.
- He's 44.
- What are you doing?
That's right. This is nice.
- It looks nice.
- I told him something earlier.
I told him to grow his hair.
- I know.
- My gosh.
I'll grow my hair
starting on November 1.
- He should grow his hair.
- If you have your hair cut short,
it should look good on you.
But your jaw area looks
like a middle-aged man now.
Because I'm a middle-aged man.
That's why!
(Exploding)
What?
- Get lost!
- He's upset.
Actually...
Are you wearing a skirt or shorts?
It's a skirt!
- This is a skirt!
- Stop it.
- A skirt.
- Your children are watching.
It looks like a skirt.
Before we start today's race,
- I will take your phones.
- Why?
- Please give it to me.
- What?
- I don't have my phone with me.
- Why do you want my phone?
No.
- My phone...
- Please give it to me.
- Why?
- This is important.
- Just take mine.
- Why my phone?
- This is mine.
- Where's mine?
Why?
Why my phone?
(They hand over their phones
with doubts.)
- All our phones?
- What are they writing down?
- They're writing down something.
- What is this for?
I need to check the stock prices.
Now I will tell you the rules
for today's race.
- Please bring in the roulettes.
- Okay.
We're spinning the roulette
from the beginning.
Oh, right. It's the penalty.
What? A roulette?
- I forgot about the penalty.
- That's right.
It's the penalty project.
You know what?
- They started collecting opinions.
- Really?
As you can see, each roulette has
28 slots with your names on them.
- Yes.
- Each roulette has our names.
What is this for?
There will be four missions.
You'll get empty slots
according to your rankings.
You can write the name
of a member you want on the slots...
- and put them on your roulette.
- I should attack others.
You will spin the roulette to decide
which person gets a penalty sticker.
(They will spin the roulette
and give a penalty sticker.)
- Can I write down any name I want?
- Yes.
- Whom should I pick?
- We can choose.
- Who should it be?
- I can pick anyone I want.
So you should try to get
as many empty slots as you can.
This is about probability.
And you just
finished your first mission.
- We did?
- When?
(We already did it?)
We just determined the ranking
with the remaining battery level...
- of your phones.
- What?
My battery was full.
- Mine was very low.
- My battery was almost dead.
Number one is Jong Kook,
100 percent.
It was full.
- I knew it.
- He didn't use his phone at all.
Number two is Ji Hyo, 99 percent.
- Doesn't she use her phone at all?
- I know.
Number three is Jae Suk,
97 percent.
What?
Number four is Haha, 95 percent.
- What about me?
- I guess I'm the last.
Number five is So Min, 90 percent.
Am I number six?
Number six is Suk Jin, 75 percent.
- My gosh.
- I charged my phone.
This is like our stamina.
The last is Se Chan, 50 percent.
- Did you not charge your phone?
- I don't usually charge it fully.
- I see.
- You'll get the empty slots.
Number 1 gets 7 slots.
- I see.
- That's good.
- I should've charged my phone.
- This is nice.
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Jae Suk,
Haha, So Min, Suk Jin, Se Chan)
My goodness.
- I get only two slots.
- Why did I...
I think it would be fun...
if Suk Jin got a penalty.
Whom should I pick?
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo
got penalty stickers last week.
- That's right.
- Yes.
We should distribute the stickers.
- Whom should I pick?
- Who should it be?
- Jae Suk, why...
- Hey, why...
Why do you not agree
that you look like a grandma?
- I agree.
- Do you agree?
- I do.
- Okay.
- So Min.
- Yes.
- I agree.
- Okay.
- Still talking about a grandma?
- Do you not like this shirt?
(Do you not like this shirt?)
- I love it.
- Okay.
- So Min, I agree.
- So Min, I'm happy...
- that I got changed because of you.
- Okay. I get it.
Whom should I attack then?
So I can cover the whole section.
You can completely
cover Section One.
What do I do then?
First, I need Ji Suk Jin.
- Why me?
- Ji.
I'm so envious. I got only one slot.
(Se Chan got only 1 slot.)
Can you give me one?
Can we give the slots to others?
No.
Today, I really don't know
whom I should attack.
Today, it's somewhat...
It's not like I'm mad at anyone yet.
I don't want to write down
any names yet.
I bet they will write Jae Suk's
name a lot because of the opening.
Haha, I will write down
your name on five slots.
Let me see.
(Se Chan also wrote
Jae Suk's name.)
- Why did you pick me?
- I have only one slot.
(The pink cardigan has become
a public enemy.)
Okay. So this is how it goes.
I get it.
Jae Suk, I have only one.
You have 1, so I'll have 1.
(Getting his revenge)
Haha has 2, so I'll have 2.
(This is the beginning of a war.)
All right.
Then there's Suk Jin.
I'll write down Suk Jin's name.
Why?
(They write each other's names
on 1 slot each.)
I have no choice but to pick
the members who chose me.
Don't be so emotional.
We're doing this for fun.
Yoo Jae Suk on three slots.
- What?
- Jong Kook.
- Yoo Jae Suk for three?
- Done.
Why did you write down my name?
Why did you pick me, Haha?
(He sounds calm.)
(He just said
he was doing this for fun.)
Why did you write my name?
Ha.
- They all wrote down my name.
- Ha.
- Why?
There are people
who weigh on my mind.
(Throwing a tantrum)
- Done.
- Gosh.
(He wrote Haha's name
on 5 slots in a row.)
Because I wrote his name
on one slot?
- I'm just...
- They are five.
I mean, he picked...
It went up fivefold
because I wrote his name.
- I already got a sticker last week.
- He's throwing a tantrum.
- And...
- I didn't...
- Jong Kook. I didn't pick you.
- Why does it have to be me?
I already got a sticker last week.
Don't you think so?
It's a war from the beginning.
- Ji Hyo, why did you write my name?
- No.
I'm just being fair.
- It's not fair. Why...
- This is so...
Because of your grandma sweater.
This is only fair.
Are you guys done?
- And you checked them all.
- Yes.
You will get changed
and move on to the next mission.
- Okay.
- Yes.
It's cold.
Hey.
Gosh, this is...
Are we writing down something again?
Or maybe it's a drawing game.
Aren't we going to play
a drawing game anymore?
Yes! It's a sketchbook.
- What?
- I haven't been here in a while.
Why? Why do you say that?
This is where
you had a blind date before.
- Right. When I looked like a mess.
- Just...
stay quiet if you don't have
anything to say.
You don't have to comment...
- on everything I say.
- We haven't been here in a while.
My gosh.
I wrote 1 and got 5.
Right?
This is what I say all the time.
I just don't like
an unprovoked attack.
- That's just...
- I had my reasons.
- You did?
- You have your reasons.
- You just don't know that.
- Let's do this.
Why did you write Jong Kook's name
all of a sudden?
You had no reason.
Yes.
- I had.
- You had a reason.
It drives me crazy
that these two get along so well.
(They make a fatal duo
when they get along well.)
I don't like it either.
Jong Kook and I are inseparable now.
Don't be like that!
You should slander each other.
I don't have anything
to say about him.
I just don't like it when he takes
off his shirt on another show.
- So what?
- All right.
This mission is...
Solomon's Choice where
citizens will cast their votes...
to determine your rankings.
- My gosh.
- Is that so?
You will have a free discussion
on various topics...
and write down your own answers.
And we will conduct a survey
of citizens for about an hour.
It's all set...
- in Hongdae and Shinchon like this.
- For real?
(The ballot boards are
all set in Hongdae and Shinchon.)
- This is interesting.
- My gosh.
- Should we get more votes?
- I can win.
There will be
three different subjects.
The first ballot board is
set at a shopping mall...
in Shinchon where there are many
office workers...
- and college students.
- Shinchon?
- Shinchon is...
- It's Shinchon.
And the second ballot board is set
in a karaoke room at Hongdae...
where there are many
young people and foreigners.
(A karaoke room at Hongdae)
Lastly, there will be online voting.
- Online.
- Online voting?
- Okay. Good.
- Online.
The member with the most votes
will be ranked number one.
And you'll get
the roulette slots accordingly.
- But this...
- This is important.
I'm not sure I can win.
The thing is,
your answers will be anonymous.
- That's fair.
- We should do that.
Some people must have
preconceptions about each of us.
It's different from affection.
I'll win over Generation MZ.
Then will they see our debate?
- Of course not.
- No, only your opinions.
- Nice.
- Only our opinions.
- We have a chance to win.
- Nice.
- Yes, we have a chance to win.
- I'm worried.
- Use your personal experience.
- Of course.
If I have no experience...
- You can imagine the situation.
- That's okay, right?
- You can tell someone else's story.
- What topic could there be?
You must've experienced everything
since you've lived long enough.
But why are you scolding her?
- I'll figure it out on my own.
- You've lived long enough.
- I know you're trying to help her,
- Right.
- I mean, she's not that young.
- but you're being unreasonable.
- Don't talk with a scolding tone.
- She must've experienced a lot.
- Suk Jin, come on.
- I'll figure it out on my own.
- I'll tell you the first topic.
- What is it?
- Love?
The bossiest comment
you've ever heard.
(The bossiest comment)
- That's easy.
- The comment that I've heard?
- Yes.
- The bossiest comment?
(What comment could the citizens
most relate to?)
- This topic is...
- There are so many.
- "Back in my days..."
- I know a very simple comment.
Most people would think of...
- the phrase "back in my days."
- That should be left out.
- Such a phrase like that...
- "Back in my days..."
I just heard a bossy comment.
- Me too.
- What was it?
As soon as I came, Jong Kook said...
You heard him, right?
"Why is the door open
when the air conditioner is on?"
- That's not a bossy comment.
- I see.
- You should write that one.
- You meant I should close it.
- Write that down.
- No, I didn't.
Or is it the drawing game?
(Before the mission began)
Won't we ever play
the drawing game again?
(The door was slightly open
because of the power cords.)
Shouldn't we close the door
since the air conditioner is on?
(So Min looks at him nervously.)
We're wasting so much energy.
Right, So Min?
Are you going to close it?
(So Min got up
as the environmentalist complained.)
Good.
That's the youngest member's job.
On the other side.
You should fold that, So Min.
- You meant I should close it.
- That's right.
- No, I didn't.
- I don't think he meant that.
- I've heard something really bossy.
- I think he wanted me to close it.
No, I didn't.
"Just do it."
It's what Suk Jin says often.
- "Come on. Just do it."
- "Just do it."
- "Stop talking." I'll write it.
- Is it a bossy comment?
"Stop talking."
I also say, "Don't think too much."
- "That's how it is" is the worst.
- Right.
- I just heard a bossy comment.
- "Just do it."
Why? What did you hear?
What is it?
"Aren't you old enough
to think of it?"
That's so annoying.
(Aren't you old enough
to think of it?)
(Feeling guilty)
That's the worst.
- Who said that?
- He says that to me and Jae Suk.
- Was it Jae Suk?
- Suk Jin, you just said it to me.
- Suk Jin said it.
- To whom?
- Suk Jin said it to me just now.
- Yes, he did.
- I clearly heard it.
- I didn't say that.
- You said it.
- I've heard this.
- Why are you lying?
- "What do you know?"
- But that's true.
- Right. I do not know.
- That's...
- But I live my life in my way.
- My way, my life.
- It doesn't sound bossy.
"My life, my way."
- Then why does he act bossy?
- "What do you know?"
- It's because...
- The viewers...
- "Then what do you know?"
- "Hey."
- We should guess the first place.
- The thought of it alone angers me.
- "Hey, what are you wearing?"
He sounds so bossy.
"Hey, what are you wearing?"
It's a bossy comment, right?
- But you see...
- You heard that earlier.
Reading the words is not
good enough.
- It depends on the tone of voice.
- Right.
- "Just be quiet."
- What about this one?
"Hey, that's not a good idea."
"That's not a good idea."
- "Hey, listen."
- Right. That's a good one.
- All office workers would hear it.
- "That's not a good idea."
- "Hey, that's not a good idea."
- That's the perfect tone.
- "That's not a good idea."
(Jae Suk can say the comment
in a perfectly bossy manner.)
- "Shut your mouth. That's not it."
- "Shut your mouth?"
(The reason why he can say it
with a perfect tone)
(No,
I don't think that's a good idea.)
He didn't even let me finish.
(He often cuts others off
and says, "That's not a good idea.")
- This is a perfect example.
- "Hey, what do you know?"
- "What do you know?"
- "What?"
Suk Jin makes
a lot of bossy comments.
- Really?
- Indeed. "Will you sit there?"
- That's not a bossy comment.
- "Will you eat that?"
- I ask those questions politely.
- Suk Jin asks, "Will you eat it?"
- "Will you eat it?"
- What about this one?
- "Why are you so late?"
- I know that, but...
- "I'll leave. Do it without me."
- That's thoughtful, not bossy.
- Suk Jin used to say it...
in the early days of Running Man.
That's what he'd say
when he's upset.
- That's him sulking.
- No.
- Really? This isn't bossy?
- That's not bossy but sulky.
- Why do you think it's bossy?
- "I'll leave."
- "I'll leave. Do it without me."
- Who could be that petty?
- He swore after saying this.
- I was just upset.
He swore. I'll add it.
That sounds just petty.
"He swore."
He swore after saying this.
(He added more details.)
And then, he said,
"That filthy jerk Haha."
"Filthy?"
(The story is being updated
nonstop.)
- I didn't say that. Come on.
- You did say that.
- I didn't call him "filthy jerk."
- Yes, you did.
- Why would you come between us?
- It's true.
The week after that, you started...
- staring at me from head to toe.
- Right.
- He said that.
- Hey, Haha.
- I love you.
- Did he really say that?
- Yes, Suk Jin said that.
- That's what a petty man would say.
- "I'll leave. Do it without me."
- That's a bossy comment.
Would this be considered bossy too?
"I'd like to propose a toast."
Does it sound bossy?
- Of course, it is.
- It sounds a little bit bossy.
EYY!
- Enjoy your youth!
- MFLF!
Men's friendships last forever.
Such phrases are old-fashioned.
Super cool!
- There are a lot of such phrases.
- Don't we propose a toast...
when we have a team dinner?
- Especially Jae Suk.
- Don't you do that often?
- He uses a lot of old phrases too.
- To liven up the mood. It's fun.
When my dad uses this word,
it drives my mom crazy.
- It has three syllables.
- What is it?
This would drive you crazy.
It drives you crazy too.
But it's not bossy...
- "Here's advice just for you."
- Right. This could be...
- That's the worst.
- ranked first.
- I came up with this comment.
- Okay.
"Anyway!"
- What's that?
- No.
"Anyway!"
- What's that?
- No.
- "Anyway?"
- I thought he was listening to me.
I explained something to him
for 30 minutes.
Then he said, "Anyway..."
- He wasn't listening to me.
- "Anyway!"
- "In any case."
- "Anyhow..."
- "Quiet down."
- "That's not a good idea."
- "Shut your mouth."
- "The world has changed."
- Right. "The world has changed."
- "The world has changed a lot."
- That's a good one.
- It's the worst thing to hear.
- "You should be grateful."
- "The world has changed."
- "The world..."
Isn't that what you always say?
- That's right. I often say this.
- I mean...
- That's what you always say.
- "Look at this."
- I've made my decision.
- Why is he so sensitive about it?
- "I'm not so bossy, right?"
- Yes.
- I've picked my answer.
- That's such a bossy comment.
- I wrote my answer.
- What is it?
That's what
a bossy person would say.
- "Tell me honestly."
- I'll add to that.
- "I'm not so bossy, right?"
- In fact...
(He got inspiration.)
- They don't know they're bossy.
- Right.
When we have guests
who are members of idol groups,
I always ask this
and ended up being called bossy.
- What is it?
- What do you ask?
"Would you consider me a friend
or an uncle?"
I hate it the most. It's the worst.
- It really is the worst.
- That's the worst.
You'd be considered an uncle.
- Why would he ask that?
- I see.
Right. He must want to know that.
Haha, I think that's a good one.
- "A friend or an uncle?"
- He's insecure about his position.
- Right. Stop worrying about it.
- That's bossy.
- Normally, people say "Shut it..."
- What is yours?
- instead of "Be quiet."
- Oh, I see.
- "Shut it and do as I say." What?
- Isn't it similar to my answer?
"Just do it. Stop talking."
It's different.
They're two different expressions.
- "Be quiet and do as I say."
- "Do as I say."
- It's the same as mine.
- No, it's different.
- You won't accept it, right?
- It's different.
- I wrote it before he did.
- I wrote it first, you punk.
- See?
- "Be quiet..."
- See? He swore again.
- Why...
- Why do you keep swearing?
- That's not a swear word.
- Why would you swear at me?
- The word "punk..."
can be found in novels
and Korean dictionaries.
- You shouldn't...
- "Be quiet and do as I say."
- See? I told you so.
- "I'm saying this for your sake."
I think this is a good one.
- That's what I hate to hear.
- What do you mean?
- Which comment?
- "I'm saying this for your sake."
- I really hate to hear that.
- That's a lie.
- Exactly.
- It's annoying. It's a lie.
- They say it for their own sake.
Those who actually care about you
would never say that.
- "It's because I love you."
- Sorry?
"I'm saying this
because I love you."
Stop copying others' answers.
- I mean...
- It has a different nuance.
- Our answers are all very similar.
- Why would you do that?
Stop copying others' answers.
- They're similar to one another.
- I think this will be ranked high.
- I've made my decision.
- Then go with it.
- Then go with this answer.
- I'll go with this one.
- We all wrote our answers.
- "The world has changed."
- Let's read our answers.
- That's a good one.
- Ji Hyo, what's your answer?
- "The world has changed."
- It's what she told us about.
- I picked...
"Aren't you old enough
to think of it?"
- Right.
- That won't be ranked high.
I'll give you a piece of advice.
You...
- "I'll give you a piece of advice."
I'll go with that.
"I'll give you a piece of advice."
- I'll just write down what he says.
- You see...
- Change your answer.
- Suk Jin likes to give advice.
- He's like a book of answers.
I'm saying this
because we're close friends.
- Write down what Suk Jin says.
- It's the same thing.
That's the same thing.
You should write that comment.
- That's okay.
- Change your answer to that.
- I'll stick to what I wrote.
- I like it. "I'll give you advice."
- We're done.
- Okay. It's been decided.
We'll carry out a survey
with these answers for an hour.
This will be done at Shinchon,
right?
I want to go to Shinchon.
- Suk Jin and I went there often.
- Right.
(What will the citizens choose
as the bossiest comment?)
(Giggling)
That's what Haha would say.
(So Min: Tell me honestly.
I'm not so bossy, right?)
- "Back in my day" is annoying.
- I hate "The world has changed."
- That's bossy.
- That doesn't sound bossy at all.
(Haha: Would you consider me
a friend or an uncle?)
(The survey continues actively
for an hour.)
"Back in my day." This is the worst.
- I never said any of those.
- You're lying.
I found it.
- I said that?
- Yes.
- You asked that question.
- "Would you consider me an uncle?"
(They're having a fun debate
about the bossy comments.)
I'm a college student.
And I'm 21 years old.
We all go to the same school.
The two of us chose number three.
I picked number five.
He just said,
"I'm not bossy, right?"
He said it while we were talking.
I thought, "That's exactly what
a bossy person would say."
I really don't think I'm bossy.
(If you don't know,
you're really bossy.)
- That's true.
- Yes.
Asking if he or she is bossy
alone...
proves that the person is bossy.
Those who don't know
that they are bossy...
think they're trendy
and have a young mind.
Among the people who have said it
to me,
there was none who wasn't bossy.
Honestly, you can't find anyone
who's not bossy like me.
What do you mean?
I'm saying
that I'm not bossy at all.
You are bossy.
Do you know what "bossy" means?
Well... A person like Kim Jong Kook?
(A 13-year-old child's
candid evaluation)
I can tell he's bossy
only by looking at him.
- Number 5.
- Number five?
- Yes.
That's a typical bossy comment.
It's what my grandfather often says.
It makes me feel uncomfortable
and makes me want to go to my room.
I think that I want him
to stop saying such a thing.
Number five. It's offensive.
It sounds like the person is
looking down on me.
"The world has changed."
I hated to hear that
when I was a little boy.
But I found myself saying it
more often as I aged.
Then you should go back to the past.
(What would you feel
when you hear this?)
I picked number seven.
It's obvious that the person wants
to hear a particular answer.
I think the person just wants to be
considered a friend.
It feels like the person wants
to get along with Generation MZ.
It sounds like the person wants
to look younger than he or she is.
(So the survey among the citizens
in Shinchon went on.)
- I heard this so many times.
- This is the worst.
- This is it. Yes, it is.
- No.
- It's the same as "Back in my day."
- I don't think so.
(The worst comment
chosen by the citizens...)
(will be revealed
after the mission ends.)
I'll give you the second topic.
It's for the survey at Hongdae.
- Many young people go there.
- It's about time.
It's my hometown.
The best pick-up line or action
to give the person you like...
- butterflies.
- Come on.
- That's too easy.
- All you have to do is...
smile at her.
You don't need to say anything.
"You look so pretty today."
Just make eye contact with her
and smile at her.
- I know the best pick-up line.
- I have no idea.
I said to my wife before...
when she got in the car,
"Gosh, I'm so annoyed."
- She asked,
- I know.
- "Why? Are you in trouble?"
- I know that story.
I said, "You look gorgeous."
- She liked it.
- This works in all situations.
- She liked it so much.
- "You look so pretty today."
That sounds like a pick-up line
from the 1980s.
- It sounds like a pick-up line...
- "I'm so annoyed." Why?
- from the 1980s.
- Indeed.
It sounds so old-fashioned
that I want to hold a hearing.
Isn't it a good pick-up line?
"Gosh, I'm so annoyed."
- Many people use this pick-up line.
- Not long ago,
- someone said this to me.
- What did he say?
- I wasn't doing anything special.
- Yes.
I just scooped the rice with a spoon
and put it in my mouth.
- And?
- He chuckled and said,
"So Min, you're so cute."
(So Min was eating normally,
and he said she was cute.)
I think...
(What?)
- What's that?
- that his birthday was coming soon.
- No. That's not true.
- I'm sure of it.
- Check if he has a debt.
- Right.
- Hey, you're wrong.
- But he really said it.
You paid for the food, right?
No. He burst out laughing
even when I was just breathing.
- I didn't do anything funny.
- It's not what you think it is.
- Even when I just tucked my hair...
- So did you... Yes.
But you shouldn't fall for that.
- But I was flattered.
- That's not right.
- Did you lend him money?
- No, I didn't.
Do you really think so?
You need to act a little bit
when saying this.
- "You look so pretty today."
- You should say it in a cute way.
- But they can only read the words.
- They can't hear us, right?
- No, they'll only read the words.
- I see. Okay.
I don't know.
I'll just write a simple comment.
(He's drunk.)
He's drunk.
(Drooling)
- Then...
- You... You look so pretty today.
(You... You look so pretty today.)
(The overaction
that would never work on anyone)
"You look so pretty."
That's too cheesy.
- When people used pagers,
- That's better.
- many used this pick-up line.
- You mean, 8282?
- Come on. What's that?
- If we go back to those days,
- things will get complicated.
- That's so old-fashioned.
Back in the day, we all used...
This is amazing.
- "Hurry up, my angel?"
- "Hurry up, my angel."
- My gosh. That's too old-fashioned.
- This would suit you better.
- The number 1004.
- "Please hurry."
- It was...
- so popular back in the day.
- That's so funny.
- "Welcome. Please hurry."
- It was popular.
- What do you think of this comment?
- What?
- "I miss you?"
- Yes.
"I miss you?" That's too ordinary.
- I think that's...
- Try to think of something special.
- Suk Jin.
- Did I make you upset?
- Are you upset with me?
- Ji Hyo hasn't...
- No. Why would I be upset with you?
- Then why do you...
- keep criticizing my answers?
- Or... It's simple, but...
It's simple, but what do you think?
"Where shall we go today?"
- No. That wouldn't work.
- "Just go home."
(Just go home.)
(It's a comment that makes a girl
want to send him home.)
- "Just go home?"
- "Just go home."
- Yes.
- Jae Suk, I wrote my answer.
- Or if I...
- "I'd love to come here with you."
- Come on. I would hate that.
Why?
You'd be at the gym.
- No. What's wrong?
- You want to work out with her?
This was the only pick-up line
I could come up with.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Guys.
- Take a listen.
- My gosh. He's...
- so old-fashioned.
- What is it?
- It worked back in the day.
Gosh. I don't like it.
"You might be bothered
by trivial things."
"Be more confident.
Read the initial letters."
- It means "Go out with me."
- Gosh!
(Go out with me.)
- What's that?
- It would make my heart flutter.
It's an acrostic poem
that means "Go out with me."
- I really like it.
- It's romantic.
"What?
Why is he asking me out suddenly?"
- It's funny though.
- Yes. I'll go with this.
- Right. I think it's a good one.
- "You might be bothered..."
"by trivial things."
"Be more confident. Read the initial
letters." It means "Go out with me."
- It would make her heart flutter.
- It's romantic because...
(Meanwhile, a man is
writing down something quietly.)
It would make her heart flutter...
- only if she's interested in you.
- Look at Jae Suk.
- He's just an old fossil.
- What is it?
- Show me.
- Why would he...
- Why did he write a toast speech?
- What did he write?
JRS.
- "Just like a robot and steel,"
- "Just like..."
"I will keep you safe."
- That's good.
- Good. That would work.
"Just like a robot and steel..."
- JRS.
By the way,
this moment makes me sad.
You guys thought of
a lot of bossy comments.
But not this time. I guess you don't
have much love experience.
- Suk Jin, it's difficult.
- The key to romance.
Can you help us a little?
Shall I read you some examples?
Yes, please. What are those?
"I'm not hitting on you."
"I'm betting my life on you."
(I'm not hitting on you.
I'm betting my life on you.)
(It's such a cheesy and sleazy
pick-up line.)
(They love pick-up lines like this.)
- Oh, my. I...
- Really? Should we go that far?
- I...
- That's just amazing.
- Should it be that cheesy?
- So Min, what would you do?
It's amazing. I'll go with it.
- I mean, I would...
- So Min, what would you do?
(She's lost for words.)
- I would...
- Can't I?
If a man says that,
I would risk my life for him.
- I can use it, right?
- "I'm not hitting on you."
I can parody the line, right?
(The man from the 1980s tries
to copy the answer.)
- "I'm not hitting on you."
- It'd make her heart flutter.
- "I'm betting my life on you."
- If a man says that...
(Meanwhile, he's practicing
the pick-up line he just learned.)
- "I'm not hitting on you."
- My goodness.
- "I'm betting my life on you."
(So Min loves it.)
- That was good. I love it.
- "I'm calling you."
- I really love it.
- That wouldn't work.
We can use it since it's an example.
No, we can't.
"I'm not hitting on you.
I'm tripping you."
(The gym lover ruined
the romantic mood.)
- Write that down, Suk Jin.
- No.
Then I'll compromise.
I'll come up with something
cheesy and romantic.
(What's So Min's answer
that's half cheesy, half bland?)
- So Min added a theatrical vibe.
- What is it?
- Are you writing a book?
- Show me. I'm so curious.
- What is it?
- "The person makes a mistake."
- That's cheesy.
- "Unbelievable."
"You're incorrigible."
"You'll have to be
my responsibility."
- That's cheesy.
- That's too much.
I like this pick-up line.
(It's only cheesy, not bland.)
(Touched)
- I felt it.
- I like this pick-up line.
- It made my heart flutter.
- Right.
(Only Haha likes her pick-up line.)
- It made my heart flutter.
- Good. I like it.
What else?
- It's game over.
- Se Chan.
Write, "You drive me crazy. Darn."
(You drive me crazy. Darn.)
He told me to write, "Darn."
- Hey.
- That's what makes it romantic.
"You drive me crazy. Darn."
(His straightforward confession
made Mirani crazy too.)
- Right.
- Oh, gosh.
I heard about something
that young people do these days.
A man dumps water on his girlfriend.
- Why?
- She says, "What are you doing?"
Then he says,
"I'm watering a flower."
- Suk Jin, that's not romantic.
- "I'm watering a flower."
(Everyone hates it.)
- What is he doing?
- "I'm watering a flower."
- Times have changed.
- They actually do that.
- You should know that.
- I mean...
- You'll be criticized for this.
- Right.
- Why? Isn't it flattering?
- Dumping water on a girl?
- Of course, it's upsetting.
- Really?
- It's upsetting.
- I think it'd be okay...
- if you just opened a bottle.
- I see.
- That's not right.
- "I didn't ask for water."
"I should water my flower."
That'd be okay.
- Right. That's romantic.
- Right?
- No.
- Wait.
I'll be ranked first with this line.
Can I write one of the examples?
- No, you can't use the example.
- One of the examples.
Go ahead.
- Go ahead.
- I'll go with this.
"I'm not hitting on you."
"I'm betting my life on you."
This is amazing.
- Okay. Are you done?
- Yes.
- "You drive me crazy."
- It'll be asked at Hongdae...
- for one hour.
- Okay.
(The streets in Hongdae at 10 a.m.
on Monday are still empty.)
(4. Where shall we go today?)
(6. I'd love to come here with you.
7. You look so pretty today.)
(The survey begins.)
"You might be bothered
by trivial things."
(Se Chan: Go out with me.)
"Read the first letters.
Go out with me."
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook's comments
got many votes in the beginning.)
- It's either number 2 or 6, right?
- I'll pick this comment.
I picked "I miss you a lot."
The fact that there's someone
who misses me...
would make my heart flutter.
Since the person thought of me
in his daily life,
I think that means
he's interested in me.
Rather than a straightforward
confession or a compliment,
this comment feels more romantic.
- Number 2.
- Number 2?
Go ahead. What about you?
I pick number five.
Number five? What is it?
That's funny.
"I'm not hitting on you.
I'm betting my life on you."
Are you sure
you want to vote for number five?
What about this one?
"Unbelievable."
"You're incorrigible."
You're so annoying!
"You'll have to be
my responsibility."
It's the worst. I hate it.
"I'd love to come here with you."
That's what I chose.
I was leaning toward number three,
but then he said it to me out loud.
- It...
- He played out the scene.
I felt sick,
so I went with number six.
(The words made me sick.)
This is the worst.
(This is the worst.)
(1: Yang Se Chan)
It's the worst.
This is the worst.
(1: Yang Se Chan)
Entry number one.
"Read the first letters."
That just makes me angry.
Entry number one...
seems too childish
for a serious situation.
How should I put this?
This is what you'd say
after learning the theory of love.
(What was voted as
the best and worst pick-up line?)
The next one is a minor
but a heroic story of yours.
You are to reveal something good
that you did.
- Something good we did?
- Yes, that relates to you.
Choose one that will
impress the people.
Are you supposed to write
the whole story?
This is going to be posted online.
- Mine's pretty long.
- Online?
It can't be something
super impressive though.
- Something small.
- It must be small.
Just how frivolous should it be?
Like carrying heavy bags
for a neighbor...
- from the elevator.
- Not something like that.
Someone farted during filming
but I didn't say anything...
even though the smell was there.
- That's good enough.
- That I approve.
- Would that be okay?
- So Min's the one who farted.
Why would you...
- She must've had an upset stomach.
- What are you talking about?
It wasn't me.
You can't call her out like that.
I didn't say anything
about Se Chan's stinky feet.
- When?
- Wasn't that nice of me?
- Is that allowed?
- Of course.
- I turned a blind eye to it.
- Must it have been among us?
No, it can be something you did
outside of Running Man.
But mine's pretty long.
- Do you have one?
- Well,
this was edited out of the show
because I said it myself.
Jae Joon and I were in a car,
and we came across a taxi
parked in the middle of the road.
The driver was screaming for help,
so Jae Joon and I stopped.
A drunk passenger of his...
was fighting
to take control of the wheel,
so they were in a frenzy.
The driver was screaming for help,
but other cars...
drove past him
on the four-lane road.
Jae Joon and I
parked our car behind the taxi,
got out, and grabbed
the drunkard to stop him.
I also called the police as well.
The police came by
and handled the rest.
- Why does no one know about this?
- Can you write that all down?
Shouldn't the taxi driver
be thanking you instead?
It's why I can't write it down.
Hold on, I got one.
- On Mapo Bridge...
- This is a true story.
A taxi bumped into my car
from behind.
The rear bumper got caved in.
I felt bad though,
so I just let him go.
I've done that many times as well.
We've all done that many times.
- Of course.
- Then write it down.
Why do you sound angry?
- Write it down.
- There's no need to be angry.
Why add that you've done it
many times before?
There was no need for that.
- I...
- He's like that sometimes.
I've gone after
a hit-and-run driver before.
(Suk Jin's second attempt)
Did you manage to stop him?
I wasn't able to.
(I wasn't able to.)
(He didn't manage
to stop the driver.)
- You should've.
- So you just chased him around?
I can't believe you.
How is that a heroic story
if you didn't catch the guy?
The driver hit a person
and drove off.
At Namdaemun Market...
- Maybe it was on his way.
- A car hit a pedestrian.
- It was a minor incident but...
- What about the plate number?
The driver drove off at high speed
after putting out his taillights.
I drove after him,
- but couldn't catch up to the car.
- In my senior year...
I once mentioned this
on a TV show once.
It happened back
when I was in high school.
(Back when Jae Suk
was in high school)
On my way to school,
I saw high school kids smoking.
(Jae Suk came across
high school kids who were smoking.)
- That sounds dangerous.
- It was 1 against 3.
It could've been nasty.
I don't know
what came over me, but...
- When you were in high school?
- That's right.
I don't know what came over me.
Maybe a sense of justice
ignited inside me.
It was 1 against 3,
but I asked what they were doing.
- What?
- They replied,
"Who do you think you are?"
- I said, "Put out the cigarettes."
- You approached them first?
"Put out the cigarettes."
- I don't know what came over me.
(Jae Suk patronized
other kids his age.)
"Who are you to tell us
to put them out?"
- If only it were me.
- I got scared,
but I asked how old they were.
They said,
"we're 20."
"We're 20."
(We're 20.)
What happened next?
They were older than you.
- They were older than you.
- So...
They were old enough to smoke.
- Did you apologize?
- And?
So I got beaten for it.
(I got beaten for it.)
What came over you?
- I don't know.
- They weren't in school uniforms.
They seemed my age.
- They must've looked young.
- I saw them as high school kids.
- Like Haha.
- I strongly believed...
that high school kids
shouldn't smoke.
Getting cheeky with men
older than me...
earned me a beating.
- Still.
- I showed up at school that day...
in a shirt
that had been pulled by the neck.
- How sad.
- You must've been embarrassed.
They must've been flustered.
- I don't know what came over me.
- Here's my story.
- What is it?
- In middle school,
I packed lunches for friends
who couldn't afford lunch.
- Really?
- Yes, thanks to my mom.
- Your mom did all the hard work.
- Exactly!
- The friends...
- Say that on "My Little Old Boy."
You weren't the one
who packed the lunches.
- My friend...
- You should've packed them.
- He...
- He would always...
go out to the playground
during lunchtime.
I get you were being nice.
- That's all that matter.
- Your mom did all the work.
How could I have packed him lunch
when I didn't even pack my own?
Are you sure you didn't steal
other kids' lunches?
You ate other kids' lunches while...
Yes, that's true.
We're supposed to share anyway.
I'll write this as my heroic story.
Even though I hated Haha's clothes,
I praised him by saying...
- that he looked stylish.
- That's a nice one.
That really was nice of you.
You said someone was good looking
even though there was no difference?
Isn't that
what you said to me earlier?
- Se Chan, you look great today.
- What do you mean?
- He lost some weight.
- You look handsome.
- It was to encourage you.
- How loyal of you.
- Of course.
- You wanted to encourage me.
- We're the same, then.
- Words of encouragement.
That's also why I said this.
This is my heroic story.
While walking my dog,
I cleaned up after other dogs...
as well as cleaning up after my own.
- That was sweet of you.
- Nice.
- Yours and other dogs.
- That was nice of you.
- You did well.
- Cleaning up after other dogs.
- I also cleaned the garbage.
- How nice of you.
Here's mine.
What is it?
The meat I carefully grilled...
was taken from me by a friend,
but I didn't say anything.
- Unbelievable.
- And I didn't touch the meat...
my friend had been grilling.
- Well...
- You...
- You sound like a loser.
- That's camaraderie.
You're such a loser.
- Wasn't it mature of me?
- Yes, but you sound like a loser.
"I didn't eat the meat
someone else grilled."
"I won't eat yours."
(The consideration of a man at 44.)
- It's tough.
- That's also a heroic story.
Jae Suk is shy about these things.
Do you remember
when we all went to dinner together?
You dropped So Min home...
even though it took you
two more hours to get home yourself.
That's what you call
a small but heroic story.
- Of course.
- It took you three hours.
- It wasn't on the way.
- I don't see that as heroic.
It's something anyone could've done.
It's normal for a colleague
to drop another colleague off.
- Add on to that.
- That's what I should put down.
"When Suk Jin
turned his back on her..."
(When Suk Jin
turned his back on her...)
- While knowing.
- While knowing!
- He ignored her.
- Even though...
- it was raining...
- It didn't rain.
- No, it rained.
- It rained.
It was drizzling.
- No, it poured.
- It was pouring.
So Min was trying to catch a cab.
On a rainy day,
when she couldn't catch a cab...
You asked Suk Jin
to give you a ride home.
No, I didn't ask him.
- She didn't ask me.
- I see.
Even though Suk Jin's place
and mine were in the same direction,
he pretended not to hear Jae Suk...
when he offered me a drive home.
- Suk Jin had the advantage.
- Even though...
But he didn't offer me a ride.
Jae Suk already offered,
so who am I to offer her
a ride home too?
- That'd be weird.
- Even though...
Come on, So Min. I gave you a ride
to Incheon Airport recently.
That was for a show.
- So...
- Be quiet, will you?
(Suk Jin fails
to salvage his image.)
This won't make it in the top three.
- This is what I'm going with.
- What is it?
I let someone else
have the 40g protein snack...
and had
the 20g protein snack instead.
- That's huge!
- How generous of you.
- This is incredibly huge.
- That...
That is worth mentioning.
To those who lift weights...
- That's huge.
- It is a touching story.
Are we good?
Did you take the photos?
Hold up what you wrote.
Thank you for taking the time
to write these down.
What you wrote
have been put up for a vote...
both online and on the streets.
This is huge.
The votes will be tallied
while you have lunch...
- and the results will be revealed.
- Okay!
- Nice!
- Yes!
- This won't be in the top three.
- Nicely done.
(The online voting begins.)
(Running Man Online Poll)
(The suggestions
were put to a vote...)
(both in Hongdae and Shinchon.)
(Who got the most votes?)
The votes have been tallied
and the results are out.
- Come on!
- Right.
I doubt I made it
high up in the ranking.
- I think otherwise.
- I call upon the MZ generation.
Here's the result
for the online poll.
- Sure.
- I doubt I scored many votes.
- The heroic story...
- I'm not too hopeful for that one.
- Me neither.
- It was just for fun.
I bet Ji Hyo got a lot of votes.
She mentioned the dogs, right?
I was only trying to be cute.
(I was only trying to be cute.)
(Whose heroic story
was chosen as the best?)
(The result)
- With 46...
- Gosh, that's a lot.
- Me?
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Seriously?
- No way.
- Yes!
I'm the one who reminded you
of this anecdote.
- I appreciate it.
- I assisted you.
- This...
- Please don't forget that.
(Out of 4,272 votes,
he received 2,004 votes.)
Jae Suk, you...
- Seriously?
- It's at 47 percent.
- I won first place?
- Come on.
- Of course.
- It's me!
- The dogs.
- I knew it.
I would've ranked higher
had I stuck with the lunch story.
In third place is So Min
who complimented one's looks...
even though he didn't
look all that handsome.
- So Min?
- That's in third place?
Many wrote the reason as to
why they voted for each story.
"Giving someone a ride home
is the textbook move of a hero."
"Time is gold, and he shared
his gold with a colleague."
My gosh!
- Nicely put.
- I love that comment.
- That's cool.
Time is gold.
- He always does it.
- That's meaningful.
"By revealing it, Seok Sam is given
a chance to reflect on himself."
That's also true.
- That's also true.
- Right. It's a nice story.
The point is he pretended
not to hear it.
Yes.
- Someone said it wasn't good.
- I see.
"Did he have to badmouth someone
to say a good thing about himself?"
That's true as well.
That's a clear judgment.
- That's sharp.
- It's good.
- It fits our sentiment these days.
- Yes.
And there's someone
who didn't like...
So Min's fake compliment
about someone's ugly look.
"She has to give a direct advice
so that her colleague can improve."
That's right.
That's good.
- You should be honest.
- It's...
- convincing as well.
- That's funny.
- That's true.
- Yes.
"It's hard to say it's good that
he didn't tease about the fart..."
"in the middle of the shoot."
- Right.
- He didn't do his job.
- He should've said it for the show.
- Yes.
- He didn't do his job.
- He missed a chance to be funny.
About Haha's story about meat.
"That's pathetic."
I told you it was pathetic.
"Thinking like that itself
is shameless."
Bite me.
- "Bite me?"
- I'll eat all the meat then.
Look. That's pathetic too.
- What's with "Bite me?"
- That's so...
It's about the compliment about
Haha's outfit, which was last place.
Yes, that's me. What did they say?
"It's like a flattery
of a disloyal subject."
(It's like a flattery
of a disloyal subject.)
- They're eloquent.
- They're eloquent. I acknowledge.
"That's why Haha
is still living an illusion."
- That's true.
- That's right.
"Sometimes, realistic advice is
better than a lie for your friend."
Realistic advice.
- So that he can realize.
- Being objective.
The next is "the words
from an old fossil."
The words from an old fossil.
- I'm curious about that.
- Please let me rank high.
(Revealing)
- That's right.
- Who is first place?
(Which sounds the most
boomer-like among these?)
- Wait. What?
- Number five...
- got the most votes.
- "The world has changed."
(Boomer Ji is 1st place.)
- He's such a boomer.
- Suk Jin.
I told you so.
"The world has changed."
- I'm in last place again.
- Second place is So Min.
- These guys...
- Third place is Jae Suk.
Fourth place is Haha.
Jong Kook is in 5th place, Ji Hyo in
6th place, and Se Chan in 7th place.
Look at them.
What do they know?
- What made their heart flutter.
- It's...
- At this rate, I have no hope.
- It's my weakness.
- I won't be ranked high.
- I'm anticipating.
- What I said is plain. It's weak.
- It was weak.
- You're anticipating?
Which one received the most votes?
"I miss you a lot" got a lot.
- It got a lot of votes.
- It's "I miss you a lot."
"I'd love to come here with you."
- Many people chose it.
- I'm in last place.
I'm in last place again.
(Last place 3 times in a row)
He's in last place.
"I miss you a lot." Yes.
- Indeed, love...
- It's classic.
- doesn't need grandeur modifiers.
- Right.
"I miss you" is the best.
- "I miss you." It's honest.
- Yes.
- "I miss you."
- You don't need pretty words.
That's true.
Right. You don't need those things.
Adding the total number of votes and
percentage for the online survey,
- the ranks were decided.
- I'm in last place.
First place is Jae Suk.
You should remember me.
This is annoying.
Second place is unexpected.
It's Suk Jin.
Thank you.
That's from years of experience.
Third place is Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo did better than I thought.
Fourth place is So Min.
Fifth place, Jong Kook, sixth place,
Haha, and seventh place, Se Chan.
I declare war against
Millennials and Generation MZ.
- How can you not know?
- It's okay.
- Should I put it on the second one?
- Yes.
That's right. Round two.
Why did you write my name again?
I can't deal with you today.
I can't deal with you today Haha.
I just wrote one.
(Disappointed)
Okay. Go ahead.
When I become the first place,
I'll write your names only.
- Then I'll do it right now.
- I got it.
- All right. I got it.
- You got it?
- Okay. Let's stop here.
- Let's stop here.
So MIn, did you write four?
Five? Good. Provoke me.
That's good. I'll write So Min
no matter what next time.
Please let me
become the first place.
I'll fill it with So Min's name.
- Did you all put it on?
- Yes.
- Let me explain the next mission.
- Okay.
It's Yoom Yoom Human Fish
where you should eat a donut...
hung on the fishing line.
It sounds fun.
Before doing the mission,
pick one member to help you.
The member who was picked
can refuse.
The member trying the mission should
stand at the starting point...
and eat the donut
hung on the fishing line.
The assistant should hold
the member's arms behind them.
So that the member can lean
to eat the donut.
I see.
- Holding is important.
- Right.
If you succeed, you can try
the next one in the back.
The one who eats the donut that is
farther will be ranked higher.
- Core muscles are important.
- They should be able to hold us.
- It's war.
The one who will be holding us
would be important, right?
It's very important.
We can reject, right?
No simulation?
If you refuse too many times,
they might write your name...
- on the roulette.
- Let's start without simulation.
- Really?
- We can't refuse too many times.
How do we get to choose?
I'll try.
- That's unusual.
- I'll help him.
- Really?
I'm better.
- I...
- Jong Kook is mine. Don't pick him.
- They have to hold me, right?
- Yes.
- I'll choose Jong Kook.
- Okay.
Are you going to accept it?
- Yes.
- You can refuse it.
- I'll do it.
- If he refuses,
- he might take revenge.
- Sure. I'll do it.
- Writing his name on the roulette.
- Thank you.
I'll hold you well. Don't worry.
Can we pick Jong Kook again?
- Yes, you can.
- We can pick him again?
- He's popular.
- But...
- I can't trust the other guys.
- Who is going to do this?
How should I do it?
- How? Since you have to eat it...
- Yes.
Hold on.
Isn't it best to eat this way?
- I don't think I can go far.
- Or stretch the side.
Try it without a donut first.
- It works.
- Keep going.
I can eat this for sure.
- It's the third.
- Jong Kook.
Pull me more. Okay.
- Okay.
- I said not to worry.
I'll try the third one.
- One spot further.
- You're going to do this, right?
- This position.
- Yes.
- It's...
- He wrote your name too many times.
- What if he writes my name again?
- One, two, three, four.
- If he's in last place...
- It's hard to refuse.
- Right. Or he will write your name.
- Yes.
- Here I go.
- Go.
I'll try.
I'll do it properly
since we're working together.
- Squat all the way down.
- All right.
(He starts leaning slowly.)
But why did you write my name?
The one behind him
can betray him, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- You can't do it if you're weak.
- Haha's grip got weaker.
- Hey.
- Wait.
(Sticky rice cake makeup)
- Why did you do that?
- I got it.
- Hey, you should stretch your arms.
- Jong Kook couldn't hold it.
- His strength...
- He should stretch his arms,
but he kept doing this.
- You made it impossible for him.
- I did my best, didn't I?
- Yes, you did.
- I did my best.
Why did you keep your arms
like this? You should stretch them.
He's frustrating.
Was it me?
- It was you.
- I stretched my arms.
I'll do it one more time for you.
Let him do it one more time.
- I'll give you one more chance.
- Yes.
Hey. Stretch your arms.
Don't do this.
Gosh.
I'll do it properly this time.
I'll sit completely.
Stretch your arms.
- I'm totally stretching my arms.
- I'm going to sit. Hey.
- Try it. Hold me tightly.
- Here I go.
Go.
Stretch your arms. Yes.
Does it work or not?
He looks like a catfish.
- Does it work? Should I go down?
- It's hard.
- His lips touched it.
- Did his knees touch the floor?
- His knees touched it.
- They touched it.
- Keep your knees off.
- They totally touched the floor.
He did it.
- Keep your knees off.
- They totally touched the floor.
(He completed stage 4.)
We should remove the second one.
You need a lot of strength.
Gosh.
This is the farthest.
- Are you going to do it?
- I don't think I can do it.
- The one you did earlier...
- I don't think he can do more.
- Right.
- Hold me tightly.
I can hold it
as much as I did earlier.
- Try it.
- Will Jong Kook be able to hold it?
- Look.
- His arms can't do it.
- His arms can't reach.
- It'll work.
His arms can't do it.
- His arms can't reach.
- It'll work.
(Laughing)
(His sticky rice makeup
looks heavier.)
- Gosh.
- It's funny.
You should let me go when I fall.
What?
- Why would I let you go?
- If you hold me so tightly...
You'll fall even harder
if I let you go.
- Jong Kook did his best.
- What should I do?
- In the middle...
Jong Kook, my back hurts so much.
Get up. Okay.
What should I do?
No one can do it.
I'll try.
- Ji Hyo will try it?
- Ji Hyo.
- Who do you want?
- Jong Kook.
- Can you hold me?
- Okay. Come.
I think I can do it.
How are you going to do it?
Are you going to try it?
- Yes.
- Give me your hands.
Hold my hands here.
The donut...
Get into position first.
- Jong Kook...
- The donut.
also pronounces it as "donut."
- The donut is quite far.
Get into position.
Older people pronounce it
as "donut."
- Are you in position?
- Yes.
- Ji Hyo is pretty flexible.
- Jong Kook.
Your bottom should go down too,
Ji Hyo.
She looks like a lizard.
- She can't reach it.
- It's actually hard.
- She's getting it.
- Bite it.
All right. Let's go down, Ji Hyo.
- She's getting it.
- There you go.
- Let's go down, Ji Hyo.
- She's getting it.
- There you go.
(She fell on the flour slowly.)
- It's hard.
- Let go of her.
- That's as far as we can go.
- She just went down straight.
- She even used her whole body.
- Don't your hands hurt?
- I did reach it,
but it didn't come into my mouth.
What if we fall after taking a bite?
That will be counted.
(It'll be counted as long as
they take a bite of it.)
We don't have to hold each other.
- Why?
- We can just take a bite of it.
- No, but that's...
- So you can fall as you eat?
That's not easy to do.
- Why not?
- No, it won't work.
- Come on, So Min.
- It won't work?
- Of course not.
- It won't?
I'll give it a go.
Go ahead, So Min. Who will hold her?
It's not easy to eat it.
So Min said she'd
jump to bite it off.
I succeed as long as
I take a bite, right?
- Then I will...
- I felt it as I did it.
- One, two, three...
- They should be way taller.
I want it a little further
than Level Four.
- A little further than Haha's.
- It's impossible to do it.
- It is?
- A little further than Level Four?
But Haha did it at Level Four.
Are you going to jump
and bite it off?
- Yes. I'll give it a try.
- It'll be funny.
- Give it a try, So Min.
- It could work.
- As expected.
- She said I just need to bite.
- Great.
- Let's go, Tiger Moth!
- Without touching it.
- I like that spirit.
- It's great!
- Tiger Moth!
- Try it with your spirit!
- You can do it!
If you succeed in this,
I won't write down your name
for the whole day.
- Your name.
- Really?
Yes, I mean it.
I should try the same way
after seeing So Min go.
Right? It's not a bad idea, right?
You need strength like Superman's...
which you can fly in the air.
- She must stop midway.
- After you jump,
you should turn like this
and take a bite.
Please shoot it in slow motion too
in case she eats it.
Is she a hero?
I'm so nervous.
- I'm so nervous.
- I applaud your challenging spirit.
- I can't succeed in it anyway...
- Let's go.
if I eat it like this.
- It's ready.
(Here I go!)
Gosh, So Min.
(Laughing)
- That was cool.
- You looked like a fool.
So Min failed.
- Let me try one more time.
- You looked like a tiger moth.
What's even worse
is that she got scared.
(She got scared.)
- She got scared midway.
- So Min...
So it was useless to run up to it.
- She got scared.
- She got really scared.
- It was scary.
- Right.
- I could reach it, though.
- Yes, but it bounces off.
I should try her way.
- I could reach it.
- You?
- Really?
- Jong Kook, you'll give it a go?
- There's no other way.
- You should open your mouth wide.
No one can hold me.
- Why not?
- I'll hold you.
- I'll do it for you.
- I think it'll work...
if I don't get too greedy.
Maybe I'll go for Level Three.
It's better to succeed
in Level Three.
I'll go for Level Three.
- Which level did Haha succeed in?
- Level Four.
- He succeeded in Level Four?
I think I can do this much.
I'll bite off one.
You'll secure Level Three first.
- Then you'll go for another one?
- Because you have to bend.
- You want me to hold you?
- Will you hold me?
- You want me to do it?
- I think you can.
- Hold on.
- Give me your hand.
- Hold me like this.
- Haha.
It'll be funny
if Haha betrays him here.
(It'll be funny
if Haha betrays him here.)
If Haha...
Jong Kook.
(This won't do. Move!)
Don't you know him?
- I didn't do anything!
- His eyes already flipped.
The look in his eyes
looked suspicious, right?
You come here.
- I can't trust him either.
- Why not?
- Hold on.
- You must check their eyes.
Look at them.
Which one will you choose?
Jong Kook, make your choice.
There's no one I can trust here.
- Look at us.
- Look into our eyes.
Look into our eyes.
What should I do?
- Jong Kook.
- Do you want us to do it?
(Will he choose the eyes of
halibut or frozen pollack?)
(Contemplating which fish to choose)
You should just do it. Come here.
His eyes
are already flipped, though.
- Haha, you can do it!
- You chose the person...
you should've avoided the most.
- His eyes are flipped. This is bad.
- You can do it!
Look at his eyes.
Haha, you know
I'm working really hard, right?
Okay.
- Hey.
- I think it'll work.
How come it didn't?
- Haha is...
- Let's go, Haha!
(Practicing how to betray him
with his flipped eyes)
You can do it! Don't be scared.
You got this!
- That's it.
- Let's make a big hit.
- Don't bend my arm.
- I'm trying to hold you.
It looks great.
- You shouldn't...
- You look stable.
You can't do that, Haha.
- Haha. You should also...
- Haha.
- lean back after placing your foot.
- That's right.
- That way, you can support me.
- That way, it'll be balanced.
Look at his eyes.
Hey.
His eyes are already zonked out.
You should lean back
with your foot on me.
We need to make a V shape
so our weight will be balanced.
- A V shape?
- That's right.
Not this kind of V. This one.
That's the fun of it.
But if I write his name...
Jong Kook has written my name
so many times.
So you ought to take revenge.
You just need to hold out a little.
But Haha won't just stay still.
- But Haha...
- He's done for.
- Hey, don't say such things.
- Why not?
We're only saying this
for your sake.
- Look at his eyes.
- Don't do that.
It's all for your sake.
- Look at his eyes.
- He's already gone crazy.
Haha is grabbing his hand
in a way...
- that'll be easy to let go.
- If he just pushes Jong Kook...
- with his knee...
- His grip is getting loose.
- Push him with your knee.
- Look at his grip getting loose.
- Gosh.
- He's letting him go.
- That's it. Come closer.
- We just need to grab the string.
All right. A little closer.
Just a bit more.
(Pulling a prank
with the fishing pole)
(He explodes in the end.)
No, Suk Jin told me...
Suk Jin told me to do that!
- That's not true.
- Suk Jin told me to do that.
- Suk Jin told me.
- That's enough.
All right!
Gosh, seriously.
(The prankster got scolded
by Jong Kook again.)
Let's go for it. Let's make it work.
I'm not trying to be greedy here.
Let me get closer, Haha. That's it.
Haha, you should go closer.
No, I'm almost there. There you go.
You have no idea how tightly
he's grabbing me.
I can't do anything right now.
- I can't do anything.
- You're like a pillar.
He's grabbing me so tight
so he won't fall.
Just lick it.
- Bite it.
- Gosh.
- He got it.
- Goodness.
- You did it.
(Gosh.)
- Gosh, he did it.
He's no joke.
- Gosh, he's...
- Gosh, seriously...
I only went for Level Three!
- Se Chan.
- Yes.
Let's try a different approach.
Let's try a backflip.
- A backflip?
- Oh, with your back against it?
- Will it work?
- Look at this.
Jae Suk, I locked my feet
with yours. Great.
But I can't lean back
if you lock me too hard.
How far will you go?
Or you can grab my shirt.
There you go.
- Like "The Matrix?"
- There you go.
- This is great.
- Yes, it's great.
- It'll work.
- That's it. This will work.
- I'll go for Level Three.
That's too weak.
You should go for Level 3.5...
- because the angle...
- Go for Level 3.5.
- It's possible for Level 3.5.
- You should face front first.
- That's right.
- Facing front won't do.
- It's difficult.
- This is Level 3.5.
Go for it, Jae Suk.
- It's hard this way.
- Just try it.
This way. Will it work?
It will work.
(Surprised)
(Hold on!)
Hold on!
- Hey, Se Chan.
- All right.
- We haven't even begun.
- But this will work.
- But it'll work.
- Hey.
We haven't even begun.
But I was trying on the grip.
You can go far as long as the person
at the back doesn't betray.
- Jae Suk.
- I'll go with my back against it.
- All right. Grab it.
- I'll lock my feet with yours.
You want me to grab it?
I locked my feet with yours.
- Take a look.
- Hold on.
- Wait.
- You got it.
You got it? No, wait!
I'm not ready yet.
(He ate it?)
You got it? No, wait!
I'm not ready yet.
- Is this how it's done?
- He did it.
Didn't his head touch the floor?
No, he didn't say he'd go.
He needs to say he'll go.
I'm sure that he'll let go of me...
if I try it again.
You need to count that.
- I won't let go of you!
- Otherwise, I can't do it.
- Jae Suk, I will never let go.
- Hyung In, I can't do this.
You need to count it.
- Darn it.
- Will you let go of him?
No, I won't because I need you
to hold me for my turn.
- He'll let go of me for sure.
- Get up now.
- Come on.
- Hurry.
- He'll let go of me for sure.
He will let go of me.
- Don't worry, Jae Suk.
- All right, it'll be counted.
- Great.
- Come on!
- Then I'll go for Level 4.5.
- This isn't right!
- It was a practice.
- Let's vote.
- Right. It was a rehearsal.
- It really was a practice.
Whatever! I'll write only Jae Suk's
name for the next one.
- Write his name.
- If I get to write a name,
I'll write one person's name
in all seven slots.
I'll succeed in Level 4.5.
Then Se Chan won't let you.
Why is he so confident
that he'll get seven slots?
- This is stable.
- Won't you slip with this?
- It might fall.
- It'll work for sure.
It'll snap.
I think it'll snap.
- This is great.
- Hold on.
- It'll snap.
Wait.
I told you to wait!
- Why didn't you hold me?
- I need to get ready too!
- Hey!
- Don't just lie down.
- You should've grabbed me!
- Why did you go down?
Let's go.
Se Chan...
(Ripping)
Hey, why did you untie it?
Hey. Se Chan, this isn't right.
- All right.
- I'll hold you when you do it.
- You're right.
- Right?
- I'll hold you like this.
- Okay.
- Is he going for Level 4.5?
- Yes, he is.
- Level 4.5?
- Come a little closer.
- Should I? I'm good.
- You should step on me.
Se Chan has been in last place
many times recently.
Se Chan, why are you...
- Darn it.
- Why are you...
(Ripping)
(The belt hit him
in the wrong spot.)
- Well done.
- Oh, no...
- He failed, right?
- He failed.
He failed.
- Darn it. Hey!
- Jae Suk, you failed.
- It just ripped.
- How could you...
- How could you let go?
- It ripped!
Why did you...
You should let them
succeed once first.
Then Level 3.5 was counted right?
What a bummer.
I could've done it.
- Just try it.
- It's such a bummer.
From here...
(You'll fall just like this.)
You'll fall just like this.
(Flopped)
Suk Jin, I'll do it for you.
Wait a minute. Wasn't that a couple
on a honeymoon?
- Let me do it for you.
- Wait a minute.
Wasn't that a couple on a honeymoon?
I felt weird too.
- Hey...
- I felt weird too.
Wasn't that like your wedding night?
- Trust me.
- Hey!
- Hold on. It was obviously...
- Darn you.
- like a wedding night.
- Just trust me.
Or we could do this.
You know the grasshopper pose, right?
That will work.
You should put your feet
on his legs.
- You can't use your hands!
- No, not like that.
- Go forward a little.
- Not like that.
- You should grab over here.
- Okay.
- You know the "Titanic" pose.
- That's it.
Lift your hands, Suk Jin. In one...
- Lift him up.
- You need to get your hands off.
There you go.
- Lift him up.
- You need to get your hands off.
There you go.
(He face-planted on the floor.)
How are you going to do this?
I didn't do anything.
(It seems like
Suk Jin can't think clearly.)
Hold on. How do I do this?
- I don't have a strong core.
- Listen.
It's not a matter of your core.
It will work
if Jae Suk holds you right.
- Grab my pockets.
- Okay.
Okay. Grab my pockets.
You got them, right?
- Will it work?
- I got them.
- You feel stable, right?
- I love it.
- Good.
- Go for Level 3. That's Level 4.
- Okay.
- It's too far.
- This far.
- That's a good idea.
I can go that far.
- Here you go.
- "Here you go?"
Why did you say, "Here you go?"
- Are we going?
- "Here you go?"
- "Here you go."
- Why did you say, "Here you go?"
(He says it correctly
and gives it a go!)
Jae Suk, let's go!
For goodness' sake.
Stop pulling.
- I am trying to go down.
- All right.
Jae Suk should pull.
His mouth touched the donut. Eat it.
There you go.
Jae Suk, you need to lower him.
- He got it.
He ate it.
- Jae Suk, you need to lower him.
- Go down.
- He got it.
He ate it.
You succeeded in Level Three.
- Why...
- Let's do it the same way.
- Then I will succeed in it.
- Why did you do it so nicely?
- Let's do it the same way.
I ate it.
I will go for Level Four this time.
Lower him.
Here I go.
- I don't think he will betray him.
- You need to eat it.
- I wouldn't betray him.
- I mean... Hey.
He looks serious.
- Hey.
- He looks serious.
Hold on.
(Showing his underwear)
Hey!
Suk Jin showed his underwear.
I can't believe you.
- Hey.
- I didn't do it on purpose.
I was pulling with all my might.
I couldn't see.
- I couldn't see.
- That's no excuse.
- The entire world will see it.
- When you went down,
- I had to lower my body.
- I saw his eyes.
- Jae Suk's eyes were serious.
- That's right.
- I didn't fool around, did I?
- He did it with seriousness.
- I didn't fool around.
- I will grab this part.
- Don't do that.
- It would be better.
- It would be nice.
- It would be much better.
- This is nice.
All right.
- A bit lower.
- I got you. A bit lower?
A bit lower.
- He ate it.
- See?
- Did he eat it?
- I guess he ate it.
Success.
Did he succeed in Level Four?
I ate it as I went down.
- Right?
- I see.
You have my acknowledgment.
Someone help me.
I need to place first this time.
- I will help you.
- Okay.
- I won't fool around.
- Really?
- Se Chan, it's your turn.
- I will help you.
- I ate it as I went down.
- Level 3.5.
- I ate a lot.
- I will help you.
Se Chan, do it the other way
so that you face the camera.
There you go.
There you go. That's good.
I think you stink.
I am sorry.
- My goodness.
- I am sorry.
- Hey.
Did Mr. Sour strike?
I am sorry.
Hey.
(He smelled grandma's meju
even before Chuseok.)
Did you put something on your feet?
Hang in there.
- That's teamwork.
- Okay. I will help you.
Se Chan, you have an advantage
since you have a protruding mouth.
- He ate it.
- Yes.
I will give you the final rankings.
- First place, Suk Jin.
- Yes.
Second place, Haha.
Third place, Se Chan.
Fourth place, Jae Suk.
Fifth place, Jong Kook.
Sixth place, So Min.
- Seventh place, Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
I give hope to people in their 50s.
Since I have six stickers,
I might put everyone's name.
(He begins to put
the roulette stickers.)
Okay. I will do it like that.
I can accept that.
You should leave me out.
Why would I leave you out?
- Won't you leave me out?
- Aren't we on the same boat?
Are you going to write my name?
Then I will write your name
on all stickers.
- Then I will write your name too.
- Go ahead.
- It will be each other's loss.
- You are right.
- Seriously.
- Leave me out.
- Who wrote my name?
I wrote everyone's name
except for mine.
- I can accept one sticker.
- In any case...
Yes.
- Let's distribute them evenly...
- You wrote my name.
so that the outcome will be random.
Stop writing my name.
- You wrote my name.
- Should I keep writing your name?
- Write my name.
- Should I do that?
- I will write your name.
I will write Ji Suk Jin
on every slot.
I will write Yoo Jae Suk
- Okay.
- Okay. Write my name.
I will write your name
on every slot.
Seriously.
Write my name.
- Did you write my name?
- On every slot.
- I wrote it on every slot.
- Fine. Okay.
I will write your name
on my future stickers too.
- Same here. Suit yourself.
- Okay.
Good.
If you write my name,
I will write your name.
Did you write my name?
You wrote my name?
Okay.
I wrote Kim Jong Kook on two slots.
- I will explain the last mission.
- Okay.
In childhood, have you played
a game called Kkomkkomi?
- What?
- Kkomkkomi?
- Doesn't it involve hiding?
- Yes.
This mission is Kkomkkomi,
a childhood game...
which is a mix of tag
and hide-and-seek.
- I see.
- I know what it is.
- I played Dabanggu.
- It involves hiding.
- I played Dabanggu too.
- I played Dabanggu.
- You go, "Kkomkkomi."
- It's different in each region.
- It's my first time hearing it.
- Kkomkkomi?
While the tagger
goes and touches a certain point,
other members will hide
with bells attached to their shoes.
When the tagger comes back
to the starting point...
and yells, "Kkomkkomi, kkomkkomi,
Gangnam's swallow is here,"
the search begins.
You are out if you get tagged.
If you succeed in touching the flag
without getting tagged...
and yell, "Kkomkkomi,"
- you will receive points.
- That's right.
You will receive three points,
which is the highest point.
Those who didn't get tagged
in the set time...
will get zero points.
Those who got tagged out
will receive negative points...
- in the order it happened.
- That means...
- we need to yell "Kkomkkomi."
- I know.
We need to win points.
Zero points mean nothing.
You will win points
if you come out and touch the flag.
We need to yell "Kkomkkomi."
You will play three rounds.
The tagger's score will be
the number of missed members...
times minus three.
The order of the scores
will determine the rankings.
Does it go into your nostril?
(They had a preliminary mission
of Playing the Nose Flute.)
Suk Jin is the tagger.
We will set up the cameras.
(Suk Jin becomes the tagger
thanks to his poor lung capacity.)
- Suk Jin, do you start here?
- Do I start here?
Are you ready?
Where can we hide?
The 1st and 2nd floors
of the building can be used.
Where? Here?
- So I start here and...
- Go downstairs and come back.
- People will hide during that time.
Okay.
Come back and say,
"Kkomkkomi. kkomkkomi..."
- Then the game begins.
- Then...
- you can search for the members.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
- This is hard.
- Set, go.
- Where should I go?
- This isn't easy.
- Let's go.
- Set, go.
(Suk Jin runs fast as he can.)
Should I just make myself visible?
Seriously. This isn't easy.
I will touch the flag right away.
- I will make myself visible.
- That would be better.
We just say, "Kkomkkomi."
(So Min hides under a table.)
(Ji Hyo goes inside to be safe.)
He won't think to look here.
Please hide me.
(Suk Jin reaches the point.)
(He works hard
and even adds sound effect.)
(Jae Suk, Jong Kook, and Haha
didn't hide yet.)
This spot is a dead end.
I think I can stay here.
He won't be able to catch me.
(The current location)
This spot is a dead end.
(The tagger appears.)
- Will it begin already?
- He came back very quickly.
Kkomkkomi, kkomkkomi,
Gangnam's swallow is here.
(Now, they will be eliminated
if Suk Jin touches them!)
He came back too quickly.
(Now, they will be eliminated
if Suk Jin touches them!)
(He charges toward Jong Kook
without fear!)
He came back too quickly.
(At that moment)
(Peek-a-boo)
Do we just yell "Kkomkkomi?"
Kkomkkomi!
(Se Chan yelled "Kkomkkomi!")
For goodness' sake.
(Now is my chance.)
- Kkomkkomi!
- For goodness' sake.
(2 kkomkkomis in a row)
- Kkomkkomi!
All right.
(So Min was hiding nearby.)
(4 people succeeded in
yelling "Kkomkkomi.")
- For goodness' sake.
- Kkomkkomi!
So Min, success.
(Jong Kook had no intention
to hide from the start.)
I touched you.
(Suk Jin's camera)
(After losing 4 people,
he succeeded in touching Jong Kook.)
- He got Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook is out.
Only Ji Hyo remains.
(Only Ji Hyo remains.)
This isn't easy.
- It's hard.
- From different directions...
The tagger is lonely in this game.
- The tagger is the loneliest.
- That's why...
I don't want to be a tagger.
It makes me sad.
It's the role So Min hates the most.
- Seriously.
- So Min, stop moving.
- Why?
- I hear the bell.
(Teasing him with the bells)
It's confusing.
He won't think
to search the vicinities.
(Ji Hyo is in the building.)
Now!
(Turning around)
Where is she?
- She isn't here.
- The tagger is lonely in this game.
Where is she?
- Time's up.
- Zero points.
You failed to find Ji Hyo.
Suk Jin, you caught one member.
- Minus 15.
- Your score is minus 15.
The tagger is at a disadvantage.
- Seriously.
- I won't place last.
I will place last.
- Kkomkkomi!
- Where were you?
I was over there.
- You can't do it. Time's up.
- Time's up?
- Time's up, Ji Hyo.
- Really?
This time, the tagger will be
Jong Kook...
since he was the only member
who got caught.
- Jong Kook?
- My goodness.
- It will be difficult.
- This is bad.
- It won't be easy.
- Jong Kook.
- What should I do?
- It won't be easy.
Jong Kook is a bit...
- I should go inside.
I have no other choice.
Jong Kook is too scary.
What should I do?
- I will go easy on you.
- It's closer than you think.
The flag is closer than you think.
You can reach it in no time.
If you are ready,
let's begin right away.
- Shall we begin?
- We should go inside.
Take your time.
Set, go.
(Round 2 begins.)
It won't be easy
since Jong Kook is the tagger.
(He sets off
as if he is warming up.)
(Ji Hyo and Haha
decide to wait inside the building.)
(Suk Jin and Se Chan head
toward the staff members.)
This way.
Come here.
Move a bit to the back.
I need one person.
Okay. A bit more.
A bit more.
(Suk Jin makes a wall
of staff members.)
(Se Chan chooses the table
next to the staff members.)
(The tension is thick
compared to the last round.)
- Where should I hide? This is bad.
- Where should I go?
Jae Suk, don't come this way.
Why?
(The cowardly siblings hide
at the same spot.)
He will definitely come here.
(He reaches the halfway point.)
Kkomkkomi, kkomkkomi,
Gangnam's swallow...
As soon as he enters,
we need to run.
I should hide here.
- Please help me.
- Okay.
When Jong Kook comes,
I will go and yell "Kkomkkomi."
He wouldn't think to look here.
How would he think to look here?
It would be unimaginable.
(Will they avoid Jong Kook's radar
as they wish?)
(Jong Kook comes back
in a relaxed way.)
(Scanning)
Kkomkkomi, kkomkkomi,
Gangnam's swallow is here.
(The arrival of Gangnam's swallow
scares them badly.)
My goodness.
(The arrival of Gangnam's swallow
scares them badly.)
(Glancing over)
(Jong Kook's camera)
(Screaming)
(It only took 5 seconds.)
How did you find me?
- I saw you.
- Suk Jin is out.
How did you find me?
I saw you right away.
(Thank goodness.)
(He spots
the suspicious blue outfit.)
Who was that?
(Startled)
Se Chan is out.
I could see your back.
- We can't outrun Jong Kook,
- I could see it.
so we resort to tricks.
Jong Kook is coming.
(Jae Suk and So Min's hiding place)
The production crew.
(What should we do?)
Over there.
if they are inside...
(Jong Kook heads over
to So Min and Jae Suk!)
You might succeed
if you make a run for it now.
(His eyes widen more
and his mouth protrudes more.)
You might succeed
if you make a run for it now.
(Did he spot them?)
Come now.
(Screaming)
(Jae Suk gets taken out
by himself.)
My goodness.
(Haha runs upon hearing
Jae Suk's scream.)
Kkomkkomi.
(Haha yelled "Kkomkkomi.")
- Okay. Yes!
- What? Are you out?
For goodness' sake.
We get too scared
to contend against him.
- For goodness' sake.
- Did he catch all of you guys?
Yes.
No way.
So Min and Ji Hyo remain.
Too bad.
(The survivors look
for the right time to run out.)
(Jong Kook heads toward Ji Hyo.)
(Did he leave?)
(He left!)
- He hasn't left yet!
- Hey.
(Chiming)
(Detective Jong Kook
was looking in all directions.)
- Why did you come out?
- I thought he left.
The cameraman gave me a sign...
- that he left.
- I knew one member was there.
- Gosh, So Min.
- Too bad.
How is Ji Hyo so good at hiding?
Why is he over there?
Time's up.
Ji Hyo, please come on out.
- Where is she?
- She is so good at hiding.
(Jong Kook caught four members.)
- For goodness' sake.
- Good.
Is it over?
I think she is coming from there.
Congratulations. Hurry over here.
(Ji Hyo succeeded in hiding
2 times in a row.)
Suk Jin was the tagger before,
so this round's tagger will be...
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Thank goodness.
- Thank goodness.
- Okay.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Ready. Set, go.
Set, go.
(Round 3 begins.)
(As soon as Jae Suk leaves,)
(Se Chan takes off his top.)
(He uses camouflage
to look like a staff member.)
(He hides in a lousy way again.)
I will win points in this round.
(Laughing)
Kkomkkomi,
kkomkkomi,
Gangnam's swallow is here.
(They face each other.)
Jong Kook, I see...
- that you want to get eliminated.
- I will win points.
(While Jae Suk's eyes are
on Jong Kook)
(Laughing)
Kkomkkomi.
(Se Chan yelled "Kkomkkomi.")
- Suk Jin.
- Touch.
(Suk Jin ran out
at the wrong time.)
(He ran as fast as he could,
but he didn't stand a chance.)
(Touch!)
I thought someone would be here.
(Sad)
You changed.
(Only Se Chan succeeded
in yelling "Kkomkkomi!")
- He is fast.
Kkomkkomi.
It's better to get him
out of the picture.
(Jong Kook succeeded
in yelling "Kkomkkomi.")
All right.
Kkomkkomi.
Now is your chance.
- Come. Hurry up.
- Now is your chance.
- Kkomkkomi.
I touched you first.
- I did it first, right?
- Kkomkkomi.
- I touched you first.
- You didn't touch the flag.
- I did!
- She didn't touch the flag.
- So Min didn't do it.
- They are out.
- Was I supposed to touch it?
- She didn't touch the flag.
- Both of them are out.
I touched the flag first.
- So Min is out.
- Out.
Didn't So Min touch the flag?
- No.
- It's too bad.
Was I supposed to touch it?
- I will give you the results.
- Okay.
First place, Haha.
First place?
Second place, Ji Hyo.
Third place, Se Chan.
Fourth place, So Min.
- Fifth place, Jong Kook.
- I didn't place last.
- I keep placing fifth.
- Sixth place, Jae Suk.
Seventh place, Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
You will fill out the slots
for the last time.
We will spin the roulettes
one at a time.
The moment your name comes out,
you will get a penalty sticker.
You could get seven penalty stickers
if you are unfortunate.
(A total of 7 stickers
will be distributed.)
(There will be 7 express tickets...)
(to the legendary penalties!)
- Whose name should I write?
This is so stressful.
It's okay.
My name is
on the most number of slots.
My name is on many slots.
Whose name is on the fewest slots?
I should write them down.
- Is it Haha?
- My name is on many slots.
Is it Ji Hyo?
Suk Jin, I got chosen last week.
You are right.
Suk Jin wrote down my name
on many slots.
That's not true.
Your name is only on two slots.
- Really?
- Three.
Hey.
- It can't be helped.
- What's wrong with you?
It can't be helped.
You only wrote my name.
I have no other choice.
- For goodness' sake.
- I have no other choice.
On how many slots is my name?
- Haha wrote my name on many slots.
- What?
So Min wrote my name
on so many slots!
I only did it
because you wrote down...
- my name earlier.
- I didn't write down your name.
That's not true.
You wrote down my name.
- So I wrote down your name.
- You wrote it on two slots, right?
I will write your name on two slots.
I will write your name again then.
Haha.
Are you serious?
So Min.
- You just wrote down my name.
- It's a match. He wrote it down.
Haha again.
So Min again.
Haha and So Min are having a match.
- You...
- You wrote my name again.
- I will fill all the slots.
- Are you serious?
- Then I will do the same.
- It's a match.
Haha.
(They fill the slots
with each other's names.)
- Why did you write my name?
- Go.
- You wrote my name.
Hey, So Min.
So Min wrote your name once.
Se Chan doesn't disappoint.
- Look at this.
- Hey.
- I wrote it once.
- He wrote it once.
You wrote my name too.
This is wrong.
- No one else wrote my name.
- Let's begin.
I give up at this point.
Se Chan, spin your roulette first.
- Spin it.
- My name is on too many slots.
- This is...
- Hey.
Most of the slots are for Se Chan.
It will either be Se Chan or So Min.
Let's begin.
If I get picked, it would mean
that I am very unlucky.
- You are too much.
- Here I go.
- Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- One,
- two,
- Please.
three.
- It will be funny...
if Jae Suk gets picked.
- His name is on one slot.
- It will be the worst situation.
- It will be funny.
- You will be the unluckiest man.
It will be the worst situation.
I think it's you.
- It's So Min.
- No.
I think it's you.
- It's So Min.
- No.
- So Min.
(So Min gets picked.)
So Min.
(So Min gets picked
with Se Chan's slots on both sides.)
- Please put one sticker.
- Really?
- All right!
- How many stickers will there be?
There will be seven stickers.
My goodness.
So Min, I put your name
on the right spot.
My slot was right next to it.
(The first penalty sticker
goes to So Min.)
Many penalty stickers
will be distributed today.
Seriously.
A total of seven penalty stickers.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
It will be bad
if he doesn't get chosen.
- Most of them are for Jae Suk.
- Here I go.
(Jae Suk's roulette is covered
in Suk Jin's name.)
He wrote my name on every slot.
Someone might get
two penalty stickers today.
- Please don't let it be me.
- No!
(What will be the result?)
(Suk Jin, Jae Suk,
Haha, Ji Hyo, and Se Chan)
Please don't let it be me.
(Ji Suk Jin)
(Suk Jin gets picked.)
(Of course.)
Congratulations.
Let's go.
- I hope this spot gets picked.
- Okay.
I hope this spot gets picked.
- Suk Jin.
- This spot.
- Please.
- Let's go.
- We should put them all together.
- Right.
(Suk Jin's roulette has
many slots with Jae Suk's name.)
(Suk Jin's Roulette: Suk Jin 12,
Jae Suk 9, Jong Kook 3)
(Haha, Ji Hyo 1, So Min, Se Chan 1)
It sounds funny.
Ji Suk Jin!
(Ji Suk Jin)
- It could've been me.
- It's Ji Suk Jin.
That was so close.
Suk Jin is penetrating his way up.
I think I'll be next.
(He got 2 stickers in an instant.)
He's in the lead.
- Gosh, it could've been you.
- He's taking the lead.
- It's my turn.
- All right.
- It's Haha. That's...
- I know.
Seriously, this is...
Spin the roulette.
He wrote your name a lot.
(Haha's Roulette:
Haha 9, Jae Suk 7, So Min 6)
It doesn't make any sound.
This is so annoying.
(Haha, Jae Suk, and So Min have
similar chances of winning.)
It doesn't make any sound.
Darn it!
(It's Haha.)
(He got himself a sticker.)
- Great.
- It's Haha!
- I can't believe this.
- This is nice.
(Jae Suk and So Min survived.)
Haha.
This is great.
- I know. It's nice.
- Spin it.
(Ji Hyo's Roulette: Ji Hyo 10,
Suk Jin 6, Jae Suk 5)
(Ji Hyo mainly focused
on Suk Jin and Jae Suk.)
- What if I'm picked?
- I'm nervous.
It makes me nervous.
(Ji Hyo's Roulette: Ji Hyo 10,
Suk Jin 6, Jae Suk 5)
- Haha!
- Haha.
(Haha who had his name
on only 2 slots?)
(It slowly moves
to Jae Suk's slot.)
- It's moving.
- Keep moving.
It's Haha.
(But it stopped.)
Haha gets two stickers.
It could've been Jae Suk.
- I know.
- It was so close.
It's Haha! My goodness.
Let's do this.
- Please.
- Jeon So Min!
- We don't know it yet.
- So Min.
- Let's go, So Min.
So Min, please.
(So Min's name is on most slots
of her roulette.)
It has to be you. So Min.
- It's Haha.
- Darn it!
(It's Haha again!)
(He gets picked 3 times in a row.)
This is Haha's day.
Haha, today is your day.
- What if I get Haha's name again?
- Your day.
- This is crazy.
- Why did you provoke me?
It will be amazing
if we get Haha's name again.
- I have Haha's name here.
- This is the last one.
- There is Haha's name.
- On this line.
It all says Haha.
Haha is the star of the day.
- Here I go.
- This is...
- No.
- All right.
(But Haha has only a chance
of one sixth.)
This is so...
(Jong Kook's Roulette:
Jong Kook 12, Suk Jin 8, Haha 5)
He wrote my name a lot.
(Jong Kook and Suk Jin
are most likely to get picked.)
Haha.
(Jong Kook's Roulette:
Jong Kook 12, Suk Jin 8, Haha 5)
(Who will be the last member
to get a penalty sticker?)
Haha.
- It's Haha.
- Darn it!
(Haha)
This is ridiculous!
It's Haha.
(Something unbelievable
just happened.)
(They are all flustered.)
Haha will be going.
- Four stickers.
- My gosh.
We have seven stickers today.
And Haha gets four of them.
- I know.
- Suk Jin gets two.
- You shouldn't have upset me.
- And So Min gets one.
Se Chan and Jae Suk didn't get any.
Jae Suk hasn't gotten any stickers.
I survived!
- Jae Suk has no stickers.
- I can't believe this.
I can't believe I survived.
- It will be Jae Suk next week.
- This is a four-week-long project.
So we have two weeks left.
- I should hang in there.
- What should Haha do?
- This is not bad.
- Two weeks later,
you'll go to get a penalty.
No.
Let's hurry and split up today.
- Good. Let's go.
- We should hurry.
- I have a bad feeling about this.
- This doesn't feel good.
- Let's go home.
- Good work.
- Good work today.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
We might get 20 stickers next week.
(Whatever Penalty Project
Status Board)
(A luxury store is about to be open
on a rainy summer day.)
(Elegance Yoo and Kim)
(A luxury store is about to be open
on a rainy summer day.)
(The store is filled
with expensive items.)
(A clerk who doesn't know much
about luxury goods, Kim Jong Kook)
(A countrified manager, Yoo Jae Suk)
(I'll slash the prices.)
(Hip Jiri)
(Next to it is
a trendy hip hop shop.)
(A shameless owner, Ji Suk Jin)
(A hip hop loser clerk 1,
Yang Se Chan)
(A hip hop loser clerk 2, Haha)
(Those who live and die
for being hip...)
(are plotting something together.)
(Hello.)
We should do that.
My goodness.
(Ji Hyo is at Hip Jiri.)
- This is...
- It's been a long time, Ji Hyo.
- Come here.
- This place is hip.
- We have new products.
- Tell me what you want.
(This is expensive.)
(This is Kanye West style.)
(Amazed)
- I like this one.
- This is crazy.
- One, two, three.
My goodness.
(The clerks'
amazing sales ability...)
(makes her open her purse.)
(And So Min...)
(loses her heart
to cheap fake items.)
(How much is this?)
(I'll make it 300 dollars.)
(The pushovers pay big money
without a shadow of doubt.)
Is it you?
(A lady with a loud voice,
Choi Yeo Jin)
(A lady with eloquence, Ok Ja Yeon)
(The two ladies with loud voices...)
(have Ji Hyo's back.)
(A lady with commanding aura,
Jin Seo Yeon)
(Refund everything.)
The price is ridiculous
for this fabric.
But why do you...
(This is fake.)
I'll make it 100 dollars.
- That's...
- No.
I'll give you five dollars.
Is your friend...
(Is your friend a thug?)
(The tough ladies conquer
the variety show world.)
That's unbelievable.
(Their spirits are...)
(strong.)
(Their bodies are...)
(The war of strong warriors begins.)
(Be Strong For My Way)