(Running Man finally arrived
in Cheorwon last week.)
(But the members were told to make
a choice as soon as they got there.)
I just stop betting
once I make some money over a bet.
I go no matter what.
I never stop.
(Go no matter what!)
(He just got gimbap.)
If I said stop,
I would've gone in there?
(That's how they began
the Go-Stop Race in Cheorwon.)
(A choice for the first activity)
(Jong Kook who values safety
chose Stop.)
(The tiger moths Jae Suk
and Suk Jin chose Go!)
(Go is for the hiking course.)
(The two unlucky guys
actually walked to the observatory.)
(Those who chose Stop
enjoyed the monorail ride.)
(Jong Kook chose Stop again
for the next course.)
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin chose Go
3 times in a row.)
(Those who chose Go went rafting.)
(The two stubborn guys
had to struggle.)
(A choice for lunch!)
(Jong Kook chose Stop
4 times in a row.)
(Jae Suk chose Go
All right.
We got the same results again.
- Four members chose Go.
- Okay.
- And three members chose Stop.
- Seriously?
You should've changed
your choice to Stop.
- For me...
- Seriously, make Go good.
I can't choose Stop with him.
Hey, I bet Stop is
a good thing again.
Seriously, I worked out
my lower body a lot today.
- Me too. I walked up the stairs.
- That's good exercise.
- Should I open Go first?
- You can open it.
Please.
(Will there be a twist for Go?)
You can open it.
Please.
This is so annoying. What's this?
(Meal set: rice, soy sauce,
and laver from Suk Jin's hometown)
(Laver, rice, and soy sauce)
- This is ridiculous.
- Isn't this a good thing?
- Why do you not change?
- It's just laver and soy sauce?
- This is a variety show.
- What's with her?
There should be a twist
in a variety show.
- I'll open the other one.
- Can I make a guess?
- I bet this is beef.
- Let me open it.
(Then what is Stop for?)
- My gosh.
- Darn it.
What's going on?
(It's a pork belly party.)
What's happening to me?
Why did you not change?
Why won't you change?
- My gosh. Why did you do this?
- Why did you not change?
- Why...
- How would we change our choice?
- This is about our pride.
- Seriously, you're...
Let's take this to the end.
- I'm serious.
- Hey.
- You...
- You'll see.
- I'll choose Go again.
- Let's do this until next week.
- I'll choose Go until the end.
- Jae Suk.
I told you before.
Stop being so stubborn.
- Just change your choice once.
- Will you let it go?
Why do you keep choosing Go?
- You should change your choice.
- All right.
We have delicious rice behind you.
And we have some meat.
Please enjoy it.
- That sounds great.
- This is pork belly.
- I wish we had ramyeon.
- This is great.
I'll grill it.
Let's grill it.
It looks really delicious.
I can't believe this.
(Team Go eats their rice
with soy sauce.)
I'm sick of eating this.
Isn't this soy sauce for raw fish?
This tastes like sushi.
It tastes like sushi, doesn't it?
- Why did you not change at all?
- Why did you not change?
It would've been fun
if she had changed it here.
Hyung In, you're really stubborn.
You never change it.
Do you have any sesame oil?
This would taste really good
with pork belly.
Of course.
Ji Hyo, you really
like black pepper.
- What?
- Ji Hyo loves black pepper.
- She keeps peppering the meat.
- Isn't this nice?
I'm sorry,
but I can make a wrap with the meat.
This is big enough to make a wrap.
I'm so sorry.
(Feeling bitter)
(He tries the pork belly sushi.)
This is really good.
(Amazed)
This is so tasty.
- Jong Kook, the meat is so good.
- I know.
Can't you at least give us
some sesame oil?
This is really long.
- I'm starving, so it tastes good.
- My gosh.
It actually tastes good because
we had fun in the water earlier.
This looks really good.
Hunger is the best sauce.
He's saying silly things again.
- He's out of his mind today.
- He's scaring me.
- He's...
- How many alter egos does he have?
He shows his true color
when he forgets about the cameras.
But he comes to his senses
when he sees the cameras.
Can you give us
some vegetables for a wrap?
- No, I can't.
- What about a pepper?
I can't.
I think this is really pathetic.
- He keeps asking for things.
- I know.
Why did you put the laver
all the way over there?
- Suk Jin.
- What's with him?
How many alter egos do you have?
- Which ego was that?
- He has three people inside him.
- My 6th ego.
- That was your 6th ego?
- I'll give meat to only one of you.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- All right.
- Rock-paper-scissors. Yes.
- I won.
- Thank you.
I'll give it to the one who loses.
It's me.
- No, the last one to lose.
- It's me.
- I'm the one who lost.
- The last one to lose.
I'll give it to you.
Why would you give it to a loser?
- Are you sure you lost?
- Yes.
(The pork belly goes to Haha.)
Try this.
Haha, you can cut it in half.
- Share it with us.
- You can share it.
- You can cut it.
- Share it with us.
- Cut it...
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Forget about rock-paper-scissors.
- Only one person.
- Just cut it in half.
- Just share it with me.
- You can cut it in half.
- They want to share it.
What's with him? Just cut it.
Let's just go and eat it.
Okay. Let's eat.
- Forget about the rules.
- I don't know. I'll just eat it.
We're here on a trip.
- Suk Jin, you can't do that.
- No, you can't.
Don't be like that.
Why would you stop me?
You can't do that.
(Bowing)
- Thank you.
- I'll try it.
- Enjoy it.
(Smacking his lips)
This is really good.
Gosh, the garlic leaves are so good.
- Did you do it?
- Did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes.
- I really loved it.
- It's time for your last choice.
- Gosh, this is really...
I've already made up my mind.
- What?
- Go.
She will change at least once.
- This choice is about going home.
- You were right about that.
(If they make the right choice here,
they can go home right away.)
- Really?
- We can go home right away.
You should make a choice
only on your gut feeling.
Should I choose Stop?
- Those who get to go home...
- Gosh, this is really...
will get in
your manager's car here...
- and go home right away.
- Are you serious?
My goodness.
It depends on how you put it.
And the rest of you will go
to the flower garden near here.
You will enjoy
your last course there.
- I saw it earlier.
- That's the worst.
- I want to go there.
- I've had enough.
- I don't want to see anything.
- I know it's beautiful, but...
Honestly, I want to go there.
But would it say "Go home?"
- We should go now.
- Or...
- is it "Go to the flower garden?"
- Jae Suk.
Shall we choose Stop this time?
- Suk Jin.
- By the way,
- is it settled already?
- Yes.
- Is it "Go home?"
- This one is...
- quite tricky.
- They already have the board.
I really don't know
what she's up to.
- This is psychological warfare.
- I know.
- She keeps...
- Should I change my choice here?
- She never changed her choice.
- No, she might change.
- She's been on a single path.
- There have been three Stops.
- Will there be another Stop?
- But...
if she wanted a twist,
she would go on a single path.
- I bet Go is a bad thing.
- Hyung In is...
- She's...
- She's quite stubborn.
She's a lunatic.
She wasn't like that before.
She suddenly changed.
What's scary about Hyung In is
that she is...
a kind lunatic.
- She's a KW.
- A KW.
She's a KW.
A kind weirdo is the scariest one.
- A KW.
- That's the worst.
A kind weirdo is the scariest one.
It says I should choose Stop.
I tried it three times.
I tried it three times,
and it said I should choose Stop.
- Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk, you and Suk Jin...
Jae Suk, I tried it three times,
and it said I should choose Stop.
I'll...
- I'll just...
- Go?
Come out.
- Did you choose?
- Go.
(He chooses Go again.)
I can't follow him.
- Go or Stop?
- He's so unlucky.
Stop.
- But Jae Suk didn't...
- Go or Stop?
get the penalty last time.
He's been quite lucky recently.
- Is there a hint?
- We need to get lucky this time.
- This is it.
- To be honest,
this is the only one
we need to make the right choice on.
- Today, I chose...
- Nothing else matters.
Stop every time.
I chose Stop all day.
- Will you change it to Go?
- Hey, that's the two tiger moths.
- The two tiger moths.
- I can't choose Go.
(So Min chose Stop all day,
but she changed her choice to Go.)
I should change it
at the last minute.
- I chose Stop all day.
- If you and Jae Suk choose Go,
I will choose Stop!
- I will choose Stop!
- Gosh, this isn't going to be good.
- Oh, dear.
- Gosh, it's going to be worse.
- Once you choose Go...
- No.
- You should stick to Go.
- You two...
What should I do to go home?
Should I choose Stop?
Is Go for going home?
- Can I choose again?
- If you're rational about it,
Go is for going home.
Think of it that way.
- Ji Hyo, can you go first?
- Can I do it again?
I also chose Stop all day.
- Will you choose Go?
- I'll choose Go.
- Then it must be Go.
- Of course.
- I choose Go.
- Stop means you should stop.
- I'm...
- Stop is not going.
It wasn't my turn,
so I'll do it again.
- You already chose Stop.
- You chose.
What are you talking about?
Then I'll choose Go.
I think I should choose Stop.
- No, Jae Suk.
- Next week...
I don't think so either.
Hyung In asked
why we wouldn't change our choices.
That's why I changed mine.
You just said
you didn't make your choice.
Can I try it again?
Just choose Stop.
Okay. I think we should
choose Stop for everything.
I think that's
what Hyung In intended.
Make the right choice.
All...
- All Stop.
- Is it Stop?
Because she has no reason...
- to change at the last minute.
- I just chose Go...
- because that was my first choice.
- So there's no twist?
- Should I stick with my choice?
- Yes.
Jong Kook will choose Stop.
- Jong Kook will go on one path.
- I should go.
If I change my choice here,
I will be more upset.
- Right. Choose Stop.
- I'll stick with my choice.
- I'll just...
- I should've...
Okay. I'll choose Stop.
I think Stop is a good thing.
It was Stop all day,
so I'm confused.
It was Stop all day long.
- This is crazy.
- If I can go again, I choose Stop.
- Let's do this!
- Stop!
- I think Stop is a good thing.
- Good.
- Let's go. We'll see.
- All right.
Those who chose Go are Jae Suk,
- Ji Hyo, and So Min.
- Yes.
So this is like
Jae Suk versus Suk Jin.
- Gosh, this is so thrilling.
- I'm the only one who chose Go...
the whole time.
I changed my choice.
- I changed it too.
- I changed.
- Please.
- Give us the board.
Go is...
(Go has been a thorny path today.)
(What's the last choice
for going home?)
(Go for a shoot!)
Those who chose Go will do a shoot.
(Jae Suk will do
an additional shoot.)
Those who chose Go will do a shoot.
(We can go home now!)
There was no twist!
- It was Stop to the end.
- Unbelievable.
- I can't believe this.
- I knew it.
- The kind weirdo.
- You're really something.
- Go for a shoot.
- You can "stop" the shoot here.
- We can "stop" the shoot here.
- Yes.
- It didn't mean "to go home."
- See?
I chose the opposite
of So Min's choice.
She always gets unlucky
at the end of the show.
- Yoo Jae Suk, go
- Go
- This is the worst.
- Jae Suk is so unlucky.
The three of you will
go to the flower field...
- with many good photo spots.
- They'll love it.
- Enjoy the final tour course.
- That sounds great.
- Take good photos there.
- Enjoy yourselves.
- Let's go.
- He's bad at taking photos.
- Jae Suk should go there.
- I'm curious about something.
- It's so beautiful here.
- He'll get much air time as always.
- Of course.
Why didn't you create a twist?
- Is this okay? Why did you do that?
- I mean...
- Hyung In, you're scary.
- There was no twist, not even once.
- Why did you do that?
- Is she simply stubborn?
- We'll go crazy if we do it again.
- Let's just go. It's no big deal.
- I mean, why...
- We'll totally go crazy.
Why didn't you create a twist?
The four of you can go home now.
- Let's get going. We'll be off.
- Thank you.
- Have fun, guys.
- See you later.
- We'll get going.
- We'll leave so you can have fun.
- See you later.
- Let's go.
- I'll get going.
- Bye, guys.
- See you later.
- Bye, So Min.
- Hyung In, you're so scary.
You could've been left alone.
- Let's all go together.
- This never happened before.
I mean,
why would she stick to one path?
Oh, my. It's beautiful.
It's pretty, but it would've been
better if I had gone home.
- My, it's so pretty.
- Look at that.
Oh, my. I really like purple.
How pretty. Hey, look at this.
(Ji Hyo and So Min feel better
thanks to the flowers.)
We must take photos of this.
- Nice. It really is pretty.
- It's pretty, right?
Aren't you glad we came here?
- What?
- What I'm saying is...
- Going home would've been better.
- that at least...
- we get to enjoy this scenery.
- Where should we sit?
(They get in a vehicle
for the flower field tour.)
- Darn it.
- Give it to me.
Jae Suk,
please try to enjoy yourself.
- But I'm not in a good mood.
- We...
- I'm excited. It's so beautiful.
- I'm feeling good.
I'm half excited and half upset.
- This scenery...
- I mean, don't you think...
- This is nice, but...
- they should've changed it?
Normally, people make a twist.
You were so stubborn too.
- Right. Jae Suk was stubborn too.
- So Min, I just keep going.
And I don't like to stop.
I always go for it.
My, look at that.
It's pretty.
I want to go home,
but I'm enjoying this at the same time.
We would be happier
if we were on our way home.
I'll take close-up photos of them.
- How come they're all purple?
- Right? They're all purple.
They planted purple flowers
intentionally.
- It's beautiful.
- That hut will make a good photo.
(Exclaiming)
- It's pretty.
- Jae Suk, smile a little.
- Well, I'm doing my best.
- Jae Suk.
Go faster!
We're moving fast enough.
- Jae Suk, this is fun, right?
- Yes, I'm having a great time.
- Of course.
- It's fun because I'm with you two.
Let's stop here to look around
for a while.
- Can we take some photos here?
- Sure.
I don't want to take photos at all.
Jae Suk,
let's take a photo together.
Can I stay here?
(He refuses to get off.)
Jae Suk, come on.
- But...
- Jae Suk, come and have a look.
Gosh. Seriously.
- Shall I take a photo of you?
- You know how it feels...
- when you want to stop...
- You're so pretty.
visiting tourist spots
on a school trip, right?
- Shall I take a photo of you?
- Ji Hyo, take a photo of me.
Right. It really is pretty.
(Zoned-out Crazy Sisters are
busy taking photos.)
It's so beautiful.
There are many beautiful spots
in Cheorwon.
Jae Suk, you're good
at taking photos, right?
- Of course.
- Can you take a photo of us?
I'll do that.
Are we in the frame?
You guys look gorgeous.
Great. This is amazing.
(Zoned-out Crazy Sisters are
cheerful while working overtime.)
- Oh, my. It's great.
- We should save this memory.
Catch me if you can!
(Screaming)
- Oh, boy.
- Hey, let's get going.
- Let's leave before she gets back.
- Let's go.
- Hurry up and get in.
Catch me if you can!
- Let's go.
- Where are you going?
- We don't have time for that.
Where are you going?
(So Min got too excited abruptly
because of the flowers.)
Wait for me.
I want to take a selfie
with the purple flowers.
- I don't want to take photos.
- I prefer the purple ones.
(A week later)
- Oh, that's true.
- Hey, hi.
- Hello.
- You're here.
- Jae Suk, you're here.
- Hello.
- Hi. I got here earlier than you.
- Stop lying. You didn't.
- Hello. Excuse me.
- I was in that small room.
- Why?
I was told
that I needed to fix my hair...
My gosh. You started
carrying this around again?
- Hey.
- That suits you.
My gosh. Look at that.
Jong Kook, that's too big.
Is that a trophy or something?
- Exactly.
- He drinks from a trophy?
- Is that a trophy?
- What brand is it from?
I don't know.
- Do you still use that? It's huge.
- Oh, I found it.
So Min, what's with your hair?
- I got a new haircut.
- You have bangs now.
Yes. Everyone reacted the same way.
- How did everyone react?
- They didn't seem surprised.
They seemed taken aback.
I pretended I didn't know.
I heard that we'd be
having guests today.
- Really?
- I don't think so.
- NewJeans.
Hey, you... Oh, I get it.
- You see, So Min...
- Look at her hair.
- Is that why you got that haircut?
- No.
- I had bangs when I was 20.
- NewJeans.
- The trend is back after ten years.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- So I tried it once again.
- Keeping up with the trend...
- Did you want to look funny too?
- I don't like it so much.
- Tell me honestly.
- Why? I think she looks pretty.
Just like how comedians
wear bald wigs.
To be honest...
- NewJeans?
- Honestly... No.
- When Haha shaved his head,
- Yes.
- he looked so funny.
- Right.
- That's why I tried this style.
- Right?
- You should shave the front.
- You should shave your head too.
- You should've shaved this area.
- Or all except that area.
I don't think she did it
just to look pretty.
- Right.
- She wanted to look funny too.
Jong Kook, let's talk later.
(So Min's new haircut only gave
the others a reason to tease her.)
Before we begin the race officially,
- we'll give you ten diamonds each.
- What's going on?
- We get diamonds?
- Will NewJeans be here?
- No. He was talking about So Min.
- We get diamonds today. No.
- Maybe NewJeans will be here...
- Everyone got it.
You won't keep those diamonds.
Choose 2 members
and give them 5 diamonds each.
- Why should I?
- Directly?
- No, you will...
- Why should I give these away?
Well, that's the rule.
Oh, I see.
Don't be taken aback.
- You'll compete individually.
- Yes.
Obviously, the more diamonds,
the better.
The number of diamonds you have
will be revealed at the end.
So don't tell the others
how many diamonds you have.
Now, you will take turns
going to another room...
and put your diamonds in the baskets
of the members you choose.
(They'll move to the next room
to give away their diamonds.)
So we'll use diamonds
instead of potatoes today.
Shouldn't we tell each other?
Then I'll give mine to NewJeans.
You can discuss it before we begin.
- To our today's guest, NewJeans.
- Really?
- Gosh. That's not my intention.
- So Min, this is your chance.
- But...
- Do whatever you want.
- Whatever you want.
- Since she made me laugh,
I'll give mine to her too.
- I'll choose So Min and NewJeans.
- I'll give mine to So Min.
- I'll give mine to So Min too.
- You're making me uncomfortable.
Treat me as you always do!
This makes me uncomfortable.
Who wants to go first?
- I want to see...
- Shall I go first?
- Go ahead.
- Yes. Okay.
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
- Let's give each other some.
- My protruding mouth brother. Okay.
As the protruding mouth brothers,
let's give some to each other.
- Okay. I'll give you some.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- And Yeosu.
- Se Chan.
- Oh, right.
- Yes?
Se Chan, you have nothing in common
with Suk Jin, right?
Right. Not a thing.
Already?
(Se Chan enters the other room.)
Hello.
I'll give five of them
to my protruding mouth brother.
(He'll give five diamonds
to Jae Suk as he promised.)
And...
(Who did he give
the rest of the five diamonds to?)
(Haha said
he'd give his diamonds to So Min.)
Five for each, right?
I can't keep any, right?
I'll give half to So Min as I said.
So Min gave us a good laugh
with her new haircut.
So I'll give mine to So Min.
She's a valuable member.
And...
I'll give five diamonds
to NewJeans, So Min.
(Ji Hyo chose So Min as well.)
- I've already made my decision.
- Let me think.
- I thought about it a lot.
- So Min must've received a lot.
- I just want to give them some.
- Can I give away just one?
(What will the diamonds be
used for?)
(Today's set will be revealed now.)
(Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Suk Jin,
Ji Hyo, Haha, Se Chan, So Min)
(There are seven separate rooms.)
I'm hungry.
Something smells delicious.
- It's food, right? Am I wrong?
- Yes.
What is this?
I think we are playing a quiz game.
Gosh. I'm done for.
They did a great job.
What? Are we playing a quiz game?
Darn it.
I haven't studied for a while.
It's a quiz game.
What kind of quiz game?
I'm in trouble. It's a quiz game.
Se Chan, it must be a quiz game.
- So Min, I'm done for. Help me.
- Okay.
It looks like a quiz game.
It's a quiz game.
Give us a question.
Until further instructions,
- you're not allowed to come out.
- Of course.
Shortly,
you will receive the diamonds...
- that you obtained.
- Yes.
Count the diamonds quietly...
so that the others can't hear you.
- Got it.
- Okay.
Oh, you'll send them to my phone?
(Oh, you'll send them to my phone?)
I wonder how many I received.
(Although he has poor hearing...)
I shouldn't let the others know.
(Almost Deaf Ji has
a wild imagination.)
What? Oh, I thought you'd text me
to tell me the number.
There must be some in the case.
It's quite heavy.
(He received the jewelry briefcase
with excitement.)
Wait.
Oh, my. I received a briefcase.
Oh, my. I received mine.
- Great.
- This is...
I don't think I received many.
Shall I open it?
(They will check the number
of diamonds they obtained.)
- I'm sure I have no diamonds.
- Let's check.
(They will check the number
of diamonds they obtained.)
Let's open it.
(Ms. Jeon, the guest,
who seemed popular)
(Surprised)
Wow, that's a lot.
This is great.
I received a lot.
- This is like a festival!
- Thank you.
Not bad.
- Guys!
- Yes?
Thank you!
- Don't mention it.
- No problem, So Min.
- I love you!
- So Min, good luck.
- I hope you win today.
- You made the opening funny.
Seok Sam, I'm sorry!
Guys, are you serious?
- Suk Jin.
- I'm sorry.
- You should thank me, Suk Jin.
- I'm sorry, Seok Sam.
- I don't believe you.
- Ji Hyo.
I wanted to give you some, but
I couldn't find a reason to do so.
Today's race is
Mr. Run, How's the Food Over There?
- Okay.
- "Narco-Saints?"
- "How's the Food Over There?"
- We prepared...
- all kinds of delicacies for you.
- Wow.
(Various delicacies are prepared
for the members.)
In each round,
you'll be given one question.
If all of you get it right,
all of you get to eat food.
- Right? I knew it.
- Let's eat together!
This reminds me of "Narco-Saints."
- It's like "Narco-Saints."
- Should all of us...
- get the right answer?
- Yes, all of you.
- That's too hard.
- To pull it off,
the diamonds you have will play
an important role.
Yes.
Before the quiz starts,
you'll turn in some diamonds
without letting the others know.
If the total is more than seven,
you'll be given an easy question.
If it's between 4 and 6,
the difficulty level will be normal.
If it's three or fewer,
you'll be given a hard question.
- Let's all enjoy delicious food!
- Let's do this!
- Let's turn in one diamond each.
- Let's eat some food!
- If you have a lot, submit some.
- Let's turn in one diamond each.
Suk Jin,
turn some in no matter what.
Of course, I will. Trust me.
We get to eat food
only when all of us get it right.
- All of us should get it right.
- We always lied.
But let's gather diamonds this time
and show them what we can do!
We've been doing this together
for 13 years!
Let's create a heartwarming scene
since it's been 13 years.
Be quiet!
(Se Chan stops him.)
Who is being so loud?
Guys, did you have breakfast?
Hey, Ms. Jeon.
- Did you have breakfast?
- Have you eaten?
- Listen, everyone.
(But...)
But one of you is a spy.
- Oh, gosh.
- What?
That's not fair.
The spy's goal is
to make it to the top three...
with the most diamonds
without getting caught.
- Gosh.
- Come on.
The citizens will win
if they arrest the spy.
The citizen with the most diamonds
will receive a prize,
and the spy will receive a penalty.
The citizens will lose
if they fail to arrest the spy.
All of them except for the citizen
with the most diamonds...
will receive a penalty.
- All of the citizens?
- We should catch the spy.
- Yes, we should catch the spy.
- The more diamonds you have,
- It's Se Chan.
- the better chance you have of winning.
- The spy...
- Se Chan must be the spy.
- Why me?
- Hey.
Se Chan,
you're unusually quiet today.
I'm not the spy.
- You were suspicious.
- You see, if one of us is a spy,
we won't be able to gather
seven diamonds.
That's right.
But we can get the right answer.
But won't the spy give
a wrong answer intentionally?
(The spy could give a wrong answer
to sabotage the citizens.)
Before we begin the first round,
we'll reveal the dish.
- What is it?
- Please come out and check it.
Oh, gosh.
- I should go out?
- The menu could motivate us.
- Wow. It must be Korean beef.
- It'll be cooked here.
- I really want to eat it.
- You're nervous, right?
- Hello. We should eat this.
- Look at this.
Is it toma... T-bone...
- It's T-bone steak.
- Gosh. It looks crazy good.
- It looks so good.
- It looks good.
The dish for the first round is
T-bone steak.
Right? I could smell something good
when I entered.
It looks amazing.
- Can hear the sizzling sound?
- Sure.
- We should hear it.
- Let's listen to the sound.
(The chef starts grilling the meat
in front of their eyes.)
Aren't you going to sprinkle
salt and pepper?
I seasoned the meat in advance.
- She seasoned the meat.
- Let's eat it.
(Will all the members succeed
and taste the meat?)
My, it looks so delicious, right?
It looks so juicy.
Did you get a new haircut
to celebrate being chosen as a spy?
- No.
- You're standing like a spy.
- Why is your face red?
- No... What?
Why is your face red?
Wait. Jae Suk was the only one
who was late.
- He's not wearing a cap.
- He's dancing.
He's not wearing a cap
because he's the spy.
- He's the spy.
- That's why he's not wearing a cap.
He's not wearing a cap.
He had his hair done.
What are they doing?
The improv comedy couple.
- The comedy duo,
- Right.
- Yoo Jae Suk and Han Min Kwan!
- She got a new haircut...
(Yoo Jae Suk and Han Min Kwan's
Gala)
(The senior and junior comedians'
joint performance)
So Min has been making
a lot of effort.
- Now,
- Hey, you seem...
- so enthusiastic today.
- please go back to your rooms...
- and close the doors.
- Okay.
- I'm not the spy. Trust me.
- She got a new haircut.
- It's not me today.
- I don't think this is necessary.
I'm so excited to have been chosen
as a spy after a long time.
I'm exhilarated.
I'll do my best.
What is he doing?
It looks so good.
Hey, hurry up.
- Spy.
- Gosh, it looks so good.
Let's eat it!
- It looks so good.
- We can't miss it.
Let's do this! We've got this!
To decide the difficulty level
of the question,
- we'll collect diamonds first.
- Okay.
We should all turn in a diamond.
- Let's all turn in a diamond.
- Turn in as many diamonds...
as you want
through the hole next to the door.
- Let's all turn in a diamond.
- Just as I said,
if you gather seven or more,
you'll get an easy question.
- A normal one for between 4 and 6.
- Okay.
A hard one for three or fewer.
- I'll turn in a diamond.
- Right. Let's eat the food!
If all the members give
the correct answer,
all of you will get to eat the food.
And three members
randomly chosen by the staff...
- will receive ten diamonds.
- What?
- Ten diamonds?
- But if any of you fails,
- We can get more diamonds?
only two members
that the spy chooses can eat.
The rest 5 members will lose
1 diamond,
and those diamonds will be given
to the spy.
Please turn in diamonds now.
- Through the hole.
- Guys, I'll turn it in.
- Okay.
- Come on. Let's all turn it in.
Let's all turn in just one.
- Let's all turn in just one.
- Then we can gather seven.
I'm turning it in right now.
There's 1 spy, and the others will
turn in at least 1 diamond.
I'll turn in two diamonds.
One of us won't turn in any.
It will be the spy.
I'll turn in two diamonds. Yes.
(So Min decided to turn in 2
so that they can gather 7 diamonds.)
(So Min who has many diamonds
turned in two diamonds.)
- Let's all turn in one diamond.
- I just turned it in.
I turned it in too.
I'll turn in just one diamond.
Let's all turn in one diamond.
- Turn in at least 1 diamond.
- Just 1 diamond.
You can turn in one diamond.
I'm done.
(They seem to have agreed
to join forces to eat the food.)
We've got this!
Let's have the steak together.
I really want to eat the steak.
The sizzling sound is amazing.
This is driving me crazy.
The total number of diamonds
you turned in is...
(The total number of diamonds
you turned in is...)
two.
- What?
- My gosh.
- Really?
- The difficulty level is hard.
- That's unbelievable.
- My gosh.
- No one else turned in diamonds?
- Hey!
- See? I told you so.
- I'll never trust you guys again.
- For real? That's unbelievable.
- I said we couldn't do it.
But we can eat the food
if we get the right answer.
You're right, Jae Suk.
I turned in my diamonds
because I thought I couldn't do it.
None of you turned in any diamonds.
Give us a multiple choice question.
What is the smallest country
in the world...
that is located in Rome, Italy...
where the papal court is located?
- What did you say?
- What?
What is the smallest country
in the world...
- that is located in Rome, Italy...
- Suddenly, I can't remember it.
- A country?
- where the papal court is located?
It has three words.
- Three words.
- Three words?
- Where?
- Se Chan.
You heard about it
on the TV show before.
- Oh, right.
- Remember?
Try to remember it.
It's on the border of Switzerland.
(What's the smallest country in Rome
where the papal court is located?)
- What?
- The papal court is there.
- Pardon?
- The papal court.
- Where the papal court is located.
- All I remember is the papal court.
- Can't you give us a hint?
Did you say it has three words?
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- It's not Milan, is it?
- No, that's not it.
Milan is not a country. It's a city.
- Exactly.
- I can't remember the name.
- Gosh.
- Wow.
- Why can't I remember it suddenly?
- Can't you remember it?
My gosh. I can't remember it at all.
Jae Suk, you're suspicious.
You can't remember it suddenly?
I'm not lying.
I suddenly forgot the name.
There are times when you can't
remember what you know.
- We'll give you 5 seconds.
- It has 3 words?
- I don't think this is correct.
- Five.
- Why didn't you turn in diamonds?
- Four.
(She wrote "In Rome?")
- Three.
- I don't know. I can't remember it.
- Two.
- It's confusing.
One.
- Isn't it Brussels?
- Show your answers now.
Isn't it Brussels?
(Everyone reveals their answers
without confidence.)
Gosh.
I wrote this to make everyone laugh.
(Suriname)
(Papal court)
- I can't remember it.
- Is this a capital city?
All the members...
- didn't get the correct answer.
- Gosh, seriously.
- It was too difficult.
- I couldn't remember the name.
It was too difficult.
- Hey, Florence is a city.
- Really? I didn't know.
- Hey, isn't it Brussels?
- I don't know.
- Isn't it Monaco?
- What are you talking about?
- Monaco is a kingdom.
- Isn't it Monaco?
- She said it was a country.
- The answer is Vatican City State.
- Vatican City State.
- Oh, Vatican City State?
- Vatican City State?
- Vatican City State.
- Oh, it was Vatican City State.
- Why couldn't I remember this?
- Vatican City State.
- Why couldn't I remember it?
- Hey.
- She wrote "In Rome."
- You wrote "Monaco."
They wrote "In Rome,"
"Brussels," and "Papal court."
- Suk Jin, you wrote "Monaco."
- Yes?
- "Monaco?"
- What's that?
- Big Nose wrote "Monaco."
- I got confused.
- But I think...
- It's Vatican City State, right?
It wasn't as hard as I expected.
- Right? When you heard it...
- Yes, we've all heard it before.
- It's not that hard.
- Right.
But one of you could have given
the wrong answer intentionally.
- Of course. I think it's her.
- I'm sure of it.
- No, I didn't know the answer.
- You think she knows the answer?
I don't even know
Vatican City State.
- Wait. Hold on.
- The spy is...
There's no way he doesn't know
Vatican City State.
- I agree.
- Hear me out.
- I couldn't remember the name.
- Jae Suk must know the answer.
- Hold on. Vatican City State...
- Let me explain.
- I mean, I'm sure that...
- I couldn't remember it.
it's an easy question for him.
Jong Kook, I find something
even stranger than that.
- He didn't write anything.
- It's because...
- Nobody leaves it blank.
- That's right.
- He's an experienced entertainer.
- I mean...
I couldn't write a wrong answer
because...
But he knows all the capital cities.
- Yes, I know all of them.
- He's the spy.
- No, I'm not.
- Diamonds...
- I wouldn't have made it obvious.
Listen.
Let me share my sharp thinking.
It could be him,
but this is a quiz game, right?
So it must be someone who's expected
to give a wrong answer. One of them.
You think it's me?
We wouldn't find it suspicious
if one of them got it wrong.
- Aren't I right?
- Wait.
- But...
- Hold on.
I think it's either
Jae Suk or Se Chan.
- It's odd he didn't write anything.
- That's not it.
- That's the weirdest part.
- That's because...
He would know Vatican City for sure.
- Vatican...
- It wasn't puzzling.
- I know, but I drew a blank.
- That's not it.
Nothing came to mind.
- It's just odd.
- When you're the Variety King?
- You wrote nothing.
- Well, he...
- It's dereliction of duty.
- It doesn't make any sense.
How can he not write anything
when he's a veteran of 35 years?
- Hold on.
- I'm sure of it.
Let's get ourselves
an easier one first.
- That's right.
- Yes, an easier one.
- Vatican City wasn't easy.
- Let's hand in our diamonds.
- And...
- Let's fish out the spy.
- One who doesn't hand in one.
- Right.
- Two each...
- It only just came back to me.
Hold on a second.
- It's ready.
- First of all,
since you didn't
answer the question correctly,
only the two chosen by the spy
will get to eat.
- This looks incredible.
- The two chosen by the spy are...
(Who did the spy choose?)
- Suk Jin?
- So Min and Haha.
- Why though?
- One of them is the spy.
- It's not me.
- The spy chose himself or herself.
- It's So Min.
- No, the spy wouldn't do that.
- Is that so?
(It's him!)
So the spy is among us?
- Of course.
- It isn't me.
- It's Jae Suk.
- I know Vatican City, but...
There's no way
you wouldn't know that.
- You sometimes draw a blank.
- The spy could've chosen himself.
- Because...
- Himself?
Can I tuck in?
- Yes, go ahead.
- Right here?
(A juicy steak grilled with butter)
- This looks great.
- Is this Korean beef?
- What?
- What about stir-fried pork?
(A juicy steak grilled with butter)
It's medium-rare.
This looks incredible.
I'll enjoy this.
(Thanks to the spy, Haha and So Min
enjoy the T-bone steak.)
Are we really allowed to eat this?
(They forget about the spy
and enjoy their meal.)
Check this out.
This is insane.
It's so good.
You grilled it to perfection.
- Could the spy love me?
- Maybe me as well.
Why is the spy being nice to us?
Am I being pitied?
- From what I see...
- So Min.
- Look.
- That looks delicious.
It's weird that Haha's there.
Haha didn't know the answer,
so he could've just
written his name instead.
- But those two?
- Let's hand in some diamonds.
- I wonder who chose them.
- We'll hand in diamonds this time.
You failed to answer
the question correctly,
so they got to enjoy the steak.
- The others lost a diamond each.
- Exactly.
- We were going to lose them anyway.
- The spy will receive the diamonds.
Apart from those eating,
we all lose a diamond each.
So the spy gets five diamonds?
Before we move on to the next round,
you will be given a mission
that'll help guess who the spy is.
The winner of that game...
will get to see their current rank
or someone else's.
It could help you determine
who the spy is.
(The spy must finish in 3rd place!)
This game will get you partying,
and it's called
Mr. Run, Do You Know the Song?
What was that again?
Each of you will select a year
between 1995 and 2022.
A popular song
from that year will play.
When the song pauses,
you are to continue with the song.
- I see.
- I get it.
The one who chose the year
will get a chance to sing it first.
You will win two points
if you succeed in your round.
If you fail,
the mic will be up for grabs,
and it will be worth one point.
Get it wrong,
and you'll lose a point.
(Get it right to win a point,
Get it wrong and lose a point)
Let's start with the 90s.
From 1998 to 2000.
- I hardly listened to songs then.
- The early 2000s.
I'm starting with 1995.
Knowing the song
and being able to sing it...
- are two different things.
- Exactly.
Is it going to be
just a popular song,
or one that topped the charts?
It'll be one from the top ten list.
How about 2005?
- Back when I was 20?
- Yes.
- I'll go with 2005. When I was 20.
- You listen to a lot of music...
- in your teens and your early 20s.
- Right.
Let it be an easy one.
Is this the one?
- I know the song. It's by Buzz.
- Yes, Buzz.
Is this "Thorn?"
- Is this "Thorn?"
- Widened eyes
No, not now. When the song pauses.
When it pauses.
Follow the lyrics
and listen to the song.
I know there is only one of you
- I don't know this song very well.
- It's why I want you no matter what
- I don't know this either.
- It goes, "Don't make me cry."
I know the song, but not the lyrics.
- Love me
- It was, "Love me."
Don't make me cry
More often said than breathing
(More often said than breathing)
Than breathing
- I almost had it.
- What happened?
- The rest of it.
- It's not as easy as it looks.
- I never sang along to this song.
- Me neither.
I don't know songs by Buzz.
I never sang them
since I don't like Min Kyung Hoon.
Because you didn't like him?
- Not now though, right?
- We're close friends now.
Give it a try if you know the song.
- Anyone?
- Sing that part.
I don't know the lyrics.
(It's a song many have sung before.)
I know I'm right.
- Love me
- Don't make me cry
- Words more often said
- Than breathing
- What is it?
Than breathing
But I can't say it with confidence
All I do is hide my feelings
- That's the kind of coward I am
(All I do is hide my feelings,
that's the kind of coward I am)
(Se Chan is correct!)
- It came to you.
- Right, it came to me.
- But...
- You sang that really well.
- Really?
- You only get one point though.
If it were your first try,
you would've gotten two.
Still, it came to us.
You need help from those around you.
- A coward
- The help is crucial.
This is tricky.
I'm completely clueless.
Did you say from the 90s?
Ji Hyo, have you ever...
gone to a karaoke before?
No, that's why I'm...
Before she does anything,
- she always seemed worried.
- Let me see.
- The 2000s? 2002.
- How about 2000?
- Just choose a random year.
- The year 2002.
- "Oh! Pilsung Korea" could play.
- It's a possibility.
She doesn't know that song.
- "Oh! Pilsung Korea?"
- I don't.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
It's BoA's song.
("No.1" by BoA)
- It's BoA's song.
- You shined a light
- It's "No.1."
- I know this song.
You saw me when
my relationship ended
You're still my number one
Don't look for me
Take my sadness away
Up in the clouds
It's not as easy as it seems.
I feel my number one
- I'm still my number one
- I can't recall the lyrics.
- Don't look for me
- Isn't it "deep inside me?"
- I don't know.
- Don't look for me
- Even my sadness
(Humming meaningless syllables)
What on earth was that?
- I'll take a shot at this.
- You're still my number one
Why are you up there?
I know the song.
As if.
- Let him try.
- I bet he'll fail.
(You saw me when
my relationship ended)
Don't look for me
To me, you
- Are you kidding me?
- That was awful.
- What was that?
- Are you the spy?
- I suddenly drew a blank.
- I'm sorry to say this but...
Suk Jin, you lose a point.
Why?
- You lose points.
- So just stay put.
You lost a point for running wild.
- You lose points for trying.
- He wanted to seem young.
- But...
- See?
That's what you get
for wanting more screen time.
I should've got to sing
from "I feel my number one."
It's "You still my number one."
It's not "I feel." It's new...
- You still my number one?
- This seems impossible.
Don't look for me
- Secretly
Little by little, I cried
- Jae Suk, go for it.
- And I
Finally
We'll move on to the next song.
What the...
- But I just went up there.
- Can't you give him a chance?
How about this?
- We should...
- Jae Suk,
how about 1998?
- Maybe a song by H.O.T.
- We'll go with a year that...
- had a song many sang along to.
- Right.
(A song many sang along to?)
How about 2004 which was when
the World Cup took place?
- It was 2002.
- Right, 2002.
- It was in 2002 and 2006.
- Yes, 2002.
During the 2002 World Cup.
- Then...
- I'm going 1996, 1997, and 1998.
- How about 2007?
- Sounds good.
- The year 2007.
- Go for it.
That's when BigBang debuted.
Exactly. That's why
I mentioned 2007.
- Yes, 2007.
- That sounds better.
But if you think about it...
- BigBang!
- It's BigBang's song.
("Lies" by BigBang)
- It's BigBang.
- Is this "Lies?"
- Here we go.
- He doesn't know the lyrics.
- This is "Lies."
- Lies
- Late night, while it rained
- Do you know the lyrics?
I don't know the rap.
- I'm confident
- He listened to this a lot.
Please. You've got this.
(I miss you, but I can't see you,
it's over, I'll be right there)
I'm so sorry, but I love you,
but they are all lies
Only now do I know that
I need you
So sorry but I love you
(So sorry but I love you)
Seriously?
Why don't you know the lyrics?
He knows the lyrics,
but he can't sing to the beat.
Why didn't you pause
at the section that I know?
He's just as old
as everyone his age.
You could tell he wasn't sure.
He went like this.
I need you
That's how it goes.
- He even missed the beat.
- Anyway, how does it go?
I thought he was going to get it.
The staff have it rough.
Games are always cut short,
and we don't know
the lyrics to the songs.
- How does it go?
- He even missed the beat.
Isn't it "sharp words in anger?"
- Unknowingly, I let you go
- I let you go
Go for it, Se Chan.
- Give it a try.
- I think I know it.
(Se Chan who can sing to the beat
gives it a try.)
He'll get it this time.
(I miss you, but I can't see you,
it's over, I'll be right there)
I'm so sorry, but I love you,
but they are all lies
Only now do I know that, I need you
I'm so sorry, but I love you,
so the sharp words
I said out of spite,
and I unknowingly let you go
- I'm so sorry
- Yes!
- Nice!
- Come on!
- But...
- I thought I was right.
- You weren't.
Don't you agree
that he looks like a hillbilly?
- I mean it.
- Come on.
- Haha, I'm 37, you know.
- It took me aback.
Actually,
- I found him really charming.
- Really?
How can he be charming
when his lips were sticking out?
- Ever since Yeosu...
- Exactly.
- He's been growing on you.
- Well...
- You found that charming?
- He sang it well.
- Wasn't it good?
- Yes.
I'm so sorry, but I love you
He looked really ugly.
- I need you
- You found that charming?
He's a decent singer.
Then I...
Jong Kook, go with 1995.
- Should I? I'll go with 1995.
- Go.
If it's 1995, Turbo...
("Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung)
It's "Eve's Warning."
- Wait.
- Park Mi Kyung?
He knows it.
(His body reacts to the intro.)
Is this not it?
- It's "As if..."
- This is the move.
- The dance break.
- Pull it down.
- "As if."
- It starts with "today, you..."
"Today, you avoid me as always."
(The beat from those days
makes him excited.)
- Today, you avoid me as always
- And think about something else
- Let's go.
- Kungddari hwiba
- You don't know the exact lyrics?
- I don't know.
I know the song,
but I don't know the lyrics.
(Besides you, a cool guy)
A cool guy
- Let's go.
- Hits on me
- And I'm tempted sometimes
- As if you're the only one capable
- Capable
I don't know.
(The old-time singer
doesn't know someone else's songs.)
- What was it?
- As if
- You're the only one capable
- If you're trying
- As if you're the only one capable
- To fool me like that, I...
If you're trying to fool me
like that
- Then I...
- That's right.
- Will not be faithful anymore, I...
- Anymore, I...
- There you go.
- Is this right?
That's right.
- So Min got one right.
- Will just leave you
Songs from those days
are easier than the others.
- It's much better.
- I'll do it too.
I'll go with 1996.
I really don't know the lyrics.
- Me, neither.
- I really don't know.
("Affection" by Young Turks Club)
- It's Young Turks Club.
- I know it.
- From the beginning.
- For our love
I know it.
- You said you really loved me
- You said you can't live without me
- I believed it as the truth
- I suddenly can't remember.
- You're nervous, right?
- You can't remember the lyrics.
- And now, you want to break up
(We...)
We...
- From the first word.
- I loved
- You
- He lost.
Do you think you know it?
- You said you really loved me
- You said you can't live without me
- I believed it as the truth
- She knows it.
- And now, you want to break up
(What about...)
- What about
- What?
- "What about me?"
- No.
- Is it not right?
- That's the chorus.
- What really angers me...
is that they play
the part we know only.
You can't let us guess
the part many people don't know.
I'll let you know the first line.
- Okay.
- "What about the remaining love?"
- Yes.
- What about the remaining love?
- What about our memories?
- When I cry because I miss you
- "When I cry..."
- And now...
- And now, you want to break up
- No.
- You want to break up
- It doesn't make sense.
- It's the chorus.
- What...
- What about me...
- No, it's not.
- It's "without you."
- It's "What about remaining love?"
- How can I live without you?
(They just told him the lyrics
"What about remaining love?")
- How can I live without you?
- It's "remaining love."
- What about remaining love?
- What about without memories?
- It's "Be happy without you."
- When I cry because I miss you
- And now, you want to break up
- When I cry...
- because...
- Is this a repeating song?
- When I cry because I miss you
- Because I miss you
- Now, what should I do?
- No.
- Now...
Isn't it "What should I do now?"
- No. That's not the part.
- What on earth should I do?
- It's "What on earth should I do?"
- "What on earth should I do?"
- What on earth should I do?
- Should I do?
- No, it must be a dream
- Must be a dream, I can't forget
- It's "What on earth should I do?"
- Okay, I got it.
- Try it.
- "What on earth should I do?"
- I really hope it's right.
- Jae Suk...
- will get nervous 100 percent.
- But is it right...
- for us to cheer each other up?
- Go.
- Good. Go.
- We should get it right first.
Jae Suk, sing it loud.
(Will he be able to finish the song,
overcoming his game anxiety?)
- You said you really loved me
(You said you can't live without me)
I'm nervous again.
(I believed it as the truth)
It's "remaining love."
(And now, you want to break up)
- What about remaining love?
- Remaining love?
- What about our memories?
- When I cry because I miss you
- What on earth should I do?
- That's right.
- Is this right?
- No, it must be a dream
- It must be a dream
- I can't forget you
I miss those days.
- It was nice.
- But is it right for us...
to cooperate
and make one of us succeed?
- Is it an individual game or what?
- It's not right, but...
- It's an individual match, but...
- It's a warm-up.
- It puts us in a good mood.
- Is that so?
- Yes. It puts us in a good mood.
- I worked so hard.
- Here we go.
- Gosh.
(The song mission that feels like
a get-together continued like that.)
"I went."
- I went around a fishy quayside
- Is this "Challenge 1000 Songs?"
- As if it was my world
(Acting like a thug)
It's sung by Can.
Yes, I know.
- With my two fists
- Let's go.
(Assistant Manager Ha
in charge of entertainment)
Where?
- Don't insult me that I'm cunning
- Without fear
They'll play from "Don't insult me."
- Don't insult me that I'm cunning
Even if I wander
- Come on. Move over.
- around dirty backstreets
- You were late.
- I'll do it.
I'm doing it.
It's my first time I finally
I don't sing this part.
- We should guess this part.
- Fell deeply in love
You should've played
the previous part.
Why did you...
But wait.
Based on the result,
the winner is Se Chan.
- As expected.
- You should come...
and ask us about the rank
of the person you're curious about.
- Then we will answer.
- This is...
No. The spy could work hard.
- Why?
- You can ask about yourself...
or someone else.
- I'm not a spy.
- If he's a spy, he worked hard...
to hide his identity.
- Right. To hide his identity.
- Sit down.
- That's why you worked hard.
- I said I'm not.
- I can ask about 3 people?
- No. Just 1.
- What?
- I said I'm not. Vatican is...
- I think it's Se Chan.
- The ranking?
- I'm really not.
- You can ask about yourself...
or someone else.
Jealous
Share it with us.
- We did it together.
- Think that someone was jealous
Share it with us.
- We did it together.
- Suk Jin.
(Se Chan checks
the ranking of Suk Jin.)
- Is that the one?
- This is the ranking.
Really?
- It's made.
- If it's made, the guys...
- Did you see it?
- Why?
- Whose ranking is the lowest?
- Why? What is it?
Can I share it?
- It's up to you.
- Do as you want.
Share with us. We did it together.
- Who did you ask about?
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine. Why?
- Why do you keep pushing me?
- For what?
- I think Suk Jin can slow down.
- Why?
I guess he has many.
- No.
- What did you ask about?
- The ranking.
- What ranking?
The gem ranking.
I guess he doesn't have a lot.
Be quiet.
- Does he have nothing?
- He checked the ranking.
- We'll reveal the next food.
- My stomach hurts.
What ranking is it?
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- What ranking is it?
I was thrilled
to guess all the lyrics right.
What is it this time? Noodles?
Is it noodles? It's ramyeon.
- No. It's ramyeon.
- It's ramyeon. It's crazy.
(Crowding)
- Let's eat it no matter what.
- I'll definitely hand it in.
- We should do it.
- Let's do it.
- Let's do an easy one and hand it.
- It's a snow crab.
It's a snow crab.
Full of umami.
- This is a must.
- It's seafood.
Regardless of it,
let's give them two.
- But, Jae Suk...
- Let's give them two.
I think one of us should
give them more.
It's the spy
who hasn't given anything.
Oh, someone can't afford it?
- So...
- Is it...
- impossible to give it to them?
- So one of us should be confident.
- I got it.
- Excuse me.
- I'll give them 2 this time.
- You should give them 2.
- Rich people should give 2.
- Give them 2.
- I'll give them 2.
- I'll give them 1.
Wait. Then we can deduce.
Let's exclude him first.
- Then the ones who don't give...
- One, two, three,
four, five, six, and seven.
- Jae Suk will not give them his.
- Who is going to give them two?
I'll give them two.
- I'll give them two this time.
- Yes. Give them two.
- Then it should be eight.
- It'll be obvious.
I'll give them exactly two
this time.
- Let's make it 8.
- If we make it 8,
- we can check it.
- Okay.
- Okay. Go in.
- The spy is going to be revealed.
- Go.
- Go inside and close the door.
- I'll trust you guys this time.
I'll take out two this time.
- One?
- Let's make it.
- Are you a beggar?
- He's a genius.
- Take it out, okay?
- Hey.
I think
Suk Jin doesn't have anything.
I won't have to give them mine.
They think I have nothing.
I do have some.
Not giving it to them
is meaningless.
Let's find the spy.
Not giving it to them
is meaningless.
If you don't give it to them,
they will take it anyway.
(More than 7 gems: Easy,
Between 4 and 6 gems: Normal,)
I'll take out two.
- Okay. Let's get the easy one.
- Let's go.
- Before the second quiz,
take out the diamonds
to decide the difficulty level.
I'll really trust you.
I'll give them mine too.
But you don't have any.
(Retrieving)
(Sealing in the pocket
without anyone knowing)
I'm really going to hand it in.
I'm handing it in this time.
I submitted.
(Jae Suk submitted 2
as he promised.)
(So Min also promised to submit 2.)
Jae Suk. I submitted two.
I'm handing it in.
Let's go.
We have to find the spy,
so let's hand it in.
I already did.
Let's check our teamwork.
You submitted a total of...
seven diamonds.
- What?
- We did it.
(They planned to collect 8,
but they only collected 7.)
- Someone didn't submit it.
- This question is easy.
- Who didn't submit it?
- Someone didn't submit it.
It's someone who had to submit one,
right?
- I can't believe it.
- Gosh.
The person who had to submit one
didn't submit it.
- Here's the question.
- I told you.
- Gosh.
- Sim Cheong...
threw herself into the sea
to make her father open his eyes.
What's the name of the sea she fell?
What?
(Indangsu)
Easy.
Of course I know.
(Several members write it
without hesitation.)
This isn't easy at all.
This...
- The sea has a name?
- This isn't easy at all.
Is it Imdangsu or Indangsu?
Hold on. Indangsu...
Is this... Imdangsu?
Imjeongsu? Imdangsu?
What's the first letter?
Isn't it Indangsu?
Is it Imdangsu?
(Is it Imdangsu?)
- It's confusing.
- You have five seconds.
Jong Kook.
She sells herself for 300 sacks
of rice and throws herself...
into here!
- Did I remind you?
- Two.
- One. Show your answer.
- Yes, you reminded me.
(Revealing the answer)
- Show your answer.
- Isn't this it?
(Imdangsu)
Gosh.
Wait. Sim Cheong...
(Imdangsu)
Sim Cheong threw herself
into Imdangsu.
Everyone...
- Probably not.
- did not get it right.
- Gosh.
- I knew it.
(They failed to get the answer.)
- Who was it?
- Jae Suk.
- I knew it.
- Isn't this Indangsu?
- But...
- It's Indangsu.
- Indangsu.
- Is it In or Im?
- He got it.
- In.
- I wrote Im.
(I wrote Im.)
- Is it In or Im?
- It's Indangsu.
- Indangsu.
- It's In.
- It's not Imdangsu.
I wasn't sure whether
it was In or Im.
- Come here if you wrote Imdangsu.
- Imdangsu?
- I wrote Im.
That sounds like someone's name.
- I got confused.
- And...
- The spelling is important.
- I told you it's not easy.
- So Min. Did you submit two?
- I did.
- Did you submit two?
- Yes.
Then one of the people who had to
submit one is the spy.
- I submitted one.
- Me too.
I submitted one.
- Haha didn't submit it.
- It's either Haha...
- or Ji Hyo.
- You didn't submit it, did you?
- Haha didn't submit it.
- I submitted two.
It's Haha.
You didn't submit it, did you?
- Is it still weird?
- You got the answer.
- Yes. Indangsu.
- This is crazy.
- It's Haha.
- I wrote In at first.
- Haha didn't submit it.
- I submitted two.
- I really submitted it.
- You didn't submit it, did you?
- You don't know Indangsu?
- Look.
- I wrote nieun and changed it.
- You should've stuck to it.
Stop it.
- Indangsu didn't sound right.
- You Empty Heads.
Is it In as a person?
- That's still...
- Haha didn't submit it.
a lot of improvement.
You only got one letter wrong.
- Is it Haha?
- What?
Is it Haha?
I think it's either Haha or Ji Hyo.
- I'm sure...
- You think so?
- you'll be surprised.
- It's Haha. Haha didn't submit it.
- No?
- He didn't submit it.
If they submitted two each,
he didn't submit it for sure.
- I submitted two.
- What about Ji Hyo?
Is it In as a human?
I think so.
Because not everyone got the answer,
only two people the spy picked
in advance can eat.
- That's me.
- But...
If the spy knows me,
he'd let me eat for sure.
The spy picked...
- Probably himself.
- Not me.
He probably included himself
in the second time.
Yoo Jae Suk and Jeon So Min.
I'm eating again?
(Yoo Jae Suk and Jeon So Min)
- Does he like So Min?
- I get to...
I get to eat again?
Also, except for those two,
we'll collect one diamond each...
- It's not you, is it?
- and give it to the spy.
- Who likes So Min so much?
It's not Ji Hyo. She doesn't...
Is it Ji Hyo?
It's not me.
- Jae Suk...
- It's really not me.
He said he'll submit one.
But why did he submit two?
- Jae Suk. How many did you submit?
- At least three.
- Two.
- He said he'll submit three.
- You submitted two?
- Two.
- Then it should be eight...
- At first, he said three.
if you submitted two.
So someone said he'll submit one...
- You submitted one then.
- Yes.
No. I submitted two.
Was ramyeon not worth two?
- Yes. So he submitted only one.
- No.
It's not me for sure.
He let me eat ramyeon.
You're not the only one
who likes ramyeon.
- I like ramyeon too.
- I like it more, you punk.
- I like it more.
I like it more than you
no matter what.
I'm crazy for ramyeon.
My name is ramyeon.
- Hey.
- Maybe the spy...
keeps choosing Jae Suk and So Min
to frame them.
- At first...
- Excuse me.
- you were the spy, but...
- You have no diamonds.
Stay out of this.
You have no diamond?
He has no diamond.
- I do.
- If you don't have any, don't talk.
- Can the spy pick himself?
You may eat now.
I'm sorry.
I'm curious. It's not that
he likes me, but frames me?
- He's making fun of you.
- Am I being framed?
- He's making fun of me?
- Yes.
- He's making fun of you now.
- Is the spy...
- Except for Jae Suk and So Min,
- Am I being framed?
- give me one diamond each.
- Gosh.
- This is crazy.
- We have to give it to you?
Yes. You have to hand it to me.
So Min. It's not you, is it?
It's really not me.
It's not you either?
It's not me.
Oh, thank you so much.
Thank you for the food. Thank you.
It's so savory.
It's got seafood.
(Savory seafood ramyeon with a crab)
That looks so good.
I love seafood ramyeon so much.
Give me my phone.
(Slurping)
I love that sound.
It's so refreshing.
It's got the light scent of crab.
On YouTube,
- That looks so good.
- each broadcasting station...
- has the scene of me...
- No.
You told me to give it to the spy.
- has the scene of me...
- No.
(You told me to give it to the spy.)
You said it's for the spy.
(Giving the gem
to the suspected spy)
- It's not me. I swear.
- The spy...
must've collected
so many diamonds by now, right?
He must've collected so many.
Jae Suk. I have a feeling it's you.
It could be him, right?
If it's me,
I wouldn't let So Min
eat twice in a row.
Right.
- It's him.
- That's obvious.
- Yes.
- It's either him...
- or...
- He can avoid the suspicion.
He's trying to frame me.
I wouldn't let Jae Suk...
have ramyeon as a joke.
- Wouldn't it be strange...
- He's eating because he's the spy.
if the spy is eating?
The only person who would
make this decision...
is Ji Hyo.
- I was thinking Ji Hyo too.
- Because she's kind?
It's really not me.
- Don't twist it?
- Exactly.
If I was the spy, I wouldn't let
Jae Suk eat ramyeon.
- Is the spy...
- What if he's the spy?
- He'd eat.
- Yes.
- Because he's playful.
- I'd eat too.
Let So Min eat the steak?
I wouldn't do that.
Exactly. The only person
who would let So Min...
have the steak is Ji Hyo.
No.
To frame me.
I didn't know it was steak
and ramyeon.
- You didn't know?
- She told us.
- What?
- Do you have a problem?
- You didn't know.
- You didn't know it was steak?
You selected them
without knowing the menu?
It's not me. Don't frame it on me.
You're going to regret it.
How can you not know
it was steak and ramyeon?
They showed us before the start.
That's not it.
She's saying she's the spy,
- but without knowing the menu,
- She's the spy.
- she picked them.
- She made a mistake.
- But...
- That's what she meant.
- Right?
- I didn't know.
It's funny that she said it.
You didn't know it was steak?
But they showed us.
When?
- You didn't see the T-bone steak?
No, not now.
- When?
- You mean before?
- Not now.
- When you received the mission?
- Now...
- They didn't tell you?
- That's right.
- Okay.
They didn't tell you?
They didn't tell you the first menu?
- Frame it on me.
- They only asked about who to eat.
- Exactly.
- They didn't tell her the menu.
- Okay. Frame it on me.
- When she received the mission.
But if it's not me, don't regret it.
- That's true.
- No.
If it's not me, don't regret it.
I agree with Jong Kook's opinion
because...
You always agree
with Jong Kook's opinion.
No, the only person who would
let So Min have two meals...
is Ji Hyo.
- Fine. Frame it on me.
- It's Ji Hyo.
- But remember it's not me.
- Jae Suk too.
Let's finish up the food...
and move on to the next mission.
We don't get to eat?
No.
So you should always have breakfast.
Thank you for the food.
(With suspicion,
they move for the next mission.)
This mission is
Mr. Run, Are You Holding the Rope Tight?
(After the second mission
to get a hint on the ranking...)
One point for Jong Kook.
- Minus 30...
- Gosh.
Wait.
There!
(The last person is Ji Hyo.)
- Ten points.
- Ten points?
- That's amazing.
Ji Hyo placed first.
I'll tell Ji Hyo...
the person's ranking of her choice.
What if she's the spy?
- What if she's the spy?
- Whose ranking did you ask?
- I think it was Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
- She's not the spy, is it?
- I don't know.
I want to know my own ranking.
(Ji Hyo suddenly checks
her own ranking.)
(1st place)
What's this?
(Ji Hyo turns around after checking
she's in 1st place.)
The spy must place within top three.
(The spy must be in top 3 to win.)
- It could be her.
- Top three?
- Is everyone getting the penalty?
- Yes.
If the spy wins,
everyone except for the spy...
will get the penalty.
It could be Ji Hyo.
The spy has to rank in top three?
The food for the third quiz is
beef jeon and shrimp jeon.
- Shrimp jeon?
- Shrimp jeon sounds good.
That's why I smelled jeon earlier.
The smell of fritters is so good.
Please enter your room
and close the door.
I guess we're not getting
any food today.
Please submit the diamond first
to decide the quiz level.
How are we going to do it?
Let's submit one each.
- So collect seven in total.
- Let's submit one each.
Same as last time.
I can't submit two.
I don't have enough.
The person who has more
should submit two.
- So Min.
- This is the last time...
I'll submit two.
(This is the last round I submit 2!)
(So Min readily submits 2 diamonds.)
Two diamonds.
I submitted two diamonds.
- Submit one each.
- Okay.
- So Min, submit two.
Hold on.
Why does Suk Jin keep saying okay
when he has zero diamonds?
At the very least,
seven diamonds will be collected.
Suk Jin doesn't have any.
- Hey.
- I will submit one.
I submitted one.
Ji Hyo, submit one.
I can't do it.
(Laughing)
(He changed his mind in 1 second.)
I don't have many diamonds.
- Now, please submit the diamonds.
- Okay.
- I will submit 1.
- I submitted 1.
The diamonds will be collected now.
Let's go.
It will be a problem
if there are less than five.
We need to catch the spy.
I submitted one.
The number of diamonds
you have submitted is...
- six.
- Hey!
- For goodness' sake.
- I submitted one.
- Six.
- Hey!
- For goodness' sake.
- I submitted one.
I swear I submitted one.
This is...
The difficulty level is normal.
- We were so close.
- We were one diamond short.
We were so close.
- The spy didn't submit a diamond.
- It seems that way.
I will give you the question.
Who brought cotton seeds from China
during Goryeo Dynasty?
What?
Isn't the difficulty level easy?
You should know the answer.
(Answer: Mun Ik Jeom)
The difficulty level is easy.
(Haha writes down the answer
right away.)
Hold on.
(Hold on.)
Is it right?
Hold on. Is it Mun Ik Jeon
or Mun Ik Jeom?
I am confused. Is it Jeon or Jeom?
(Empty Heads
are struggling already.)
- Hold on.
- Don't you know the answer?
Hold on.
Why can't I remember the name?
No way.
Cotton seeds. Hold on.
Who was it?
(Who was it?)
- Lee Bang Won?
- I will give you five seconds.
It would make no sense
if you get this wrong.
- I will give you five seconds.
- Hold on.
- Five.
- You should know this.
- Four.
- Hold on.
- It's so easy.
- Hey!
Three.
Isn't it Lee Bang Won?
- Two.
- I don't know the answer.
- Who brought the cotton seeds?
- One.
Raise the board.
Se Chan!
- I am sorry.
- Se Chan!
Haha, the difficulty level is hard.
- It isn't hard. It's easy.
- How is it hard?
- I know this, but I can't remember.
- You know this, Jong Kook.
- Cotton seeds.
- Hold on.
- This is too much.
- You should know the answer.
Please come on out.
- I don't know the answer.
- Really?
- Do you really not know the answer?
The spy picked two members
who can eat.
Pick me this once.
They are Suk Jin and Se Chan.
- I got picked.
- You finally got picked.
- What?
- Maybe the spy picked...
- random members.
- The rest of the members...
- must submit one diamond each.
- Really?
- The two of you can eat.
- Okay.
- Beef jeon sounds delicious.
- My goodness.
Shrimp jeon and beef jeon.
The food looks amazing.
(A table with beef jeon
and shrimp jeon)
Shrimp jeon.
It's my first time
eating shrimp jeon.
Shrimp will be in season soon.
Haha, shrimp will be in season soon.
Is it tender?
(Jealous)
- It's insane.
- Is it tasty?
- It looks delicious.
- I know.
- Beef jeon looks tasty.
- It's insane.
- I haven't had this before.
- Shrimp...
- is in season.
- It's tasty these days.
I think...
It might be Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo?
- One of us is a spy.
- Seriously.
- I think it's Ji Hyo.
I think it's Ji Hyo.
Hold on. How about Jong Kook?
- It could be Jong Kook.
- Think about it.
I came up with a strategy earlier.
What do you think of that?
- It was sharp.
- Do you honestly think it's me?
You don't honestly think
it's me, do you?
- But...
- You might have done it on purpose.
You might have done it on purpose.
- I might have done it on purpose?
- Yes.
- Mun Ik Jeom.
- Jong Kook didn't get it right.
- I got it right.
But Mun Ik Jeom...
(Jong Kook didn't get
Mun Ik Jeom right.)
I admit that it was suspicious.
Although it was an easy question,
- I couldn't remember the answer.
- It happens at times.
- I really couldn't remember it.
Mun Ik Jeom...
- It might be Jong Kook.
- I admit that it was suspicious.
- I admit it.
- It's very strange.
My mind went blank.
I couldn't remember it.
Why couldn't I remember Mun Ik Jeom?
It's so tasty.
- I got Mun Ik Jeom right.
- Suk Jin, that's mine.
- No. You had two.
- I got it right too.
- What?
- You had two.
- I had one.
- Really?
As for the shrimp jeon,
I had 2 and you had 1.
- You are right.
- Yes.
I couldn't remember it.
(He divided
the beef jeons precisely.)
- You were counting.
- Of course.
What?
Each person gets 2 beef jeons
and 2 shrimp jeons.
I had two beef jeons.
- Suk Jin was counting.
- Suk Jin said to me,
"You had two beef jeons.
That's mine."
Suk Jin isn't the spy.
- He isn't. He just wanted to eat.
- He just wanted to eat.
It's so tasty.
- Suk Jin, you are cute.
- He is so cute.
My goodness.
- It's so tasty.
- But the spy...
excluded me on purpose.
- It's strange.
- Ji Hyo is...
- Ji Hyo, aren't you the spy?
- I am not the spy.
- You are a strong candidate.
Go ahead and vote for me then.
- But I am not the spy.
- We are making deductions.
- We need to catch the spy.
- But...
- if...
- I can see your shadow, you punk!
- Gosh.
- You startled me.
You startled me.
(Haha suddenly got scolded.)
What was that?
I thought you were swearing at me.
(Haha got caught right away.)
My teacher, Ms. Lee Yeong Ja
did that back in elementary school.
- I apologize for swearing.
- Ms. Lee, are you doing well?
- I was so angry.
- It wasn't too bad.
The light was on him.
- He didn't know that.
- The light was on him.
- You saw his shadow.
- You can see it.
I can see it.
"I can see your shadow, you punk!"
- Are you done with the food?
- Yes.
Now comes the last mission
for a hint on the ranking.
These are real lottery tickets.
The one who wins the highest amount
of money will be the winner.
That person will learn
another member's ranking.
You see the prize
at the bottom, right?
You just need to get
the matching number.
- I got a dud.
- Here.
Let me get one.
- I got one.
- How much is that?
- It's a dud.
- It's one dollar, right?
I need to get four.
- Five.
- It's a dud.
- One more.
- We can't win a prize.
- Give me another ticket.
If I get 500,000 dollars,
I will share.
- All right. I...
- Let's have a team dinner.
- I won one dollar.
- How much?
How much is the prize? One dollar?
- Hold on.
- He won one dollar.
- He won.
- Did you win with one dollar?
- He won one dollar.
- I won, right?
- How did you win one dollar?
- Three.
No one else won one dollar.
You can ask for anyone's ranking.
- He is the spy.
- Whose ranking will you ask for?
He is suspicious.
I swear I am not the spy.
Don't worry.
You don't suspect me, do you?
- He is strange.
- I swear I am not the spy.
So Min just said...
- Me?
- I am not the spy.
- Okay.
- So Min's eyes...
- are shifting a lot.
- What?
- I...
- You arrived early too.
- Really?
- Ji Hyo was there too.
- Do you know what's strange?
- What?
She submitted diamonds
unlike the usual times.
- It's unrelated.
- But...
- It's her.
- I am suddenly being suspected.
Did she get these bangs
for her role as a spy?
(Did she get these bangs
for her role as a spy?)
- Then I would be incredulous.
- That might be the case.
- Today,
- Is this hair a must for a spy?
she got those bangs
to get absorbed in the role.
I am not the spy.
Don't suspect me so suddenly.
Whose ranking should I check?
- The spy has many diamonds.
- That's right.
I can't ask you to tell me
who is in the first place, right?
You can't do that.
Give me the name...
- to learn his or her ranking.
- This is driving me crazy.
(So Min submitted diamonds
generously today.)
- So Min must be in the first place.
- Yes.
So Min.
Ji Hyo came early.
I am not the spy.
(He checks So Min's ranking.)
(So Min's ranking is...)
Really?
(Haha returns
with a puzzled look on his face.)
It's unexpected.
- Why?
- Whose ranking did you check?
- I gave So Min diamonds.
- Okay.
Did you check So Min's ranking?
- Is it unexpected?
- I used a lot of diamonds.
- She doesn't have many diamonds.
- She isn't in the top three.
- So Min?
- Is it unexpected?
- Then So Min isn't the spy.
- So Min isn't the spy.
- Do you know why I revealed this?
- No.
I gave you all the information.
Haha might be lying.
- I meant my words.
- But his reactions came right away.
- Neither So Min nor I am the spy.
- Then who is the spy?
- We don't know about you.
- I am not the spy.
I am not the spy...
because I can't be in the top three
in terms of the number of diamonds.
- Thus, I am not the spy. What?
- But the spy keeps getting more.
But the spy keeps getting more.
- Even if I get more...
- Perhaps you discarded some.
- This could be the case.
- No.
The spy needs to be
in the top three.
If Suk Jin couldn't do it
despite being the spy,
the production crew
might be frustrated.
He is like a useless card.
- This episode might get scrapped.
- I know.
- "What's going on?"
- They might be frustrated.
- "How is he so bad at this?"
The production crew
might be frustrated.
The food you can win
with the last quiz is...
croffle and iced Americano.
- I need to eat them.
Please bring in the items.
- They will make it fresh.
- Jae Suk is the spy.
It must be hot.
The croffle must be hot.
- They brought the dough.
- Is this shine muscat?
Will you spray whipped cream
on the top?
- Please spray a lot.
- Okay.
- Why? Will you eat it?
- If I get to eat it,
- please add less cream.
- It's the dough.
- She is suspicious.
- It looks delicious.
- Stevia.
- She asked for a lot of cream.
She talked as if she can eat it.
Powder.
- Do you get to decide?
- It looks so tasty.
If you get picked, you are the spy.
No way. You saw
how many diamonds I have.
- I did,
- But So Min...
but you could move up
to get included in the top three.
How many diamonds
do the top three have?
- She is in fourth place.
- Really?
If she wins this round,
- she will be included.
- In the final top three.
I had a lot of diamonds,
but I used them up.
- I used them frivolously.
- Right?
- That's right.
- In that case,
we submitted six diamonds earlier.
I will submit 1 diamond.
Let's make the total 7.
- It won't work.
- Submit diamonds as you did.
- It won't work this time.
- You can submit one diamond, right?
Submit diamonds as you did.
I will add one to the total.
- Then we will have 7 diamonds.
Let's go.
- Let's do this.
- What should we do?
Submit diamonds as you did.
- I will add 1 to the total.
- I will submit 1.
- Will you submit a diamond?
- Of course.
- I don't know about this.
- Will you submit a diamond or not?
I don't think I will submit it.
- No?
- Don't submit a diamond.
Then our plan will be ruined.
If you don't submit a diamond,
our plan will be ruined.
(Will they be able
to collect 7 diamonds?)
You are done thinking, right?
Please submit the diamonds...
that will determine
the difficulty level.
It's too hard.
- Let's submit diamonds this time.
- Someone submit three diamonds.
Having diamonds is meaningless
unless you place first.
- Jae Suk won't submit any.
- I will.
Will you?
I only have a few diamonds,
but I will do it.
I will submit two.
I will submit one.
- I will submit 1 for real.
- I will submit 1.
- Will you submit 1?
(The members shout
that they will submit diamonds.)
- I submitted it.
- I will submit it.
(If you don't submit any,
I will kill you.)
If you don't submit any,
I will kill you.
(He makes a scary promise.)
- I will submit it.
- That's too much.
- Jong Kook, you are scary.
- I will kill you.
(He promises to take revenge
if they fail to meet the quota.)
Submit one each. I just did it.
- Submit it.
- Okay.
- Submit it for real.
- Okay. Let's submit.
Did you finish submitting diamonds?
- Yes.
- The total number of diamonds is...
(The total number of diamonds is...)
Five.
- Hey.
- For goodness' sake.
(The total number is five.)
(They failed to collect 7.)
Who didn't submit it?
- Who didn't submit it?
- Who was it?
- Jae Suk didn't submit it.
- I did.
I could tell from his face
that he wouldn't submit any.
- I submitted it.
- Gosh.
The difficulty level is normal.
- Let's do this.
- It will be hard.
Let's take on normal.
(The difficulty level
for the last question is normal.)
The difficulty level is normal.
In folk religion and Taoism,
there are ten things
that symbolize eternal youth.
Excuse me?
The sun, mountains, water, rocks,
pine trees, the moon or clouds,
herbs of eternal youth, turtles,
cranes, and deer.
What are these things called?
(They write down the answer
upon hearing the question.)
This is doable, right?
- This is doable.
- What about the ten things? Go on.
You know the answer, right?
The question gives it away.
Give me the question from the start.
- Haha, you are suspicious.
- I don't know the answer.
Don't you know the answer?
Hey, it's... Ten things.
Don't give him a hint.
You have five seconds.
Hold on.
Five, four, three...
Ten things?
- Two.
- Why is everyone keeping quiet?
One! Raise the board.
Haha is really suspicious.
How does he not know the answer?
They won't get it right.
(How did the 4 younger members do?)
(They failed to answer correctly.)
It's used often.
It appears often on variety shows.
Not everyone answered correctly.
- For goodness' sake.
- Who was it?
- Was it Haha?
- Haha.
- This is why...
- It was easy.
- Haha is the spy.
- It's him.
It was easy.
(Ji Hyo answered correctly.)
- What did you write?
- Ten Symbols of Longevity, right?
It's Ten Symbols of Longevity.
- It was easy.
- I got it wrong.
- Haha.
- "Nirvana?"
- Reaching the state of Nirvana.
- Why did you write "Nirvana?"
- Seriously.
- Reaching the state of Nirvana.
- Don't you know the answer?
- Why isn't it the answer?
- "Reaching the state of Nirvana?"
(Peeking)
It's Ten Symbols of Longevity.
(Haha bursts out laughing
after reading the room.)
- What did you write?
- Reaching the state of Nirvana.
- I am going to go.
- Hey.
- Ten Symbols of Longevity.
- He is the spy.
- I am going to go.
- He is suspicious.
- What did he write? Let me see.
- I am sorry.
What?
- What did he write?
- What?
Haha, go.
- What did he write?
- He wrote, "Ten Zodiac."
- Go.
- For goodness' sake.
- Don't you know the answer?
- You mean the Chinese Zodiac.
- Ten Zodiac.
- I am sorry.
I am sorry.
Producer, I am sorry.
- I am sorry. Producer, I am sorry.
- Listen.
- I am going. I am sorry.
- If you don't know this...
- It makes no sense.
- But I got it wrong too.
It makes no sense.
He might have gotten it confused
with the Chinese Zodiac.
The question clearly said
"Ten things."
I can't believe the seven of us
failed to answer correctly once.
- Since I got it right, it's easy.
- Why did you write "Nirvana?"
Reaching the state of Nirvana.
- I had no idea.
- I am sorry.
- She is suspicious too.
It's one of them.
- I am not the spy.
- How do you not know it?
You failed to answer correctly
as the group,
so the spy chose two people
who will eat the food.
Suk Jin and So Min.
- It's So Min.
- I am not the spy.
- Earlier, she said,
"When you give me the croffle,"
- "spray a lot of whipped cream."
- I heard that too.
- I am not the spy.
- It's So Min.
- This is a trap.
- She said it without thinking.
- She knew she would eat.
- This is a trap.
She said it without thinking.
- She was like a prophet.
She really wanted to eat it.
I told you earlier.
- She...
- She chose herself.
- She couldn't help it.
- That was why she chose Suk Jin.
- The spy...
- No.
- It can't be So Min.
- This is a trap.
Do you think she did her best?
The spy knows the ranking, right?
She should have been included
in the top three.
It's understandable.
- Why don't you think it's her?
- But she... Listen.
Her ranking is too low.
Think about it.
- It isn't So Min.
- When we get a question wrong,
- how many does the spy get?
- I don't know.
- Five or more.
- Here is what I think.
Five or more.
Let's come clean.
Who gave diamonds to So Min?
- I gave her diamonds.
- Same here.
- I did too.
- You gave her diamonds too.
- Then she got 15 diamonds.
- Did you give So Min diamonds?
- I gave her diamonds.
- Same here.
- I did too.
- You gave her diamonds too.
- Then she got 15 diamonds.
- Did you give So Min diamonds?
She got 15 diamonds.
Think about it.
She got 15 diamonds from 3 people.
Even if she submitted
two diamonds at a time,
she would have gotten
at least five diamonds...
for every wrong question
if she were a spy.
- Then she can't be in 4th place.
- She can't be in 4th place.
- She isn't the spy.
- I am not the spy.
- She isn't the spy?
I got goosebumps.
Listen. She is the spy.
- That was exactly why...
- Do you think the top two have...
- over 26 diamonds?
- She submitted diamonds...
to keep the number low.
- She had too many.
- I didn't submit many diamonds.
She isn't the type
to submit diamonds.
Then...
- She isn't the type to do that.
- Listen to me.
- Why... What are you doing?
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, you are suspicious.
- What?
- Why can't you accept...
- a logical explanation?
- Suk Jin is suspicious.
I gave diamonds
to Jae Suk and So Min.
to Jong Kook and So Min.
How about you?
- You and... Yes.
- Me.
- Hold on. Right.
- That's right.
Then who are in the top two?
- No!
- The top three.
How many diamonds
did they start with?
The spy has to be in the top two...
- given the current situation.
- That's right. Of course.
It's time to arrest the spy.
Please give us another question.
- That's right.
- I am begging you.
Can't we do it here?
Would you give a question
to each member?
Please give us another chance.
We can't apprehend the spy this way.
Since you don't have a lot of hints,
- we will give you another question.
- Okay.
We don't have a lot of hints.
Give us an easy question.
You will learn the ranking...
- of the person of your choice.
- Okay.
We need a hint, so let's do this.
Ten Zodiac.
Let's get this right.
This isn't my room.
This isn't my room. Hold on.
Hold on.
This is my room.
(The owner of the room
got here late.)
You startled me.
Get out.
Why did you enter my room?
You startled me.
I thought I was mistaken.
(He succeeded to tease Suk Jin.)
That was so funny.
It's a very easy question.
(The difficulty level is easy.)
Let's get it right.
What's the 20th letter
of the alphabet?
- What do you mean?
- This really hurts my pride.
Do we need to stoop this low?
What do you mean?
- I, J, K...
- C, D, E, F, G...
(They use fingers.)
(He writes down the letters.)
O, P, Q, R...
- You have five seconds.
- Hold on.
- Five, four,
- No! Hold on!
- three,
- You have to know this.
two, one. Raise the board.
Raise the board.
(Everyone submits the answer.)
Not everyone answered correctly.
- What?
- Really?
(They failed to answer correctly.)
- Hey.
- Who is it?
- It's T.
(Suk Jin, Jong Kook,
and Se Chan got T.)
T. Did you get it wrong?
I changed my answer from T to Y.
- It's him.
- Y?
Oh, 5 times 4 is 20.
- Five times 4 is 20.
- It's T.
Hey, 5 times 4 is 20.
I changed my answer from T to Y.
- Isn't it W?
- What is he talking about?
- W.
- Jae Suk.
- Five times 4 is 20.
- It's T.
(Confused)
- A, B, C, D, E, F, G,
- I changed my answer from T to Y.
H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P, Q,
R, S, T.
How could you get it wrong?
How did you get W?
A, B, C, D, E, F, G
- H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P
- Hold on.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G,
- H, I, J, K, L, M, N,
- L, M, N,
- O, P, Q, R, S, T.
- Did you get it wrong?
- The 20th letter.
- Jae Suk.
- I messed up since I sang it.
- A, B, C, D, E, F, G
- I wrote T down.
- H, I, J, K
- What's wrong with him?
- A, B, C, D, E, F
- Why did you count like that?
- How was I supposed to count?
A, B, C, D, E, F, G
You should count like that.
- A, B, C, D, E, F, G
- For goodness' sake.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G
H, I, J, K, L, M, N
- Give us another chance.
We have no idea.
It just got more confusing.
- A, B, C, D, E, F, G
- For goodness' sake.
- It's strange that Haha ate meat...
- Who counts like that?
in the morning.
- It's Haha.
- It's strange.
- It makes no sense...
- It's Haha.
- that you got it wrong.
- He had T at first. I heard it.
- It's Haha.
- This is how I messed up.
- It makes no sense.
Five times 4 is 20. For a second,
I thought I needed another line.
I thought I had four lines.
I swear.
"Ten Zodiac" was suspicious too.
It makes no sense
that he failed to get T.
- I am the worst Empty Head.
- It's Haha.
It makes no sense.
- How did this happen?
The production crew
was trying to give us a hint.
- Seriously.
- They were spoonfeeding us.
Now, the race is over.
- But...
- Just take a wild guess.
It's time to apprehend the spy.
Please spread out
and vote for the suspicious member.
I will give you the ballot.
Did Se Chan eat?
I ate once.
- Did you eat once?
- Yes. I had beef jeon.
Why is no one suspecting Se Chan?
Who? I am not the spy.
- Come here.
- I am not the spy.
His name never came up.
The innocent ones are gathered here.
- I am not the spy.
- He isn't making deductions.
- I swear I am not the spy.
- He isn't even trying.
- He always denies it.
- You aren't the spy, are you?
- Suk Jin.
- Ji Hyo, why are you smiling?
I turned in my ballot already.
Why did she come out smiling?
Ji Hyo is so suspicious too.
- I am not the spy.
- I turned it in.
- Haha.
- She came out smiling.
- I swear I am not the spy.
- No.
- Jong Kook, I am not the spy.
I suddenly had this thought.
It's about
the production crew's intention.
- Today, we had questions.
- Yes.
They couldn't have chosen someone...
- who is good at a quiz.
- That's right.
- Haha is very fitting.
He is right in the middle.
- "Ten Zodiac" was too much.
- I know.
Think of Haha's style.
Haha would've eaten
to hide that he's a spy.
- Of course.
- That's Haha.
I know. It bothers me
that he had the first meal.
- That's why I'm sure it's Haha.
- This feels strange.
You think it's me when I'm not,
so I want to keep acting.
Is it Ji Hyo
who hasn't eaten at all?
- Yes.
- Ji Hyo didn't eat.
- And Jong Kook.
- I ate.
- Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
- I didn't eat either.
But think of her character.
If she was a spy,
she wouldn't eat at all.
She wouldn't write her name.
- She'd give it to others?
- Yes.
- I would've eaten the last one.
- If Haha was a spy...
You know he's sly.
- I would've eaten the last one.
- He would've eaten the first one.
A lot of us are quite sly.
Who's not sly here?
- You're also sly.
- This is a variety show.
- Isn't your nickname Sly Ji?
- We all are sly.
- That's who we are.
- You're right.
- You keep pointing me out.
- This is confusing.
But I think one of those who keep
pointing me out is a spy.
You say things like that
when you're a spy.
- He's always like that.
- No. I never said this before.
- Yes, you did.
- Get a grip.
Before I take off your glasses
and slap you in the face.
I think it's you.
- Listen.
- I said no. This is crazy.
- I'm sure that's him.
- No.
- Seriously, I'm not a spy.
- The shadow.
- His answer was so disappointing.
- Right.
If we were a spy,
it would be too obvious.
- He's just in the middle.
- I can't even say his answer.
- Hang on.
- This is so upsetting.
(Jae Suk finds out something.)
It's Haha.
- You.
- It's not those three empty heads.
(Jae Suk approaches Se Chan.)
No. I'm telling you it's not me.
Why are you blushing?
- No, I'm not.
- Look at me.
I'm not a spy. I'm serious.
- It's Se Chan.
- Se Chan, why are you blushing?
I'm telling you. It's not me.
Why can't Se Chan be a spy?
Do you remember
when we did "Heungboojeon?"
- No, it's not me.
- I remember.
- Se Chan was...
- Seriously, I'm not a spy.
- It must be Haha.
- Why are you blushing?
(Running Man, Episode 613)
(Hang on.)
(Jae Suk saw Se Chan's face
and identified him as a spy.)
(Jae Suk suddenly changed
his choice and suspected Se Chan.)
(And Se Chan was the real spy.)
(Jae Suk showed his remarkable
powers of observation.)
- Seriously, it's not me. It's Haha.
- How many times did you eat?
- Why are you blushing?
- Once.
- Why is your face red?
- Look at his face.
What did you eat?
Touch my hand. It's so white, right?
- Come here.
- I'm not nervous at all. Look.
- Right.
- Look. I'm not sweating.
No. He's sweating a lot.
He's sweating even more.
- It's so damp.
- It's just that...
- he's not feeling well.
- I'm not a spy.
I'm telling you it's not me.
- No one was suspicious of Se Chan.
- This is serious.
Because I'm not a spy.
Because Se Chan...
- There was nothing I could do.
- He tried his best.
- It's not me.
- He did try hard...
- for the song quizzes.
- Right.
- Dong Hoon.
- It's not me.
- Haha...
- I give you five seconds.
- What do we do?
- I should go with Haha.
(The final voting begins.)
- Haha? Really?
- I think it's Haha.
- Because...
- Se Chan got the quizzes right.
I got all the questions right.
Your answer was really suspicious.
But this is...
I don't know.
There's nothing we can do.
If I get it wrong again,
that means I don't know you guys.
I'll feel betrayed.
Gosh, the real spy
must be really thrilled now.
- The results are in.
- This is crazy.
- Okay.
- I don't know.
Haha got five votes,
- and he's chosen as a spy.
- My goodness.
- We had no choice.
- I'm sorry, Haha.
Ji Hyo got the other two votes.
- Okay.
- It can't be helped.
First, Haha, bring your mission bag.
I'm not a spy.
It must be filled with gems.
Haha is chosen as a spy.
(Haha is chosen as the spy suspect.)
Open your bag as I count to three
and reveal your identity.
- I hope it's him.
- I'm not sure though.
- I hope he's the spy.
- I don't know.
- I have no idea.
- The spy's bag says spy on it.
- Really?
- Does it say that?
(The spy's bag has
the spy's name tag on it.)
- What about gems?
- Please.
(Please.)
- One.
- I bet he has many gems.
- Please.
Two.
(Haha gave a lot of wrong answers.)
(What's Haha's identity?)
- I bet he has many gems.
- Please.
Two.
Three.
(Revealing his identity)
No?
Was it that obvious?
(Was it that obvious?)
No?
(There's no name tag?)
He has no gems?
(Haha isn't the spy.)
- He has a lot.
- A lot?
He has a few, but that's not a lot.
You should've insisted
that you weren't a spy.
Why did you...
You should've insisted
that you weren't a spy.
(Flustered)
- This is driving me crazy.
- Hey.
- Haha.
- You should've insisted harder.
I'm sorry,
but I knew it wasn't Haha.
Hey, why were you alone there...
when we were discussing?
- I said it wasn't him.
- Haha.
Didn't I tell you?
What was "Ten Zodiac" for?
- What was that?
- I racked my brains...
to come up with that.
- Seriously...
- You failed to catch the spy.
- Today's spy was...
- Who is it?
(Today's real spy is...)
- Yang Se Chan.
- Yes!
I told you so.
- I saw his face.
- Bang!
- Yang Se Chan.
- Yes!
(I saw his face)
(I told you so.)
(Jae Suk almost caught the spy
again by looking at the face.)
- It was Yang Se Chan.
- Hang on.
(Se Chan managed to clear
himself of suspicion.)
I'm out of breath.
(When he got the gems
at the beginning of the race...)
(Yang Se Chan, you are a spy
with 0 gems.)
(If you make the top 3 without
getting caught, you win.)
(This is how
Spy Yang Se Chan survived.)
(1. He didn't send in gems
to make the questions difficult.)
(Relieved)
(2. He doubted the other members
whenever he had a chance.)
(3. He let So Min eat 3 times
so the suspicion fell on her.)
(But Spy Yang faced a crisis.)
(1st crisis:
Haha's chase after gems)
(He answered nonchalantly.)
(Shaky eyes)
- You...
- It's not the three empty heads.
(2nd crisis: Jae Suk's
facial expression analysis)
(He strongly denied it
and escaped the crisis.)
- Yes!
- I saw his face.
I don't think
I can eat for ten days.
- You know what?
- I was so nervous.
- I saw his face from the back.
- Okay.
I saw Se Chan's expression again.
I'm sorry, but I told you.
- But the voting...
- Why did you not suspect him?
- You should've said that.
- I said that about everyone.
I said he was suspicious.
They always say they knew it
after it was over.
- He just...
- Look at him.
This is what he does.
- He suspects everyone.
- He does.
- We didn't choose the spy.
- Who did?
- You distributed the gems, right?
- Yes.
- How many did I get?
- The member...
who got the fewest gems...
- was the spy.
- Who gave gems to me?
And Se Chan got nothing.
No one? So...
- No one?
- When Jong Kook asked,
"Who did you give it to?"
I was afraid everyone would be quiet
when he asked about me.
I was terrified at the moment.
You tell me. Why did you
give me three meals?
- What?
- Three meals.
To make them suspect you.
Isn't that because you like me?
- So the suspicion falls on you.
- She just likes it.
She just likes
that he took care of her.
- Gosh.
- That was perfect timing.
- Jae Suk got ramyeon.
- The one with the fewest gems...
- So he should make the top three.
- That's the mission.
- You were number six.
- So...
I will tell you the final ranking.
- Number seven is Suk Jin.
- What?
You have two gems.
That's cute.
- That doesn't matter.
- Number six is Jae Suk.
- You have four gems.
- Gosh.
Number five is Haha.
You have six gems.
Ji Hyo and So Min have...
- seven gems each.
- Is Jong Kook number one?
- Number two is Jong Kook.
- I'm second place?
- You have eight gems. Number one...
- You have a lot.
- How many do I have?
- is Se Chan with 16 gems.
From 0 to 16 gems. That's amazing.
So everyone except
Se Chan and Jong Kook...
- will get the penalty.
- Yes!
- Jong Kook! This is great.
- Great.
This isn't so bad.
- This is nice. Okay.
- Okay.
- This isn't so bad.
- This is great.
I'm so happy Jong Kook
didn't suspect me today.
Here's today's penalty.
You'll be locked up in your rooms...
until you give the right answer
to the quizzes we give you.
Can't we go home
before we get it right?
That's just...
I'd rather get slapped with water.
- That would be better.
- I'm sorry,
but let me go home before nine.
- The penalty isn't so bad.
- I need to put my kids to sleep.
This is too harsh for the members.
You will need more questions.
What you have is not enough.
Bye, Jong Kook. Bye, Haha.
I'll stay and hear
the first two questions.
Hey, So Min.
- So Min.
- My gosh.
- Who is it?
- So Min.
- Yes?
- Jae Suk.
Please help us.
Here's the question.
Is that Se Chan?
It is a request to not publish...
information or news...
until a certain period of time.
- What is it called?
- What did you say?
So Min, give your answer.
- What? A halt?
- What?
We have two members
who gave the correct answer.
Yoo Jae Suk and Ji Suk Jin.
Come on out.
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin
are the first ones to escape.)
I'll give you the question.
He's famous for his speech
that starts, "I have a dream."
He won the Nobel Peace Prize
in 1964.
Who is he?
The answer is...
(Martin Luther King)
I don't know.
(To So Min, "I have a dream" is
the lyrics of "Goose's Dream.")
I have no idea.
Haha can go home.
What's the process where a plant
produces food with light?
You should know this one.
- This is the next question.
- The next one.
I'll give you an easy question.
This is an easy one.
I'll give you another one.
This is easy.
It lives in the sea.
(It lives in the sea.)
In an emergency, it ejects
black ink and runs away.
It has eight legs. What is it?
- Correct.
- Pass.
- Let's go home.
- Go home.
(One rainy day in Seoul)
(The members go out on the streets.)
(Feeling all excited,)
(they will wander
around the city all day.)
(For this pleasant trip,)
(there's one rule.)
All right. Who should I ask?
There's someone. Hang on.
I'm too nervous to ask.
(What's the most famous thing
on Mount Nam?)
(The locks?)
(The locks? Okay.)
Hello.
(What's the most famous thing
on Mount Nam?)
(The locks.)
(It's the locks again.)
What's the most famous thing?
(They keep asking,)
(but the answer doesn't change.)
- Please let me ask you a question.
- Excuse me.
(What's the answer
that they want to hear...)
(after asking over and over again?)
(A Walk Around
the Famous Neighborhood)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)