(March 14, White Day)
(The shoot began
on the warm White Day.)
Hello.
- Please slate once.
- Okay.
So Min is injured, so I'll do it.
Instead of So Min. One, two, three.
So Min...
So Min put the cast back on.
She got it off too soon.
- And she was being too frivolous.
- Right.
- On her little toe,
- I knew this would happen.
- a small crack was found.
- Really?
It opened up again.
It was my first time
breaking a bone.
You should stop when you feel pain.
You were right about that
I shouldn't go into rehab...
- when it hurts.
- Exactly.
- You should stop.
- Right.
So Min can't wait...
to run around again.
She's frustrated...
- because she can't.
- You should get some rest.
- She wants to dance.
- I really want to dance.
Dance with only one leg.
- Stop it.
- What do I do?
- That's enough.
(Playful)
- Dance with your upper body.
- A situation like this...
- I want to dance.
- Dance with your upper body.
You shouldn't be like this.
- You want to do things like this.
- I really want to do it.
This is driving me crazy.
- Stop it.
- Don't do that.
- Hey.
You might hurt your leg again.
Enough. Stop it.
- So Min.
- Just leave her be.
You're not young enough
to heal right away.
She's an aunt.
- Right.
- An aunt talking about blood types.
Aunt So Min, stop it.
By the way, Ji Hyo has been...
- posting a lot of photos.
- They are really cool.
- Who took them?
- Who took those photos?
- You care about your social media.
- What's with you?
- I'm curious.
- What's gotten into you?
Recently, people say...
- That looks really cool.
- that I look like an old lady.
- What are you talking about?
- That's not true.
- No way.
- So I wanted to try a new style.
- I see.
- So I'm trying.
Did someone tell you how to pose?
Yes.
- Really?
- They nagged me a lot.
- That's nice.
- They came up with some ideas?
- Did they tell you what to do?
- Who did that?
- It looks so natural.
- So did you...
- hire someone?
- No.
It's just that my staff
told me what to do.
- They taught me how to pose.
- I see.
I can see that.
- They are pretty.
- She looks different now.
- They are going viral.
- I'm working hard.
So they are not
from your daily life.
She's trying new things.
But you shouldn't be too contrived
on your social media.
It should show your life as it is.
- You can't make things up.
- You think it's artificial.
That's what people do
on social media these days.
- Is that what they do?
- That's what young people do.
You always take photos
in a shirt with wide armholes.
- Showing his nipples.
- Nipples...
- Photos of his nipples.
- I'm just the same.
- You take photos of your nipples.
- Photos of his nipples.
What are you talking about?
It's not like I show
my nipples on purpose.
But I can see your nipples.
- My nipples...
- It can happen.
It's not like...
When people take photos of me...
- This is what you do.
- They just come out.
Why would I do this?
A nipple shot.
- He's strange.
- Don't you do this a lot?
- I don't.
- You don't?
- That's not what I do.
- It's not?
Of course.
- Gosh.
- A nipple shot?
A nipple shot?
- That's funny.
- He likes it.
- It's hilarious.
- Suk Jin likes it.
It sounds funny. A nipple shot.
- A nipple shot sounds funny.
- My social media isn't R-rated.
That's nice.
Today, to celebrate spring,
we have invited some actresses...
- who wanted to join our show.
- Oh, dear.
Jae Suk, introduce them one by one.
Before I introduce today's guests...
Last week, BTOB was
supposed to be here.
- Right.
- I know.
They couldn't join us
because of COVID-19.
- It happens a lot these days.
- I know.
I heard something today.
One of our guests for today
tested positive, right?
- Yes.
- Right.
That's what he was going to say.
Why did you bring it up?
Am I not supposed to say that?
Jong Kook, he's the captain.
- Hey, I'm the captain.
- I mean...
I have to attend a meeting
after the shoot today.
- You will go home after this.
- Right.
- But I have to go to Mok-dong.
- I see. It's close.
Jong Kook is Captain Nipple.
Oh, right. You are the captain too.
- Captain Nipple.
- He's Captain Nipple.
I see.
(Imitating Captain Nipple)
- That's just Na Hoon A.
- Really?
That's Na Hoon A.
You take a lot of nipple shots.
(Today's guests who will be
with the two reliable captains)
That's funny.
All right. Let's bring
in the guests for today.
Let me introduce our first guest.
We have Park Ah In.
(The first guest Park Ah In)
(Actress Park Ah In)
- She's famous.
- Her acting is amazing.
(She transforms
into many different characters.)
("Mr. Sunshine", "Descendants
of The Sun", "Sweet Home")
- She's amazing.
- Ah In.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Ah In, nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Welcome.
Ah In, please introduce yourself.
- I'm Actress Park Ah In.
- I see.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- I'm nervous.
- Please tell us about your dramas.
- Okay.
- "Mr. Sunshine"...
- It can wait.
- I'm saying this because...
- I'm sorry.
- We want her to feel comfortable...
- Why are you being bossy?
- I'm not being bossy.
- Be nice.
I just want to get to know her.
If you want to know, just ask me.
I'll tell you about her.
Is it wrong to ask her
about her dramas?
All right. Let me tell you
about her most famous works.
- "Mr. Sunshine".
- I really liked the drama.
She played Go Ae Soon,
Kim Tae Ri's cousin.
The one who gambled.
(She played Go Ae Soon
on "Mr. Sunshine".)
- I get it.
- Do you remember that?
- Of course, I do.
- I know.
- I remember.
- You're her.
- And "Descendants of The Sun".
- On "Descendants of The Sun",
she played a chest surgeon
from a rich family.
- "Descendants of The Sun".
- I remember her.
- The hair...
- I remember that.
- You fought with her.
- Exactly.
- I know.
- She's like a professional woman.
She looks like a city girl.
- You mostly play bad girls, right?
- Yes.
- Mostly mean girls.
- Mean girls.
Right.
It's like...
This is my first time meeting her,
but this is how I feel.
She looks like a chest surgeon
who appears on a morning TV show.
- Right.
- And...
- a lawyer.
- An eloquent lawyer.
- She looks like a lawyer.
- Right.
Even when she stands,
she looks a little like...
Most people look like this,
- but she stands like this.
- That's what professors do.
- She looks like a professor.
- Really?
- Yes.
- A professional woman.
This is Ah In's
first time on Running Man.
I'm really nervous.
- Are you nervous?
- Did you sleep well?
I woke up at around 4 a.m.
- Did you wake up?
- Wake up?
- When did you go to sleep?
- What time did you go to sleep?
Around 9 p.m.
That's early.
- That's early.
- She went to bed early.
- She had a good night's sleep.
- She slept a lot.
She slept more than I did.
- That's when you should wake up.
- She slept more than I did.
You slept for seven hours.
- But you...
- That's when you should wake up.
- It was time to wake up.
- Most people...
sleep seven hours a day.
It's just that you woke up at 4am.
I was worried I wouldn't
be able to sleep.
You don't sound nervous at all.
- You were worried.
- I was nervous.
Do you usually sleep
for like 16 hours?
She says there was a member
of Running Man she wanted to meet.
- Who is it?
- He looks...
like a man I had a crush on
back in college.
Who is it?
- So I'm a huge fan.
- I see.
(They all seem excited
even though they don't show it.)
So... But can I tell you that later?
- When I show my specialty.
- Sure.
- When she shows her specialty.
- Specialty?
And there's someone
you don't want to be on a team with.
- Jong Kook?
- Why?
Why?
(She reveals it right away.)
So it's not Jong Kook.
Jong Kook isn't the one she likes.
- You're not him.
- You're out.
She's not a fan of yours.
- Jong Kook...
- He's her number one choice.
- He's...
- He thought it would be him.
You don't want to be on
a team with me?
No. I think he will be too quiet.
- I see.
- That's not true.
He's really talkative.
- He's like an old woman.
- He talks a lot.
- It's just...
- He talks like an old woman.
She says you seem quiet.
But there's more.
"I think he's too quiet,
so he won't take good care of me."
- That's not true.
- I'm caring.
He doesn't seem so nice and kind.
- He is very kind.
- He is nice and kind.
- But he's...
- Bo Pil.
Make me look good.
What did you do with my image?
(He's a victim
of the thug-like image.)
- You should change the BGM.
- Jong Kook has...
an image of obstinacy.
- That's surprising.
- Obstinacy.
- It is surprising.
- I thought it would be him.
You know that? I made
three guests into stars.
- My goodness.
- Stop saying that.
I made them stars.
- That's what I did.
- Seriously.
- You should be a star yourself.
- That's ridiculous.
- What are they doing now?
- Sa Rok is...
- Sa Rok?
- It's Sae Rok.
Right, Sae Rok.
- What's her family name?
- Just stay still.
- I thought he was...
- I had no idea who it was.
- I didn't know what he was saying.
- What's Sa Rok?
- Who's Sa Rok?
- Is it a dog's name?
Look. I have the big picture.
- This is how I introduce her name.
- What's her family name?
- Eun Sae Rok?
- Eun Sae Rok.
You're getting
a lot of comments now.
They say you should try
to make yourself known.
(They say you should try
to make yourself known.)
(Laughing)
Chan Hee is laughing.
- Sae Rok, are you doing well?
- He likes it.
- He likes jokes like this.
- Sae Rok.
All right.
- I made a few guests into stars.
- And...
Ah In will...
After a little while...
- When all the guests are here,
- I'm curious.
she will show us her specialty.
- All right.
- She prepared something.
Thank you.
Let me introduce our next guest.
She is Kim Hee Jung.
(The second guest Kim Hee Jung)
- Oh, dear.
- All right.
She's Hee Jung.
(In the drama "Tough Guy's Love",
she played Won Bin's niece Ggok Ji.)
(She was a talented child actress.)
(She has grown
into an excellent actress.)
(She's now a key player for
FC Wonder Women on "Shooting Stars".)
- Nice to meet you.
- Welcome.
(Nice to meet you.)
- Hey.
- I'm so nervous.
(I'm so nervous.)
- Nice to meet you. What's wrong?
- Hello.
I worked out too hard,
so my legs are...
Hello.
She says she worked out too hard.
She can't walk well.
- Hello.
- She plays soccer.
- That's right.
- Really?
On "Shooting Stars".
Let me introduce her.
It's been 23 years since her debut.
- Did you say 23 years?
- She's a big senior.
Her famous work is
the KBS drama "Tough Guy's Love".
When she was young...
I know the drama.
"Tough Guy's Love".
I thought
you were talking about him.
- No, I'm Nipples.
- Nipples.
I'm Nipples.
And she's "Tough Guy's Love".
- He's Kim Nipple.
- I'm...
- Stop it. That's enough.
- Kim Nipple?
Enough is enough.
- Nipple Instagram.
- Kim Nipple.
Don't you have something
to do with it?
It's just that I have low nipples.
- Low nipples.
He has low nipples.
He's Kim Nipple,
and he's Low Nipple.
- Low Nipple.
- Low Nipple and he's...
(They are becoming one
when talking about nipples.)
We are talking
too much about nipples.
(All they've talked
about is nipples.)
So Min likes it.
I like that.
So Min...
looked like this.
- Low Nipple.
- So Min likes that.
All right. We have Hee Jung here.
She used to be in a dance crew
with Honey J.
- She's a great dancer.
- She dances so well.
- She's amazing.
- I want to see her dance.
I thought she would be...
- a good dancer for some reason.
- You did?
Have you ever met us
when you were on the dance team?
- Yes.
- I did.
- Did you?
- When I was on the dance team?
- Yes. When you were a dancer.
- And did you see us, Ah In?
(Did Ah In see us?)
I saw you when you
performed with a dance team.
I was talking about Hee Jung.
It's all right.
- What's with you, Professor Park?
- I didn't know.
I guess Professor Park
is half asleep.
- She didn't get enough sleep.
- I thought...
she used to be a dancer.
I will stay quiet.
She's just trying
to join the conversation.
- I didn't understand what you said.
- Today,
Hee Jung is dressed...
like a dancer.
- Like the captain of a dance crew.
- Like a girls' hip hop dancer.
- She has that vibe.
- Just like a girls' hip hop dancer.
- She's here to show off her dance.
- Great.
- We'll see her dance later.
- I'm excited.
- I can't wait.
- Our today's guests are amazing.
- They'll show off their talents.
- I'm excited to see it.
She must be amazing since she
used to be a member of a dance crew.
- Now, let's meet the last guest.
- Okay.
- Next up is Roh Jeong Eui.
- All right!
She starred in "Our Beloved Summer".
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Oh, my.
- Welcome.
- I saw her in the drama.
- Oh, my.
- "Our Beloved Summer".
I just wanted to know what you were
doing since you ignored my calls.
(Jeong Eui played a bold idol star
in the drama "Our Beloved Summer".)
I was going to stay
just for five more minutes.
I have to be on a live music show
shortly.
(She made a strong impression
through her confident character.)
(The rising star, Roh Jeong Eui)
I could eat you alive.
- She's a great actress.
- Jeong Eui, welcome.
- Hello.
(Jeong Eui came out
with something in her hand.)
- Hello.
- Is today White Day?
- Yes, it is.
- I brought something for everyone.
- A woman gives a man chocolate.
- March 14.
- It's a White Day gift.
- Oh, my. Thank you.
- Here you go.
- Thank you so much.
- I got you one too, So Min.
- Thank you.
Does a woman give a man chocolates
or vice versa?
- A man gives a woman chocolates.
- A man does on this day.
- Here you go.
- Thank you for this, Jeong Eui.
Let me tell you something
about Jeong Eui.
Jeong Eui said...
- that she was a Running Man kid,
- Right.
- and she liked the show so much...
- Yes.
- that she even dreamed about it.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Is that true?
I had a dream where I came on
the show three times.
- Oh, my.
- Do you remember the details?
In those dreams,
I was chased by the members.
- I'm sure she was chased by me.
- Many people have such a dream.
- Mostly, they're chased by me.
- Yes.
Many people even wet themselves
while being chased by him.
- So we had to pause for a while.
- That's right.
It's a true story.
Did you really have
that kind of dream?
- Yes. I've been a huge fan...
- That's understandable.
- Right.
- since I was in elementary school.
- I'm grateful. You grew up well.
- Indeed.
We've met all of our guests
including Jeong Eui.
As I said earlier, the three guests
prepared something to show us.
- They prepared it for Running Man.
- Yes.
- That's so exciting.
- Really?
- Ah In, Hee Jung,
- I'm excited.
- and Jeong Eui.
- Yes.
They'll show off their talents
1 by 1. Ah In said earlier...
that she'd let us know
which member she wanted to...
- team up with while performing.
- That's right.
- Are you ready?
- Yes, I'm ready.
- Good. Ah In will perform first.
- Okay.
- Let me just put on a skirt.
- Sure.
- She watched "X-Man" as a kid.
- Probably.
- I'll put it on quickly.
- She brought a sword. Oh, my.
Will she cut the person she wants
as a teammate with that sword?
- Hold on.
- Could she stab that person?
- That person must be the one.
- I guess so.
- Now...
- Oh, my.
- Ah In is...
- She looks like a pro dancer in it.
- Now...
- I'm not so good at it.
- Ah In will perform a dance for us.
- Yes. I'll just...
- I'll do my best.
- Let's give Ah In...
- a big round of applause.
- Yes!
(Professor Park will perform
a sword dance.)
- She looks charismatic.
- She's amazing.
- I'm impressed.
- That's incredible. Oh, I'm sorry.
- She picked up the sword.
I can feel it.
Will you slash the person's neck?
My, she's amazing.
(Ah In caught Haha off guard.)
- It must be him.
- Haha?
- I think it's Haha.
- It must be Haha.
I can tell she has
a lot of experience. She's amazing.
- She's pointing at Se Chan.
- She's pointing at him.
- She startled me.
- Is it Se Chan?
(Who could be the man?)
Is it me?
It's Suk Jin.
- It's Suk Jin.
- Me?
No, that can't be.
I don't believe it.
No.
That can't be true.
- It's Suk Jin.
- Is it really me?
- There's no way.
- She picked Seok Sam.
Is it really me?
- This is the 1st time in 10 years.
- No!
(It's so hard to believe
that she picked Seok Sam.)
- My gosh. I'm so grateful to her.
- Hold on.
- That can't be true.
- That was unexpected.
- Thank you so much, Ah In.
- Isn't it the 1st time in 10 years?
I think the whole part should be
edited out.
- He...
- No. Hey.
- I'm a huge fan of his.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I'm flattered.
- I love his TikTok videos too.
Oh, my videos?
(Surprisingly, his TikTok videos
made him popular.)
- TikTok Grandpa.
- Oh, I see.
- She's a fan of TikTok Grandpa's.
- She likes my TikTok videos?
- Also, he's always calm and steady.
- That's unexpected.
- I like a calm and steady person.
- Oh, I see.
- His nickname is Petty.
- I'm always calm.
- We call him Petty.
- Yes, we call him Petty.
When I'm with someone who's
so funny and extremely energetic,
- I get a little daunted.
- You feel pressured.
- I make others comfortable.
- Indeed.
- I really want to team up with you.
- That's great.
- I understand. Okay.
- I mean it.
- It turns out...
- I'm a big fan of yours.
- Thank you.
- that Ah In likes TikTok Grandpa...
also known as Petty...
- There are hidden fans like me.
- Exactly.
- I know, right?
- Yes.
- I'll do my best.
- Okay.
- That's great.
- I guess he has many shy fans.
- Exactly. I'm a shy person.
- I see.
- True.
- I don't tell others I'm his fan.
- It's embarrassing to tell others.
- Yes.
- So...
- He's my favorite celebrity.
- Why is it embarrassing?
- He's her favorite celebrity.
Like a secret you can tell...
- no one else but your best friend.
- Exactly.
- I know what that means.
- You think you might get teased.
You can't talk about it
when there are more than two people.
- That's right.
- But I keep being drawn to him.
But you can't help but
be drawn to him.
- He keeps drawing my attention.
- Yes.
- And I feel protective of him.
- Exactly.
- That's right.
While everyone else is talking about
top stars,
- you want to mention Suk Jin.
- That's right.
- But you can't.
- I know what that feels like.
- They might think...
- "Can I talk about him?"
- "Would they think I'm weird?"
- Right.
- "They could."
- Of course.
- Why?
- Stop it.
- Enough is enough.
- What's wrong?
- Hey, I do have pride.
- What's the matter?
You've all contemplated being
Suk Jin's fan at least once, right?
- Gosh. Stop it already.
- Wait.
- That's enough.
- You don't have to hide it anymore.
They all will
come out of the closet.
- You don't have to hide it anymore.
- Don't be shy.
- Don't be embarrassed.
- You can say that you like me.
When you meet your whole family
on a national holiday,
ask everyone, "Is it okay
for me to be Ji Suk Jin's fan?"
(Ask your family, "Is it okay
for me to be Ji Suk Jin's fan?")
(Ji Suk Jin Challenge)
- He looks happy.
- It takes great courage.
- I didn't know he was like that.
- That's not true.
- Great. Next, following Ah In,
- Yes.
Hee Jung will perform a dance.
(Following Ah In,
Hee Jung will perform a dance.)
(She begins
while showing off her groove.)
- She has a good groove.
- She's great.
She's amazing.
She has such a good groove.
- She won't start right away.
- Right.
Let's go!
She's good.
(The former dance crew member's
stunning girls' hip hop dance)
She's incredible.
(Cheering)
(So she finished her sexy
girls' hip hop dance performance.)
- You should form a girl group.
- I agree.
Jeong Eui wants to dance too.
Let's see Ah In's dance first.
(Sorry, coming through.)
- She startled me.
- She's amazing.
Go, Professor Park!
- I love you, Professor Park!
- That's impressive.
(She looks like a professor
who joined her students on a trip.)
- Professor Park.
- She's a great dancer.
- She's really good at dancing.
- She looks so serious.
- But her dance is a little strange.
- She's great.
- Way to go!
- That was amazing.
(Cheering and shouting)
(Are they shouting, "School"?)
- Boombastic!
- That was amazing.
(Loud)
Hey, that song was popular
a long time ago.
I got carried away.
- Hey.
- I want to stand next to you.
- What was that?
- I got too excited.
Let's let them dance again.
- Jeong Eui doesn't just dance...
- That was amazing.
as well as an idol star,
but also can make an idol face.
- She looks so bubbly.
- Indeed.
The dimples on her cheeks...
- Like an ending fairy.
- I want to see her ending face.
Can you show us your ending pose?
- The pose at the end.
- Something like this.
- In a close-up shot at the end.
- Okay.
- Hold it for about three seconds.
- One, two, three.
- One.
- She looks a bit awkward.
- Two.
- She's not an idol singer.
- I can see that.
- She's never performed on stage.
- Exactly.
- You asked her to do it.
- She's definitely not an idol star.
- She's not desperate for this.
- Exactly.
- She doesn't have to be.
- Her acting career matters more.
Those who are desperate to be
on variety shows would do this.
So Min, can you show us?
- That's a good idea.
- Let's let So Min try it.
- Try it.
- So Min, show us.
- Which camera should I see?
- She's desperate.
- That one.
- Chan Hee's camera.
- Ready, go.
- Go.
- That's not what an idol would do.
- I want to team up with her.
- You should control your breathing.
- What kind of idol would do that?
- That was too much.
- Hey.
- My gosh.
- You looked scary.
Exactly.
- Ji Hyo, do you want to try it?
- Ji Hyo will do it well.
- Good.
- Which camera should I see?
- Ji Hyo, that's good.
- Good.
- She might fall asleep.
- That's right.
(Breathing heavily)
- Why are you breathing like that?
- Why would you...
- Why?
- She did her best.
- I saw them breathing like that.
- Right.
- Did you just finish jogging?
- We're all quite old.
We're all just like Rain.
Did you just finish jogging?
We're all old-fashioned.
Let's give the three guests
a round of applause.
(Ah In, Jeong Eui, and Hee Jung will
join us for the race.)
- Thank you so much.
- You all did a great job.
Today, with the three actresses
who look great in spring...
and like Running Man,
we'll have the Not Spring, Candy
or Penalty race.
To celebrate White Day,
we planned a couple race.
In every mission, you'll pair up
with the opposite gender.
- I see.
Since it's White Day,
after each mission ends,
the male members can pick
one female member...
- to give a candy.
- I see.
The girls won't know who gave who.
Those who didn't get any candies...
- will get one penalty ball.
- What?
- Oh, really?
- A penalty ball?
The girls who didn't get
any candies.
The female member who gets
the least penalty balls will win...
and receive a prize.
The female member with the most
penalty balls will get a penalty.
Meanwhile, the female members can
exchange the candies they got...
with ballots at the end of the race.
They will use the ballots
for the male member popularity poll.
The first place will get a prize,
and the last place will get
a penalty.
The winner of each mission will get
a benefit for the popularity poll,
so you should do your best
to win each mission.
(They need to win the opposite
gender over to win the race.)
Before we begin the race,
I'd like to tell you about the rule
that Captain Ji suggested.
- Really?
- Yes.
- They might be a little shy.
- True.
- So let's add a funny element.
- Okay.
One of the male members will
act as a female member.
And one of the female members will
act as a male member.
Which ones?
You can do it.
No. I won't do it.
- I'm...
- You'd look good though.
I can't do it
because I look like a tough guy.
I'm considering Jong Kook
and Jae Suk.
But I think Jae Suk would enjoy it
more than Jong Kook would.
Which of Ji Hyo and So Min should
dress as a man?
Ji Hyo would look better
when dressed as a man,
but it'd be funnier
if So Min did it.
- Let's pick So Min.
- She has never done it before.
- She hasn't.
- Right.
So today, Jae Suk,
your name is Jenny.
- No wonder why it says "Jenny".
- Oh, I see.
- So Min, you're Jeon So Bal.
- So Bal?
- So Bal.
- Oh, I see.
- Yes.
That's why.
Please put on your wigs.
- Pick a wig.
- I have to wear a wig?
- It's Suk Jin's idea, right?
- Ji Hyo, I'll be a man.
- The lady from "Snowpiercer."
- "Snowpiercer?"
- "Snowpiercer." I'm a big fan.
He does look like Tilda Swinton.
- Exactly.
- "No."
- He really looks like her.
- As if it were intentional...
He reminds me of
the movie "Get Out."
Noh Joo Hyun is here.
(Noh Joo Hyun is here.)
"Why Can't We Stop Them."
(So Bal looks like a handsome man
in his 40s.)
- Mr. Noh.
- You look handsome.
- Mr. Noh Joo Hyun.
- You look really handsome.
The game you'll play to choose...
your partner
for the first mission is...
The Same Mole We Have.
- "The same mole"?
- The girls will...
- be in a different room.
- Okay.
- The guys will pick a nickname,
- Yes.
and draw a mole
on one another's face.
After that,
we'll draw the same mole on a board.
The girls will choose their partners
based on the shapes of the moles.
(The girls will pick their partners
based on the moles and nicknames.)
And the girls should draw
the same moles on their faces.
- Really?
- Yes.
- The girls will go upstairs now.
- Of course.
- Got it.
- Okay.
Jenny is going upstairs.
- Yes.
- Jenny.
Where should I draw the mole?
Who should be my partner?
Among the cast members
of Running Man,
there's no one
that I want to pair up with.
Do you want to pair up
with Jong Kook?
- Me? Anyone but Suk Jin.
- Yes.
- Anyone but Suk Jin would be fine.
- Right.
Then we can just let Ah In
pair up with him.
- That sounds great.
- Suk Jin and...
If you really pick him
only by seeing the mole...
- Then we're destined to pair up.
- Exactly.
What's taking them so long?
Well...
Jenny can't stop checking herself
in the mirror. Is that okay?
(The adolescent girl
who loves herself too much)
- Jenny... Oh, gosh.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Jenny has such a small forehead.
She has a small forehead.
Your forehead...
- Why?
- It's too small.
- Her forehead is too small.
Having a small forehead isn't
a big deal.
I cut the fringe intentionally.
- But your forehead...
- Worry about your foreheads.
Mind your own business.
- I have a nasty temper.
- Do you?
Did you all appear on the show
"The Mate"?
- Hey, how about we have a sauna?
- Yes?
- No. What are you talking about?
- Hey.
Let's have a sauna together
after the shoot.
- Are you sure?
- Let's play soccer too.
Come on. Oh, man.
So Bal is so funny.
(Her role is an ordinary man,
but she acts like a thug.)
- Everyone.
- Yes.
- First, pick a nickname...
that the girls can't assume
to be yours easily.
- What should I pick?
- Pick your nickname.
I pick...
(I pick...)
Eric.
I...
I'll be Brad Pitt.
- Brad Pitt?
- Brad Pitt.
My nickname is Superpower.
Superpower?
I'll be Hamster.
- But that's obvious.
- What about you, Jong Kook?
What should I pick?
You should be Nipple.
- Nipple?
- That'd be too obvious.
- How about Jjujju?
- What?
Jjujju? That would be obvious too.
Should I pick that one?
- No. It's irrelevant.
- How about Secret Jjujju?
Secret Jjujju.
- Secret Jjujju sounds perfect.
- Secret Jjujju.
- Okay. I'm Secret Jjujju.
- That sounds good.
- My nickname is Secret Jjujju.
- Secret Jjujju.
Secret Jjujju.
- I can do this all day.
- That's okay.
(They start drawing a mole
without hesitating.)
- It's easier to use this way.
- Yes.
- You should press it down.
- It's smoother on the side.
I play a sad character.
(I play a sad character.)
(They just have to draw a mole,
but they're being creative.)
Suk Jin, I think you should
make it darker.
Se Chan, don't you think
that's too much?
I'm done.
I have it all over my nose.
- I drew along my lip line too.
- That's...
Hey, no one will choose you.
(Cocky)
Hey, your nickname Superpower
suits you.
(With the mustache,
Superpower So Bal acts arrogantly.)
- If you were a man,
- But men wouldn't act like that.
I bet you would be such a womanizer.
- Every woman would fall for me.
- Right?
She wouldn't be as popular
if she were a man.
Brother, come on.
(Brother, come on.)
Why are you acting like a thug?
- Don't all men act like this?
- Not all men...
- act like that.
- Why do you keep moving your mouth?
- She's trying to look like a man.
- She keeps doing that.
- Don't all men do this?
- Are you eating a candy?
- We don't do that.
- What's that?
- Brother.
- We don't do that.
This is what we all do.
Why do you do that?
(What do you do that for?)
- What do you do that for?
- And this too.
Why do you do that?
While sitting down, you stand up
and walk like this. "Let's go."
(Walking awkwardly)
"Wait."
(Only the men can relate to it.
So Bal can't understand it.)
Oh, I get it. You mean, this?
- Like this?
- All men do this.
Hey, stop it.
(She's so eager to imitate them.)
- Am I doing it right?
- All men can relate to it.
(So Bal wants to try everything
that the other guys do.)
(The men picked their nicknames
and drew their moles.)
(Secret Jjujju, Hamster, Eric,
Superpower, Brad Pitt)
The time has come.
My gosh. What's that?
What's that?
- Superpower must be Haha.
- My gosh.
And Hamster must be...
- I think it's Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
Secret Jjujju.
Let me see.
I think that Eric is So Bal.
Brad Pitt must be Se Chan.
Hamster must be Seok Sam.
Secret Jjujju must be Kim Nipple.
(Jenny guessed
only 1 nickname right.)
Me?
(Ah In is the 1st girl
to choose her partner.)
(She desperately hopes to pick
Suk Jin.)
Should I pick an easy one?
It's hard to decide.
There are many shy fans of mine.
(Brad Pitt Suk Jin drew a big mole
on his forehead.)
He looks happy.
- Do you really want Seok Sam?
- Don't change your mind.
Yes, I want to pair up with him.
I think he'll make me comfortable.
Now, we'll meet Brad Pitt's partner.
- Okay.
- Who could that be?
- Did they choose their partners?
- Brad Pitt's partner...
Brad Pitt.
Ah In seemed to like Suk Jin
so much.
- I know, right? Could it be...
- I think...
- Ah In?
- I'm sure she picked you.
- Maybe not. She only saw the mole.
- I'm sure of it.
She must've known which one was you.
I bet she picked you.
Brad Pitt's partner,
please come out.
I hope she picked Suk Jin.
Brad Pitt's partner,
please come out.
(Who is the partner of Suk Jin
who's waiting for his number 1 fan?)
Hey.
(Jenny appears.)
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
- Darn. I'm so unlucky.
- Jenny.
- Jae Suk.
- Ah In...
- Why would you pick me?
- Why?
- We were expecting Ah In.
Why would you pick me?
I guess you guys made it confusing.
- Ah In should've picked him.
- It's not confusing.
It's so obvious that it's Suk Jin.
Why...
- I mean, the nose...
- It's simple.
Why?
Ah In picked the mole on the nose
because she thought it was Suk Jin.
(Ah In thought the mole on the nose
was Suk Jin's.)
- What? She picked Se Chan?
- Really?
Oh, she thought it was a signal.
- I mean... Gosh.
- Oh, she thought it was a signal.
- Why is it Seok Sam?
- Seriously.
Gosh. Why did this happen
on a day like this?
- Why is it Seok Sam?
- I'm so annoyed.
- Why is it you?
- Jae Suk, didn't you know?
- I had no idea.
- I thought it was intentional.
I don't like this.
Hey, are you saying
that Ah In drew this...
- on her nose?
- Oh, no.
- I feel bad for her.
- I thought...
- Just to be my partner?
- Yes.
Ah In drew the same mole
on her nose to pair up with you.
- I feel bad for her.
- I thought...
(Hee Jung appears.)
- What's going on?
- She made a big sacrifice.
- Whose partner is she?
- Poor Ah In.
- Oh, she picked Jong Kook.
- Oh, right.
(She picked Secret Jjujju.)
I picked SJ.
- Right. Thanks.
- SJ.
- SJ, Secret Jjujju.
- That's right.
- The next member is coming out.
- I thought it was him.
(Next, Jeong Eui appears.)
- Oh, gosh. She hit her face on it.
- What happened?
- Are you okay?
- Open your eyes.
Are you okay?
- She drew tears.
- She's crying.
I asked you if you were okay.
(She picked Haha as her partner.)
Jeong Eui.
We thought this one was...
- Se Chan.
- You thought that was me?
- Oh, right. Yes, that's right.
- Right.
- Move backward.
- Thinking that she drew that...
She says that Ah In looks cute
with this mole. I didn't want...
- I'm so upset.
- Ah In must be...
- Poor her.
- Exactly.
(Ah In appears.)
I had no idea she would... Oh, gosh.
I feel so bad for her.
- What a shame. I had no idea.
- Poor her.
- It's okay for a man, but...
- Ah In, I'm so sorry.
- It's too much.
I clearly told Suk Jin...
- that I wanted to pair up with him.
- I know.
- And he agreed to it.
- One, two, three.
- I'm sorry.
(Both said, "I'm sorry.")
- What a shame.
- I'm sorry.
- I thought...
- I asked you to be my partner...
during the break.
Yes, but we didn't discuss
where I should draw a mole.
We all thought it was you.
- Exactly. He drew...
- Exactly.
We all thought it was you
because your nickname is Big Nose.
I know.
I didn't do it intentionally.
- We thought it symbolized Big Nose.
- Exactly.
(Right then, Ji Hyo appears.)
My princess.
- My princess is here.
- She picked Superpower.
- My little princess.
- I'm glad she picked So Bal.
- We didn't know it was her.
- This is great.
- Don't walk up the stairs, So Bal.
- Ji Hyo, you picked me.
I knew it was you.
- My lovely princess.
- Let's move aside a little.
- Gosh. What a shame.
- It's such a shame.
- My princess.
- Gosh, seriously.
I said I would be happy
as long as it wasn't Seok Sam.
(They all found out
who were their partners.)
- Gosh. Look at that.
- What's that?
- Oh, gosh.
- I guess it's a water bomb.
Right. Water will fall.
A water bomb over our heads? Okay.
I guess we'll wear a hat though.
Oh, water will fall on our heads.
I had to leave
while trimming my wig.
- I know.
- Would a man with your face...
be popular with girls?
Of course.
(Of course.)
My little princess.
- A pretty boy.
- Oh, my.
Don't you think she looks so great
in that hairstyle?
- My princess.
- Just like the cartoon character...
I want her to have this hairstyle.
- I told you about the character.
- I mean it.
So Min, you should wear that wig
in real life.
Exactly.
Oh, my.
There comes Jenny.
She's wearing hairpins.
- Who? Jenny?
- You look so pretty,
- Jenny.
- Darn.
He really is ugly, isn't he?
He isn't satisfied
with this situation.
How did you know that?
Are you satisfied
with your partners?
No!
I'm not.
- I'm not even talking to him.
- Unbelievable.
- Don't even call him my partner.
- Can't you see we're sitting apart?
Please be more considerate.
- What?
- Don't be absurd.
How gentler can I be?
No, not you.
- He meant Suk Jin.
- We'll get into it later on.
- Wait and see.
- Jenny's a fierce one, isn't she?
- Of course.
- How scary.
How could I possibly like her?
Anyway, let's begin the first game.
In the first game,
you will see just how sharp
your partner is.
This is Head Smack Detective.
Head Smack Detective?
One team will put on hats...
and sit below the water balloon.
The rest of you
will stand behind them.
Out of those standing in the back,
one team will step forward...
and smack the heads of those seated.
- I see.
- For instance,
let's say that Jenny and Suk Jin
were seated.
Ji Hyo would smack someone...
and then So Bal
would smack the other person.
The couple seated will deliberate
who smacked their heads.
Get it right and you'll swap places.
Get it wrong and the other couple
will earn a point.
It's about telling who hit whom.
We won't know
until we play the game.
Ten minutes after the game begins,
the water balloons will explode.
The couple that gets soaked
will lose three points.
(The couple that gets soaked
will lose three points.)
Who will like to go first?
Maybe Jenny and...
- Us.
- Sure, we'll go first.
Sure thing.
Goodness.
Only one couple
will smack our heads from behind.
- Two in total.
- Right.
You need to guess...
- who hit you.
- We need to get it right.
They need to be able
to know who hit them,
- so put some force behind it.
- Of course.
The hat can go flying, right?
- Okay.
- That's perfectly fine.
You can tell who it is
by how they hit others.
- Everyone has a unique touch.
- That's right.
Let the game begin.
- Do we close our eyes?
- And go.
(The game begins.)
Just so you know,
- So Min can't sit this out.
- No, she can't.
- This...
- Let's trade places.
What on earth?
- No, wait.
- That's not it.
(Jenny gets smacked once.)
(Jenny gets smacked twice.)
- No, wait.
- That's not it.
Sorry, we'll do that again.
(Confusion occurs.)
You should've hit the other person.
You should've hit Suk Jin.
- It wasn't done correctly.
- I heard loud sounds.
- Wait.
- We didn't quite get it.
We didn't quite get the rules.
- How so?
- So Min was supposed to hit you.
- How can you not get this?
- I know who it was.
They didn't quite
understand the rules.
- You got smacked twice, right?
- Right.
She didn't quite
understand the rules.
- Ji Hyo hit you.
- Ji Hyo hit you...
- and So Min hit you too.
- You should hit the other person.
I'll remember
the touch of your hands though.
- Especially you.
- I know it too.
These two.
- I know their touch.
- Do you get the rules now?
- We'll start over.
- So Min, come on.
Let's walk around behind them first.
- Right, let's rotate.
- Not in front of them.
That's a good idea.
Let's confuse them a little.
- I can tell who it is.
- Go!
- Let's wait it out a little.
- Those well-mannered...
- Swoosh!
- You startled me.
- Don't go in front of them.
- I know who's well-mannered.
- I know.
- I can tell.
(Jong Kook smacks Jenny's head.)
(Ho!)
The partner's up next.
She flew ahead...
which means it wasn't So Min.
(Jong Kook's partner Hee Jung
smacks Suk Jin's head.)
Get guessing.
The hand was delicate.
It was a woman's.
Judging by the thin hand,
it has to be a woman's.
- I smelled her perfume as well.
- This isn't easy, you know.
- It's hard.
- It's not easy.
It was a woman.
(The oldest detective recalls
how the hand felt.)
Was it Jong Kook?
No, I think it was Se Chan.
Se Chan and Ah In.
He can't look me in the eyes.
- He can't.
- Se Chan?
But Se Chan would've
smacked us hard.
- Was it So Min?
- So Min?
She flew forward
after someone smacked you.
That was So Min.
- Maybe it was really her.
- No way.
It can't be her.
- How stupid can you be?
- They're arguing.
Can't you be nicer to Jenny?
- Be nicer.
- He's not Jae Suk today.
- This is Jenny.
- She's your partner.
- Stupid?
- Be nicer.
Just think about it.
- You're partners.
- After you were hit,
she flew out in front of you.
It couldn't have been her.
She was only trying to trick us.
How about this, then?
- How did he know?
- I was smacked like this.
This is how it was for me.
- In my case...
- No way.
- I was smacked like this.
- What?
- Check this out.
- Show me.
I was smacked like this.
Get back here.
This has turned
into a comedy sketch.
- Get back here.
- A comedy sketch.
That was like a comedy sketch.
That hurt.
Did someone hit you that hard?
That's how it was for me.
Take your pick, then.
- Who do you think it was?
- So Min and Ji Hyo?
- Let's go with Haha.
- Haha and Jeong Eui.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Jeong Eui.
- Haha.
- Darn it.
- Please sit back down.
- The balloons didn't explode.
- Unbelievable.
(Hee Jung and Jong Kook
score a point.)
Guess whenever you're ready.
(Groaning)
(Ah In's full swing)
You have to stay seated.
That was insane!
- No way.
- That hurt.
(Se Chan smacks Jenny.)
Did that hurt or not?
- Did that hurt or not?
- It really hurt.
- It hurt for me as well.
- I was smacked hard.
The couple with both our members.
Busted. She caught my eye.
Her? So Min?
No, not her.
Ah In went like this.
(Swoosh)
- What did she do?
- How did she react?
The second I stood up,
she went like this.
(She immediately looked away.)
- Was it Se Chan?
- Right.
- Se Chan and...
- But I was hit really hard.
- A guy hit me.
- I know I'm right.
- It was a guy!
No, it was Ah In.
- It wasn't me.
- Ah In smacked you on the head.
- Let me see your hand.
- I saw how she reacted.
- Really?
- Look at Haha's expression.
Se Chan's the one who smacked me.
- That's who we're going with?
- Se Chan and...
- How stupid can you be?
- He called him stupid again.
- Park Ah In.
Okay!
Another couple will sit down.
- Did she...
- It was Ah In.
- Ah In...
- Were you the one who hit me?
Ah In couldn't look me in the eyes.
It's hard to tell who it is
when the guest smacks you really hard.
Ah In likes to smack people around.
She laid it on him.
It was no joke.
They all seem eager to play.
We can't fool around
because of the balloons.
(Who will smack them
on their heads this time?)
I can feel your presence.
Okay, I felt a punch.
That was a woman's.
- Did someone hit you?
- It wasn't rough.
It wasn't rough? Got it.
I know it was So Min.
I wasn't hit very hard.
Then it was Ji Hyo.
- Say it was Ji Hyo.
- Yes, Ji Hyo and...
- So Min's the one who punched me.
- Did it hurt?
They're on the same team, right?
- I was punched.
- Got it.
- Who was it?
- So Min.
- And Ji Hyo.
- They didn't even look at us.
- So Min.
- And Ji Hyo.
(They were caught in record time.)
- Nice!
- Why am I so obvious?
Why am I so obvious?
- Well...
- Why did you use your fist?
What's wrong with you?
So Min, come on.
- Why do I always get caught?
- How do they know it's her?
So Min, get a grip on yourself.
- Unbelievable.
- How did you know it was me?
- Jeong Eui, come on.
- This is fun.
Ah In's having a blast.
She's like, "This is fun."
(Professor Park
is enjoying the game.)
- It's nice to be back.
- It gets confusing.
(So Bal and Ji Hyo
will be smacked on the head.)
- Sorry.
- Watch your step.
Jae Suk, seriously?
(Like a short-track skater)
- This time, it'll be Jae Suk.
- Okay.
I mean, Jenny. One...
One...
I think it really was Jae Suk.
I think it was Jae Suk.
I mean it. The hand felt edgy.
- I think it was Jae Suk.
- No, you can't look.
- What?
- Are you kidding me?
(She looks back.)
- What?
- Are you kidding me?
- Sorry.
- What's the matter with You?
- Again.
- Do it again.
- What's with her?
- All right.
- Do it again.
- You can't keep doing this.
- That's wrong.
- But...
Don't live your life this way.
He said...
Let's put our hands forward.
- I'm sorry.
- Shoot your arms out.
Who will it be?
Haha?
- Sure thing.
- Haha, go ahead.
On three, Haha and his partner
will smack their heads.
- In 1, 2, 3.
Should I hit her
on the count of three?
- No, I'll do it.
- Sure.
- All right.
- In 1, 2, 3.
(Smack!)
- Hey!
- Not yet!
(Not yet!)
- Seriously?
- Come on!
- I'm done playing this game.
- What's wrong with her?
- What's the matter with you?
- She's ruining a good game.
Stop peeking!
I didn't mean it.
It was involuntary.
- But...
- You'll do it again.
- Seriously?
- Unbelievable.
I can't help myself.
Only look back when you're told to.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
What's wrong with me?
- There's no need to cry.
- I'm tearing up.
- Ji Hyo...
- It just happened.
Why do I keep looking back?
- What's with me?
- It's hard for her to sit still.
Go ahead and smack me again.
Then...
Please gather around again.
Jeong Eui and Hee Jung
should hit them respectively.
They aren't on the same team,
but who cares.
Whoever wants to hit them
should hit them.
Here we go.
Who will it be?
Have you made up your minds?
- One, two, three!
- Three!
- In 1, 2, 3.
(Smack!)
All I felt was a tap.
Guess who it was.
(The investigation begins.)
It was Jeong Eui.
Really?
I think it was Jeong Eui who hit me.
- I think Haha hit you.
- Really?
- Haha?
- Did you hit them both?
- Was it Haha?
- Will she get this right?
No, Jeong Eui's the one who hit me.
- What?
- Jeong Eui hit me, not you.
I felt a man's touch.
Could it have been Suk Jin?
(Oh!)
- Oh?
- Yes, oh!
Are you a caveman?
- What was that?
- What on earth was that?
You're allowed to speak, you know.
- Am I allowed to speak?
- Are you a monkey?
He's terrible
at comedy sketches, you see.
- He sounded like a caveman.
- It felt rough though.
- How perceptive.
- I think...
- It wasn't Suk Jin.
- I think it came from this way.
- Why can't you tell who it was?
- How come...
From this direction.
Haha could've hit you like this.
- By crossing directions?
- Just know that it wasn't...
Jenny or Suk Jin.
Jeong Eui.
- It wasn't me.
- It wasn't me or Suk Jin.
- It wasn't.
- It really wasn't.
(Anyone could be the culprit,
so who was it?)
I'll go with Haha then.
- But...
- Sure.
- In 1, 2, 3. Haha.
- Jeong Eui.
(Did Ji Hyo guess right?)
- See?
- How did you know?
- I knew it was Jeong Eui.
- No way.
- Unbelievable.
Please take your seats.
Jeong Eui's been messing with us
all throughout the game.
- Jeong Eui...
- She isn't playing around.
- What was that?
- My gosh!
(The water balloons popped.)
(Screaming)
- What was that? Why did they pop?
- Goodness.
- That scared me.
- Why did they pop on us?
- All right!
- Why did they suddenly pop?
- That's minus three points for you.
- All right!
It was an accident.
- You got unlucky.
- All right!
(Monk Haha and Jeong Eui
were very surprised.)
All right!
You find everything fun, don't you?
It's time to announce the ranking.
You'll get the benefits
needed at the end...
according to your ranking.
- Is that so?
- Okay.
First place goes to Jong Kook
and Hee Jung who got three points.
(1st place: Jong Kook and Hee Jung)
They did well.
- Yes!
- Second place...
goes to Se Chan and Ah In.
(2nd place: Se Chan and Ah In)
Jenny and Suk Jin
and So Min and Ji Hyo...
are both in third place.
Haha and Jeong Eui
are in last place.
Seriously...
We'll give you benefits
according to the results.
We'll hand out candies
as the first mission ended.
(First handing out of candies)
The male members will head outside
with candies that have their names.
You'll see boxes with the names
of the female members.
Open the box of the female member
you want to partner up with next...
- and put your candy in.
- Got it.
If two or more male members
pick the same female member,
the female member will pick
her partner.
Who's going first?
If there's a female member
who receives no candies,
she'll get penalty balls.
- Those with no candies?
- Yes.
- That's...
- That's mean.
- Don't worry, Ah In.
- All right.
- We get one each?
- It's okay.
- You won't betray me, will you?
- Of course not.
- I can play well.
- Okay.
Can you tell us
which male member you prefer?
Let's start with Jenny.
- With who?
- With Jenny.
- Jenny.
- Who would you like?
I won't change my mind.
Why don't you appeal yourself
with dancing?
- So we can pick you.
- Come on.
- I bet I wasn't that bad.
- I...
It's weird that you'd appeal
yourself to get candy.
Don't put your candies in my box.
I'm serious.
- That's quite appealing.
- Jenny!
I find him appealing.
- You don't want it?
- No. Don't put it in my box.
- Are you sure?
- Hey, you're charming.
You're charming.
(You're charming.)
You're strangely charming.
- So Bal...
- She's stepping up.
If you want,
then you can put yours in mine.
- Is that so?
- But you told us not to.
Where's your place?
So Min's hair is funny.
- She's so funny.
- My place?
Her pick-up line is so old though.
- Ji Hyo, it's your turn.
- She's hilarious.
I...
I have faith in my partner.
- You mean So Bal?
- So Min.
You can't trust people like her.
But So Bal... Hey.
(Kneeling performance)
You know what she told me earlier?
She said she wouldn't
change her mind,
but she went up to Jenny...
- and said, "Where's your place?"
- "Where's your place?"
- That's her charm.
- I'm a bad boy.
- Hey.
- That's her charm.
- Right?
You're the only one I love.
Did something get in your eye?
(You mean this?)
- What about Ah In?
- Suk Jin agreed to pick me.
(Suk Jin and Shy Suk Jin
have finished making a deal.)
- Gosh, she dumped me.
- She doesn't know who Suk Jin is.
Ah In isn't even looking at me.
Okay, fine.
- I bet no one wants you.
- I'm going for Jenny.
All right.
But Ah In is older than you.
- Pardon?
- She's older.
- What?
- How old are you, Ah In?
Oh, me?
- I'm sorry, but...
- I was born in 1985.
- I'm so sorry, Ah In.
- She's older than you?
I'm so sorry, Ah In.
She's older than you?
- Hey! Why you...
- I didn't know either!
- You're older than me?
- She's older than me?
I made a slip too.
I thought she was way younger
than me.
- I also thought she was younger.
- So I called her casually.
- Really?
- I'm so sorry, Ah In.
- You'd better behave yourself.
- How old are you?
- I'm so sorry!
- He was born in 1986.
- She was born in 1985.
- I was born in 1985.
- Sorry, I was born in 1986.
- I'm a year younger. I'm sorry.
- Ah In.
- I'm sorry, Ah In.
- So Min.
- Se Chan.
- I'm sorry.
I naturally thought
she'd be younger than me.
You both made mistakes.
- How embarrassing.
- You should address her properly.
- I had no idea.
- All right.
Let's start with Suk Jin.
- Shall I go first?
- Yes.
But the thing is...
- Ah In.
- You look so young.
- Yes, Suk Jin?
- You see, Running Man is...
- What is he on about?
- Speak properly.
- What? "Running Nan?"
I hope you won't be hurt.
You want to partner up
with someone else?
- What's with him?
- What's with him, seriously?
- He can't even speak properly.
- Mister, what did you say?
Didn't he say "Running Min?"
(Seok Sam becomes less attractive
every time he opens his mouth.)
- What is Running Min?
- Running Min.
Running Min?
Mister! Don't put your candy
in my box!
I will never!
I won't let you be
if you put yours in mine, old man.
I won't!
(Who will Suk Jin choose?)
Should I surprise Jenny?
(In which box
did Suk Jin put his candy?)
- I'll...
- I almost went crazy there.
- put it in here.
- Jeong Eui wasn't good at games.
All right.
Everyone has made their decision.
Female members,
please stand in front of your boxes.
Come forward.
Please open them
on the count of three.
- Okay.
- One.
I think Jenny got a lot.
Two, three.
(Opening their boxes)
(Where did the male members'
candies go?)
Why are there so many?
I have one.
- Yes!
- Why are there so many?
Why did I get so many?
Jenny is so popular.
What happened?
- Ji Hyo is in trouble.
- Why did I get so many?
(Suk Jin chose Ah In.
Se Chan and So Bal chose Jenny.)
(Haha chose Jeong Eui.)
(Jong Kook chose Hee Jung.)
- Wait. Who didn't get any?
- Why did...
Yes!
I knew it.
Why did I get so many?
Ji Hyo got none.
(Ji Hyo got no candies,
so she got a penalty ball.)
I knew So Min would betray me.
- You're partners with Jong Kook.
- I let you go because I love you.
So Jenny will receive
one more benefit.
- Right.
- And you can choose...
a member you like better.
Gosh, this is...
Jenny, those who love each other
look like each other.
Look at our mouths.
This is clearly true love.
He's right.
(Staring intently)
- You guys are practically married.
- Why don't you appeal yourselves?
- Appeal yourselves.
- Jenny.
- No, wait.
So Bal, you're too cheesy. Get out.
- Yes!
- Why?
(Sad)
You should stay next to Ji Hyo
and protect her.
You're way too cheesy.
- Ji Hyo, you should...
- So Bal and Ji Hyo are reunited.
- How dare you ask...
- They're reunited!
where my place is?
Go to her!
- Can't I reject her?
- How dare you ask...
where my place is
at times like this?
(Kneeling to apologize)
(There you go.)
- I hate gestures like that.
- I love you.
I love you.
(So Bal kneels all the time
to maintain her relationship.)
- You're the only one I love.
- You might get beaten at this rate.
- You might be beaten.
- You're good, So Bal.
- You're the only one I love.
- So Bal is so smooth.
- Forget it.
I want to have a baby with you.
Forget it!
"I want to have a baby with you?"
- She wants a baby?
- Let's move to have lunch.
- Okay!
- Let's go!
We're sitting with our partners?
All right.
I have to sit with my partner?
- You can sit here for now.
- Okay.
- Or you can sit here.
- You became so polite.
No, that's not it.
(Se Chan has suddenly become polite
to Ah In.)
He's become way too polite.
So Min, you look exactly
like Princess Knight, right?
Yes, I look exactly like her.
There's an old animation
called "Princess Knight."
- We have the exact same hairstyle.
- Yes, you do.
And she wears princess' dresses too.
Gosh, I want to
have braised pollack.
- What did you say?
- Okay, Suk Jin.
(He suddenly wants to have
braised pollack.)
Okay, Suk Jin.
You can get off and have it.
Go ahead, Suk Jin.
(They tell Suk Jin to get off
as he wants braised pollack.)
- Braised pollack...
- He's getting off!
Please wait, sir!
He's getting off for real.
- Never mind.
- Suk Jin...
- You're not having it, right?
- I'll have it when I get home.
- Please hold, sir.
- I'll get it delivered at home.
- Sir!
- He said he won't eat it.
Please stop the bus.
- Never mind, sir.
- Please stop.
They're joking.
Please get off, Suk Jin.
He said we were joking.
You can say whatever you want.
- It's okay.
- You're our captain, after all.
- He's right.
- Go ahead.
Suk Jin, that's my water.
- No, it's mine.
- I just had it.
- No, I...
- I put it in here after I had it.
- Really? I had it too.
- You should get off and have it.
- Sir!
- He'll get off to have water.
Good work today.
- He actually stopped the bus.
- It's okay. I found mine.
The bus set off again.
All right.
The guests didn't hesitate
to hit my head today.
- I know. They hit really well.
- I was really surprised.
- Because Ah In...
- She knows...
because she's watched
our show a lot.
- So she knows.
- Jeong Eui also hit very hard.
- Jeong Eui hits hard.
- So she knows.
- What was that?
- There you go.
(Hey! Who was that?)
- The thing is...
- You're smiling.
It's Jenny.
You're smiling. You can't fool me.
- It wasn't me.
- Yes, it was.
- I'm sure it was you.
- It wasn't me.
- It was me.
(It was me.)
- You didn't get me.
- You didn't get her.
Was it really you?
- It was really her.
- It was Hee Jung.
You hit me so hard.
- She can hit hard.
- It was Hee Jung.
If you think about it,
what Hee Jung did was weird.
Why did she suddenly hit him?
- No, I...
- They told her to.
- We've only met today.
- We told her to.
Let it go, Suk Jin.
- It's okay, Hee Jung.
- I was starving. I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- She said she gets sensitive.
I'm so happy...
- Since we love and trust you,
- that you're with us today.
- we played with you.
- Of course.
It's okay. You can hit my head
anytime you want today.
This is what Running Min
is all about.
It's Running Min.
This is what Running Min
is all about.
"Is there a spy among us?"
- "A spy."
- "Find the spy."
- "A spy..."
- "in Running Min."
- "Find him."
There's no time
for Suk Jin to rest.
This is why
he sometimes falls asleep.
He passes out from exhaustion.
Suk Jin, you can lean on my hand.
I'll support your head.
- It's okay.
- I'll support your head.
- He's the best.
- Hey.
Stop it, everyone.
My fan is here today.
- Who?
- My fan is here.
- Oh, right.
- So stop it.
- Oh, Ah In?
- We must help save his face.
Since his fan is here...
He's become really polite.
- Of course.
- Because I didn't know her age.
I'm usually polite.
I thought you were younger than me.
Didn't you go through
something similar before?
- Right, he did.
- That guy from Germany.
- What?
- Who was that guy again?
- It was Yoo Teo.
- Right. It was Teo.
I was like, "How old are you again?"
He said he was 40.
So I apologized right away.
(He apologized right away.)
(Teo, who was born in 1981,
visited Running Man as a guest.)
(Teo.)
(How old are you, Teo?)
(I'm 40.)
(I'm sorry.)
(Se Chan was rude to Teo
who was 5 years older than him.)
(And to Yeon Hee who visited
on the same day...)
(How old are you, Yeon Hee?)
(I was born in 1988.)
Yeon Hee is younger than us.
(He treated Yeon Hee
as someone older.)
(You talk casually to those
who are older than you.)
(He made many mistakes
to the guests that day.)
But Ah In
seemed younger than Se Chan.
- You make so many mistakes.
- I know.
It's because they all look young.
He was only trying to be nice.
Captain Ji prepared
a Korean food buffet.
- It sounds delicious.
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
- Did he pay with his own money?
No, we used our money.
- That's too bad.
- Of course they should.
You should treat us with your money
since you're a captain.
- That's...
- Suk Jin would never do that.
- That'd be too much.
- But I bet...
- he prepared candies, at least.
- He's not that considerate.
- I bet he prepared candies.
- Right.
- Why are you eating so much today?
- That'd be going overboard.
- You're eating so many candies.
- Why are you eating so much?
Jeong Eui, I'm addicted to this.
He's had 30 of them already.
- I can't stop eating it.
- His hands...
- His hands are shaking.
- He's so strange.
How many is he having?
- You said you don't like sweets.
- He's become strange.
But this is so addictive.
Everyone, after we get there,
and while having lunch,
a mafia will carry out
their hidden mission.
(There's a hidden mission
for the mafia.)
(The mafia will carry out
their mission during lunch?)
- What?
- There's a mafia among us?
No, we'll decide
who'll become the mafia.
- What?
- We'll decide now.
You'll get off one by one,
and a couple will become mafias
through drawing lots.
And the mafias must carry out
their mission during lunch.
- I see.
- The rest of you must catch them.
- They'll be caught for sure.
- They will be.
If I become the mafia...
My hands will shake...
- if Jong Kook looks at me.
- I know.
"Oh, it's you?"
Let me tell you in advance.
I'll be doing strange things.
- Me too.
- I'll be doing strange things.
Why? We have to guess
who the mafias are.
Mafias are usually at ease.
They'll pretend to be on purpose.
All right.
- Let's do it.
- Something smells delicious.
Please...
It won't be easy to carry out
the mission during lunch.
I have done it before.
So we're a team, right?
- Yes, you are.
- That's right.
- You'll pick 1 out of 5 cards.
- Which one should we pick?
(There's only one card
that says mafia.)
- Go ahead.
- This one?
Just don't pick
the mafia card. Please.
(Which card did Jeong Eui pick?)
All right!
- We're civilians.
- Let's eat at ease.
- Ji Hyo and So Bal.
- Yes.
"So Bal?"
There are four cards here.
(Civilian)
That's a relief.
(Ji Hyo and So Bal
are civilians as well.)
(Unlike the two who are relieved
after picking the civilian card...)
- You want to be a mafia?
- Yes, I do.
I wish I could be a mafia.
She wants to be a mafia,
but I don't.
I wish I could be a mafia.
- Please pick one.
- One of the two?
(There are three cards left.)
- One of the two? One of the three?
- Among these three.
- You should pick it.
- Me?
Yes.
(Will Ah In become a mafia
as she wished?)
We're civilians.
Do we bring it with us?
(Sadly, Suk Jin and Ah In
became civilians.)
- We have to pick one?
- This is...
(Jenny picked one boldly
as soon as he came in.)
(They picked the mafia card.)
- What?
- You are...
Why did you pick this?
Today's mission is very simple.
You'll be having
a Korean food buffet.
- Everyone will be given a plate.
- Okay.
If one has food on their plate,
the other one can't put food
on his plate.
- What does that mean?
It means you can't have food
on your plates at the same time.
Even just a little.
(They can't have food
on their plates at the same time.)
It's similar to the mission
where one had to remain standing.
- It's the worst.
- It is.
- Don't eat a lot.
- Okay.
- Let's just eat a little.
- Let's eat little by little.
- You'll have to eat lightly today.
- Got it.
Cup noodles are considered one too.
- Okay.
Got it.
- Do we start right away?
- Yes.
- Do we go up here?
- The rest are up there.
It sounds fun.
She looks relaxed.
- So Bal.
- Yes?
- Are you fixing your hair?
- Yes.
You don't even wash your hair?
Don't people wash their hair
once a week?
- So Min.
- Gosh.
What kind of man behaves like this?
No one does this.
Who does that?
- What are you, a thug?
- Can you make it more natural?
Men don't act that way.
(While So Bal
is acting like a thug...)
Jenny.
Jenny?
What?
- There are only three seats.
- You weren't doing anything?
- There are three.
- We were.
- Are you the mafia?
- What did you do?
Jenny, sit here.
Suk Jin is crossing his arms.
This must be it.
- Yes.
- I see.
All right.
- It's started.
- Mafia.
- Jong Kook.
- Come sit here.
Let's see if anyone
is behaving strangely.
You're crossing your arms.
- Let me see your faces.
- You're crossing your arms.
- Is anyone acting strange?
- Let me scan your faces.
(He starts scanning them
as soon as he enters.)
- Is anyone acting strange?
- Let me scan your faces.
All right.
- You're not the type to cross arms.
- All right.
Great.
Jae Suk didn't even look at me once
and kept looking away...
when I came in.
(Viper picked out the mafias
as soon as it began.)
(Will they be able to get away
from Viper?)
- All right.
- Everyone,
we'll bring in the buffet
that Captain Ji requested.
- Yes!
- All right!
Everyone, I insisted on
having this today.
Please give me a round of applause.
- All right. Thank you.
- Thank you.
You look so happy.
There are cup noodles too.
Those are my favorite.
There's pork cutlet too.
Braised spicy chicken.
There's fried rice as well.
- Wow, this is...
- There are noodles too.
(I should have this with noodles.)
- This is octopus.
- I should have this with noodles.
I'll have fried rice.
(Laughing)
- Pork cutlets are...
- This is...
- What is it?
- Is it good?
You should just eat comfortably.
They're the mafias.
- Who?
- This team.
- Team Red.
- Why do you think it's us?
- Just eat comfortably.
- Why did he pick us?
He's at it again.
- He's at it again.
- Just eat comfortably.
- Thank you.
- Jong Kook.
- We don't even have to see it.
- It's them?
It'll be too unfair if we pick them
after seeing their behavior.
- So I'll just...
- It's them?
pick them as mafias
from the beginning.
He's at it again.
- But...
- How frustrating.
Strangely,
his hunches are always right.
- I should just eat comfortably.
- Yes, go ahead.
- Let's eat.
- Thank you for the food.
- Mafias, just enjoy your meal.
- I'll start with noodles.
- All right.
We think...
- those two are behaving strangely.
- I want noodles too.
Or it could be them.
Haha is being strange too.
- I'll have noodles.
- There's a drumstick.
Haha is being strange too.
(Jae Suk can't put food
on his plate.)
Should I have tteokbokki?
Gosh, this is...
Wait. Should I have ramyeon?
(He moves to the corner
while grumbling.)
- Why did you spill it?
- I'm a civilian for sure.
Gosh, this is...
- Let's have this.
- Who eats so loudly?
- It looks like...
- Thank you for the food.
Se Chan and Jae Suk
are moving separately.
I'm just boiling hot water
for cup noodles.
I have to boil the water first.
I was so hungry.
I can't even speak.
(Se Chan began his own feast.)
Can I have some of the noodles
you mixed?
Why are you eating mine?
(So Bal's unexpected move)
- Eating someone's food.
- It's because he took a lot.
- Look at that.
- That's strange.
- Why are you suddenly eating his?
- You're eating Se Chan's food.
But there are noodles
in front of you.
Because he took a lot.
(So Bal helps the mafias
by stealing Se Chan's noodles.)
So Min, I'm sorry,
but we all have to catch the mafias.
You shouldn't confuse others.
- I didn't intend to.
- Your action... That was strange.
(Thanks to So Min,
Jong Kook is paying less attention.)
So Min took someone else's food?
I love noodles.
(He can't have the noodles
when it's right in front of him.)
You should mix noodles
with seasoned octopus.
Right?
Hey, finish your food already.
(Let me eat some food too.)
"Finish your food"? That's strange.
Why is he rushing him?
- He has to finish it first?
- You should finish it already.
What's going on?
- There's rice here.
- Really?
(While Se Chan is shoving noodles
in his mouth,)
This looks so good.
(Jae Suk
just goes through noodles.)
I should mix seasoned octopus
with this.
Who are you talking to, Jae Suk?
I'm talking to myself.
(Meanwhile,
Se Chan finally emptied his plate.)
You must watch carefully
what other teams are doing.
(As soon as Se Chan
emptied his plate,)
(Jae Suk fills his plate
with food.)
This looks really good.
It looks incredible.
See if the water is boiled.
Jae Suk and Se Chan...
are having noodles.
- This is...
- The noodles are really good.
- I just love noodles.
- This is...
- Jong Kook, I just love noodles.
- Stealing others' food.
- It's really good, right?
But... Hey.
It's as if Jong Kook
is on a stakeout.
(Detective Kim's stakeout)
What?
He was doing this while eating.
(His eyes were fixed on the suspects
as he ate.)
Detective Kim Nipple,
you're amazing.
You're amazing,
Detective Kim Nipple.
(Even his nipples are glaring
at the suspects.)
Are you going to have that?
No, I'm good.
- Then you should...
- It's okay. You can have it.
(Se Chan stalls for time
in the corner while Jae Suk eats.)
I think this is Jae Suk's.
- Can I have Coke?
- Of course you can.
(In the meantime,
Jae Suk emptied his plate.)
This is just so good.
(Se Chan saw that Jae Suk
emptied his plate.)
This is...
There's no webfoot octopus here?
- Right.
- It's so natural.
(Right then, Jae Suk reached out
to get more food.)
- Do you need anything, Ah In?
- No, it's okay.
The pork cutlet is really good.
The old-style pork cutlet.
- The pork cutlet...
- Yes, the old-style pork cutlet.
is light and nice.
Let me try some of tteokbokki.
(Adding tteokbokki
on top of pork cutlet)
- Aren't you eating too much?
- Sorry?
- No.
You have three more minutes.
You can have your meal comfortably
for three more minutes.
(The civilians keep a close watch
as there's not much time left.)
Isn't he acting awkward?
(Jenny, who even got tteokbokki,)
(starts having cup noodles.)
The chopsticks. My gosh.
Where's each team sitting?
Two here and two there.
The pork cutlet is so good!
Maybe the mission is
to sit together...
and never get up.
Why don't we try getting up?
This is so good.
- How about we try...
- We can all try getting up now.
- I did get up earlier.
- Haha did get up earlier.
(Hold on...)
Are you done already?
(Are you done already?)
(Flustered)
- I am going to eat more.
- Are you done?
- Why aren't you eating?
- He hasn't eaten much.
Why aren't you eating?
Haha, you have done this before.
Don't be so cruel.
- Why aren't you eating?
- He hasn't said much either.
- I am going to eat more.
- Are you waiting for Jae Suk?
- Who?
- Can you eat...
only when Jae Suk isn't eating?
(Can you eat
only when Jae Suk isn't eating?)
- It's not like that.
- That must be it.
That must be it.
I saw him pick up Coca-Cola earlier.
He looked at Jae Suk...
and pretended to drink
until Jae Suk was done chewing.
- It's not like that.
- Eat something.
- When Jae Suk...
- I can eat.
- It doesn't matter.
- Eat something.
- Eat at the same time.
- It doesn't matter.
- It's strange.
- His plate is empty.
Besides...
He can't eat
because Jae Suk is eating.
I can eat.
- That's not true.
- Try kimchi.
I ate kimchi earlier.
Did you eat everything earlier?
- Aren't you going to eat more?
- I am.
- Why aren't you eating?
- Are you going to eat or not?
I am thinking.
Se Chan loves to eat food,
but his plate...
- Lunchtime is over.
- Already?
It's time to apprehend
the mafia members.
- Jae Suk and Se Chan.
- Us?
Se Chan and Jae Suk.
Se Chan and Jenny.
Se Chan behaved so strangely.
Se Chan.
With four votes, Se Chan and Jenny
became the candidates.
The mafia members are...
Jenny and Se Chan.
We were right.
We aren't mafia members.
- It was so obvious.
- Are you guys mafia members?
Why did you get so much food?
Were you starved?
If one member had food on his plate,
the other member couldn't eat.
The mission was too difficult.
He got both tonkatsu and tteokbokki
on his plate.
Why did you get young radish kimchi?
You didn't even eat it.
I looked suspicious
because my plate was empty.
- That's right. You didn't eat much.
- But these are my favorite dishes.
- These are my favorite dishes.
- You failed from the start.
As soon as Jong Kook entered,
he looked at Jae Suk and said,
- "Oh."
"Guys, you can relax and eat."
- You know...
- "It's Jenny."
It wasn't just Jae Suk.
Se Chan's face was rigid too.
The moment Jong Kook did that,
the production crew went...
They couldn't eat in peace.
(Sighing)
You saw
how quiet they became, right?
The two of you will receive
a disadvantage at the end.
Other teams will receive a benefit.
However, one team will be excluded.
- Jenny and Se Chan can choose.
- Really?
One team won't receive a benefit.
- In that case...
- Yes.
Our decision is obvious.
Yes. Jong Kook and...
What?
(Jong Kook gets punished
for making them suffocate.)
Of course.
Hear me out for a second.
Did I pressure you
while you were eating?
- You did that from the start.
- Listen.
- Jong Kook.
- No, I didn't.
- I simply shared my opinion.
- Listen.
I told you to relax and eat.
"Jae Suk didn't look at me."
Then we sat down, right?
"All right. Relax and eat."
"The answer is given."
(The answer is given.)
- It wasn't like that.
- You pressured us, okay?
Who made you uncomfortable
while you ate?
- It was Haha.
- Haha.
- But Haha.
- To be honest,
it was Jong Kook's accusation...
- that drove me to that extent.
- That's right.
That little...
Jong Kook was so certain.
That's ridiculous.
I only said one thing.
Since their opinions are divided,
we will choose Suk Jin and...
- Why?
- Hold on.
(Suk Jin receives the shocking news
while eating.)
Hold on.
- Isn't that the solution?
- Yes.
- Both of them feel victimized,
- That's right.
- so we can't choose them.
- That's right. I didn't do much.
Isn't that right, Se Chan?
Both of them feel victimized.
- They feel victimized? Hey.
- No way.
You punk.
- Do you want a scalding?
- "You punk."
(He meant to say "Scolding".)
- He wasn't scary at all.
- He can't speak.
"Do you want a scalding?"
What are you talking about?
"You punk."
"Do you want a scalding?"
Otherwise, we could pick Ji Hyo...
- and So Min.
- Why?
- That's right.
- Come on, Jae Suk.
- If you remember,
So Min did something strange
to show that she is a civilian.
I simply did that
since he had a lot of noodles.
After you finish your meal,
we will meet at the last location.
Okay.
It's men's last chance to pick
a woman who will get the candy.
- She needs someone who can...
- Why would I change my pick?
(They deliver their candies
to the women they like.)
Whom should I pick?
(It's So Bal's turn.)
(With her injured leg,
she ponders in a cool way.)
What should I do?
Whom should I pick?
(Whom should I pick?)
(Sighing)
(Whom will So Bal pick?)
For goodness' sake.
- Hurry over here, So Bal.
- Hey.
Run over here.
- You are the youngest one.
- Hey.
- Listen.
- Don't do it.
- So Bal needs to get beaten up.
- What?
What was that?
- Hey.
- Stand up straight.
- What are those fashionable shoes?
- Fashionable shoes.
- Mister.
- "Mister?"
Who do you think you are?
Look at this.
So Bal is uncontrollable.
- So Bal is uncontrollable.
- You little...
Not even my dad scolds me.
Who do you think you are?
(Spitting)
(Laughing)
- He is happy.
- You are cute.
That came out of nowhere.
"You are cute."
All right, everyone.
- The gentlemen put in the candies.
- Really?
One, two, three.
For goodness' sake.
(Hee Jung and Jeong Eui: 2 candies
Ji Hyo: 1 candy)
Come on.
- What?
- There's a new guy.
- You are so mean.
- Ah In, I had my reasons.
- What?
- Ah In.
- You are so mean.
- Ah In, I had my reasons.
I wanted you to try having
another member...
- as a partner.
- But there are no candies.
They must be happy.
Hee Jung and Jeong Eui
received two votes each.
Jenny and Ah In
will receive a penalty ball.
Let's start with Hee Jung.
I thought I could become the best...
by stealing Jong Kook's woman.
Get your hands out of the pockets.
- Hey.
- Don't be so arrogant.
Don't be smug
just because you are handsome.
If you are handsome, act like it.
- It's so hard to choose one.
- Put it down.
You won't see them again
after this game.
- You won't see them again.
- Jenny.
Seriously.
(Jenny speaks her mind.)
- In that case...
- Good idea.
So Bal is out.
- I am sorry.
- That taught you right.
- Hey.
- My goodness.
This is how life is.
You got rejected.
Get lost, you punk.
Jeong Eui rejected Haha.
- Jeong Eui rejected Haha.
- Jeong Eui chose Se Chan.
- Okay.
- Did she reject me?
Hey, come here.
- Little one, come here.
- You got rejected too, Octopus.
- Octopus.
- You didn't even think.
We agreed to be cool about it.
- All right.
- Be cool about it.
Ah In, choose the man you want.
I am confident.
That's good.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- Octopus.
- Team "How Do You Play?"
- Octopus, come here.
- Let's go.
- Team "How Do You Play?"
They shouldn't be together.
- Are they Team "How Do You Play?"
- Okay. I have the same partner.
- What is this?
- There are circular saws.
Things will get cut off.
- No way.
- Look. There are circular saws.
- Things will get cut off.
- I see.
- This is scary.
Things will get cut off today.
All right, everyone.
The two of you are attached.
Ah In, he is handsome.
- He is my boyfriend.
- She cares about a man's looks.
Here comes the last mission.
Ji Hyo and Suk Jin...
don't even look at each other.
- They aren't close.
- We have done that for 13 years.
- We are a family.
- That's right.
Here comes the last mission.
If you fail to get the answer,
you could fall from the tree
and get a heart attack.
- It's the Heart Attack Quiz.
- It's a quiz.
Heart Attack Quiz.
- Is it a quiz?
Okay.
- We are a good team.
- So Min.
You aren't So Min. Ji Hyo.
- Is it a quiz?
- I am bad at it.
I am Empty Head.
I am stupid.
Jenny was the king
of "Janghak Quiz."
Each match will be
between two teams.
Two people will sit
on the wooden board.
Two people.
And these are...
the names of the viewers
who love Running Man.
- Really?
- Yes.
They sent us
their information and questions.
- My goodness.
- Thus,
the viewers are
of various age groups...
from a kindergartener
to an office worker.
The team that has a priority...
- will pick a name.
- Okay.
Then you will check the information
that comes with the name.
- The board consists of 20 sections.
- Okay.
You will decide how many sections
you want to bet on a question.
- That's right.
- We will bet sections.
You will receive the question
afterward.
The opposing team will lose sections
if you answer it correctly.
The match ends
if your board collapses.
- Okay.
- All right.
The difficulty levels differ,
so choose the question well.
- Okay.
- You need to choose the name well.
You can guess the age from the name.
Ye Eun would be a good choice.
I don't know anyone
named Saet Byeol.
My friends are named Eun Sook,
- Mi Young...
- That's right.
- Eun Jeong.
- Eun Ja.
Gyeong Nam would belong
to someone old.
Other teams can sit down.
- Team 2 and Team 3, wear a helmet.
- Are we going first?
- Okay.
- This is scary.
- You know,
it's really scary
even though the height isn't great.
Which team wants to go first?
- That team will go first.
- In that case...
- I am nervous.
- What?
Go first.
- Why?
- It's better to go first.
- Really?
- Okay.
- We will go first.
- You can't take it back.
Pick a name of your choice.
- All right.
- Pick one.
(Which name
would give them an advantage?)
- Which one do you want?
- Kim Jong Kook.
- How about Kim Jong Kook?
- Kim Jong Kook?
- Yes.
It must be hard
to live with that name.
Kim Gook Jong?
It must be hard
to live with that name.
A 27-year-old.
- A senior economy major.
- S University.
- No.
- It will be difficult.
The question will be difficult.
- Suk Jin.
- Did you major in management?
- Yes, I did.
An economy-related question
would be nice.
I don't know much about the economy.
Suk Jin would know.
- It would be nice.
- I don't know anything.
You have a priority on the question.
Decide how many sections
you want to bet.
- Bet five sections.
- A man named Kim Jong Kook...
- should do sports.
- How many sections?
(Jong Kook can't allow
such a thing.)
- How many are there?
- How many sections should we bet?
- About...
- Two?
Since he is an economics major,
we shouldn't bet many sections.
Suk Jin invests in stocks.
- I was a management major.
- He knows a lot about the field.
- Shall we bet one section?
- Let's do that.
- Come on.
- The number is too small.
(The number is too small.)
Suk Jin knows a lot
about the economy.
- Bet three sections.
- Come on.
He is...
Then we will bet two sections.
- Two sections.
- Yes.
For goodness' sake.
Bet four or more sections.
He is glaring at me.
- Why did I go last?
- You went last.
Why did I go last?
Why did you stop saying something?
Why would you bet 2 sections?
Bet 3 sections.
- Leave us be.
- All right.
- The difficulty level will be high.
- Here comes the question.
Let's see.
This question was submitted
by Kim Jong Kook.
What's a management technique...
which involves consigning a task
to a third party?
What?
- What's a management technique...
- I don't know.
which involves consigning a task
to a third party?
- A management technique?
- Yes.
- To a third party?
- A management technique.
(Kim Jong Kook)
- Puppet boss.
- Third-party act.
- CFO.
Tell us this much.
Is the answer Korean or English?
It's English.
- English.
- Is it English?
- Agency.
- What was the question again?
It involves giving a task
to another company.
- You must have heard it often.
- I know.
- What is it?
- Is it a proverb?
- Whatever TV.
(Whatever TV?)
You are in trouble.
- You are in trouble.
- What will you do?
You are in trouble.
What will you do?
Giving a task to a third party.
- Yes.
- A third party. English.
(He pretends to know the answer.)
- How could you not know it?
- Suk Jin would know the answer.
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
Consulting.
- Come on.
- Consulting is incorrect.
- This is...
- It has three syllables.
- Three syllables?
- That's right.
And it's English?
- Yes.
- Puppet boss.
Maximus?
- Three syllables?
- Puppet boss.
Puppet boss.
(He says "Puppet boss" is
a management technique.)
You will recognize
it when you hear it.
- We will recognize it.
- This is driving me crazy.
Would you give me a letter?
Can I give them a hint?
- Give us a letter.
- You gave them many hints.
The answer has
three syllables, right?
- I will give you the first one.
- A letter.
(His gesture gives them
the first syllable.)
- What is that?
- Let's go.
It's a crucial hint.
What?
Let's go.
(He even mouths the word.)
- Let me answer.
(Suk Jin was faster!)
- Suk Jin.
- Let me answer.
- Outsourcing.
- Outsourcing. That's right.
- Didn't I say it faster?
You said it faster.
Why didn't you answer sooner?
It's basic knowledge.
- Outsourcing. Right?
- I didn't know.
- How did you know?
- I know what outsourcing is.
- I read newspapers.
- You read newspapers.
- Do you read newspapers these days?
- Outsourcing.
- What is up with you?
Didn't I say it faster?
The sections are getting cut.
- Didn't I say it faster?
- What?
(Whirring)
The sections are getting cut.
Behind them.
(The saw begins to cut
the sections.)
Behind them.
(The loud noise makes them fearful!)
This is no joke.
Behind them.
- I said it faster.
- The show became spectacular.
They are tipping forward.
(Oh!)
Stop!
We have the preview now.
- Boombastic.
No!
Boombastic!
Skrr
(The secret behind
the blockbuster-worthy preview)
Running Man must have
a lot of money for production.
There is Ji Seok Jun.
Shall we pick Ji Seok Jun?
- Sure.
- Let's go. We pick Ji Seok Jun.
Seok Jun.
- Seok Jun.
- I bet he isn't old.
- A 24-year-old.
- An aspiring civil servant.
- We will bet two sections.
- No.
Bet five sections.
- Suk Jin.
- You are weak.
- We will bet five sections.
- Okay.
Let's do this.
Instead of ten sections,
we will bet five sections.
That's life.
- How many rounds will you have?
- Let's get it right.
- End the match in five rounds.
- Ji Hyo.
This question should be easy.
This question was submitted
by Ji Seok Jun.
What's the judicial authority
of Joseon Dynasty...
that received orders from the king
to interrogate criminals?
I think I know this one.
- Joseon Dynasty.
- You have ten seconds.
- Isn't it an executioner?
- A judicial authority.
It isn't an executioner.
No?
An executioner isn't
a judicial authority.
- Hurry up.
- Three,
- Hurry up. I know the answer.
- two,
one.
- What's the answer?
- Isn't it Police Bureau?
Of course not.
- Justice Pao.
- A government office.
You criminal!
- Lock him up.
- You criminal!
- Drag him away right now.
- That's right.
- Guards!
- Guards, drag him away...
and beat him up.
- Beat him up with a paddle.
- A paddle.
If you know the answer,
give us a hint.
- It's...
- Hadongkwan.
- That restaurant has tasty food.
- That's right.
- Hadongkwan.
Feed him gukbap!
Gomtang has a refreshing taste!
It's only open till 2 a.m.
(Their ridiculous hints don't help.)
- Seriously.
- I feel like I know the answer.
- Right?
- We bet five sections.
We will know once we hear it.
Let me answer.
- Department of Justice.
- That's right.
- Okay.
- Yes!
- Let's go.
- I just remembered it.
- No!
Drag Ji Suk Jin
to Department of Justice!
I am sorry.
I will get the next one right,
Ji Hyo.
Send the criminal
to Department of Justice.
(The circular saw
cuts the sections.)
(Gosh!)
- Suk Jin is scared.
- This is nerve-racking.
This is driving me crazy.
(The circular saw goes in deep.)
- I am curious.
- Someone will...
Suk Jin, stop moving.
It cut more than five sections.
All right.
(It went a bit more.)
- Stop moving.
- It went a bit more.
We do it by hand,
so please understand.
The next one.
I am scared.
- We will go with Yang Se Eun.
- This is scary.
All right.
- A cafe.
- A 29-year-old who runs a cafe.
- Bet five sections.
- Five sections.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Five sections.
The Maori people of New Zealand
greet each other...
by rubbing a body part.
Which body part is this?
I think it's the forehead.
- Nose or forehead.
- That's right.
Let me answer.
- Go.
- Nose.
(They got the correct answer
with ease!)
- Nose.
- I was a bit uncertain.
Here we go.
(Team Jong Kook's
wooden board gets cut.)
They might fall.
(Whirring)
I think we will fall.
- Are you okay?
- I think we will fall.
Come on.
(The circular saw is
right behind them.)
Why didn't they fall yet?
I am scared.
(The onlookers are more fussy.)
- Oh, my goodness.
- No!
- They didn't fall yet.
- Oh, my goodness.
They will fall.
- Boombastic!
- They didn't fall.
- Skrr
Are you sitting at the back?
No, we aren't.
We are sitting properly.
- Jong Kook, how about Han Sang Il?
- What?
An elementary schooler
will be Kwak Si Woo.
- Would Si Woo be young?
- He would be a child.
- Would he be young?
- Yes.
- Shall we go with Si Woo?
- The name is trendy these days.
Okay. We will go with Kwak Si Woo.
I bet Si Woo is old.
He is a child. I am certain of it.
For goodness' sake.
(A 37-year-old office worker,
Kwak Si Woo)
He is in the IT industry!
What a surprise!
- Boombastic!
- What a surprise!
Is he 37 years old?
Boombastic.
He lives young.
- I bet he has a babyface.
- Yes.
- I...
- I bet he has a babyface.
Here comes the question.
- Okay.
- We won. They will fall.
What's a different term
for computer programming...
which involves making programs
with computer languages...
such as C, Java, Python, etc.?
- For goodness' sake.
I don't own a computer at home.
Who uses a computer these days?
For goodness' sake.
What's a term for making programs?
I know this one.
- Making programs?
- Yes.
For goodness' sake.
Programs?
The answer has two syllables, right?
- Making programs?
- Begin the countdown.
- Hold on.
- Five...
Making programs?
Give them a hint.
- Coding?
- Yes.
Three.
- What?
- Two.
What could it be?
- That's right.
- One.
- Really?
- That's right.
Let me answer.
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
Ji Hyo.
- Coding.
- Yes.
I see.
Coding.
We will fall.
- You never know.
- They will fall.
- We will fall.
- Let's go.
(The board is already tilted,
but five more sections will be cut!)
There is no hope.
Bye!
(Breaking)
(Jong Kook and Hee Jung are out!)
- Are you okay?
- That's scary.
(In the next match,
Jae Suk and Haha lost!)
They lasted long.
- Okay.
- Metaverse is everywhere.
Se Chan and Jeong Eui won.
(Empty Head is good at quizzes
these days.)
I finally got one answer right.
- Okay.
- Metaverse.
- Please stand at the front.
- Yes.
Yes.
- All the missions are over.
- Yes.
Women received a penalty ball
every time they got zero candies.
More penalty balls
have been added...
in accordance with the result
of each mission.
Women will have
the popularity poll for men first.
The candies you have received today
are your ballots.
(Women can use those ballots
for the popularity poll.)
You understood, right?
Those who received many candies
have many ballots.
Votes have been distributed
as per the mission results.
Combining the result
of the popularity poll...
will give us the final rankings.
(The last place
will get the penalty.)
I will now reveal
how many ballots each woman has.
- Ji Hyo has one ballot.
- Oh, no.
Ah In has three ballots.
She has a lot.
Hee Jung has four ballots.
Jeong Hui has five ballots.
Why does she have so many?
Jenny has two ballots.
Use those ballots for the poll.
The man who places last
will get the penalty.
- Without fail?
- Yes.
How many ballots does Jenny have?
Two.
Jenny.
(Se Chan suddenly becomes nice.)
Hello.
- I am in your care, Jenny.
- Jenny.
Those jerks.
"Those jerks?"
- How does Jenny have two ballots?
- Jenny.
- Those jerks.
- Come on.
Those weaklings.
- Jenny voted quickly.
- Write my name on one ballot.
- Those weaklings.
- Jenny voted so quickly.
Jenny is done voting already.
For goodness' sake.
We shouldn't pressure them.
Ah In, did you vote for me?
- All right. The results are in.
- Okay.
The men's winner.
- Winner?
- Winner.
- It's a popularity poll.
- I bet it's Suk Jin.
- I don't think it's me.
- Jong Kook.
I think it is Suk Jin.
We have three winners.
- Really?
- That's nice.
Because you got extra votes
after each mission.
- But I never won.
- I never won any mission.
- I want to be the winner.
- So we have...
- three winners here.
- Okay.
(Who are the 3 winners?)
I don't want to get a penalty.
Haha, Se Chan, and So Bal.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Are you sure?
(1 mission and 4 votes,1 mission
and 4 votes, 2 missions and 3 votes)
Jong Kook...
What happened?
- What...
- Jong Kook.
I won a lot today.
Jeong Eui, I'm so touched.
- Thank you.
I don't want to be the last.
- I don't want to be the last.
- My gosh.
Didn't she have four votes?
What happened?
And the thing is...
Didn't I win any mission?
Not even once?
I don't know.
(When she made her 2nd choice)
(Hee Jung got candies from So Bal
and Jong Kook and chose Jong Kook.)
I'm sorry.
(She felt bad for So Bal
when she was eliminated.)
(She gave 2 votes to Jong Kook
and another 2 to So Bal.)
I gave them two votes each.
Thank you.
(Thanks to her,
So Bal has survived.)
- Well...
- Suk Jin and Jong Kook.
One of you got 4 votes,
and the other got 3 votes.
It's decided by one vote.
This is unbelievable.
- I think I won twice.
- Jong Kook.
The loser with three votes is...
(The loser is decided
by only 1 vote.)
(Ah In didn't want to be
on the same team with Jong Kook.)
(And Suk Jin is
Ah In's favorite star.)
Ji Suk Jin.
- What?
- I voted for him.
- Good for you.
- I'm so relieved.
- Ah In.
- I voted for you. I'm serious.
- I really did.
How many votes?
I thought I had to split the votes.
Gosh.
You should've
given me all your votes.
Ah In knew that.
- She knew she could vote for you.
- You should've voted for me.
Ah In knew she could give
all her votes to one person.
It could've been dangerous for me.
The three winners will play
rock-paper-scissors for the prize.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- This will be my first time...
to win as a man.
- Princess Knight.
- My first time to be...
- the men's winner.
- I'll show paper.
You should keep playing as a man.
- Princess Knight.
- You are lucky as a man.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(So Bal wins?)
You're the winner.
- You must be thrilled.
- You're the men's winner.
- So Bal.
- This is my first time.
- You should carry the wig with you.
- Next week...
You should carry it around.
You look like Ahn Young Mi.
- Princess Knight.
- You're right.
You look like Ahn Young Mi.
Hey, stop it.
- You called me Ahn Young Mi.
- You're good.
Kids are watching.
- You called me Ahn Young Mi.
- That's too much.
- That's good.
- Hey.
This isn't like "Radio Star."
- Jenny.
- That's enough.
The men's winner is Jeon So Bal.
- Good job.
- She's the men's winner.
I'm so jealous.
Now we will decide
the female member to get a penalty.
I'll announce the numbers
of penalty balls.
It must be Jae Suk.
The woman with the fewest
penalty balls is the winner.
And the one with the most
penalty balls will get a penalty.
Roh Jeong Eui has one ball.
(Jeong Eui 1)
Park Ah In has two.
Song Ji Hyo has three.
Kim Hee Jung has three.
And Yoo Jenny has five.
- My goodness.
- Okay.
Roh Jeong Eui with the fewest
penalty balls is the winner.
Please bring in the prize.
- My goodness.
- You never win as a woman.
- This is my first time to win...
- As a man...
as a man.
What? This is a designer label.
- It's a designer label.
- It's Gucci.
All right. The prize for today is...
- For a man...
(For a man...)
We have a brand-name necktie.
Hey!
You can't do this to me.
You can give it to your dad.
- I mean...
- A brand-name scarf for a woman.
- Give it to your dad.
- Great.
Give it to your dad.
- Give it to your dad.
- My gosh.
- This is pretty.
- You can wear it, Jeong Eui.
- This is nice.
- So Min.
- It's pink.
- I'm envious.
This is pretty.
(She puts it on right away.)
Bombastic
(Manager Jeon is feeling excited
during the office get-together.)
Jeong Eui looks pretty.
- I'm so upset.
- She's pretty.
- It looks good on you.
- You look great, Jeong Eui.
Jenny and Suk Jin will...
My goodness.
This is your first time as a couple.
- The first couple.
- Gosh.
- That means bad luck.
- I can't believe this.
- Bombastic.
- Skrr
- I'll announce today's penalty.
- Okay.
- I'm glad you're doing this.
- Why?
- Today is White Day.
- Right.
You will make a bouquet of roses for
your beloved ones before going home.
- That's a lot of work.
- It's perfect.
- I hate it.
- All right.
- Bye.
- I'll see you later.
- I've never done this before.
- Have you tried this before?
No way.
I've never done this before.
I will...
use only one kind.
I will mix different roses.
This is pretty.
That's half-hearted.
I think red roses are pretty.
- You should use things like this.
- Gosh, no.
I just need these.
You can't be like that.
Gosh.
Actually, I'm a little shy
to buy my wife flowers.
I can use the penalty as an excuse.
My wife recently bought a vase.
In a fit of anger?
No wonder why she did.
Gosh, seriously...
Anyway, for my wife...
You're saying that too much.
That doesn't sound sincere.
When he was a newlywed,
he went to play video games
without his wife all the time.
You should know that.
- That's true.
- He was really...
The past doesn't matter.
What matters is the present.
You don't buy her flowers a lot.
Have you done this before?
Sure.
- Do you do this often?
- Yes.
What is this?
- Let go of it.
- This is...
Even a bundle of wild flowers...
would look better than this.
(It's a bouquet of unidentified
flowers that look like weeds.)
- This is like...
- What's wrong?
I can't wait
to read comments on this.
(I can't wait
to read comments on this.)
They would say, "Suk Jin is giving
a lick and a promise to go home."
- I know. That's what they say.
- Right.
What's the big deal?
We won't live for 100 years anyway.
Then why did you invest in the US funds?
(Then why did you invest in the US funds?)
I still want to live...
- well off for the 100 years.
- You say life is no big deal,
but why did you invest
so much in the US funds?
- Well...
- You prepare for the future.
I should be prepared for the 100 years.
(Now they are wrapping the flowers.)
- My gosh.
- What are you doing?
What's all this?
- This is strange.
I can't make it look pretty.
- Look at this.
- All right.
- This is different.
- What's different?
(The bouquet is done.)
This is the best I can do.
I'll give this to my wife.
That's big.
- This is it.
- This is mine.
You're done.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(We'd like to thank Jeong Eui,
Hee Jung, and Ah In...)
(for joining us today
with their cheerful energy.)
(A few days later)
- How cute.
- My puppy.
(What is Ji Hyo doing here
on Friday when she's off?)
(And Se Chan?)
This is so hilarious.
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan are
having a preliminary meeting.)
Captain Ji...
(It's Captain Ji...)
(who called them here.)
(I'm the busiest one here.)
(I'm busy.)
(Depart from games.)
(Widen our spectrum.)
(Captain Ji's last pledge
full of populism)
(No missions)
(No penalties)
(It's literally a race
where they just have fun.)
(They find everything they eat...)
(and everything
they play with themselves.)
(They do everything
they want to do.)
(It's a 100-percent
independent personalized trip.)
Fold a finger
if you are not wearing glasses.
(They are allowed
to do anything here!)
(As Captain Ji imagined,)
(they enjoy their freedom
to the fullest.)
(Right at the moment...)
(A suspicious secret
that interrupts their free time?)
(It was one o'clock earlier.)
This is strange.
The pens are everywhere.
(It's somewhat suspicious.)
(Captain Ji's retirement trip)
(Captain Ji's
Imagination Comes True)