Hello.
The weather is nice today.
Hey, you're here. Hi.
Hello.
Gosh, it's been a while
since I came here last time.
- This place is...
- Hello.
- I come here when I go cycling.
- A convenience store.
I used to come here a lot.
Are we going to eat ramyeon
at the Han River?
This is where we eat ramyeon.
- Hello.
- Let's eat ramyeon.
- Ramyeon at the Han River.
- This is a place for ramyeon.
I had breakfast.
- I ate too.
- Where? Banpo?
- Yes.
- My gosh.
- Are we going to sit here?
- Are you in there?
Are you in there?
(An unwelcome guest shows up.)
It's like a car wash.
- Excuse me.
- Anyone in there?
A table for three.
I'm here too.
- Hey.
- Go in.
This is a car wash.
- Excuse me.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- This is a car wash.
Wash yourself.
Why would he wear something like that?
Bring the camera. This is a car wash.
- It's a car wash.
- A car wash.
Se Chan is all dressed up today.
Why aren't you saying anything?
- Who?
- Don't I look cute?
- This is perfect for the Han River.
- He's dressed up.
You're dressed like a boyfriend's friend.
No, this is what cute boyfriends wear.
- It's called the boyfriend look.
- The boyfriend's friend look.
Se Chan is quite a dresser.
- Did you go to a beauty shop?
- Yes, I did.
- Why?
- That's interesting.
The beauty shop is only
a seven-minute walk from my house.
- But you...
- So did you go to a beauty shop?
Yes. My gosh, Jae Suk!
So did you go to a beauty shop?
(Disheveled hair)
What are you doing? This is...
- I got my hair done.
- It's okay. It looks natural.
- I can't believe this.
- Why? It's nice.
- It looks natural.
- What do you think you're doing?
All right.
- We really wanted to do this.
- It's like stepping on a new shoe.
- I know.
- He's unstoppable.
(Tidying his hair)
Why do you keep
going to a beauty shop these days?
What? Jae Suk, please.
- We have news about Suk Jin.
- What?
What is it?
Seriously?
- Really?
- What?
- But...
- What's that?
- You?
No way.
- Did you go there?
- Was it on the news?
He attended the wedding.
- What?
- Was it on the news?
- Did you attend the wedding?
- On the news?
(They can't believe their ears.)
Why did you go to Hyun Bin
and Son Ye Jin's wedding?
- "Ji Suk Jin wasn't invited."
- What?
- "But he..."
- Did you really go?
- Why?
- Why did you go there?
Why did you go?
- Which one do you know?
- Was it for your YouTube channel?
- Has he lost his mind?
- No way.
Does he know Son Ye Jin's parents?
I didn't know
they were holding a wedding there.
I just went there for work.
- Why did you go?
- It was for work.
- Why would you do that?
- This is embarrassing.
Why did you go there
when you weren't invited?
I know neither of them.
- Does he work at a wedding hall?
- Why did you go then?
- For work.
- What did you do there?
- For work?
- To do a TV show.
- This is really embarrassing.
- I had a shoot there.
You're lying. You went there
to film the wedding.
- Shame on you.
- As if it was a coincidence.
- I'm so sorry.
- Seriously...
- It's funny it was on the news.
- I apologize.
- That's unbelievable.
- "Uninvited Ji Suk Jin."
- That's the worst.
- I just went to work.
The reporters... This is upsetting.
- Why did you go there?
- Hey.
I'm not the kind of person
who sneaks into a stranger's wedding.
- You must've been dressed up.
- Of course.
I bet he was all dressed up.
He just goes around
attending top stars' weddings.
Don't you have any pride?
What did I do?
Why did you go there
when you weren't invited?
- You're Ji Suk Jin of Running Man.
- "Uninvited Ji Suk Jin."
- Hey.
- I'm so upset.
Why did they not invite him?
I went there at 11 a.m.
when the wedding was at 4 p.m.
- Why did you go there so early?
- At 11...
- You should be there at 3:50 p.m.
- What's wrong with you?
- Why did you go so early?
- You're ridiculous.
You must've told your wife this.
"I'm going to the wedding."
"Whose wedding?"
"Son Ye Jin and Hyun Bin."
But you weren't invited.
- That's unbelievable.
- He wasn't invited.
- By the way...
- And he told his manager.
"I need to go to a wedding.
Make a beauty shop appointment."
Seriously.
- Gosh, that's hilarious.
- You're really...
We're at the Han River after a long time.
Today, you will go around
many shops and stores...
spending as much money as you want.
It's called
How Much Do You Want to Spend Race.
You will each choose
one of the debit cards...
in the production crew's names.
I see.
The seven cards have
certain amounts of money...
ranging from 10 dollars to 200 dollars...
in them.
But you will start the race
without figuring out...
the amount of money in your card.
I see.
Now you will number yourselves
by playing a game.
- Then we will pay.
- Yes. Number one goes first.
And you can pay as much as you want.
The last one to go
will have to pay the balance.
- My goodness.
- What if you are short of money?
Those who go broke
will be a slave right away.
- Oh, no.
- We will have slaves.
A slave will serve the members
in the slave costume.
If you become a slave,
you have to use your own card.
- Really?
- Yes. Do you understand?
- That would be the worst.
- I don't want to go broke.
And the one with the least
amount of money...
will be the winner at the end of the race.
Those who go broke or have more
than ten dollars will get a penalty.
- We can't spend much money.
- Not the one with the most money?
- I see.
- We should spend less money.
I mean, we should spend
a moderate amount of money.
If you have 200 dollars,
you will have to spend...
- quite a lot to win the race.
- That's right.
All right. Now you will pick
the debit cards to use today.
- We never know what to choose.
- I can't tell.
It's from 10 to 200 dollars.
Don't let So Min pick first.
They have names on them.
You should take the head writer's card.
It must have the biggest amount.
(Team producer, head writer,
second producer, second writer)
(Administrative producer,
junior producer, junior writer)
- The team producer's.
- I pick Ju Yong's.
- What about Hyung In's?
- No. I pick Hyung In's.
- You should pick Hyung In.
- I want Ju Yong.
- I pick Bo Pil.
- Hey.
I picked yours.
- Bo Pil.
- Hyung In is in charge of me.
- Ju Yong, are you sure?
- The man of Sunday.
I wonder if there's a twist.
That's the problem.
- Right.
- I bet there's a twist.
- What about Hyung In's?
- I pick Ji Yeon's.
- You should pick Hyung In.
- I want Bo Pil.
Hey. Se Chan picked Ji Yeon's card.
Ji Yeon, I picked you.
Ji Yeon, I picked your card.
(He bets the junior producer's
card has more money.)
Hyung In is...
Ju Yong, I picked you.
(Suk Jin hesitates.)
- I...
- Bo Pil.
(And he picks the junior writer's card.)
I think I picked the wrong one.
The junior writer...
You can't take it back.
- Let me change...
- It must have a lot of money.
- You think?
- Yes.
Ji Yeon? All right.
Why?
(So Min picks the head writer's card.)
It must have a lot of money.
- You think?
- I pick Seo Rim.
(Jae Suk is done choosing a card.)
- You each picked a card.
- Yes.
The first place where you will use
your card is the convenience store.
- Do you see the store behind you?
- Yes.
You can pick anything
you want to eat or use...
at the store now.
- I should eat ramyeon.
- Without paying?
- We just put them in a bag?
- I just had breakfast.
- Me too.
- I ate too.
- I'll eat ramyeon.
- That doesn't happen a lot.
I'll eat something sweet.
- I should buy some batteries.
- In the morning...
- Batteries?
- Hey.
- Why would you buy batteries?
- You always buy daily necessities.
- Batteries.
Why would you buy household goods here?
- Why would you buy batteries?
- You'll be rich.
- I will buy a mat.
- Hello.
- Why a mat?
- No reason.
Se Chan, you should buy
some dog food here.
That's a good idea.
- Hello.
Hello.
It's a convenience store.
Should I eat some ramyeon?
- Let's eat ramyeon.
- I should probably eat ramyeon.
Let's share it.
- Can we cook ramyeon here?
- Cooked ramyeon.
They have everything here.
- So Min
- Where are the eggs?
- Eggs?
- I'll have ramyeon.
I'll eat ramyeon.
- Bombastic.
- Where...
We click well, don't we?
- Yes.
- Yaman.
Yaman. Bombastic.
I should buy a protein bar.
I will buy a box of Band-Aid.
Jae Suk, why would you
buy a daily necessity?
You should buy something to eat.
I'm out of Band-Aids.
That doesn't matter.
My goodness.
Do they sell disposable batteries
for smartphones?
- Suk Jin.
- This is nice.
- Why are you being like this?
- What?
Why do you buy a daily necessity?
It's not like that.
- Hydrogen peroxide.
- Should I buy some batteries?
What? Is this a battery club or what?
The world has become
much easier to live in.
- I will...
- I'll buy these.
(Ramyeon, egg,
sparkling water, pickled radish)
Why are you nitpicking at what I eat?
Milk.
Chopsticks.
- What are you buying?
- I picked chocolate balls.
- And almonds.
- I knew you'd buy them.
I guess you all are having ramyeon.
You're dressed like a kid today,
so you look like a kid.
I do?
I'm 44.
Am I supposed to add
the seasoning at the beginning?
Put them all in together.
- You should add an egg.
- It's boiling.
- You know you should stir it well.
- It looks good.
It's always good to eat ramyeon outside.
- Enjoy.
- Look at this ramyeon.
- I think I made a good choice.
- I know.
The ramyeon does look delicious.
This is amazing.
(The young members of Running Man
start eating ramyeon.)
You have to eat it.
This is really good.
(Amazed)
- This is crazy.
- It's so tasty.
- It's really good.
- Almond. Protein.
- Almonds are good for men.
- Really?
I was going to make
almond cookies for you.
You should've made them.
You can make them today.
- Make them today.
- I'll have some.
- That day...
- I want them too.
I should've had a cooking class.
It would've been great.
- You think?
- I love my cookies.
Who bought this mat?
- Jae Suk bought the mat.
- Why?
- He bought the mat.
- You need this at the Han River.
- That's true.
It can also be a fashion accessory.
- Like a bag.
- You can wear it like a bag.
- It's a mat bag.
- You should go like this.
(The Han River fashion)
Wait, Jae Suk.
Why do you need glue at the Han River?
- Why did you buy glue?
- And Band-Aids.
- Why?
I need to fix Na Eun's toy.
- He pretends to be a family man.
- My gosh.
- Don't buy household goods here.
- Na Eun's toy is broken.
- I need to fix it.
- My gosh.
You bought it because I bought one.
- You imitated me.
- Why did you buy it?
- Do you...
- I had no time...
- Do you know why he bought glue?
- Why?
To bond with his wife.
(Overreacting)
Go ahead and bond with her.
- Hey.
- Good one, right?
- You're on fire.
- We already have a special bond.
- He says I'm on fire.
- Jae Suk is so funny.
I'm on fire today.
There he goes again.
Why is he so excited today?
He's like that when we eat.
Have you been taking some herbal medicine?
No.
You pass out at home
after doing this, right?
- No.
- After making a fuss all day.
I can't rest at home.
- Then again, you have two kids.
- I can't rest.
I had a fight with Ji Ho yesterday.
You did?
(He had a fight with his son.)
- Yes.
- It's funny you fought with him.
- We had a fight.
- How old is he?
Ji Ho is 13.
- Really?
- He's about that age.
- He must be feisty at that age.
- He is feisty.
This is really delicious.
- Everyone.
- Yes.
Now it's time to pay.
- Really?
- I really enjoyed the food.
You spent 99.9 dollars
at this convenience store.
- That's not a lot.
- That's a lot.
- You should determine the order.
For what?
The order of payment.
Number one will go first,
and you can pay as much as you want.
- As much as I want?
- Yes.
- That's a good thing.
- It is.
- All right then.
- I want to pay.
Let's play the Game of Wits.
I'm at a disadvantage.
- Why?
- Why are you at a disadvantage?
- I'm not good at the game.
What game do you want to play?
Tipcat?
- I like rock-paper-scissors.
- Tipcat?
- Rock-paper-scissors?
- That's not fun.
- Let's play the Game of Wits.
- Rock-paper-scissors is not fun.
I hate those who want to play
rock-paper-scissors in the morning.
- This is really upsetting.
- He's upset.
Is the Game of Wits fun?
You're upset.
I'm sick and tired of the Game of Wits.
- Why are you yelling?
- It's not like that.
- Hey.
- I can't believe this.
There are a lot of guys
doing this at the Han River.
This happens a lot at the Han River.
Why are you yelling?
(They are fighting over a game
while having fun.)
- Jae Suk, let's just...
- Let's play 007 Bang.
- The 007 Bang game?
- The Silent 007 Bang game.
All right. Let's do that.
The one who loses
the game is the last one to go.
- It goes in reverse order.
- Okay.
Silent.
- Like this.
- Okay.
- You should start like this.
- I'm not supposed to shout, right?
- You should raise your hands.
- Okay.
You should start like this.
Why would we do that? Don't lie to me.
- That's true.
- We have to do this.
- It's a lie.
- That's true.
- How dare you...
- I'm telling you the truth.
- You made a fool of me.
- He's being weird. Are you drunk?
(A drunk man found at the Han River)
- My gosh.
- What are you doing?
I was sitting like this.
Suk Jin is being weird today.
- What's with you?
- Suk Jin.
- This is the rule.
- I'll do this instead.
- I can do anything.
- Just do anything you want.
It starts as I'm done drawing a star.
- Am I the first one to go?
- Yes.
(Zero, zero, seven)
(Bang)
- You should raise your arms.
- He's out.
You should raise your arms.
- You're out.
- You lost.
- Why did you not do it?
- What's wrong with you?
- He's doing this.
- What's with you?
- He's doing this now.
- He's out.
- He's being like this.
What's with you?
- You're out.
He's the first one to pay.
- No, he's the last one.
- The last.
- That was a rehearsal.
- You're the last.
- Jong Kook.
- Me?
- Do it again.
This is it.
(Zero, zero, seven)
(Bang)
(Defense succeeded)
(Zero, zero, seven)
(Bang)
- That was late.
- You were late. You're out.
(So Min was late, so she's out.)
Again.
- The five of us are left.
- Got it.
(Zero, zero, seven)
(Bang)
(Zero, zero, seven, bang!)
- I'm dead.
- He's out.
(Haha is out because he pointed
at Suk Jin who was already out.)
- Stay focused.
- What's with you guys?
- He's been dead for a while.
- You're out.
- I lost in the first round.
- Out.
(Number 5, 6, and 7)
- Ji Hyo goes first.
- This is difficult.
(Zero, zero, seven?)
(He points at Se Chan and then himself.)
- You're out.
- What are you doing?
You pointed at me.
- Why did you point at yourself?
- What was that?
- Why did you...
- I was in a hurry.
- What was that?
- I was in a rush.
- Why did you do that?
- What were you doing?
I was in a hurry.
(He feels nervous when he plays games.)
- The three of us are left.
- Three.
- Shall we play rock-paper-scissors?
- Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors
Okay.
- Spend ten dollars.
- All right then.
Number one goes first.
You can pay as much as you want
among the 99 dollars.
- Spend 10 dollars.
- Pay 10 dollars.
You're the first one to go.
You should pay ten dollars.
Number 1 should pay 10 dollars.
The least amount is 0.1 dollars.
Can I pay 0.1 dollars?
You promised you'd pay ten dollars.
I'm just asking.
(Se Chan picked
the junior producer's card.)
Gosh today...
I will...
I'll spend all my money.
How much is it in total?
It's 99.9 dollars.
(The total amount is 99.9 dollars.)
(Junior producer, Go Ji Yeon)
(He pays the amount he wants
with the junior producer's card.)
Payment completed.
- Thank you.
- Please remove your card.
- Do I pay here?
- Yes.
(Next up is Jong Kook.)
I'll pay.
Here's my card.
(And Ji Hyo is done making the payment.)
- Who's next?
- Jae Suk.
How much did you pay?
You'll see.
Welcome.
(He checks the balance.)
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
It is 99.6 dollars.
(The balance is 99.6 dollars.)
It's 99.9 dollars.
I'll pay 0.1 dollars.
(Transaction for 0.1 dollars at 25)
Really?
Then I'll pay 0.1 dollars.
It is 99.6 dollars.
(Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo
paid 0.1 dollars each.)
- You guys are so mean.
- Why?
Why?
My goodness.
You know you should
spend some money, right?
- I know. This is the beginning.
- I spent a lot.
(The remaining members are
feeling anxious.)
We don't need to spend too much.
(The second writer, Gang Seo Rim)
I'll pay 0.1 dollars.
(Transaction for 0.1 dollars
at 25, Han River Banpo Store 1)
Thank you.
You should spend as much as I did.
You punks.
I know you paid 0.1 dollars.
How much did you pay?
How much is the balance?
It's 99.5 dollars.
Did you say 99.5 dollars?
Is it 99.5 dollars?
(It hardly made a dent
in the total amount.)
Then I'll pay 0.1 dollars as well.
No, I'll pay 0.2 dollars.
(Team producer, Choi Bo Pil)
Hang on.
I don't have to do this.
(Team producer, Choi Bo Pil)
(Those who go broke or have more
than ten dollars get a penalty.)
Why did they pay only 0.1 dollars?
Isn't ten dollars the least amount?
- Then I'll pay nine dollars.
- Nine dollars.
(Haha paid almost ten dollars.)
- Payment completed.
- Thank you.
(Transaction for 9 dollars
at 25, Han River Banpo Store 1)
This is Hyo Im's card.
I'm sure she has 100 dollars.
She's the head writer for a reason.
She must have 100 dollars.
Maybe...
- Hello.
Well...
(Head Writer, Yang Hyo Im)
I'll pay 30 dollars.
- Thirty dollars?
- Yes.
(So Min goes bold from the start.)
- I'll put it in.
- Yes.
(If she doesn't have enough amount,
she'll be the slave immediately.)
I'm sure there's
more than 30 dollars in it.
(Payment in progress,
payment amount: 30 dollars)
- Payment completed.
- Oh, my.
- Please remove your card.
- It's done.
(Transaction for 30 dollars
at 25, Han River Banpo Store 1)
(So Min had more than 30 dollars
in the beginning.)
There's 60 dollars and 50 cents
left to pay.
Thank you.
- Goodbye.
- Thank you.
Goodbye.
You shouldn't save too much money either.
Suk Jin, I said I would pay.
Is there a chance
I don't have to spend any money?
- Yes.
- Great.
- Suk Jin, I...
- Yes?
I can imagine you in the slave costume.
(His fate depends on the amount
of money on his card.)
- Do slaves talk formerly to us?
- I mean...
Will he be a slave if he goes bankrupt?
Go on, Mr. Slave.
- Slave number one.
- Whose card did you choose?
I picked the youngest writer's card.
I see. Well...
Could I become a slave from the start?
Please pay here.
My gosh, those punks.
How much do we have left to pay?
The remaining amount is
60 dollars and 50 cents.
(The amount to pay: 60.5 dollars)
Gosh, seriously.
If it's declined, I'll be a slave.
Right? I have to pay
60 dollars and 50 cents.
Did you say 60 dollars and 50 cents?
Yes, that's the remaining amount.
- Sixty dollars and fifty cents?
- Yes.
(It's time to pay 60.5 dollars,
which will determine his future.)
This is driving me nuts.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
It could be declined.
Please.
(Seok Sam is praying solemnly.)
(Insert your card.
Payment amount: 60.5 dollars)
(Youngest Writer, Jang Ye Bin)
Please.
What?
(What could Suk Jin's fate be?)
- Okay.
- Suk Jin, don't cheat.
- Suk Jin must've paid it all.
- Right.
- It's taking him so long.
- I'm sure...
- that he'll dress as a slave.
- Maybe his card has been declined.
- Okay. Whatever happens in life,
- Did it work?
- I should enjoy every moment.
- I guess he won't be a slave.
I bet he's saved.
- That's life.
- I bet it worked.
- Did it work?
- Absolutely.
I bet it worked.
- That's life.
- It worked?
Right? That's life.
- All right, everyone.
- Look. They look so busy now.
They're in such a hurry.
One of them is bringing the costume.
It's crazy.
They're moving around so busily now.
- Suk Jin, are you a slave now?
- The staff members are in a hurry.
- They're preparing the costume.
- Exactly.
- They're all working busily.
- Is this a prank?
- Aren't you a slave?
- No.
- The total was 99.9 dollars.
- Yes.
The amount that was paid
before Suk Jin was...
- thirty-nine point four dollars.
- Really?
- I think So Min spent a lot.
- Right.
- So Min must've spent so much.
- And Suk Jin had to pay...
- sixty dollars and fifty cents.
- I guess So Min paid a big portion.
- Suk Jin's debit card...
- Yes.
(How much did his card have?)
- had ten dollars.
- My gosh.
Oh, no.
(Ye Bin's card was declined
due to insufficient funds.)
- He went broke.
- He's a slave now.
- He's a slave.
- Poor him.
- That's unbelievable.
- He had the one with ten dollars.
- You had only ten dollars, Ye Bin.
- What should we do?
- That means we had more than that.
- Ye Bin.
This is unbelievable.
Please.
(Earlier on)
(Pay)
(Payment in progress)
- Doesn't it work?
- Payment failed.
Please try again.
(The youngest writer's card had
only ten dollars.)
It says you have insufficient funds.
(He came in last in the game
when he had the least amount.)
- That means we had more than that.
- Ye Bin.
This is unbelievable.
- We have our first slave now.
- So Min, I didn't know...
- you'd spend that much.
- I can't believe I picked this one.
- How come he picked that one?
- One hundred dollars?
- He almost switched it to another.
- Right.
- I was going to switch it.
- Only ten dollars.
How did you pick the card
with ten dollars?
How would I know?
I can't believe you picked
the one with ten dollars.
Hey, how could you give
the youngest writer ten dollars?
- That was unexpected.
- Suk Jin, change your clothes.
We'll get going when he's back.
- Seok Sam is a slave. Okay.
- Okay.
He's the slave number one.
- He'll serve us, right?
- Yes.
Hey, Seok Sam.
- I'm not a slave yet.
- That's okay.
Okay. Let's go.
I'm ready. Okay.
Haha has to go number two.
My gosh.
You said it, Haha.
As if she had never used a toilet. Gosh.
- I told you, I have no anus.
- That's a lie.
- My gosh.
- You're a celebrity. Do you poop?
- Of course, I poop.
- Really? I didn't know that.
I've flushed the toilet
because you didn't.
(He got caught.)
I didn't see that coming.
Can you believe this slave?
It's taking him so long.
Seok Sam!
Let's go without him.
The slave hasn't come yet.
Gosh, he's taking too long.
He'll ride a horse to catch up.
- We used to leave him behind.
- But if we do that today,
- he'll get so mad.
- He should walk all the way there.
- Does he seem sensitive today?
- Yes, very much so.
Actually, Suk Jin loses his temper
so often lately.
He seems awfully sensitive today.
- He's going through menopause.
- I think so too.
- He gets hot flashes too.
- Well, I think...
Maybe he simply has diva syndrome.
- DS?
- Right.
- "DS"?
- He acts like a diva.
- Let's call it DS.
- Okay.
But I feel sorry for him.
I want to be nice to him.
- He might slack off.
- Think about it.
- He went there uninvited.
- Exactly.
That's just...
- It made me feel...
- That was surprising.
- That's sad.
- It's so sad.
- Let's be nice to him.
- Okay.
- Right. Suk Jin...
- Hey.
He's here.
- He's here.
- Seok Sam.
How dare you?
- Sit here, Seok Sam.
- Yes, my lord.
- Thank you.
- You look better in this costume.
I agree. Suk Jin, you look
more comfortable in it.
Why? We're just role-playing.
- Shouldn't he be polite to us?
- Come on, Suk Jin.
- Haha is right, Suk Jin.
- I just looked.
- Okay. Don't...
- Yes.
- Do not glare at me.
- I just looked. That's all.
- Understood.
- How old are you, Slave?
- Don't do that again.
- I'm 57, my lord.
(Slave Ji is 57 years old.)
"I'm 57, my lord."
- "I'm 57, my lord."
- That's right.
Did you pay for getting older faster?
How much money did you spend on it?
Why did you spend so much money
when you had only ten dollars?
It wasn't like that.
I expected you to pay...
a bigger portion than that.
- Seok Jjeon.
- Yes?
- "Seok Jjeon"?
- Who is Seok Jjeon?
- Seok Jjeon.
- I like that nickname.
- I like it too.
Seok Sam, I'll fix your headband.
- Why did you tie it like this?
- That's so kind of him.
- Indeed.
- He's so nice.
Pull it tightly.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
That makes you feel dizzy.
You start feeling dizzy in ten minutes.
- It does make you feel dizzy.
- Yes.
- It leaves dents on the forehead.
- Oh, dear.
I will try my very best
to keep you all in a good mood.
Until we have another slave.
- Seok Sam.
- Yes, my lord.
Why don't you sing for us
to keep us entertained?
- Let us hear you sing.
- Right. Sing for us.
- All right.
- Seok Sam.
(Look at me)
- Look at me
- How dare you ruin the mood?
- Sing it without using vibrato.
- Sing a K-pop song.
- Slap him in the face.
- The latest songs.
(He starts singing a K-pop song
after getting scolded.)
(I can feel)
- Stop. That's your problem.
- Your warm breath
- Breath
- Exactly.
- He has a bad habit.
- That's your habit.
You must quit doing that to be successful.
- Get rid of that habit, Seok Sam.
- My gosh.
- How dare you sing like that?
- Sing like this. I can
- Slap him in the face.
- Feel
Stop saying that.
(Emotionally exhausted)
I can feel
- I'll try again.
- That's a bad habit.
- That's right.
- Suk Jin with a bad singing habit.
(I can feel)
It's weird.
(Seok Sam can't sing
without his usual singing method.)
It's really weird, my lord.
- I can feel
- "It's really weird, my lord."
- How dare you talk back to us?
- I can feel
Slap him in the face.
- Stop saying that.
- Stop it.
(While Seok Sam keeps
getting slapped in the face...)
(They arrived at the 2nd place,
M personal color center in Gangnam.)
(All the colors in the world
gathered here.)
(What will they do at the 2nd place?)
- Please come this way.
- Okay.
- What's this?
- Seok Sam.
- This is pretty.
- Look at that bag.
- It suits my outfit color, right?
- Yes.
- That's a pretty color.
- Please have a seat.
- That's pretty.
- What's this?
I see a lot of nice T-shirts there.
It seems like we'll have to spend
a lot of money here.
We're here for the second activity,
the personal color test,
which is very popular
with people in their 20s and 30s.
- Really?
- Yes.
Why didn't I know this?
I know all the popular things.
These days, this is a popular place
to go on a date as well.
- A place like this is?
- Really? On a date?
- Yes, to find out the best color...
- That's new.
- Okay. I'll try it until next week.
- Then So Min should sit here.
Go ahead.
(Come over here.)
(Seducing her boyfriend)
- I almost moved to that sofa.
- Hey.
- People around me criticized you.
- You should sit next to her.
- Why?
- They would say,
- "Who is he to keep a distance..."
- They criticized me?
"from So Min?"
- People around me...
- It wasn't like that.
- That's not the case.
Se Chan had a girlfriend
when he kept his distance from her.
Really? Then don't you have
a girlfriend now?
- Do you have a girlfriend or not?
- His pronunciation was weird.
- What was that?
- He can't pronounce words properly.
- Answer me. Are you single?
- Suk Jin...
used to be yelled at as he imitated
dialects poorly in a comedy skit.
- Do you have a girlfriend? Tell me.
- I can imagine that.
- No, I don't.
- Do you have a girlfriend or not?
- I don't have a girlfriend.
- Suk Jin...
- Suk Jin should thank me.
- I don't have a girlfriend.
- Why?
- I introduced him to his wife.
- Exactly.
- Right. He owes you.
I also set him up...
- with his ex-girlfriend.
- What?
- What did you say?
- Did you?
- What are you talking about?
- That's TMI.
- Are we talking about the old days?
- Right.
- Right. I get it.
- It's true. I set him up with her.
You met your ex-girlfriend at a club
because I asked her to join us.
He asked her to join them?
- I can't believe you.
- What?
- Is that true?
- You've crossed the line.
- Why?
- Do you want me to keep going?
- He must know something else.
(Whispering)
I can... What's going on?
Why did you turn around?
- Whenever you guys talk about it,
- What is it? I'm upset.
Haha suddenly becomes so quiet.
- That's so interesting.
- Don't mess with me. I know things.
- That's scary.
- Be careful.
- I haven't done anything.
- There's nothing wrong with it.
- What?
- That's true.
- Goodness.
You must be good to her.
Jong Kook became quiet too.
- He also...
- They seem to know...
- about each other's past.
- He also...
He just didn't make it official.
I have nothing to hide.
- We never talk about it...
- I have no secrets.
only because you're good at fighting.
(We never talk about it
because you're strong.)
- He might beat you up.
- What?
- That's the only reason.
- That's true.
I'm itching to blurt it out.
Now, let's meet CEO Kang A Ra,
an image consultant...
and a colorist who will help you
find the best colors for you.
CEO Kang A Ra.
- Hello.
- Oh, my. Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
Her shoes are so flashy.
- That's unexpected.
- She's in killer heels.
Is this your personal color, Ms. Kang?
- Yes, it is.
- How pretty.
- You got all dolled up.
- Yes, I did.
- Please have a seat.
- Sit down, please.
I invited you all here today
to help you find...
- the best colors for you,
- That's great.
- your personal colors.
- I see.
I didn't know there was a place like this.
Is this a hot place?
I'm planning to make it one.
I'm trying to make it popular.
- That was an honest answer.
- I like that.
- I'm going to make it happen.
- She could've said it was popular.
- I'm sure many will visit here...
- I can't lie.
- after watching this.
- Suddenly,
I'm confused about where I am.
- "Sixth Sense"?
- Is this real or fake?
I got confused as well.
- "Sixth Sense"?
- This place looks...
- Running Man is real.
- Jae Suk,
- don't you think this is fake?
- What?
- No, it's real.
- It all looks fake.
- It doesn't look real.
- It looks fake somehow.
- I'll give you an introduction.
- Yes.
Here's what a personal color test
is about.
There are colors with yellow tints...
like the sunlight in the afternoon...
and with warm feelings.
They're called warm tone colors.
Warm tone colors?
And there are colors with blue tints...
and cool, refreshing feelings like
the sunlight in the early morning.
- They're called cool tone colors.
- That sounds nice too.
Simply put, people wear...
- gold and silver accessories.
- Yes.
Some people look better with gold
while the others look better...
- with silver.
- I look amazing with gold.
- Oh, you do?
- But you have a cool skin tone.
- Then you should get gold teeth.
- He has a cool skin tone.
(Then you should get gold teeth.)
Why would you go so extreme?
- He said he looked good with gold.
- Gosh, seriously.
First, we're going to find out
if you look better...
- in warm or cold colors.
- Oh, I see.
- Do people do things like this?
- I've never tried this before.
- And then,
- I'm curious.
we'll have a look at different colors...
using fabrics for the test
to find your personal colors.
- It sounds expensive.
- I understand.
- By the way...
- It must cost a lot of money.
How much is the test per person?
- It depends on the type of test.
- The price...
- It starts from 100 dollars.
- What?
- One hundred dollars?
- That's not so bad.
- It's so expensive.
- We'll all become slaves.
- We'll go broke.
- We'll get...
- a discount.
- Of course.
- Oh, we'll get a discount.
- A large group gets a discount.
- The more people,
- Of course, we'll get a discount.
- the bigger discount.
- Of course.
- I'm relieved. If it's 100 dollars,
- Okay.
- we'd go broke.
- We can only spend limited amount.
- We'll all go broke except for two.
- We're on a mission now.
- Oh, I see.
- Yes.
- Let's begin. Who will go first?
- Okay. Then...
Shall we start with Se Chan?
- Me?
- Se Chan will go first.
- Please sit here.
- He looks better in warm colors.
You don't look good at all in that color.
You look like you're sick.
- I look good in light colors.
- Now...
- You do look good in light colors.
- Se Chan looks great...
- in vivid colors.
- But I rarely wear such colors.
- He looks good in bright colors.
- He wouldn't look good with gold.
I don't think I've ever thought
about the best color for me.
- I've never thought about it.
- Right.
- I always choose light colors.
- I just pick colors I like.
I like anything that's expensive.
Now, we're going to see
if you look better...
- in warm or cool colors...
- Yes.
- using gold and silver fabrics.
- Okay.
I'll put the gold one in front of him.
If you see his face,
his skin looks more yellowish.
His face looks a little bit sallow.
- His skin looks...
- I mean...
- In that color, he reminds me...
- His face looks a bit yellow.
- of "Comedy Big League".
- As if he had jaundice.
- He looks sallow in gold.
- Right.
He looks like a rockfish
with an edible gold leaf on it.
- As if he'd been constipated,
- A sashimi restaurant...
- his face turns yellow.
- It made his face look sallow.
- Let's try the silver color.
- Let's see.
- It makes his face glow, right?
- He doesn't look too great.
- His face looks so bright now.
- Don't I look like a hairtail?
My reflection in the mirror
totally looks like a hairtail.
I think he must go back to the sea.
- He looks neat...
- I think he looks much better now.
- This one is much better.
- Right.
- His skin looks firmer now as well.
- This is so fascinating.
- You're right. I can see that.
- Right.
You look like a braised mackerel.
- Come on. Did I look better?
- You looked completely different...
- from when you were in gold.
- I looked better in silver?
- I see.
- You do look better in silver.
This is amazing.
I've never done this before.
- Now, we'll look at various colors.
- Yes.
- We'll check four shades of purple.
- I love purple.
- Four shades?
- We'll see four shades of purple.
- Four shades of purple.
- It makes his skin look darker.
- This is light, warm-toned purple.
- Well... I think...
- In this color...
- He doesn't look so great in it.
That's right.
His cheeks look a little bit red.
And I think this color makes
his mustache stand out.
- And his lips...
- Because he looks like a catfish.
He has a mustache like that of a catfish.
- He looks like a fish.
- I don't have a full mustache.
- He has a face like a catfish.
- This time,
let's try a cool-toned color
that people often wear in summer.
- He looks so neat, right?
- He looks better in it.
- It flatters his skin tone.
- Really?
- In the warm-toned color...
- Hold on a second.
Even before you showed the second color,
you said, "He looks so neat, right?"
You said it as you revealed it.
- You said it as you revealed it.
- I tried to...
- make it sound more convincing.
- I can't see it.
- She made us believe it.
- Exactly.
- I mean, after looking at it...
- She said it before dropping it.
- Right.
- Look. He looks great, right?
- That's exactly what she did.
- Look.
(He looks great, right?)
- Did you see that?
- She said it before it fell down.
- See? I think...
- That's...
- She's like a salesperson.
- She has her own pattern.
- She forced the idea on us.
- I guess...
- She must've done some research.
- She already knew our colors.
- That's my secret.
- She knew once she saw us.
- She was supposed to let us...
- Right.
- think about it before saying that.
- You see,
it's like how hypnosis works.
- He looks better in cool colors...
- Cool colors.
- than in warm colors.
- He looks better in cool colors.
- He's a cool tone guy.
- I see.
- I was wrong about that.
- That is,
he's better with a silver hairtail
than a gold ax.
- This color isn't for him.
- He doesn't look good in it.
- This is a warm-toned, a bit dark,
- elegant color for autumn.
- That doesn't suit him.
- That's right.
- It doesn't suit him.
- It makes his skin look less firm.
- That's right.
- His skin looks rough.
- Next up is a cool-toned color...
for winter, and he looks...
- He looks good in this color.
- It's not bad,
but he looks as if he were
dominated by darkness.
- Dominated by darkness?
- What is she talking about?
- I'm dominated by darkness?
- My gosh.
Hey, you must be possessed
by an evil spirit.
You think I'm possessed by an evil spirit?
- It makes him look that way.
- He's dominated by darkness.
- That color was nice. Indeed.
- It's fascinating.
I see the different looks
that different colors create.
- I see that too.
- It's interesting.
There are various shades of red
used to make lipsticks.
- It doesn't suit him at all.
- He doesn't look good in it.
It makes his face look a little bluish.
- It makes his face look lifeless.
- I think it's not so bad.
- It makes his face looks bluish...
- But...
But he looks so great in this color.
(He looks great in this color.)
Give us some time to think.
- I mean...
- Take a look at him first.
I couldn't even see it.
While I was blinking,
- she dropped it.
- You should look at him first.
- She didn't even see it.
- This is strange.
- I couldn't see it.
- You should look at him first.
- She wouldn't care what we think.
- I mean, this is...
- My goodness.
- It's a cool-toned, summer color.
- It's a cool color.
- He does look great in it though.
- Yes, he does.
- He looks much better in this.
Let's try a warm-toned
maple leaf color for autumn.
- He doesn't look great.
- It's a little dark for his skin.
- I think it's not so bad.
- And it makes his face...
- look a little yellow.
- He doesn't look sophisticated.
Now, let's check out this cool color.
He looks more calm and neat.
- You're right. He looks calm.
- He looks better in this one.
That's right.
- You see, Ms. Kang...
- I'm not so sure about it.
says, "That's right"
when we agree with her.
- She won't listen to us.
- When we don't,
she says, "But rather than this color..."
She must've done research before we came.
- Let's compare pastel colors now.
- He looks good in pastel colors.
Compare how he looks
in these bright colors...
- and in these light colors.
- That's better.
- I prefer this one.
- He looks better in this one.
These colors with higher saturation
are not bad for him...
You expected us to say
this one was better, right?
- No, that's not the case.
- I prefer this one.
- That's not the case.
- She's flustered.
I prefer this one.
- Just tell us the answer.
- She's taken aback.
- Follow my lead.
- Okay.
- The bright colors...
- She's taken aback.
- They're not bad. They suit him.
- But...
But these lighter colors make him
look more sophisticated,
and make Se Chan's face stand out.
I agree.
His face shouldn't stand out too much.
- My outfit should.
- Exactly.
I need to draw attention away from
my face.
- That's what he needs.
- He needs to distract attention.
Let's add a little gray color
to these colors.
- Now he looks...
- Oh, no.
- His face looks darker.
- I don't like that.
- He looks more sophisticated now.
- His face looks darker.
(He looks sophisticated?)
- They're all saying...
it doesn't suit me, but she claims
it makes me look sophisticated.
- I thought they were too dusky.
- No, they're not.
- No?
- The light colors are not bad.
- He looks amazing in them.
- But with more gray in them,
- they make him look sophisticated.
- It's nice.
I think I look better in this.
- We think this one is better.
- I prefer this one.
- His facial features look too soft.
- Yes, that's right.
- Yes. You have a good eye.
- Right?
- I have a good eye, right?
- But I prefer that one.
- She's right.
- You look good in light colors too.
The best color scheme for Se Chan is
the summer mute tone.
- He's a tender man.
- Mute...
- A tender man?
- Just like Song Kang.
- What? Kang?
- Come on. Song Kang?
- Just like Song Kang...
- You mean, Song Kang Ho, right?
(You mean, Song Kang Ho, right?)
- Just like Song Kang,
- He's more like Song Kang Ho.
- Se Chan is a tender guy.
- I understand.
- Okay.
- Go back to your seat.
- Song Kang? You're Yang Kang now.
- Right, Song Kang.
- Yang Kang.
Next up is Seok Sam.
We'll check out different shades
of yellow.
- It doesn't suit him.
- Not at all.
- But I like yellow.
- You don't look great in it.
- But I like this color too.
- You look like you have jaundice.
- No, it doesn't suit you.
- Let's try a cool-toned color.
- Gosh.
- It's lighter,
- His face looks sallow.
- but it makes him look pale.
- He looks like he has jaundice.
We're not trying to find a color
that makes your face look brighter.
- That's not the point.
- But his face looks sallow.
This color makes him look less lively.
- That's true.
- It makes his face look sallow.
- So this yellow...
- This one makes him look yellow.
This color makes me look...
That's because it's yellow.
- That's true, but...
- This makes him look yellow.
He can't focus on what she says.
- He got too excited.
- It makes him look lively.
He's the type that all teachers hate.
- You know what I mean, right?
- They don't listen to teachers.
- Let's move on.
- Let's try a cool color.
- I don't think...
- This doesn't suit him.
- He looks like a sick person.
- It doesn't suit me.
It makes me look older.
- He looks like a dead person.
- As if he were dying right now.
- That color...
- It takes his liveliness away.
- He looks like a dead person?
- I'm not choosing...
- the color for my shroud.
- I mean, that color...
- He looks like a dead person?
- This color makes him look lively.
- "A dead person"?
That's so mean.
- It's just the color...
- Let's try a bit darker colors...
- as well.
- It's a sophisticated color though.
- Yes, it's a sophisticated color.
- There are dress shirts...
- in this color.
- But it doesn't suit you.
It doesn't suit you.
- It doesn't suit you.
- You're forcing the idea on me.
Maybe I can nail that color.
- It's not the best color for you.
- Let's...
Ms. Kang will probably make a scene
after we leave.
"Gosh, those punks!"
- "Darn it."
- "They wouldn't stop talking."
The spring warm-toned colors
suit him best.
- He looks great in such colors.
- The spring warm-toned colors.
- Warm colors?
- Yes. Your colors are warm colors.
- Okay. Great.
- Warm colors.
- Jae Suk.
- Next up is Jae Suk.
- Me? I like blue.
- Yes.
- I like many different colors.
- I see.
Can you compare gold and silver
as you did for me?
I look better in silver.
- You look better in silver.
- Yes.
- Better than in gold.
- He wouldn't look good in gold.
- That's not your color.
- Right?
- It makes his face look green.
- He looks like an alien.
- He's like Yoda.
- Yes, an alien.
An alien for sure.
- It gives me a yellow complexion.
- Like Yoda.
- Yoda.
- That's a no.
- Hi, baby octopus.
- I know.
This is just as weird.
Where did this baby octopus come from?
- A hairtail.
- Maybe a cuttlefish.
- Yoda or baby octopus?
- He's like a baby octopus.
- This suits him better.
- Yes, silver is better.
It's better than the first one.
- Right.
- He only has two choices.
- Between gold and silver...
- Silver over gold.
Silver is more my color.
- This is a color I love.
- Different shades of blue.
- This is the color you prefer.
- Yes, I love blue.
- This is a bright aqua blue.
- I don't think this suits me.
- It gives you a greener complexion.
- Don't voice your opinion.
- Stop butting in.
- Let her do the talking.
A summer cool tone...
- No, this isn't the one.
- This is way better.
- It's like you washed your face.
- I love it.
This is the type of color I love.
- An autumn warm tone.
- No way.
- He looks dull.
- This isn't the one.
- A winter cool tone.
- Yes, this one!
(He loves it.)
Nice!
- Ms. Kang hates it though.
- I love it.
- Check out Ms. Kang.
- A lighter color suits you...
- as well as this brighter one.
- I love it.
- Blue seems to suit you.
- Right.
He's always been fond of blue.
Blue is my favorite color.
He likes cheekier colors, doesn't he?
Let's take a look at this array of colors.
- Here.
- Brighter colors are for me.
- Rather than these vivid colors...
- That looks nice.
A toned-down version of those colors...
- No way!
- These are better.
I don't like these.
- Look at Ms. Kang.
- I hate muted colors.
I don't like them.
- Why? They suit you.
- I hate muted colors.
I tend to stay away from muted colors.
No way!
Rather than these vivid colors...
- I love it.
- It gives you a greener complexion.
- Sorry?
- A greener complexion.
Who cares?
- I just love it.
- He's exhausting.
She might end up telling him to leave.
- Muted down colors...
- No, Ms. Kang!
- They suit you better.
- I hate muted colors.
She has already made her mind up,
so just accept it.
- She won't listen.
- It's her way or the highway.
What about the color black? Would it...
I don't wear black often.
- Black...
- Black?
- It's a sophisticated color.
- It's the color I'm fond of.
Black is a color
that has a sophisticated vibe to it.
It doesn't necessarily mean
that Jae Sexy...
Not him, right?
It doesn't mean
he has a sophisticated look.
Black doesn't make you look sophisticated.
It's just the vibe that black gives off.
Ms. Kang, are your opinions
based on looks?
That seems more like it.
- It depends on one's looks.
- Only the tone should matter!
- Ms. Kang, you...
- What if Gong Yoo had that on?
Unbelievable.
Let's try some patterns.
We'll see why vivid colors suit you more.
- She's persuading us.
- Rather than...
clothing with subtle patterns,
items with distinct patterns
elevate his overall look.
- That looks good on you.
- Isn't it better?
- They bring out his features.
- Vivid patterns are for you.
- A contrasting pattern...
- Checkered isn't my jam.
Right, and...
This is the one.
- I like the stronger pattern.
- Nice.
A contrasting look suits him...
which is why it's crucial for him
to wear glasses.
- That was out of concern.
- Can't he take off his glasses?
- Our looks should be irrelevant!
- Ms. Kang...
- She keeps mentioning his looks.
- Yes, constantly.
Why are you snickering back there?
- Glasses are a must.
- Unbelievable.
Let's swap out those glasses.
It's about time you did.
These are all right.
- No, you don't look all right?
- You look good.
I don't look all right?
He doesn't look all right.
But these look okay on me.
- Let me see.
- They're not for you.
- He likes them.
- But I quite like them.
Glasses like these bring out
the "Snowpiercer" lady in him.
- Absolutely.
- These suit you the best.
It's why I wear them.
Yes, they certainly do.
- These suit me.
- What suits him is anything...
- that provides contrast.
- Of course.
- How fascinating.
- These are the same.
There are certain colors that suit you.
Cool tones suit you...
and you do well with items
that provide contrast.
Next up is Haha.
- Why not?
- Haha's next.
I'm one...
to enjoy a variety of colors.
- This intrigues me.
- It's not the same...
as the colors you like.
Let's check with these colors first.
Here are the warmer tones.
Let's compare warm colors to cool colors.
- He looks sophisticated.
- These are better.
- These are much better.
- He looks younger.
He'd eat dung as a dip
if people think it's hip.
Let's see him with hipster items.
- Yes, let's see how he looks.
- Here you go.
- Take this hairpiece for example.
- Sure.
With hairpieces?
- Rather than a pastel tone...
- That's just wrong.
A more...
- The vibrant one is better.
- Hipster in the house!
- He's like G-DRAGON!
- This is it!
- G-DRAGON.
- And not a maltese?
- No, G-DRAGON.
- This is the one.
- This looks good on you.
- Join me
- This is the one.
- Gather around
(Somewhere between G-DRAGON and a maltese)
- This is the one for you.
- Haha...
- Maltese Haha.
- Vivid colors suit you more...
- which is why you look better...
- This is way better.
- from the left.
- Yes, I can see that.
It looks good on you.
It's like a dye job for a pekingese.
Just a second.
Let me clip on some more hairpieces.
(Let me clip on some more.)
Rather than muted colors like these...
(Wow...)
It's like I'm in a dog cafe.
(It's like I'm in a dog cafe.)
You've seen photos of maltese dogs, right?
That's the vibe I'm getting.
- It's not bad.
- It's not so bad.
- It's quite all right.
- You look stylish.
You should wear these like accessories.
- There you go.
- They aren't bad.
You look stylish.
Gosh. That's right. You look great.
- There you go.
- It's not too bad.
(He suffers from
stage four hipster syndrome.)
Vivid colors make him look sophisticated.
- I can't stand him.
- You look good though.
Jong Kook can't stand him.
I bet you can go out like this.
I would if this makes me
look young and stylish for sure.
- Of course you would.
- Would you wear those?
You're the bomb.
- Am I the bomb?
- You sure are.
- You're the bomb.
- Skrr
- Next up is Jong Kook.
- Kook Jong?
All right.
An autumn warm tone
like the colors of leaves.
This isn't bad.
- Right? It makes you look elegant.
- Yes. It's a vivid color.
You look exactly like your mother!
(You look exactly like your mother!)
Rather than a brighter color...
Brighter colors fail to define his angles.
His face looks flatter.
A darker shade...
- The other one's better!
- Exactly.
- That's what I secretly think.
- I like that one better too.
- Ms. Kang bit down on her lips.
- That's odd.
We don't see eye-to-eye on this.
- It's all right though.
- Personal colors...
aren't the same as those
that brighten your complexion.
- She's an expert, you know.
- That she is.
- Don't let us bother you.
- We should listen to her.
Deep autumn colors are for you.
- Deep autumn colors?
- Deep autumn colors.
- They suit you the best.
- Really?
- Ji Hyo, you're up.
- Ms. Song Ji Hyo.
- But Ji Hyo...
- She looks good in any color.
- Every color suits her.
- My money's on warm tones.
I have two shades of purple.
Please look in the mirror.
This is a warmer shade of purple
with a yellow undertone.
- Next, we have a cooler tone.
- Is that one better?
- A cooler shade of purple...
- Is "cool" the right answer?
- I...
- Got it. The cooler tone.
Okay. The cooler tone.
- No, wait.
- Let's go with the cooler tone.
The cooler tone suits you more.
- It gives her a reddish tone...
- There's a yellow undertone.
- It gives her a yellowy complexion.
- Right.
It gives her
a green undertone as well, but...
(They all cheer at the cooler tone.)
- This sure suits you more.
- The cooler tone...
- A cool tone!
- This is better.
- Cooler tones suit you.
- It gives her a clearer look.
- A cool tone.
- That's a cooler tone.
An autumn warm tone...
- makes her look duller.
- This one looks weird on you.
It creates a shadow on her face as well.
- This is the one!
- This color suits you as well.
Ji Hyo's so cool.
The lighter tone...
and darker tone both suit her...
- as long as they are a cooler tone.
- Cooler tones suit you.
- She looks better with cool tones.
- Okay!
- Nothing else came to mind.
- Brighter colors suit her too.
Ji Hyo looks good with cooler tones.
What about So Min?
- Next up is Jeonsobari.
- Warm?
I think warmer tones suit me.
- What's the correct answer?
- Pink...
- Do warmer colors suit her?
- You two are the same type.
- Which tone suits me?
- Cooler tones?
The same as in warmer tones.
- You're the same type.
- Got it.
- The same type.
- Right.
What's the answer?
You should let me know too.
- Warm tones.
- Warm tones?
- Let's see.
- What's this?
- We'll check with pink shades.
- This doesn't suit her.
- A yellowish pink...
- Is this a warm tone?
- Coral pink...
- You look incredible!
- Doesn't it suit her?
- It does!
- You look incredible.
- This one's for you.
- It brings out your features.
- It's the one for you.
But a cooler tone...
- No way.
- This is just wrong.
- It's wrong.
- The other one suits her more.
- This isn't for her.
- It makes her seem paler,
but brighter colors do seem to suit her.
- The other one is better.
- It's not bad though.
- But this is better.
- This is the one.
- It gives her a pinkish complexion.
- Absolutely.
- Doesn't she seem brighter?
- She sure does.
- Pink looks good on So Min.
- Right.
This isn't so bad,
- but a winter cool tone...
- Oh, dear.
- That's not the right expression.
- Warmer tones suit her.
Look sad.
- Sad?
- Yes, look sad.
- This one...
- It doesn't suit her.
It casts a shadow on her face.
So a bright warm spring tone...
Warm tones suit me.
Did she snatch it away?
Brighter colors...
- and spring warm colors...
- Unbelievable.
- A lighter shade.
- She won't even give me a chance.
If we're not on the same page as her...
- She won't acknowledge you.
- Lighter shades.
- To colors that don't suit you...
- She ignores you.
She told So Min to look sad.
- We all have our personal colors.
- Mine are warm tones.
Just like that,
you got to learn your personal colors.
Please give it up for the expert.
- Thank you, Ms. Kang.
- Thank you.
We had a blast.
- Someone else will soon be a slave.
- All right.
You'll now play a game
to see who pays first.
- How much is it?
(It's time to pay
for the second activity.)
At least 300 dollars, right?
- Or maybe not that much.
- Can we get a discount?
It was 30 dollars each...
- What?
- which brings the total to 210.
A total of 210 dollars?
(A total of 210 dollars)
- Someone will go bankrupt.
- At least two.
Here's the game you'll play.
Now that you know your personal colors,
you'll split into Team Cool...
- and Team Warm.
- I'm Team Cool.
- I'm Team Warm.
- Warm.
You'll now play the game.
The four of us
give off a cooler vibe while...
- We have warm hearts.
- They're dull.
- Doesn't it seem that way?
- What?
- Right?
- They can't let go of their anger.
They lack something.
Those three hold grudges.
- Check them out.
- What are you talking about?
We have a loser,
someone who holds grudges,
and someone who sulks.
What do you mean I sulk?
Here's the game you'll play.
In this game, we'll see
how knowledgeable you are.
This is Fact Check Check.
(Fact Check Check)
The rules are simple.
Listen to the keyword...
and state a fact
that is associated with it.
- A fact?
- Whatever is a fact.
- It can be anything.
- Got it.
Let's say the keyword is Yang Se Chan.
- "His brother is Yang Se Hyeong."
- Like that?
- "He's 37."
- That's right.
It can't be something like,
"He's someone I like."
Right, got it.
- It has to be a fact.
- That won't do.
Let's stick to the facts.
Anyone who doesn't state a fact...
- will lose three points.
- Got it.
I just need to avoid coming in last.
- We'll start over here.
- Sure.
Cryptocurrency.
- Cryptocurrency?
- One...
It uses blockchain technology.
- Correct.
- Right.
I haven't purchased any.
- That won't do.
- That's wrong.
- Why? But it's true.
- It's not an associated fact.
- But it's a fact.
- It is, so I'm good.
You can't say the same thing though.
I got a 50-percent return.
- What?
- How is that a fact?
Are you sure it's exactly 50 percent?
- Please show us proof.
- Got it.
It's true though.
- It's true.
- Do you now have 150 percent?
She invested 500 dollars.
What? 500 dollars?
- I invested 500 dollars.
- You got a 50-percent return?
- You made 250 dollars?
- Yes.
- Let us see it.
- Sure.
For real? You made 250 dollars?
Your rate of return is 56 percent.
It's not a fact.
- No. Wait. When did it increase?
- It has to be exactly 50 percent.
- It increased?
- Yes.
- When did it increase?
- That's a good thing.
- Sell it already!
- That's good for you.
- I didn't know.
- Sell it already!
I checked it with Se Chan
just before the shoot.
- That's minus three points.
- It increased.
Oh, my.
Bitcoin...
(The given word: Cryptocurrency)
is the best!
- Wrong!
- That's minus two points.
I've never bought Bitcoins.
- Haha said it earlier.
- I said that.
- When?
- That's minus one point.
You did?
All right!
- Great.
- Jae Suk is in first place.
- Jong Kook is in second place.
- Jong Kook?
- Se Chan is in third place.
- Yes.
Ji Hyo is in fourth place.
Haha is in fifth place.
Suk Jin is in sixth place.
- And So Min is in seventh place.
- Oh, no.
- Poor So Min.
- I'm relieved.
- So Min, goodbye.
- So Min.
You lost.
Please pay a little.
- Gosh, So Min...
- The total cost is 210 dollars.
The one in first place,
please make your payment.
We must see when So Min
turns into a slave.
It's important too.
- So Min will lose for sure.
- Let's pay as little as possible.
Jong Kook, we must pay
as little as possible.
- Hello.
(The first payer, Jae Suk)
(He's done with his payment.)
- I will make a payment.
- Thank you.
Jong Kook, just pay as much as you can.
I will make a payment.
(Accumulated amount he used: 10 cents)
(Jong Kook quickly
makes his payment as well.)
So Min, I'll pay about 30 dollars.
It's better to pay little.
(Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and Haha finish
paying with a mysterious smile.)
What's wrong with you?
Gosh, seriously.
You know that you have to pay some, right?
Why is that?
(Sullen)
I have to pay with my card?
So Min is worried
that she might become a slave.
I don't want to be a slave.
I have to pay with my card?
- Hello.
- Suk Jin.
Can you please use your money
to pay for it?
- Suk Jin is using his money.
- Suk Jin, listen.
Why don't we work together? Can you...
What?
use your money?
- You want me to pay with my money?
- Yes, I beg you.
Please, I beg you.
- It looks like...
- Please, Suk Jin.
So Min is out shopping
with her father-in-law.
- Why are you making me pay?
- He's like her father-in-law.
- Please save me this once.
- Suk Jin.
- You're a slave anyway.
- You should have a slave companion.
Please save me this once.
You're a slave anyway.
- Be the hero.
- I know I'm a slave, but...
- I'll pay you back. I'm serious.
- I'll pay 20 cents.
I'll pay you...
(So Min fails to win over
Ji the father-in-law.)
- You should have a slave companion.
- Seok Sam.
You should pay just ten cents.
How can I pay only ten cents?
(It's finally time for So Min to pay.)
You have 199.8 dollars to pay.
I shouldn't have spent
a lot in the first round.
She has to pay about 190 dollars.
That'll be over 200 dollars for sure.
I'll pay just ten cents.
I'll pay only ten cents.
I'll pay just 50 cents.
- I'll have to spend it anyway.
- You'll pay 9.2 dollars?
That'll be 9.2 dollars.
She has to pay for everything.
- This is so cruel.
- You've gone bankrupt.
- All right.
- She's gone bankrupt?
(So Min's gone bankrupt.)
Did you hear that? "You've gone bankrupt."
(Two players have already
gone bankrupt after two rounds.)
I've gone bankrupt?
- It exceeded your limit.
- You brat!
You guys aren't spending so little.
You should spend a little.
How dare a slave talk back?
- You spend too little.
- So Min's debit card...
had 80 dollars at first.
- That's a lot.
- What happened?
Someone still holds
a card that has 200 dollars.
It's not in odd numbers.
- It's not.
- But it's close to...
- She had 80 dollars?
- She did.
She spent 30 dollars earlier.
And you couldn't spend any just now.
I'd have been well off if I survived.
A hundred dollars?
This complicates things.
Someone is holding a card
with 200 dollars.
So Min had quite a lot of money.
- Yes, 80 dollars is a lot.
- I'd have been well off.
Now, So Min's become slave number two.
After she gets changed,
we'll head to the gukbap place
right in front.
- All right!
- Sounds great!
I really can't tell now.
So Min, what a bummer.
- I just lost in one game.
- Goodness.
- You weren't that bad.
- So Bal.
- My goodness.
- So Bal, you brat.
- How dare you...
- put on a hairband to look cute?
- act like a noblewoman?
(Cute)
So Bal.
Do your best when you serve them.
When we have concepts like this,
it's always these two.
- Why is it always us two?
- Why does this always happen?
Why do we always get the worst part?
I could've done well with 80 dollars.
- It wasn't bad.
- Yes, you could've done well.
With 80 dollars,
you had a chance of winning.
You'd have been okay as long as
you weren't in last place.
Is there anyone?
You can't say that.
What did you say?
"You can't say that."
Goodness, you should have
a delicious bowl of beef bone soup.
You two should eat outside on the ground.
Goodness.
On a cold day like this, we should have...
- a warm bowl of gukbap.
- We should have gukbap.
Their boiled pork slices must be good.
- So Bal, hurry and go sit inside!
- There's brisket...
- Please take a seat.
- Go sit inside!
- Please go ahead and take a seat.
- Please hurry up and sit.
Go sit inside!
- I...
- I'm going to eat a lot.
I will go sit through here.
Why would you go under the table?
- Come here, you slaves.
- Okay, my lord.
Go sit through there.
Go sit inside!
Let's have boiled pork slices.
- He'll spend more than 200 here.
- We'll have boiled pork slices.
It'll be over 200 dollars for sure.
There's a bigger serving
of beef bone soup.
- I'll have a regular one.
I'll have a regular one too.
One, two, three...
Four regular servings, and...
- I'll have a bigger serving.
- Raise your hand for bigger ones.
Sir, there are different options
for a bigger serving.
I'll take one that costs 25 dollars.
All right.
Jong Kook will have one
that costs 25 dollars.
We'll have four regular servings...
and 2 big servings that cost 25 dollars.
And we'll have two mid-sized
dishes of boiled pork slices.
Should I order two mid-sized dishes?
- Yes, we should.
- We should have two.
And what is seasoned intestines?
- No, stop. That's enough.
- Let's have it.
- Seok Sam.
- Yes, my lord.
Get an extra chair.
Oh, I...
- It's like seasoned brisket.
- It's...
- What are you doing, So Min?
- Get a chair!
Hey, second batch.
Get the intestines. No, I mean...
Can you ask them
to remove the intestines in mine?
- You don't want intestines?
- No.
All right.
Can you remove the intestines...
- in one of the regular servings?
- Seok Sam.
- Yes, my lord.
- Get a chair!
- Here's your chair.
- There are no intestines...
in regular servings.
- Okay.
- Nice.
Can you make So Bal do the work too?
So Bal, get us some broth.
- Can you give us some water?
- Wait.
It's nice to see the servers
dressed in hanbok here.
Their food must be good.
- They suit the place so well.
- They do.
Oh, it's run by father and daughter?
Yes, it is.
- Is she your daughter-in-law?
- A father-daughter gukbap place.
You're running it...
- with your daughter-in-law?
- So Min.
So Min, it's so nice
that we're having many customers.
- Right, Father.
- Right?
When will my husband return?
Your husband is missing.
- Their costumes...
- They suit this place so well.
They suit gukbap so well.
- Also,
- Hello.
So Min used to be called Gukbap.
- You're right.
- Right?
- Because she mixes her rice...
in her soup.
The spring onion kimchi looks so good.
- She's Jeon Gukbap.
- That's right!
We make our kimchi
with ingredients from Korea only.
- My gosh, it looks so good.
- It's really good.
- Yes.
- It looks good.
You get a dish each.
- The kimchi...
- It looks so good.
- You get a dish each.
- We get one dish each?
- Yes, you get one each.
- You should move away now.
It's a mission.
- What?
- What's that?
- It's a very simple mission.
- What is this?
- What is it?
- You'll be doing a challenge...
that's trending
on a short-form video platform.
It's Blowing Out Candles with Your Mouth.
- With our mouths?
- There must be many candles.
You'll put on a mouthpiece and
blow out candles for five seconds.
(They'll blow out candles for
5 seconds with a mouthpiece on.)
- With a mouthpiece?
- Wouldn't it be too easy?
- You have to blow out like this.
- Is it hard?
Who will go first?
- I'll go first.
- All right.
- Okay, Frog. You should try it.
- Great.
Would it be hard? How do I put this on?
- It's...
- You have to put it on well.
It has an upper and down side.
It says up and down on it.
- She'll turn into a zombie.
- That's it.
She's turned into a zombie.
Wait. You did put it on, right?
I did!
We'll give you five seconds
after you start.
All right.
- Do I just blow them out like this?
- Yes.
- Get ready.
- Hold your hair.
Set, go.
(Blowing)
(Here comes Jeon Bool Am.)
(Breathing out with all her heart)
- Keep going!
- Time's up.
- No!
- You're done.
- Your turn is over.
- No!
(So Bal's challenge ended
after showing off her lung capacity.)
You did it. You did well.
- She's good.
- Give me one more chance.
- That was hilarious!
- Her turn is over!
- Give me one more chance.
- Can you give me another chance?
- Hold on.
She's good.
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen...
- No!
- Hey.
She didn't blow out any candles
on that side.
- She blew out 40 candles.
- I blew out a lot.
- You blew out a lot.
- You have to...
- She blew out everything here.
- All right.
- You have to keep this in mind.
- It's not easy.
- Okay, we got it.
It's really not easy.
Okay, got it.
Ssaebssaeb.
(Se Chan is next.)
A champion is going next?
(Here comes the champion
of protruding mouth.)
Get ready.
Set, go.
That's great.
- He blew out everything!
- Time's up!
He blew out every candle!
That was really fast.
- I'm so dizzy.
- All right.
All right. Please count them.
He blew out a lot.
There are 15 candles remaining.
- He blew out 135 candles.
- All right!
(Se Chan blew out 135 candles
just within 5 seconds.)
No matter how much I think
It's Ji Hyo.
She looks pretty with it.
Ji Hyo, what made you so upset?
Why are you so upset?
- Make sure to blow them out well.
- Get ready.
- Use all your strength.
- Do a good job.
Let's go.
Set, go.
She's good.
- She's pretty good.
- Time's up. Stop.
Hey, So Min...
- She did so well.
- So Min is in last place for sure.
We'll be good as long as
we do better than So Min, right?
Of course.
Jae Suk, it's hot. You should be careful.
- It's hot.
- Ji Hyo blew out 119 candles.
I think Jong Kook will blow out
all the candles.
With that on,
- I think he'll be good.
- he looks angry.
Get ready.
- He looks really mad.
- Isn't that how he usually looks?
- Just blow them out at once.
- Set, go!
Use your lungs.
Breathe out with your chest.
He's blowing all of them out.
(He put out every candle
only after seven breaths.)
(An exhaling firefighter showed off
exceptional lung capacity.)
I can't believe he blew all of them out.
- I hate him.
- It'll be on international news.
I just hate him.
- That was incredible.
- He's the worst.
Let's enjoy our meal.
The staff worked so hard...
- to prepare this.
- How did he blow all of them out?
(Regardless of the results,
he secured first place.)
- I'm done, right?
- Yes.
(The original champion
of protruding mouth goes next.)
- Time's up.
Wait, that was...
- Wasn't that too fast?
- No, time is up.
- What is he doing?
- Time's up.
What was that?
Hold on. One, two, three, four...
- Well...
- Did you count the ones I blew out?
He blew out about 70 candles.
- Wait.
- What do you mean?
- He was counting...
- Why did you count half-heartedly?
- He just said a random number.
- Let's move on.
He said, "About 70 candles."
Why did you count half-heartedly?
You should open your mouth wide.
It's better that way.
But I think it works better if...
It's the last member.
You'd think you'd be able to
blow out better that way.
Haha, you should breathe in first.
Set, go.
(Throwing up)
(An unexpected waterfall)
- Time's up.
- What was that?
- I mean...
- He just threw up! Darn it.
- He lost!
- Come on!
- No.
- That was disgusting.
- Please give me another chance.
- He lost.
- He lost!
- What was that?
It was so gross.
- He spat out so much.
- He lost.
All right!
He blew out three candles.
- He lost.
- Only three candles.
You're not in last place anymore.
I'm so relieved.
He blew out 11 candles.
When I play a game like this...
It was so gross. What was that about?
All right, now. I'll announce the result.
This won't do.
- How did he...
- No!
Using a technique didn't work.
Jong Kook is in first place.
- Se Chan is in second place.
- All right.
Ji Hyo is in 3rd place,
Jae Suk is in 4th place.
Suk Jin is in fifth place.
- So Min is in sixth place.
- This is great.
- And Haha is in seventh place.
- How did I lose in this?
- I'm glad.
- You spat out a lot.
For your information,
the total price is 195 dollars.
- It's 195 dollars? That's a lot.
- It's 195 dollars.
- It's 195 dollars?
- Yes.
Gosh, we should spend
some money from this round.
- Right.
- If we don't spend any...
I'm going to spend about 20 dollars
this time. I mean it.
It looks so good. Thank you for the food.
- Let's add sliced green onion.
- It's so soft.
It'll be so good if you add kimchi in it.
It's really good.
Their kimchi is so good.
This is delicious.
(Se Chan is eating
without saying anything.)
I really want to bring my mother here.
There's so much meat in it.
- They'll spend some this time.
- Right.
They'll spend some money.
They'll spend about 20 to 30 dollars.
I'm going to spend some too.
- You sure you won't go bankrupt?
- You could spend about 30 dollars.
- It's time to pay.
- All right.
It's 195 dollars.
Let's start with Jong Kook.
- All right. I'll pay.
- You must spend a little.
- I have an amount in mind.
- How much should we spend?
You know what the problem is?
You might not be able to spend
the money even if you wanted to.
Gosh, I hope what I have in mind is right.
All right.
(Accumulated amount he used: 20 cents)
I'll pay 20 dollars.
- Twenty dollars?
- Yes.
(He bravely pays 20 dollars.)
Will it work? It's 20 dollars.
(Suk Jin's card had 10 dollars.)
(So Min's card had 80 dollars.)
(Jong Kook was racking his brain.)
(He expects his card to have
an amount between 10 and 80 dollars.)
Should I spend more than I should?
- But Ji Yeon's card...
- Jae Suk.
There can't be only 20 dollars
in mine, right?
- It's because...
- It could be worse.
I should try spending a lot here.
It's going to get really complicated
from now.
Hold on.
Did it work?
(He manages to make the payment.)
- Do you want the receipt?
- Yes.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
He must've spent 30 dollars.
- You must've spent 30 dollars.
- Did you?
It did work.
(It's time for Se Chan,
who only spent 20 cents, to pay.)
I'll pay...
I'll pay 45 dollars.
(I'll pay 45 dollars.)
(He boldly tries to pay 45 dollars.)
(It'll work only if his card
has more than 50 dollars.)
Does it work?
(It'll work only if his card
has more than 50 dollars.)
(He manages to make the payment.)
Thank you.
(Accumulated amount he used: 45.2 dollars)
Guys, it's so nerve-racking now.
- Right?
- Yes.
Because we're spending some money now.
I paid a lot.
- Really?
- I paid a lot.
- They'll tell you at the end.
- No.
I didn't know it had that much.
I'll pay 20 dollars.
(Accumulated amount she used: 60 cents)
Wait.
I can just punch in the numbers now.
I'll pay only ten dollars.
Sure.
(She pays only ten dollars to be safe.)
(Accumulated amount
she used: 10.6 dollars)
All right, Ji Hyo.
(Accumulated amount
she used: 10.6 dollars)
How much should I spend?
How much more do we have to pay?
(Total cost: 120 dollars)
(Accumulated amount he used: 20 cents)
- Are you going next? Or me?
- Jae Suk.
I'm sure your card
has more than 50 dollars.
Am I going next?
You won't have a chance
to spend the money on your card.
It's our last course.
This is your last chance.
- We have just one more course?
- Yes.
Then...
(How much will Jae Suk pay?)
Try spending about 48 dollars.
- Should I?
- Yes.
There could be 50 dollars in your card.
But what if there's 200 dollars
because I'm unlucky?
With 50 dollars... That could be the case.
(Accumulated amount he used: 20 cents)
I'll pay 55 dollars.
(Jae Suk tried paying 55 dollars.)
Did it work?
(Is there more than 60 dollars
in Jae Suk's card?)
Did it go through?
(It did go through!)
(Accumulated amount he used: 55.2 dollars)
Thank you.
(He's paid the most so far.)
Jae Suk's card went through.
We have no idea though.
How much did you pay?
- Wait. He's...
- He's paid quite a lot.
- No, he... Where's the receipt?
- Did it go through?
I'll go and check...
- and tell you how much is left.
- Jae Suk, your card went through?
He must've gone bankrupt. Oh, really?
- It went through?
- He said he'd pay quite a lot.
Jae Suk, right now...
(His head is spinning
as he might have 200 dollars.)
- This is...
- You have 200 dollars.
- You must have 200 dollars.
- Jae Suk, I also think...
How much more do we have to pay?
It went through very smoothly.
This is the balance?
We have only this much left?
You guys spent a lot.
Suk Jin, pay at least ten cents.
Suk Jin, you shouldn't let
Haha spend his money.
You shouldn't make him use his money.
That could be a good strategy.
No, he could have 20 dollars.
No, we should spend as much as we can.
No.
He just doesn't want to use his money.
(He just doesn't want to use his money.)
Suk Jin uses a debit card.
- He uses a debit card?
- Yes.
His wife gives him 100 dollars a week.
And he uses a charge card
for his transportation.
Wasn't he born in 1966?
He was born in 1966,
but he uses only 100 dollars a week?
- He can ride the subway for free.
- You guys are such liars.
He can ride the subway for free?
(Seok Sam is playing a slave
when he's a senior member.)
- He can ride the subway for free?
- Everything is free for him.
If it's all free,
then 100 dollars is a lot.
- Of course.
- I do have to pay for subway.
- I have to pay to ride the subway.
- How much more do we have to pay?
Isn't it free for you to use bathhouses?
- No, it's not.
- A couple of times a month.
- So Min. Leave ten cents.
- I...
I paid five dollars.
How much more do we have to pay?
(The remaining amount is 60 dollars.)
(So Min pays with her own money.)
- Thank you.
- Sure.
(So Min pays with her own money.)
(It's finally Haha's turn.)
I'll be paying the rest.
How much is there?
- Nothing.
- There's nothing left?
- It's over.
- Is this allowed?
I paid for it all.
- Why did you...
- Is this allowed?
(So Min stripped Haha
of his chance to pay.)
Yes, it's allowed!
So Min paid with her own money.
- I paid the rest.
- So Min...
- She's indeed amazing.
- So Min did it again.
How much did you spend?
- She spent 60 dollars.
- I paid the rest.
Why did you do that?
Why did you rob me of a chance?
Why? I treated you to a meal.
- You must be glad.
- The slaves...
are making it hard to predict.
- Maybe it's better this way.
- I can't be too sure.
Not making him use his money
could be a strategy.
I happily treated you all to a meal.
So that's that.
Let's move to the next course.
- Let's go!
I think this is all based on luck.
It's based on luck.
Everyone. This is the last course.
We prepared a mission
for your facial health.
Facial health? It must have
something to do with our faces.
If you think some of your members...
need to fix their faces,
pick two members...
and text their names to me.
Gosh. But this is...
- I...
Don't do it. Please don't do it.
You guys know that
there is no point in picking me, right?
Simply put, we need to pick
a member with a messed-up face.
- We need to send a text to Bo Pil?
- This is so...
- I sent it already.
- You want a text or a message?
- It doesn't matter.
- It was really easy to pick.
Me too. It reminded me of two members.
Me too.
Don't consider our jaw area.
- I'm done.
- I sent the text.
I'm not going to vote.
"I'm not going to vote?"
Jae Suk, just write your name.
It's you, Jae Suk.
Gosh.
All right. We're set.
We're set?
- You easily picked the two members.
- Yes.
- It's so annoying.
- It's Jae Suk and Se Chan.
(Jae Suk and Se Chan)
- I didn't even think twice.
- Why did you pick...
- Protruded Brothers?
- Come on.
It's so annoying.
Can you push
their protruding mouths back in?
- Jae Suk, did you write my name?
- Yes.
I wrote yours too.
(Yangsebari, Jeonsobari)
- I wrote your name too.
- It's hilarious.
It's always those two.
- How upsetting.
- This alley...
It's the alley I often come to.
It's Apgujeong.
Maybe it's that one.
- Which one?
- Loco.
This one.
- What do you mean by Loco?
- It's Loco.
He said he was going to
serve in the military.
- He got discharged already, right?
- Loco is cute.
- Is he younger than you?
- He is.
Loco is very diligent.
He's really nice too.
- Right.
- Loco is really nice.
It's rare to see a guy like him.
I want to try living like Loco.
- How?
- He is cute.
- Seokco.
- He is cool.
He is a hip-hop musician.
Being a hip-hop musician is good
only if you are successful.
Why do you think he won't be successful?
When people get started with something,
I don't tell them to become
as successful as they can be.
I recommend...
that they make a satisfactory living
without reaching the top.
- Suk Jin, right?
- Yes.
- His life is tranquil.
- It's quite comfortable...
to live like me.
You might not know this,
- but he is working toward the top.
- That's not true.
- Is he working toward the top?
- Suk Jin is greedy.
- No, I am not.
- Seriously.
- He is ambitious.
I didn't think he was greedy.
But I realized that I was wrong
at the Entertainment Awards.
- I realized that he was greedy.
- He is greedy.
I let go of my greed a long time ago.
It's the situation
that makes people greedy.
- I agree.
- I let go of my greed.
I had it when I was young.
- It's because he can see the top.
- That's right.
- That's why he is greedy.
- Think about it.
- That's not true.
- You are so close to the top.
That's not true.
The Grand Award goes to...
- Ji Suk Jin.
I never thought
a day like this would come.
That came out automatically.
- You should start crying.
- You shouldn't think...
that you know all about life.
Once you hit the age of 50,
you will know what happiness is.
- Why?
- Really?
- You were over 50 then.
- Back then,
- weren't you in your 50s?
- You haven't reached that stage.
- I feel so bad for you.
- Why?
It's stressful to be at the top.
- I am very happy.
- He is happy.
Suk Jin, have you been at the top?
Seriously. Have you been at the top?
I haven't, so I could be wrong.
- He is crying.
- It's the life you don't know,
so you shouldn't talk about it
so callously.
- That's right.
- It's the life you don't know.
He puts in a lot of energy
to stay at the top.
- It might give him happiness.
- That's right.
- You don't know what it's like.
- Of course not.
I don't know, okay?
He is happy.
The thing about happiness is...
Suk Jin, you are getting beaten up.
- Am I getting beaten up?
- Yes.
That's not what I think.
I think we are having a proper discussion.
- You are bleeding.
- Is this a discussion?
You are bleeding.
- In any case...
- You think...
- people at the top...
- Look at him.
He keeps trying to wrap things up.
- "In any case..."
- So...
- listen to me.
- People at the top...
Hey!
Listen to me!
(He ends up shouting.)
- In any case...
- We have arrived.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Hey!
- One, two, three.
Okay.
In any case, I had fun.
(Seok Sam is a good man
who puts up with the younger ones.)
Suk Jin.
- A moment ago,
- Okay.
you had a poll to pick the two members...
- who need facial correction.
- They really need it.
Thus, Jae Suk and Se Chan
will receive a facial massage.
- Of course.
- Everyone voted for them.
- But...
- They have many problems.
for entertainment,
they will receive the massage...
and give it to another member each.
- What?
- Okay.
You can pick from the remaining members.
- We can deliver what we've felt.
- That's right.
- I don't need it.
- Why did we vote for them?
- That's good.
- We picked the two vindictive ones.
You know, our bodies are aching too.
Why do you need to give us
a facial massage?
You need a facial massage too.
I guess our faces look that bad.
- For goodness' sake.
- Stick your mouth back inside.
- Jae Suk, why don't you go first?
- Me?
- It's the order of ugliness.
- Stick your mouth back inside.
I don't need it.
- I don't need a facial massage.
- Why do you think that?
- You need it.
- It should be your priority.
How will it go?
Gosh!
He looks so ugly.
So that's how it goes.
- To become handsome...
- It hurts.
- To become handsome, endure it.
- Stay still.
- Endure it for beauty.
- You should endure it.
That's right.
- Isn't it too forceful?
- Does it hurt that badly?
(Screaming)
He isn't faking it.
- He isn't faking it.
- Stay still.
You look so ugly.
I am sorry, but can I take a photo?
Stop it!
(It's an entertaining sight.)
These photos are so bad.
- Seriously.
- Stop.
They look like
they got processed with an app.
His face became puffy.
- Seriously.
- Hey.
- Your face became puffy.
- You became handsome.
- Your skin is firm now.
- Let me see your face.
- Your wrinkles are gone.
- Hey.
- Your face looks fatter.
- It's as if you got stung by a bee.
- You look handsome.
Jae Suk, you look handsome.
Gosh, it hurts.
(Then comes Se Chan
with his extraordinary jaws.)
Why do his jaws look like that?
(His oral structure is unique.)
- It hurts.
- Look at that.
Why do his jaws look like that?
- It hurts.
- Really?
Here.
(So Min's camera)
(Focusing)
You should try it.
Look at that.
That's your boyfriend.
So Min.
You are filming him with passion.
Why is the camera so close to me?
(Reporter Jeon found an exclusive item.)
It hurts so much. I am in tears.
- So Min. That's your boyfriend.
- It's his belly.
(She gets a celebrity's belly on camera.)
It's his belly.
(The Pouty Mouth Brothers' show
ends in success.)
You are becoming handsome.
Please pick a member each.
- I pick Suk Jin.
- Seok... Can we pick the same one?
- One person is enough.
- You should pick someone else.
- We can't pick the same one.
- In that case,
I pick So Min.
Why?
- Why would you pick me?
- It's going to be funny.
- I pick So Min.
- I don't need a facial massage.
- Let me sanitize my hands first.
I need to sanitize my hands too.
I don't need it.
Seriously.
Why did he suddenly pick me?
I sanitized my hands.
- Don't lie down like that.
- Okay.
Let's put your hair here.
- I see.
- That's the basic step.
- You know well.
- Yes.
- I will see what your face is like.
- Okay.
That wasn't an exaggerated reaction.
Your face is asymmetrical.
Do you chew with your left side?
This side is bigger.
- Which side?
- This side.
(Twitching)
This side is bigger.
- Which side?
- This side.
(Giggling)
The two sides are different.
I am not massaging hard.
It hurts.
- It's about to hurt.
- He isn't massaging hard.
- I am not massaging hard.
- No, he isn't.
- The right side hurts.
- I knew it.
Let's film her face.
Here comes the double chin.
It's this side.
Press hard.
(It looks like she is crying.)
- Gyata.
- Smile.
- Isn't that Gyata?
- That's good.
- Gyata.
Gyata from
"Demetan Croaker, The Boy Frog."
Keep going.
- Isn't that Gyata?
- Close your mouth.
- You look pretty.
- Do I look okay?
- You look great.
- She looks like a duck.
- Isn't that Gyata?
- No.
- It hurts there.
- That's why you need a massage.
- It feels good.
- It feels good, right?
It feels good, right?
- Let's see Gyata.
- Gyata.
- All right.
- Okay.
It feels good.
(Croak)
- It feels good, right?
- It feels good.
Shouldn't a massage lift up the skin?
- Why are you pulling it down?
- Stop it.
When she wakes up...
- I will make a smiley face.
- A smiley face.
When she wakes up...
Her face...
Her skin stretches well.
It's as if her skin is rubber.
Seriously. Why is her skin so thin?
Her skin is thin.
- It feels good.
- It feels good, right?
- All right.
- Pull my head upward.
- Upward?
- Stretch my neck. Yes.
Yes.
- It's refreshing. Don't pull them.
- I will pull your feet too.
- Don't pull them.
- One, two, three.
One, two, three.
I am sorry,
but isn't this an execution method?
Seriously.
Isn't this an execution method?
- Learn how to do it first.
- Okay.
- He knows what to do.
- That's not how you do it.
I am revving up.
- Mr. Yang.
- Yes?
What's wrong with his face?
- If you look at his nose,
- Okay.
- it's too big.
- Massage the inside of his nose.
His nostrils are sized differently.
They will come last.
They will be the finale.
I think he breathes more
with his right nostril.
I know.
It hurts.
Here.
Would you hold his legs?
- Sir.
- Stay still.
- What are you doing?
- Don't do that.
He can't take it.
(Slapping)
(He slaps Se Chan
because he can't stand the pain.)
What was that?
It hurt so much.
I will do it lightly this time.
Now, we need to decide on
the order of payment.
(It's time to decide on
the last order of payment.)
(They have a match of withstanding pain.)
- Ouch.
- She is done.
Done.
(Most of them get eliminated in 1 second.)
Thus,
Jong Kook will go 1st place.
So Min will go 2nd place.
Haha will go 3rd place.
Se Chan will go 4th place.
Suk Jin will go 5th place.
Ji Hyo will go 6th place.
- And Jae Suk will go seventh.
- I am the last one.
It cost 400 dollars to rent this place.
- Why is it so expensive?
- It cost 400 dollars.
- Did you say 400 dollars?
- Yes.
- It's so expensive.
- The last one will pay the rest.
It's so expensive. It's 400 dollars.
So Min planned...
to keep everyone from paying...
- by paying the total.
- That's right.
- The total is 400 dollars.
- I can't pay 400 dollars.
- No, you can't.
- It's too expensive.
- It can't be helped.
- I will give it a go.
I should pay a big sum.
- I should spend 100 dollars.
- We should spend money.
- I will spend money this time.
- It's time to do that.
Okay.
Jong Kook will go first.
(They need to guess their balance
and use it as much as possible.)
- I don't have a clue.
- Jae Suk, think about it.
I will give you a hint.
There are three members who have...
over 100 dollars.
- Three?
- Three.
As for the 2 members
who have less than 100 dollars,
their balances are
between 10 and 80 dollars.
- Between 10 and 80 dollars?
- That's right.
- There are two such members.
- How much do I have left?
Then there are 3 members
who have over 100 dollars.
(2 people: Between 10 and 80 dollars
3 people: Over 100 dollars)
You need to figure out
if you have over 100 dollars...
- or less than 80 dollars.
- Okay.
Did I have 30 or 50 dollars?
There are two such members.
I think I had 30 or 50 dollars.
Really?
(Jong Kook thinks
he had 30 or 50 dollars.)
I used 20.2 dollars, right?
(Total amount used: 20.2 dollars)
I used 20.2 dollars.
It's my head.
Let's say I had 30 dollars.
Okay. Let's say I had 30 dollars.
(He guesses his original balance
to be 30 dollars.)
I will pay 9.7 dollars.
(It's his plan to leave behind 10 cents.)
(He succeeds in making the payment!)
All right. Thank you.
- Go, So Min.
- So Bal, it's your turn.
- Jong Kook, you made the payment.
- Yes.
So Min.
She wanted to pay the total.
What's the remaining amount?
- It's 390.3 dollars.
- What?
- It's about 390 dollars.
They won't give you back the money.
No, we won't.
Then she wouldn't pay the total.
Don't give it back.
It won't be fun otherwise.
- They won't give it back.
- So Min won't use a lot of money.
It would be a waste.
- Spend just a little bit.
- Other people need to pay too.
I can use this much money for you guys.
- Don't do that.
- She will use ten cents.
- Will you pay the total?
- So Min, it doesn't matter.
She will use ten cents.
(What will be So Min's choice?)
In that case, I will pay 300 dollars.
(She pays 300 dollars.)
I will get the penalty.
(She uses her own money
to make more people suffer.)
Thank you.
Regardless of the result,
- I expressed my love.
- Okay.
I expressed my love.
Did you spend a lot of money?
That's bad.
How much did I start with?
Did I have 200 dollars?
Jae Suk and I might have started
with 200 dollars.
Did you say 20.2 dollars?
- Yes.
- The two of us.
We nearly spent 50 dollars.
(How much did Haha's card
originally have?)
What's the remaining amount?
What's wrong with you?
- It's 90.3 dollars.
- What?
(The remaining amount is 90.3 dollars.)
(Total amount used: 18.2 dollars)
(How much money
did the team producer's card have?)
(Total amount used: 18.2 dollars)
He is a coward,
so he won't use a lot of money.
- I am
- Hey, coward.
A coward
- He won't spend a lot.
- No.
He won't spend a lot.
I will pay 90.2 dollars.
- Did you say 90.2 dollars?
- Yes.
(It's his plan to use over 100 dollars.)
(Haha takes a risk.)
Okay.
(If he had less than 100 dollars,
he will go bankrupt.)
(The payment went through!)
(Total amount used: 108.4 dollars)
Thank you.
How did this payment go through?
(Total amount used: 108.4 dollars)
How much did I originally have?
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
It's still not my turn yet.
(Haha is worried about the balance.)
(It's Se Chan's turn
before Jae Suk and Ji Hyo.)
I wonder how much remains.
What's the remaining amount?
It's ten cents.
- What?
- It's ten cents.
(The remaining amount is only 10 cents.)
I don't know who is responsible,
but this is insane. Are you serious?
What's the remaining amount?
(Everyone found out
about the tiny amount.)
Is the remaining amount ten cents?
- Jae Suk.
- What's the remaining amount?
I will pay that much.
- Please use this card.
- Okay.
Jae Suk. Who went before me?
- Earlier...
- It's her.
- This is insane.
- No, it isn't.
- What?
- You paid a big amount, right?
I will go and tell you.
- There is no need to go.
- Why? Did the total get paid?
I paid the remaining amount.
- What is this?
- It's over.
How much did you pay?
- I didn't pay that much.
- How much did you pay?
Why did you ruin the game?
- I mean...
- After eating gukbap...
You should have let us enjoy
the nerve-racking moment.
It would have been better
had more people gone bankrupt.
- I just wanted to show my love.
- That's ridiculous.
- I mean...
- There are other ways to do it.
- Why did you do it on the show?
- You ruined the game.
You could have bought us a meal
after the shoot.
Why did you show your love
while the cameras are running?
Why did you do it
Do it when the cameras are turned off.
We have to figure out the rankings
from the remaining balances.
- Let's see what happens.
- Let's go.
- I just wanted...
- All right.
I know you meant well.
The total amount got paid off...
in four payments.
It happened in four payments.
If your remaining balance
is over ten dollars,
you will become a candidate
for the penalty...
- along with the slaves.
- I should have used more money.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes.
(Jae Suk's balance gets announced first.)
- How much did he use?
- He used 55.2 dollars.
- He used a lot.
- I used a lot for gukbap.
If he originally had 80 dollars...
(If he originally had 60 dollars,)
(he will be exempt from the penalty.)
He used 55.2 dollars.
I will reveal
the amount of money that was...
- in the second writer's card.
- How much was it?
(Second writer)
It's 120 dollars.
(120 dollars)
You planned to use 50 dollars this time.
- That was his plan.
- You planned to use 50 dollars.
(So Min, the slave, kept him
from making the last payment.)
The remaining balance is 64.8 dollars.
- You planned to use 50 dollars.
- That's right.
I have a chance.
- Jae Suk failed.
- Good job.
- Suk Jin, you went bankrupt.
- Yes.
- Up next is Haha.
- Haha.
- I am curious.
- How much did he use?
Haha used 108.4 dollars.
(Haha used 108.4 dollars.)
- In my card...
- How much was there?
Choi Bo Pil. There was 200 dollars, right?
(If he originally had 110 dollars,
he will be exempt!)
There was 190 dollars.
- There was 190 dollars?
- I did better.
- Someone else had 200 dollars.
- Seriously.
You must have 200 dollars.
He will be a candidate
since 81.6 dollars remains.
I chose the junior producer's card.
Hold on.
- Se Chan,
- You didn't twist it.
you have the junior producer's card.
Yes.
You used 45.3 dollars.
I bet he had 60 or 70 dollars.
I bet he had 50 dollars.
I will reveal the original amount.
I bet it's 60 dollars.
(Junior producer)
It's 200 dollars.
(200 dollars!)
Were you rich?
You should have told me so.
(The junior producer was richer
than they expected.)
It's impossible to guess.
The remaining balance is 154.7 dollars.
- Ji Yeon is the youngest.
- Ji Yeon.
I was going to pick Ji Yeon's card.
Seriously.
Ji Hyo is up next.
- Ji Hyo must be...
- I picked Ju Yong's card.
You used
the administrative producer's card.
You used 10.6 dollars.
Maybe there was 20 dollars.
Seriously.
- That would be incredible.
- Ju Yong's card.
(If she originally had 20 dollars,
she will be exempt.)
(How much money was on
the administrative producer's card?)
(Administrative producer)
There was 60 dollars.
(Ji Hyo becomes a candidate
since 49.4 dollars remains.)
Jong Kook is up next.
How much did he use?
- He used 29.9 dollars.
- Okay.
How much was
on the second producer's card?
I had a guess.
Hyung In wouldn't have a lot...
since he spends too much on himself.
He has the YOLO mentality.
How much was on Hyung In's card?
(If he originally had 30 dollars,
he will be exempt.)
(Second producer)
- There was 30 dollars.
- See?
I guessed the exact amount.
The remaining balance is ten cents.
Ten cents?
Is the remaining balance ten cents?
I thought he would go bankrupt.
(Detective Kim can even guess
the original balance.)
The junior producer carries 200 dollars.
Why does the junior writer carry
ten dollars?
- Seriously.
- What is up with that?
It's unfair.
The original amount was 30 dollars.
So there are six candidates
for the penalty.
- Unbelievable.
- We will play the Pirate Roulette.
This is the worst.
The penalty of the day...
suits the name,
How Much Do You Want to Spend Race.
While wearing the slave's outfit
and pillory,
buy something at a nearby store
with your own card.
(Buy something at a nearby store
with your own card.)
(Gangnamdaero will be crowded.)
- It will be so annoying.
- It will be so embarrassing.
A pillory?
That's the worst.
- That's the worst.
- That's the most annoying penalty.
This is my neighborhood.
- Seriously.
- This is your neighborhood.
Even better.
The member who was the closest
will go first.
Ji Hyo, stick in a sword.
I just need to avoid the penalty.
- That's right.
- Will one person get the penalty?
Yes.
Jae Suk.
I hope it pops out.
I can't get the penalty.
Jae Suk is lucky these days.
(WIll he prove that he is unlucky?)
Send it flying in one go.
Jae Suk is lucky these days.
I hope it pops out.
(Safe)
- Thank goodness.
- Next.
(It's Haha's turn.)
- Haha.
- I hope he gets it.
- Come on.
Go.
- Se Chan.
- Is it my turn?
Se Chan, let's go.
- Boombastic!
- He might get the penalty.
Let's do this.
(3 people avoided the penalty.)
(Will he avoid it as well?)
Skrr
- So Min.
- Skrr
(Safe)
So Min.
- She must be nervous.
- So Bal, it's your turn.
(Next comes the slave
who used over 300 dollars.)
- It will be funny if she gets it.
- Gukbap.
She used a lot of money too.
- She used a lot of money.
(Will she get the penalty as well?)
- So Bal, go.
- She used a lot of money.
(Safe)
Okay. Suk Jin.
- So Bal.
- Seok Sam.
- He is wearing the outfit.
- He can go right away.
- He can go right after the shoot.
- Go.
- Let's slate.
- Let's go.
(Will he get the penalty?)
Let's go.
(Safe)
Another round.
This is bad.
I think it will be me.
Oh, no.
- I am nervous.
- Ji Hyo, let's go.
Slave.
It's your turn.
- Go.
Okay.
- Okay. Boombastic!
- All right. Let's go.
- Boombastic!
(Quite a lot of knives are stuck already.)
(She is highly likely to get a penalty.)
- It will pop out this time.
- Let's go, So Min.
(What about this time?)
(She's safe again.)
Darn it.
(Darn it.)
Let's go, Seok Sam.
You are wearing the costume already.
(It's Seok Sam's turn again.)
- Let me help you.
- Arirang
This is really...
I'll make up my mind.
I'll choose the one that catches my eyes.
I can't choose 1 of the remaining 3.
(Nervous)
I see three slots.
- This is driving me crazy.
- That was funny.
- I don't know which one to pick.
- Just pick.
- Go ahead.
- Left or right. Which one?
All right. I think this is it. Okay.
Gosh, this is crazy.
- Okay.
- There are only a few left.
- It's Ji Hyo.
- This is so thrilling.
- Ji Hyo, you are funny.
- You have to do this.
Ji Hyo, go ahead and do it.
There are only a few left.
(Pirate Roulette is more thrilling
than ever before the worst penalty.)
(Ji Hyo hasn't been so lucky lately.)
- Stick it in.
- Yes!
(Song Ji Hyo gets the penalty.)
There are only three slots left.
- It's done!
- Yes!
My goodness.
- Boombastic!
- I've survived.
- Put on the slave costume.
- Oh, dear.
All right. And...
"And?"
I bet it's someone's birthday. In March...
Who would it be?
It's my birthday.
Right. It's So Min's birthday.
You don't have to do this though.
- This is what we always do.
- Is it your birthday?
- That's...
- Happy birthday to you
(Happy birthday.)
(Thank you.)
- So Min, happy birthday.
- Thank you.
(The junior writer
gives her the birthday cake.)
Make a wish and blow out the candles.
- Did you make a wish?
- Yes.
Yes. I hope Running Man
will be more popular.
- Thank you.
- The smoke went to her.
- The smoke went straight to her.
- She just breathed it in.
It went straight to her.
She inhaled the smoke.
Why would you do that?
- She must be upset.
- I bet she's mad.
- She seems very upset.
- Go wash your face.
Do you know how she looked
as she turned around?
- She was startled.
- Why did you do that?
(After the writer got humiliated...)
(Song Ji Hyo, the sinner shows up.)
Do you want me to go out
looking like this?
I can't believe this.
This is so embarrassing.
(The sinner crash-landed
in the middle of Gangnam.)
(The good citizens are
surprised to see her.)
- Look at her.
- I can't believe this.
It's Song Ji Hyo.
(She tries to avoid people by instinct.)
(She gets into a nearby store.)
Hello.
I didn't know there would be people.
I need to buy sanitizing wipes.
(She hurriedly picks up what she sees.)
Hello. Can I buy this one?
(Cumbersome)
(Please hurry.)
(1 second seems like 10 minutes.)
(The clerk is also feeling anxious.)
Payment completed.
- Thank you.
- Have a nice day.
Bye.
(She completes her mission
feeling humiliated.)
(Hello, viewers.)
(Thank you for letting us...)
(celebrate our 200th episode.)
(We'd like to thank...)
(our viewers.)
(Until the 600th episode,)
(our viewers have...)
(always been with us.)
(Of the viewers)
(For the viewers)
(By the viewers)
(With Viewers Special)
(What's your secret
for your strong mentality?)
(0 percent offense)
(You didn't mean to hit me
for real, right?)
(Flinching)
(Painful past)
(Painful consolation)
(It's completely different.)
(A preview of the future Running Man)
(And...)
(From the beginning to the end
of Running Man)
(A new challenge...)
(for the viewers)
(With Viewers)