(Last February)
(With the stock investment craze,)
(2021 Running Man
Investment Contest took place.)
(The self-proclaimed masters
simulated stock investments.)
(They made investments
in their own ways.)
The small investors are gathering.
(All they can count on
is information.)
(They bought information
at Information Exchange.)
(The small investors
started their investments.)
(When the Watch-Night bell rings,)
(the stock prices of the year
are released.)
(The results of their investments
in the first year)
(Some investors earned money,)
(and some investors lost money.)
Why did you not trust me?
(The novice investors' investment
with all sorts of human emotions)
- Please. Biotechnology.
- Yes!
(F Biotechnology, G Foods)
(The investment contest
turned into madness.)
(The young and rich investor
dreamed of a new life.)
(When you see others' success,)
(you get jealous.)
- I can't believe this.
- Yes!
- Okay!
- Look at that.
- I invested in biotechnology.
- I'm young and rich!
(It was like a party
when the stock prices soared.)
(J Shipbuilding)
B Entertainment
increased by 100 percent.
(Suk Jin went all in
on the shipbuilding stocks.)
(Ji Suk Jin went broke
after investing in shipbuilding.)
(He proved that he's got
the hand of Minus.)
(The investment contest
ended in great success.)
(A year later, the year 2022)
(The KOSPI reached below 2,600
hitting a 17-month low.)
(The uncertainty continues
until the second half of the year.)
(The investment gurus are gathered
again to break through the crisis.)
- Hey.
- Hello.
Hello.
- What are we doing today?
- Running Stock Investment Club.
We're investing in stocks today.
- My gosh.
- I love it.
- Investment?
- Gosh, this is...
- About stock investment...
- Is this a seminar?
So Min invested 500 dollars...
in coins and made some money.
- Right.
- It went up to 640 dollars.
But it's minus 24 percent now.
You should've sold them.
- It wasn't long ago.
- Right.
- I told you to sell them.
- It plummeted.
- She didn't listen.
- Did you invest in coins?
That's how things work
for coin and stock investment.
Once the price increases...
- Did you make a profit?
- No, I didn't.
- I didn't, but...
- Suk Jin said...
- Suk Jin.
- What?
You haven't made
any profit for 20 years.
That's not true.
- It's not like that.
- It's just strange.
I have a bigger picture.
He's a pushover.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
Why are you wearing your blanket?
- This is...
- It's a patchwork quilt.
- They look like colored paper.
- It's not like that.
You can wear pants like these if you
make money on the stock market.
- Suk Jin.
- You always say that.
- These are designer clothes.
- I feel like crying.
Why?
You're Kim Young Man,
the origami master.
Mr. Kottakji.
Gosh, I don't want
to say this, but...
- What did you say?
- He's Kim Young Man.
Mr. Kottakji.
We have Kim Young Man here.
You can wear pants like these
if you succeed.
I should make an origami crane
with your pants later.
Do you know anything
about stock investment?
Do you know
anything about this club?
I heard the stock prices
are falling a lot these days.
- Right.
- Are you all right?
- Is it bad for you?
- It's terrible.
- It's really bad.
- I invested in a few stocks,
and they all fell a lot.
I recently invested in a few stocks
with no information.
- It's the same every week.
- It's all in blue.
- That's why...
- They all should get up.
our production staff
rarely check their phones now.
When the market was thriving,
- Right.
- even during the shoot,
the cameramen checked
their phones like this.
Exactly.
- They were like this.
- Right.
They were so happy.
- It was all red.
- They worked with a smile.
But now it's nothing like that.
- It's in recession.
- They don't even touch phones.
There's an old saying
about stock investment.
"Invest when people struggle."
- Exactly. I remembered the saying.
- This is what people say.
But you're the one who's struggling.
I'm struggling.
I invested even more
while I was struggling.
You should just do the opposite
of what Suk Jin does...
- when you invest in stocks.
- Right. Just do the opposite.
I made an investment
following Suk Jin.
- What is it?
- Right? Se Chan did it too.
- The investment.
- That thing?
- I'm counting on it, Suk Jin.
- Gosh.
What is it called?
Unicorn? Star start?
- You mean a start-up?
- What is a unicorn?
I don't know.
He said something like that.
Let me tell you
what a unicorn means.
It's a company that's worth
over a billion dollars.
We hope it will be a unicorn.
But it's not one yet.
- It has a promising future.
- That's our hope.
- I didn't even know.
- It has a clear vision.
- Suk Jin...
- It doesn't have a horn yet.
Suk Jin also told me about it.
I thought about it, but I didn't
invest in it because of Suk Jin.
(I didn't invest in the company
because Suk Jin did.)
See? Jae Suk is wise.
- Jae Suk never follows him.
- It's not like that.
- It's your decision to make.
- Sure.
You shouldn't make an investment
just because of what I say.
It was my decision.
So I asked Suk Jin.
"What are you going to do?"
"I'll go for it."
So I decided to give up.
Sometimes Suk Jin does this.
- What?
- He sends some videos...
about investments and real estate.
He wants me to study.
- But Suk Jin is...
- You know people like this.
There's a student who studies hard
for his exam.
But he doesn't even know
what the test will be on.
So he doesn't do well on the test.
Suk Jin is steady though.
The land he bought 20 years ago
still remains the same.
That's just amazing.
- Hey.
- What?
- That's my sore spot.
- It is true.
- Land prices have increased a lot,
but the price of yours didn't go up.
That's really interesting.
I heard land prices increase
from one generation to the next.
- What?
- From one generation to the next.
- So will it go up after I die?
- Yes.
It will happen in his next life.
- Will it go up after I die?
- It will go to your son.
It's good for your son.
The price will go up
when your son inherits the land.
Your work is going well though.
Right.
You can't have it both ways.
- I can't have it all.
- You can't.
And your love life is going well.
I mean, with your wife.
- What?
- Your love life with your wife.
It's still hot.
"It's still hot."
(He claims
their love is still burning.)
He's so good at lying.
He's a good liar.
No. It's true.
I guess our love is burning
after all these years.
- My gosh.
- No one...
seems to believe that.
You don't understand.
Do you think I'm lying?
No one is jealous of him.
- He's just saying that.
- They think he's just saying that.
We had the Running Man
Investment Contest last year.
And we led the prosperous time
in the stock market.
- Right.
- Last year,
- things were going well.
- It was really good.
It was a masterpiece.
All those who invested in stocks...
They all made profits.
- They made a lot of money.
- Everyone was happy.
Se Chan made hundreds
of thousands of dollars...
- only with 500 dollars.
- Right.
How much did you make?
I could buy a fancy car.
Right. You made
hundreds of thousands of dollars.
So we are going to the US this time.
The US?
(The investment gurus are
going to the US this time.)
- The US?
- Really?
I don't know anything
about the US market.
The US market?
The US stock market?
(They are going to Wall Street,
the financial center of the world.)
Before you go to the US,
we will have a seminar.
- Okay.
- And we have two big investors...
who will join the seminar today.
- Really?
- Who are they?
- Experts?
- All right.
Please bring in
the big investors now.
I know one of them. Seriously...
I bet they are experts.
My gosh.
Hang on.
Gosh, Sae Ho.
- It's Young Ji.
- Hey, Young Ji.
- What?
- Sae Ho.
- My gosh.
- Young Ji.
- Nice to meet you.
- Come here, Young Ji.
What is going on?
- Hello, Young Ji.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Wait. Sae Ho.
Gosh, he reeks of perfume.
We don't need a peddler.
Gosh, that's so strong.
- Wait. Gosh, you reek with perfume.
- Look at his bracelet.
Look at his bracelet.
Gosh, that's a strong smell.
What are you wearing?
I'm sorry.
- Please slow down.
- Gosh, it's so strong.
I'll count to three.
Please don't say it
all at the same time.
- What's the copper bracelet?
- It's not a copper bracelet.
- This is...
- Copper prices fell a lot.
- It's not a copper bracelet.
- Did you melt coins to make it?
I didn't melt coins.
I went to a department store.
- Did you buy it?
- I went to a department store...
and bought it for myself.
Gosh, it hurts.
I want you to stay quiet.
We have Young Ji here.
I just don't get a chance
to explain myself.
- You don't have to say anything.
- Young Ji.
I've never seen Sae Ho...
- feel so nervous before.
- He pretends to feel nervous.
He always seems confident.
But he was stamping
his feet anxiously earlier.
- He couldn't stand still.
- The thing is...
I feel nervous during the opening.
- Because we all come at him.
- I know they will come at me.
He's wearing the sneakers again.
- Really?
- Right.
- What is the brand?
- It's Chanel.
I was told that I should
look like a successful man.
Do you invest in stocks?
Stocks?
- He does.
- I do.
But I need to watch my mouth.
Is your investment going well?
- You know it.
- What do we know?
Well... It's not like...
- This is all I can say.
- He's got more wrinkles.
I bet things are not going well.
- It's going well.
- Is it?
I got smile-wrinkles.
- Smile-wrinkles?
- Doesn't Sae Ho look scary?
Something has changed.
- Are you tanned...
- Did you get tanned?
- He got tanned.
- Or do you have a liver problem?
- I think he has a liver problem.
- Did you get tanned?
Your skin gets dark
when you have a liver problem.
He looks drunk.
You have wrinkles on your forehead.
It looks like you have jaundice.
- He seems jaundiced.
- My gosh.
By the way,
you guys are unbelievable.
I have a healthy liver.
I recently had a blood test,
and I'm very healthy.
- That's TMI.
- What about your hair?
Is it greasy
because you didn't wash it?
It's not like that.
I put some hair grease
and wax on my hair.
I saw a cow licking his hair.
Do we have a cow here?
- Young Ji is funny.
- Young Ji is joining us.
- Young Ji and I are very close.
- Right.
- We used to live together.
- What?
(Did you two live together?)
She means a TV show.
- It was "Roommates."
- The SBS TV show.
Young Ji, I was startled.
Young Ji wants to attract
people's attention.
- Did it work?
- It's for a thumbnail image.
- I was surprised.
- It's for a preview.
So is something going on
between you two?
He's not interested in Young Ji.
- He liked Nana back then.
- It's for a thumbnail image.
He liked Nana.
- He liked Nana.
- He was interested in Nana.
- He really liked her.
- That's true.
- I'm sorry.
- It's true though.
- He liked her for real.
- He liked her?
He liked her for real.
I heard he had asked her out.
- Right.
- That's...
That's TMI.
- That's TMI.
- He says it's TMI.
- We all know that.
- I've never...
said that on TV.
You sang "Confession"
in a karaoke room for her?
- That was for Jang Do Yeon.
- I see.
How many women were there?
So you like tall women.
Actually,
it doesn't have to be a tall woman.
I just liked them.
Wait. This is upsetting.
Why do you not like So Min?
- I don't like him either.
- So Min is tall.
Why do you hate her?
- I don't like him either.
- I...
I never said that I hated her.
- You two will make a cute couple.
- The thing is,
I just feel like
So Min is making jokes.
So I'm just doing the same thing.
- Why would I...
- I wanted to set you up with her.
What if I'm serious?
- What if I'm serious?
- Are you serious?
(He asks if she's serious,
pointing his finger at her.)
Why would you talk to her like that?
- Wait.
- He sounds so fastidious.
I don't like...
- the idea of these two dating.
- Actually,
this is TMI, but my parents...
like So Min a lot.
- Parents like me.
- She's so cheerful.
Then you should let
your parents have dinner with her.
- Me...
- Without you.
My parents and her?
My father also likes Sae Ho.
- He likes Sae Ho?
- He does.
Then both your parents
should meet up without you guys.
Only the parents.
- Only the parents without us.
- Right.
The families can meet up
and talk about marriage.
What perfume are you wearing?
It's a foreign brand.
You should throw it away.
Wait.
- Why would he throw it away?
- Throw it away.
Why...
- Why would he throw it away?
- It smells like cattle feed.
It's just like a stock investment.
You shouldn't throw it away
when you are told to.
I'd think,
"Should I throw it away now?"
(Groaning)
(He pinches Sae Ho
for the 2nd time.)
Stay quiet.
- Let Young Ji talk.
- Okay.
- Let her talk.
- It's Young Ji's time.
- It's Young Ji.
- Young Ji.
Hey.
Young Ji is so bright.
- What was this?
- What was that?
I wanted to look cheerful.
- He sounded so depressed.
- Right.
Your skin tone is
different from his.
Young Ji, did you go on a diet?
- You seem...
- Did you lose weight?
I've been losing some weight.
- I see.
- Why?
Is that because of
your stock investment?
- No. The stocks are fine.
- Really?
I invested in two companies.
And they are blue-chip stocks.
I've invested in them
for a long time.
I believe they will grow over time.
- And I don't check the prices.
- In stock investment,
nothing is steady.
- Why would you...
- Just say something good.
- That's how things work.
- She studied and made her choice.
She doesn't know anything
about stock investments.
Even blue-chip companies are
influenced by the flow.
What flow?
- He can't even talk right.
- The investment flows.
Did you end up like this
because you know a lot about stocks?
Of course.
Anyway, I have experienced failure.
You know what? I think
Suk Jin and Sae Ho...
look down on each other.
(Suk Jin and Sae Ho
look down on each other.)
- I'm sorry.
- Don't apologize, you punk.
They are two tankers.
- You have rough hands.
- I know. They are chapped.
- They criticize each other.
- All right.
Don't wear a fake watch.
Why would I wear a fake watch
on an SBS TV show?
- Don't wear things like that.
- Okay.
- This is it.
- Is that it?
You're done.
This is all you have, right?
Yes. This is all I have.
- You're done.
- I'm done.
The ending is somewhat lukewarm.
That's what Sae Ho always does.
There's nothing big.
You need to find something...
- to laugh at on your own.
- That's right.
I just give you some sources.
And you need to collect it yourself.
The nine of you are
gathered together...
with the dream
of going to Wall Street in New York.
I'm like DiCaprio.
You guys are genius investors.
- What?
- My gosh.
You will leave for New York
this afternoon.
- We will be busy.
- Before you leave,
you will have a seminar here.
- Will there be a seminar?
- Yes.
After each session, the members
who do a great job will get points.
As you might know,
you can use the points...
to buy information
for your stock investment.
It's important to buy information.
- Right. I watched it too.
- It is very important.
Let's go downstairs
for the seminar then.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
What is this?
- Are we studying again?
- Do we have to study?
Study?
(Don't give up. It's not too late
to escape from Empty Heads.)
Gosh, this feels familiar.
- Aren't you used to this?
- I'm used to this.
- You and So Min.
- I don't want to memorize words.
I won't be able to sleep tonight.
I will have to use my brain.
Gosh, this is so...
Young Ji is Empty Head.
She's the new Empty Head.
(She sighs looking at books.)
I'm in trouble.
Did you do well at school, Young Ji?
I was good in elementary school.
Everyone was good
in elementary school.
In elementary school, we learned
Korean language, math, and so on.
- I was in second place in school.
- Really?
- Second place?
- I gave only two wrong answers.
- You were good.
- She studied in New Zealand.
- Do you speak good English?
- No.
- Young Ji is like a native speaker.
- Really?
- Just say you are.
- Oh, right.
What are you doing?
Is that what you do?
I speak good English.
Sae Ho, you speak English, right?
- English?
- He's pretty good.
I can carry on a basic conversation.
Do you know
what "E" of e-mail stands for?
- I won't say anything.
- Why not?
- Tell us.
- I think I'm being looked down on.
- What does "E" of email stand for?
- Gosh.
- Do you know the answer, Young Ji?
- English?
Gosh, he says English.
What did you say?
- English.
- He says English.
Isn't it English mail?
He's Empty Head.
English?
- He's just making a joke.
- He's serious.
- I'm a comedian.
- English mail.
- You know I'm a comedian.
- You should be serious.
- That wasn't a joke.
- Hey, excuse me.
- "Hey, excuse me."
- Excuse me.
- Excuse-me mail?
All right.
Before you leave for New York,
you will take a class
to survive on Wall Street.
It's called
Empty Head Economics Class.
- I'm not good at this.
- Do you remember the quiz you had?
- Yes.
(Running Man Quiz Championship
took place last fall.)
(The Empty Heads had
private tutors before the quiz.)
(- "The Tale of Hong Gil Dong."
- Hohyeonghoje.)
(The tutors tried hard
to teach the Empty Heads.)
(He was under a lot of stress
teaching himself.)
(And Se Chan did a great job
after the private tutoring.)
(He gave a lot of correct answers.)
(Screw the education system
of Korea!)
(Empty Head Tutoring Quiz showed...)
(the double face
of the Korean education system.)
There will be teams...
of 1 top student
and 2 Empty Head students.
- A team of three?
- I need a tutor.
The top students will teach
the 2 students for 20 minutes.
And the six of you will
have the quiz competition.
(The 6 students will have a quiz
after 20 minutes of study.)
Who are the Empty Heads?
The teachers remain the same.
Jong Kook, Suk Jin, and Jae Suk.
- Got it. Learn from me.
- I see. Okay. Understood.
- You know I'm a good tutor, right?
- Well...
I taught her what could be asked
on the test back then.
- I'll be a star tutor again.
- Right.
Only the six empty heads will
take a quiz after the lesson.
A team gets 1 point when only 1
on the team gets a question right,
- and three points if both do.
- Both have to get it right.
- Okay. Got it.
- I understand.
- It'll be hard for both to do it.
- I'm glad I'll have a teammate.
- It won't be hard.
- The questions will cover...
the entire social studies textbook
for the 1st semester of 6th grade...
that contains
the basic knowledge of economics.
- I see.
- That's easy.
- That's offensive.
- That's so easy.
Last time, you studied
what fifth grade students learn.
- We've moved up, right?
- Right.
- Now, I'll announce the teams.
- Okay.
- Teacher Yoo Jae Suk will teach...
- Who are they?
Se Chan and Sae Ho.
- We're all comedians.
- My gosh.
- I'll teach my junior comedians.
- We're all comedians.
- Let's join our forces. Comedians!
- Comedians!
- This is great.
- Let's study hard.
- Jong Kook's students are...
- Yes.
- Ji Hyo and Haha.
- Okay.
(Kim Jong Kook's class:
Haha, Song Ji Hyo)
- I'm a great teacher.
- And Suk Jin will teach...
So Min and Young Ji.
- Oh, my.
- You know I'm a good teacher.
- Jong Kook's students are good too.
- Let's do this.
- They are, indeed.
- You have 20 minutes.
- Twenty minutes? Okay.
- Yes. Start studying.
- We can start studying now, right?
- Yes.
- Sit down.
- Please sit in the middle.
- Right. Sit in the middle.
- I don't mind.
Shall I sit in the middle?
- I'll sit in the middle.
- All right.
(Teacher Yoo has his 2 favorite men
as his students.)
Jae Suk.
You two have to memorize everything.
I'll follow your lead.
- Okay?
- I'm doomed. I'm not smart.
All right. Let's take a look.
(Unit 1 is modern history
and politics.)
You should know...
- what a revolution means.
- A revolution.
"It's to change a nation's
foundation and system completely."
- A revolution.
- This is the most important point.
- It's to make a change.
- A revolution changes everything.
- It changes everything.
- Shouldn't we study economics?
Focus. This will be asked
in the quiz.
- Will it? Okay.
- It covers the entire book.
It changes everything.
"In 1863, the Gettysburg Address..."
- You should memorize this.
- Will this be asked too?
- It could be.
- Pennsylvania?
Yes, the Gettysburg Address.
This is a speech
delivered by Lincoln.
- Lincoln?
- Yes.
- Abraham Lincoln.
- I see.
- Okay.
- Have you never seen him before?
- What?
- You mean, Lincoln?
- This is Lincoln.
I know who he is. He's...
- He's a former president of the US.
- the first president of the US.
- He's not the 1st president.
- That's George Washington.
- Oh, it's not him.
- Let me tell you about him.
Just listen to what I say
as your teacher.
- You're a student too.
- Just zip it.
- Why would you teach me?
- You're a student just like him.
- I'm the teacher.
- Exactly.
I don't think I can do this.
- Memorize what I tell you.
- You're too hard on us.
- Just memorize it as I said.
- Okay, I'll do that.
- We only have 20 minutes.
- Okay.
- Let's memorize this one.
- Se Chan, you're doing great.
- Abraham Lincoln.
- The Gettysburg Address.
(Meanwhile,
Se Chan is in the teacher's favor.)
Now, let's move on
to the April Revolution.
- This is important.
- The April Revolution.
The April Revolution.
Why did it happen, Suk Jin?
The April Revolution... Well...
You don't have to know why.
- Why would you get upset?
- No, it's not like that.
You don't have to learn
why the April Revolution happened.
Why? We have only 20 minutes,
you know.
You two just have to memorize
the terms I tell you.
Okay. Hey, memorize this name.
Jurgen Hanzpeter.
Write it down.
Jurgen Hanzpeter... This man...
It's Hinzpeter, not Hanzpeter.
- Oh, right. It's Hinzpeter.
- Jurgen Hinzpeter.
I have poor eyesight.
It's Hinzpeter.
You must have good eyesight.
He let the world know
about the pro-democracy movement...
- in Korea.
- You know, right?
- Jurgen.
- Jurgen Hinzpeter.
Jurgen Hin... "Hin" as in "white."
Memorize it like this.
- "Hin" as in "white."
- Hinzpeter.
- Okay?
Hinzpeter.
You two are studying so hard.
I'm impressed.
- "Peter" like Peppertones.
- Sorry?
- How do we study all this?
- Yes?
- You can do it.
- But...
There could be many things
you don't know.
(He's the type
who eats sweets before studying.)
We've done this before, right?
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
I think this will be asked.
I think we'll be asked
what FTA stands for.
- Free trend...
- Oh, right. That...
- agreement.
- It's trade, not trend.
- Free trade agreement.
- Yes, it's trade.
On what page is FTA?
It's at the back.
Why did you skip to that page?
This will definitely be asked.
- Memorize this.
- Quiet down. Memorize these two.
What are the basic concepts
of democracy?
What are the basic concepts?
Human dignity, freedom,
and equality.
Correct. And...
What are the principles
of democracy...
- Universal suffrage,
- I mean, democratic election.
direct suffrage, secret ballot...
- Imagine we eat jjajangmyeon.
- Okay.
I have a universal portion size.
- We all eat jjajangmyeon equally.
- Equally.
- And it's delivered directly to us.
- Directly to us.
The person who paid is a secret.
- Oh, I get it.
- Does it make sense to you?
- This will help you memorize it.
- That's a great idea.
Let's say we eat jjajangmyeon.
- Universal suffrage.
- We eat a universal portion of it.
We all eat jjajangmyeon equally.
- What does it mean?
- Direct suffrage.
- No, equal suffrage.
- Right, equal suffrage.
- To whom is it delivered? Correct.
- Directly to us.
- Who pays?
- It's a secret.
(The elite student said,
"It's a secret.")
- It's easy, right?
- Yes.
- It's a great idea.
- It's easy, right?
What does universal suffrage mean?
Every citizen of Korea over 18 has
the right...
- to vote.
- That's universal suffrage.
Now, what does equal suffrage mean?
- Every citizen has...
- Just one vote.
I was explaining...
- Don't cut him off.
- That wasn't my intention.
- Why would you...
- Are you the teacher?
- I was...
- Keep it down, please.
- Why would you interrupt me?
- Come on. Be quiet.
Sae Ho keeps acting like a teacher.
- I was just actively participating.
- Gosh.
That's not necessary.
Just memorize it.
- You're not a teacher.
- Get out if you'll keep doing this.
He's acting up when he's a student.
- I'm trying to teach you...
- What kind of teacher...
- Just listen to me as Se Chan does.
- Take notes.
- All you did was read the book.
That's all you did.
- You didn't teach us anything new.
- I gave you the key points.
- I was explaining to you.
- The key points.
Se Chan is doing well.
- I see. I'm sorry.
- He's a good teacher.
Right.
I mean, we have only 20 minutes,
but our pace is too slow.
- Be quiet.
- It's fast enough.
Get lost if you're going to
keep going on like this.
- Don't say that.
- "Get lost."
- You...
- Let's move on.
- Exactly.
- Our pace is too slow.
- Be quiet.
- This is very important.
- Please keep it down.
- You're too loud.
Why are you speaking so loudly?
- Sae Ho, you're too loud.
- And there's direct suffrage.
- We can't focus.
- I told you earlier, right?
- Everyone has a direct vote.
- Correct.
- Every citizen has...
- No one can vote for you.
Isn't that obvious?
- You're so hard on me.
- We're running out of time.
- Yes. Got it.
- You're being trained intensely.
Understood. Direct suffrage.
"Public hearing" is
an important term.
You should memorize the terms
in a box like this.
- "It's a public conference..."
"to hear the opinions of experts..."
"before a policy decision is made."
A public hearing,
a public conference.
- "There may be precedents..."
- Darn.
- Gosh. They're actually studying.
- It's okay. You can skip that part.
Of course, they should.
I can't stop yawning.
What makes you yawn?
Isn't this so fun?
- "A public hearing..."
- The National Assembly, the court.
Things like this are so intriguing.
You know, Jong Kook used to be
a thug before he started studying.
He's enjoying this so much.
- He's enjoying teaching us.
- Yes.
Memorize "fair trade" as well.
- Okay. Now...
- I didn't know he liked studying...
- I'm impressed. I guess...
- Let's move on.
- Come back and sit down, you punk!
- It means to agree on it.
You guys are studying so quietly.
- You mean, us?
- It looks so nice.
- That's right.
- We have great concentration.
Now, we're going to...
(Yawning)
- Did you just yawn?
- Don't yawn.
- You made me feel sleepy.
- Go out and wash your face.
- Wash your face.
- I can't. I'm wearing makeup.
Se Chan is studying now.
I really don't like your attitude.
- I'm sorry.
- Look at the other students.
- And your breath smelled so bad.
- That's right.
Gosh. Why would you say that?
You shouldn't do that
during a class.
Hey, how could you...
- Meet me on the rooftop later.
- Be quiet.
Hey, go easy on me today.
(Licking his finger)
Sorry, but don't lick your finger
before turning pages.
I can smell your saliva,
which is bad.
- Gosh, you're so annoying.
- It smells so bad.
- Just leave.
- What's wrong with it?
I can do whatever I want
with my own book.
Where is your manager?
Where's Sung Ho?
He left to grab something to eat.
Gross domestic product.
You should memorize this.
Gross national income.
(GDP, the total value of final goods
produced during a period of time)
- GP... I mean, GDP.
- GPA. I mean, GDP.
Yes. There's another one
other than GDP.
- GPS.
- It stands for...
"GPS?"
"Divided into three branches."
You know this one.
You learned this, right?
The last one.
Three separated... Triad?
- Gosh. That's a gang.
- Three...
The separation of powers.
- What's the legislative branch?
- The National Assembly.
- Correct.
- The judicial branch?
- Courts.
- Correct.
Don't just repeat what he says.
And what's the government?
- The executive branch.
- Correct.
You can win the quiz if you know it.
Let's do our best, Se Chan,
so we won't be called empty heads.
What's the opposite
of direct election?
- Diagonal election?
- Indirect election.
- Like straight and diagonal lines?
- Yes, diagonal election.
Direct election means
that the voters vote directly.
You have three minutes left.
- Gosh. We're in trouble.
- Gosh.
- You punk!
- What?
This is difficult.
(Everyone started cramming.)
Studying makes me yawn.
My gosh.
(Serious)
So Min, you look so cool
since you're focusing on studying.
- She's taking it seriously.
- She looks so cool.
It's because I'm not good at
memorizing things.
I'm so tired.
- Me too.
- Why are you tired? Enjoy it.
We'll begin
as soon as we finish preparing.
I'll tell you
what to memorize again.
- Se Chan, memorize what I say.
- Okay.
- I bet you will...
- Don't just talk to him. Teach me.
- All right.
- Okay.
Haha, what are the four principles
of the democratic election?
- SEUD.
- That's right.
- Secret ballot, equal suffrage,
- Correct.
- And?
- universal and direct suffrage.
- Everyone.
- Good.
- Just remember this one.
- Please come and sit here.
- Please come out now.
- Wait. Give us a moment.
- Please come out.
- Please.
Teacher Ji.
Yes?
Teacher Yoo.
- Memorize the terms in the front.
- A residents' referendum.
The local government officials
elected by the residents...
- Teachers.
- Memorize this one too.
- It should be carried out...
- Everyone.
- Please come out.
- Okay.
Let's go, everyone.
Okay. Done.
Everyone, please be seated.
I'm so nervous.
You did a great job.
Good job.
(The 20-minute study time is over.)
- Direct election.
- Correct.
The separation of powers.
- Teacher Kim.
- The separation of powers.
- The judicial branch...
- Got it.
(They cram information into their
students' brains to the end.)
Please bring your chair...
Teacher Ji.
- The legislative branch. Okay.
- Please be seated.
- It's the government.
- The executive branch.
That's the separation of powers.
Please sit down.
- You've got this.
- Stop it already.
- What are you talking about?
- Gosh, seriously.
They should study
to the last minute.
You and your students were too loud.
We weren't.
My students couldn't focus
because of you guys.
- That's...
- Gosh.
That's your students' fault.
No. You were too loud.
- It's his students' fault?
- I'm just saying...
- What?
- His students are to blame?
- What did you just say?
- That's ridiculous.
- What did my kids do wrong?
- You're a teacher.
- How could you blame the students?
- Let's begin the quiz already.
- Let's begin before we forget.
- What's your problem?
- I'm speechless.
- What? You punk, how dare you?
- Did you call him a punk?
- Stay away from me.
I'm a teacher,
- Mister, what's the problem?
- and he pointed his finger at me.
But you're not his teacher,
so he can call you "Mister."
- Right.
- That's not the point.
- You're not my teacher.
- Let's begin now, please.
Now, I'll give you the questions,
and we'll see how well
the three teachers taught them.
- Okay. Let's begin.
- Let's go.
- But...
- I don't have to be funny, right?
- You don't have to.
- I won't try to be funny.
- Right.
But you never tried to be funny.
Pardon me?
A team gets 1 point if 1 member is
correct, and 3 points if both are.
- Okay.
- Okay. Good.
If you cheat,
your team loses two points.
- Come on. None of them will cheat.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Se Chan, be confident.
- We can do this!
Since this is a team competition,
cheating won't be tolerated...
- under any circumstance.
- Of course.
- Show me your palms.
- What's wrong with you? Gosh.
- He's ridiculous.
- We would never do that.
- And why didn't you see theirs?
- Exactly.
- Hey, show me your hands.
- Where do you think you're going?
- Show me.
- Mister.
- What are you doing?
- Show me your palms.
- Why would you look at their hands?
- Hey.
- What are you doing now?
- We'll forget what we learned!
- Let me take a look.
- Gosh. What are you doing?
- Maybe she hid it in her hair.
- She'd never write it on the scalp.
- So Min might've done it.
- Kids usually write answers here.
- How could she even read it?
- Show me.
I forgot everything. Darn it.
- I forgot everything too.
- I forgot everything.
- Good.
- Give us the question, please.
- Okay.
Let's begin.
Here's your first question.
What is the speech
in which Abraham Lincoln said,
"Government of the people,
by the people, for the people,"
"shall not perish from the earth?"
(In what speech did Abraham Lincoln
say, "Government of the people,")
("by the people, for the people,
shall not perish from the earth?")
Oh, good. They know the answer.
- Of course, they know.
- Okay.
Wait. What's with those looks?
- You know the answer, right?
- You know the answer.
(You just have to memorize this.)
("Government of the people,
by the people, for the people...")
(It's the Gettysburg Address
delivered by Lincoln.)
(The scary teacher told them
to memorize the Gettysburg Address.)
Does it end with the word "speech?"
- There's a name for the speech.
- I told you about this many times.
A speech?
We should write
the name of a speech?
It's so easy.
- Write down the answer.
- Wait.
Where was this speech delivered?
Does it end with the word "speech?"
You guys know the answer, right?
You know the answer.
You learned this.
- I told you earlier...
- All right.
(Meanwhile, Young Ji and So Min...)
(started writing the answer
without hesitating.)
- You know the answer.
- The name of the speech...
You wrote it, right?
My students know the answer.
(Right then, Se Chan starts
writing the answer too.)
All right.
- Five.
- Yes. That's great.
- You wrote it, right?
- Four.
- Three.
- You don't remember that?
- Two.
- Come on.
- One.
- Good.
Now, reveal your answers.
Show your answers.
- Is this the correct answer?
- Now, reveal your answers.
(So Min and Young Ji wrote,
"The Gettysburg Address.")
(The answer: The Gettysburg Address)
- Is this the correct answer?
- Gertzburg.
- Gosh.
- Hey.
(Se Chan almost got it right.)
- Gosh.
- What...
She wrote, "The LA Speech."
- "The amazing speech."
(The amazing speech)
(Haha wrote, "The amazing speech.")
The answer is
"The Gettysburg Address."
- So...
- He wrote, "Gertzburg." Gosh.
- What's "Gertzburg?" Darn it.
- Gertzburg...
- I thought...
- What's that?
Great job.
I told you it would be asked.
(The Gettysburg Address)
(Both of Jong Kook's students
got it wrong.)
Can his answer be aired?
"The amazing speech?"
Hey, what's "The LA Speech?"
My gosh.
It's the Gettysburg Address.
- Why did you...
- Hey, Se Chan.
- I'm sorry.
- What is "Gertzburg?"
Gosh, I'm so stupid.
My students,
show your answers again.
- Why...
- Both of them got it right.
- That's not important.
- I'm proud of you.
Here goes the next question.
- The next question... Hey.
- Give us an easy one.
Make sure
to get the second one right.
What is the production
of comparatively light goods...
- such as food, textile goods,
- Great.
- and paper?
- This is good.
- Okay.
- Such as food,
(What's the industry of light goods
such as food and paper?)
(The amazing LA siblings write
the answer right away this time.)
(Teacher Ji is sure
that his students know the answer.)
(What's light industry?)
"Of comparatively light goods..."
"such as food, textile goods,
and paper."
(Teacher Ji with bad eyesight
barely read it to them.)
What's the industry...
(Jae Suk read it clearly
to his students too.)
(Now, heavy chemical industry!)
- I learned this back then.
- Right.
(China...)
(It has nothing to do with China.)
(Jae Suk also compared it
to the heavy chemical industry.)
- I see.
- Okay.
- Don't give them any hints.
- I told you about the light goods.
- Write down the answer.
- Five, four,
- three, two,
- Hurry up.
- Hurry!
- One. Show your answers.
Okay. Good. Show your answers.
(The answer: Light industry)
(Happy)
(Both of them wrote,
"light industry.")
(Both of Team Jong Kook's members
got it right as well!)
- Okay.
- Show your answers.
(How did Team Jae Suk do?)
- Gosh, he's so stupid.
- Okay.
- My gosh.
(Se Chan wrote,
"heavy cheminal industry!")
- Good job, you guys.
- Isn't it the correct answer?
- He didn't even write that right.
- What's "heavy cheminal industry?"
(Se Chan created a new word
that doesn't exist.)
Se Chan, I taught you that one.
- The light goods.
- Light industry!
Now, I remember that, Sae Ho.
I got confused because you talked...
- about heavy chemical industry.
- I guessed them all, right?
But I told you
about the light industry too.
Besides, it's "chemical,"
not "cheminal."
- Gosh, seriously.
- We're the aces.
"Cheminal?"
- What's "cheminal?"
- "Cheminal."
- I too can be funny if I want to.
- Okay. They got it right.
- What a shame.
- Don't try to be funny.
- Stay calm.
- Sir, please count down slowly.
- It's okay.
Your students are stupid.
- Stay calm. What did you just say?
- Your students are...
- They're stupid.
- Don't say that.
- You've crossed the line.
- Gosh.
It's because their teacher is not
competent enough.
- Gosh, seriously.
- They must have different talents.
I impressed myself.
- I guessed all the questions.
- My head hurts.
- Ready.
- It's okay.
Write the basic principles
of the democratic election.
- Okay. You know the answer, right?
- I told you about this, right?
I taught you this one.
(Write the basic principles
of the democratic election.)
- Jjajangmyeon.
- I taught you this earlier.
Jjajangmyeon.
We all eat jjajangmyeon...
(Could the jjajangmyeon method
have helped them memorize it?)
- Ssaebssaeb, I taught you this.
- You know it, right?
- Should I write all of them?
- Listen.
They might not have understood
the question.
No way. It's not confusing at all.
Gosh. That's not the correct answer!
What are you doing?
- You can't tell him that.
- That's not the correct answer!
(Teacher Yoo shouts angrily.)
- He's not allowed to do that.
- You can't do that.
- All right. Listen, everyone.
- Darn it.
- He just...
- You got a warning.
- Can you repeat the question?
- Ssaebssaeb.
- It's about elections.
- Don't say anything.
- Oh, right. Give me a second!
- It's about elections.
- Three, two,
- SEUD?
- Yes, that's right.
- one. Show your answers.
- You know this.
- Four!
- Three, two,
- SEUD?
- Yes, that's right.
- one. Show your answers.
(Secret ballot, universal suffrage,
direct suffrage, equal suffrage)
(The answer: Universal, equal,
direct suffrage, secret ballot)
(Universal suffrage, equal suffrage,
(The jjajangmyeon method worked.)
- What's the last word?
- "Direct suffrage."
- Did you write, "Straight?"
No, it's "direct."
Free and equal suffrage,
and secret ballot.
Is it "direct?" I'm relieved.
Only Se Chan got it wrong.
- What?
- Okay.
- Se Chan.
- Only Se Chan...
(Shaking his head)
- Gosh. What's his problem?
- I told you it was about elections.
- Empty Head!
- Listen.
- Freedom is a concept of democracy.
- I did an amazing job, right?
- It's universal suffrage.
- This is giving me a bad headache.
- Hey.
- My gosh.
- I knew all of the answers.
- You see,
Se Chan put too much information
into his brain.
Jae Suk, I'm having a bad headache.
- It was too much for him.
- That's...
I did an amazing job, right?
I guessed all the questions.
Right? What do you think?
You respect me, right?
I really do.
- SEUD. Good job.
- I wrote, "direct."
- Yes. You did well.
- I got it right.
Great job.
- Se Chan, it was too much for you.
- It was too much for me.
Guys, you're doing great.
It was too much for you.
Here goes the next question.
- Please count down slowly.
- Before that...
Teachers, you gave your students
too many hints.
- I didn't give them any hints.
- Right?
- Don't give them any hints.
- Seok Sam.
You gave them a huge hint.
- I didn't do that.
- Wait.
You're sitting
too close to the students.
- But they're not my students.
- Let's switch the seats.
- No, you shouldn't sit there.
- You can't do that.
- No.
- You can't sit here.
- Let's switch the seats.
This is the best...
- This is the right arrangement.
- Indeed.
- This is just right.
- Teacher Kim, sit over there.
- You two switch seats.
- Oh, me?
- Okay. I'll sit here.
- I didn't tell them anything.
- Let's prevent him from talking.
- Right. Let's stop him.
- I can't give them any hints.
- This is good.
Sae Ho, I feel like
I'm going to throw up.
- I'm so nervous right now.
- I'm having a bad headache.
- Me too.
- My head hurts.
My heart is beating like crazy.
Please hurry up and continue.
We're so nervous.
Please continue quickly.
- Right. Let's stop him.
- I can't give them...
(Leaning forward)
Hey, what are you doing, you punk?
I just turned around...
(Hey, what are you doing, you punk?)
(I just turned around...)
- Don't do it.
- How dare you call him a punk?
- How could you do that?
- Don't intimidate the students.
He's 41 years old.
- I felt impatient.
- I feel dizzy.
- I was too impatient.
- How dare you?
- Okay. Let's go.
- Here we go.
- We've got this!
- Se Chan.
- Let's do this!
- You two are doing great. Okay.
- Now...
- Gosh, seriously.
What are the market conditions...
where a single company controls
the entire market...
- I don't know this one.
- and the one...
where more than two companies
dominate the market?
- I don't know the answer.
- What?
- And the one...
- I taught you this earlier.
where more than two companies...
- dominate the market?
- I taught you this one.
- What?
- I taught you.
(Monopoly and oligopoly are
the market conditions...)
(where a single or a few companies
control the market.)
(Only Jong Kook told his students
to memorize the terms.)
- It's often mentioned in the news.
- Just...
- think about the meaning.
- Don't say anything.
- Five.
- Oh, gosh.
- Four.
- We talked about it.
- Three.
- Don't.
- Two.
- I read it to you guys.
- Show your answers.
- Be confident.
- I read it to you guys.
- "Market manipulation?"
- Hey!
- Be confident.
- I read it to you guys.
- I have no idea.
(Suk Jin's students are
overly confident.)
- My gosh.
- "Market manipulation?"
(She must've thought of something
that's crafty.)
- "Market manipulation?"
- Isn't it "production rate?"
(He even misspelled the words.)
(Sae Ho wrote,
"Catching 2 birds with 1 stone.")
(His answer is even worse.)
- I told you about this.
- I thought this was correct.
Ji Hyo, show your answer.
- Come on. I told you about this.
- Monopoly and oligopoly.
- Oh, right. I remember that.
Hey, I told you about this
several times.
- They all got it wrong.
- I read it to you.
We skipped this part.
- We didn't learn this.
- You learned the fair trade act.
- We didn't learn it.
- We didn't learn this.
- What a shame.
It was in the bottom left corner,
but I told them...
- to memorize it.
- Come back.
They didn't know the answer.
Stop pretending...
- you taught them.
- We couldn't have covered it all.
- But I read it several times.
- They didn't know the answer.
Only you're saying
that you taught them.
Didn't your teachers teach you that?
- No, we didn't learn it.
- No, he didn't.
- Gosh, you guys.
- Monopoly and oligopoly.
- Monopoly.
- But...
- I taught them.
What's the point of teaching them?
They didn't remember it.
The result is the same.
Still, you should've taught them.
Don't be ridiculous.
Our teacher likes to study
more than he likes to teach.
- Mister.
- Gosh.
- Yes?
- Make me a paper crane.
- Come on.
- Make me one.
- I'm not...
- the teacher that you think I am.
- Give it a try.
- The tutors aren't kidding around.
- Right?
- Here we go.
- Focus, guys.
None of that matters
if they don't know the answer.
Here we go.
In October of 1972,
a new constitutional order...
that permitted
the reelection of presidents...
and promoted
an indirect election system...
was issued.
We went over this earlier.
(Answer: The Yooshin Order)
I mentioned this earlier.
- Se Chan!
- Five.
Look at So Min
write down the answer.
Three.
(They only have 5 seconds
to write down the answer.)
- Se Chan!
- Five.
Look at So Min
write down the answer.
- She's smiling!
- Two...
- Show me your answers.
- Yes!
- The Yooshin Order.
- Right, the Yooshin Order.
(Ji Hyo and Haha couldn't remember.)
You're out.
- Yes!
- The Yooshin Order.
(Sae Ho wrote down
the correct answer.)
I can't believe him.
(Teacher's pet Se Chan
couldn't write down anything.)
- You're out.
- This is too difficult.
- Right before the quiz began.
- Unbelievable.
You said you had this in the bag!
(The Empty Head Sisters
answered correctly once again.)
They're the best.
(Other than monopoly and oligopoly,
she answered everything correctly.)
So Min answered
every question correctly!
Right, it's the Yooshin Order.
So Min, I'm pleasantly surprised.
- You don't even need to think.
- Me too!
Young Ji, you too.
Am I or am I not a spotter?
I told you I could spot the answers.
Spot your own gray hair, Suk Jin.
Young Ji and So Min don't even need
to hear the entire question.
I'm not stupid!
I'm not an empty head!
I hope your mothers
are watching this.
Ladies, your daughters
have scored the most points.
Do you see how smart my girls are?
What? No, I haven't been able to.
- My girls...
- I was too occupied with my boys.
- Before he completed the question.
- I was occupied with my boys!
How can I look at them
when I'm busy with my boys?
Currently in the lead
is Team Suk Jin.
(Groaning)
- What's wrong with you?
- What's the matter?
Why...
- What was that?
- What's wrong with you?
- Did you pull my chair out?
- Why would I do that?
- Sit down properly.
- Be careful.
- He pulled my chair out.
- Fine. Whatever.
- Gosh.
- Here's the next question.
This is one that every team studied.
What is Article 1 Section 2
of the Constitution?
- We've got this.
- What did you say again?
Song Kang Ho recited it in a movie.
- Come on.
- Seriously?
What is Article 1 Section 2
of the Constitution?
The longer one.
Gosh.
(What was it again?)
You are allowed to rephrase.
- I can't remember how it starts.
- My kids...
will write it down word for word.
- We went over it multiple times.
- Just a second.
Think of the line from the movie.
Article 1 Section 2.
"The sovereignty of
the Republic of Korea shall reside..."
"in the people,
and all state authority..."
- "shall emanate from the people."
- "From the people."
(It was gone over
by the other tutors too.)
- Hurry, will you?
- Four.
- That's right.
- Wait. I'm still writing it down.
- Then...
- You know how it goes.
Wait. I'm writing it down.
Stop. That's enough.
- Count it down!
- Give them five more seconds.
- Stop the clock.
- No, give them ten more seconds.
- Wait. I'm writing it down.
- Must we get it word for word?
- Time is up.
Show us your answer.
- It being long worries me.
He got it wrong.
- I'm still writing.
- Show us your answer.
- We'll check each answer.
- He got it wrong.
The sovereignty
resides in the people.
Check each answer individually.
- The sovereignty...
- The people speak of power.
What could the people possibly say?
I'll read mine.
- I'm almost in tears.
- The sovereignty resides...
in the people...
- and the power...
- You're reading it differently.
- You read it differently.
- His is incorrect.
- So Min got it wrong.
- Really?
- Young Ji's too.
- Yours is incorrect.
Let's see what my kids wrote.
The sovereignty of Korea
shall reside in the people...
- Only those two score points.
- Yes!
The sovereignty of Korea
shall reside in the people...
and all state authority
shall emanate from the people.
- They wrote it word for word.
- I said it'd be in the quiz.
I'm almost in tears.
- My kids...
- This is too much knowledge...
for you to swallow.
But I had it memorized.
- Me too.
- Exactly.
It's odd that they
actually got it right.
What do you mean?
They wrote it down word for word.
I'm surprised considering
how stupid they are.
They wrote it down word for word.
They couldn't possibly memorize it.
What do you mean?
- I know those two and...
- Mr. Ji, hold on.
I say this as an educator myself.
You're too old-fashioned.
- Exactly. He's the worst.
- That's not it.
- I know how they usually are.
- Also,
- I mentioned this earlier.
- Don't rain on their parade.
Even though
they should get the credit,
- you only complimented yourself.
- Teachers like them...
- will lead to...
- Can't you see I'm talking?
(Can't you see
that your teacher is talking?)
Teachers like them will lead to...
(He suddenly tells Sae Ho off.)
- I was talking just now.
- He's angry.
- That seemed old-fashioned too.
- Really?
- But the student...
- Please don't yell at them.
- Sit back down!
- Don't yell at the kids.
I'm impressed by the two of you.
- I was almost in tears just now.
- Right?
Aren't you the ones who wrote
LA Speech as an answer?
She wrote LA Speech.
I wrote the awesome speech.
Those are different.
- I wrote LA Speech.
- And together...
it's the awesome LA Speech.
- Let's wish them luck.
- Good luck.
- Let's go!
Which institution
deals with cases...
- regarding the constitutional law?
- This one you know.
I notified you of this
right before the quiz began.
(Se Chan starts
to write something down.)
Jae Suk's an intimidating teacher.
That's it. That's the one.
(Se Chan starts
to write something down.)
(The other students
write down their answers too.)
- Five, four...
- This one...
- Seriously?
- Three, two...
- Give me some more time.
- One.
- You've got this.
- The Constitutional Court.
Okay!
(Both members of Team Jae Suk
answer correctly.)
(Answer: The Constitutional Court)
- We didn't learn this one.
- You'll win anyway.
- You've got this.
- The Constitutional Court.
- Okay!
- Impeachment?
(She wrote down
anything that came to mind.)
The answer is
the Constitutional Court.
- I got it right.
- Only So Min got it wrong.
You have the same teacher,
so what is the matter with you?
No, he didn't teach us this word.
You didn't go over this.
He didn't teach us this word.
(A loud victory celebration)
His answer shouldn't
have been allowed.
He was out of time.
No way.
- Nicely done.
- There are nine judges in total.
- That's right.
- Stay put, will you?
- Nicely done, guys.
- Hold on.
Stay put, will you?
- Nicely done, guys.
- Hold on.
Who are you to tell my kids
to stay put?
- Why...
- Because they're loud.
Can't you see how quiet my kids are?
(They are so quiet.)
There's nothing wrong
with enjoying...
- the victory.
- It's nothing to be proud about.
- You're way out of line.
- The court is way above us.
Mr. Kim?
(The student keeps talking back,)
(so he threatens him with a kick.)
Mr. Kim, are you one
to pack a punch?
- Do you pack a punch?
- I do.
I don't!
What on earth is going on?
Mr. Kim, he's about to hit me.
- You scoundrel.
- He's hitting me.
- What do you mean?
- Sit back down.
Why should I listen to you?
- Look at how modest my kids are.
- Nine.
There are nine judges.
- And six must agree...
- For the case to be ruled on.
That's it! Nicely done.
How smart of you.
You're at the top of your class.
Let's get this next one right.
You need to
answer this one correctly.
Here's the next question.
Name the three basic
democratic values.
This is the one!
(The three basic democratic values)
- This one you know.
- This is the one!
- Five...
- You know this.
- Four...
- The countdown's too fast.
- This is the one.
- It's too fast.
- Come on.
- You're counting down too fast.
(Answer: Freedom,
equality, and human dignity)
(Se Chan doesn't even
need to stop and think.)
- All right. Two, one, hold it up.
- It's too fast.
- Hold it up.
- Show me your answers.
- Okay, hold it up.
- Hold it up now.
- Seriously?
- Did I get it wrong?
Why is love one of the basic values?
(Freedom, equality, and love)
(Love is added out of nowhere.)
- I thought it was love.
- Yes!
- He wrote down "love"
- Love?
Love!
I can't believe you guys.
- You guys are the best.
- Nice.
You're not giving me
enough time to write it down.
You guys are the smartest.
(Even the Empty Head Sisters
wrote down the correct answer.)
- So Min, I can't believe it.
- This is amazing.
You're the best.
- Being smart makes you sexy.
- If only I had studied in school!
Smart and sexy.
- It was a laugh, right?
- Smart and sexy.
"Dignified as humans"
doesn't seem quite right.
- What are you talking about?
- That's wrong.
That is incorrect.
- That is incorrect.
- It should be "human dignity."
- That should be incorrect.
- Hold on a second.
- How is this wrong?
They mean the same thing.
Human and human nature
are two different words.
- They're different.
- They mean different things.
I know that,
but they have similar meanings.
Objectively speaking,
- they aren't the same.
- They aren't.
(According to the textbook,
Haha gave the wrong answer.)
- They aren't the same.
- Jae Suk.
- What...
- What do you think you're doing?
What's with him?
- They aren't the same.
- Jae Suk.
(Crashing)
- What was that?
- What's with him?
- You...
- Why did you kick that?
Hold on a second.
Is this allowed?
You made our teacher mad!
- He should be reprimanded.
- Why did you kick it?
- He's scaring me.
- Why did you kick that?
I pushed it...
- but it got knocked over.
- Why...
Is he a thug?
I was only trying
to push it to the side.
Production isn't the same
as productivity.
The same goes for
human and human nature.
The teachers aren't people
to mess with.
What Haha wrote
is completely different.
Why would you leave this here?
That's my chair, you know.
No, it's mine.
- Can you make me a jewelry box?
- Let's take our seats.
You...
- Make me a jewelry box.
- You did well. It's all right.
He keeps on asking me
to make something.
Here we go.
- It's all right.
- There are only two questions left.
Only two questions.
I think you can ask them a few more.
The points you have scored are
13, 16, and 14 respectively.
It's doable.
- We can win this.
- Just one more correct answer.
Let's at least get second place.
- You guys did it.
- We've been...
on a roll, right?
Just maintain the lead.
- He's pressuring us.
- How is it that...
they were tutored by the principal?
- Exactly.
- He just told us to memorize it...
which is the way of the old.
Here we go.
My head is killing me.
What is the money earned in business
after accounting for the expenses?
- I taught you this one.
- Me too.
- I mentioned a name.
- It was on top of...
- the right hand corner.
- Three, two,
- one. Show us your answer.
- I mentioned this too.
- Show us your answer.
- The answer's profit.
- Yes. It's profit.
- Profit.
- Oh, no.
The answer is profit.
(So Min wrote the same wrong answer
as Ji Hyo.)
Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
- It's okay. "Net income" is fine.
Ji Hyo wrote "net income."
I wrote the same thing.
We're pure.
Wait. We might make it then.
We're still last place.
We explained it,
but you couldn't remember it.
Why does our teacher
keep blaming us?
- Sir, why do you keep blaming us?
- Hey.
They had a good start,
but that was all.
I taught you,
but you didn't remember.
You just studied
the first few chapters.
- The teacher keeps blaming us.
- Like a sponge.
But this teacher is no joke.
What's the point of teaching you?
Let's get this right.
The world only acknowledges
the number one.
Sit down, sir.
- Yes.
- Let's sit, teachers.
You got this. Let's go.
- This is the last question.
- Okay. It's done.
We can turn the tables
if both of them get it right.
Who is the German journalist
who took a risk to film a video...
to reveal the truth of the May 18th
Democratic Uprising...
in Gwangju in 1980 to the world?
- Sorry? A German what?
- His name?
A German journalist.
- We can turn the tables.
- Wait.
(Jurgen Hinzpeter)
(Suk Jin who just kept saying
the name to make them memorize it)
It's written here.
(Jae Suk who gave them
a detailed and thorough explanation)
(They definitely heard his name,
"Jurgen Hinzpeter.")
The name of the person?
A German journalist.
- Okay. We can turn the tables.
- Wait.
(If both of them get it right,
they can turn the tables.)
We can turn the tables.
(Will they be able to turn tables
with Mr. Yoo's teaching?)
We can turn the tables.
- Three.
- We can turn the tables.
Three.
Two.
- One.
- Wait.
Jurgen Hinzpeter.
(Jurgen Hinzpeter)
- Jurgen Hinzpeter. That's correct.
- Jurgen Hinzpeter.
- Hinzpeter.
- It's "Hinz."
It's not "Hiz."
Come on.
- It's a relief.
- Isn't it "Hiz?"
It's "Hinz."
"Hinz."
(So Min got it right.
Young Ji got it wrong.)
We're tied.
It's good. We're tied.
Who is "Karnayle Wale?"
(Both Ji Hyo and Haha got it wrong.)
- Oh, no.
- We're tied then.
We need one more question.
Jurgen Hinzpeter.
Only Sae Ho and So Min got it right.
Okay. It's good. We're tied.
"Jurgen Pepper?"
We got first place.
(Team Suk Jin won 1st place.)
This is unusual.
- Both teams are in second place.
- Give us the last question.
You got this.
- You got this.
- This is a one-on-one battle.
This is the last question
that will decide the ranking.
- I'll make sure it's fair.
- Good.
We'll be looking at the front.
No, I'll be just looking here.
(Another quiet battle
between teachers started.)
- Do I have to look that way?
- Do as you want.
- I'll look here.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
- Speak slowly, please.
Here it is.
What's the election system
where candidates are elected...
by a certain number of electors?
- It has come.
- It's done.
(What's the election system
where candidates are elected...)
(by a certain number of electors?)
(It seems Sae Ho got it.)
- Ssaebssaeb.
- What? Hold on.
(Se Chan looks confused.)
(Direct election
and indirect election!)
(He definitely explained about
direct and indirect elections.)
- This is an election system.
- Why are you telling them?
- I think we'll make it.
The other team doesn't know.
(It seems Team Jong Kook
isn't sure.)
- The other team doesn't know.
- They know it.
Two.
(But Teacher Kim also gave them
a detailed explanation about it.)
(The memorization battle
among the four students)
(The team with more members
who got it right will be 2nd place.)
- It's either of the two.
- They know it.
- Didn't they say this before?
- I didn't hear it.
Yes. We made it.
They got it right.
(Yes! We made it!)
Se Chan, show us.
(Sae Ho got it right as well.)
(How about Se Chan?)
- Se Chan didn't get it right.
- "Coup d'etat."
(Coup d'etat?)
He's eliminated.
Indirect election. That's right.
It's all good.
(Team Jong Kook won.)
- We won!
- Indirect election.
(The 2nd place is happier
than the 1st place.)
That's right.
- It's all good. Indirect election.
- We're done.
Direct election and indirect election.
I made use of it here.
Indirect election. Yes. That's it.
Gosh.
- Indirect election. Yes. That's it.
- Earlier...
Hey. Today,
I don't feel good.
You told me off about my attitude
of learning earlier, and you...
- Okay.
- It's a pity.
It's all good.
Team Suk Jin, the 1st place,
gets 15 points.
Team Jong Kook,
the 2nd place gets 10 points.
We made it.
Team Jae Suk,
the 3rd place gets 5 points.
I wrote everything.
(They are precious points that will
help them when buying stocks.)
You wrote everything.
"Indirect election" is here.
Let's take a picture
to commemorate, Mother.
(Suk Jin's promotional photo
to hand out near cram schools)
Get up.
Let's take a picture to commemorate.
We did it.
I can do it. I'm not a fool.
- I think I became ten years older.
- No. You did well.
- I can do it.
- Now, as you used your brain,
- let's go upstairs to eat.
- It's done.
- I'm not hungry at all.
- We didn't do well.
We didn't do well.
(It's time to move on
to the next seminar.)
Nice.
The scholarship student.
The top student.
It's okay. Things are going well.
- It's good.
- We're last place.
I'm proud, guys.
- You met a good teacher.
- Gosh.
- That's enough. Come on.
- Mother, we made it.
He's bragging so much.
I'm not bragging.
- It's just...
- We were just confused.
These guys are less capable.
- You taught them 100 questions.
- Sorry?
They just got ten right.
And you call yourself an amazing teacher?
He wants to get credit.
So he was like,
"These guys are less capable."
I made them succeed.
- Don't flatter yourself.
- Mother, don't misunderstand.
That's not what I mean.
After playing one game...
- I can't remember well.
- Everyone got ten years older.
It's much better to do something
with our bodies.
- For real.
- That's better.
Why are you so down?
- But Se Chan...
- My head hurts so much.
Se Chan forgot
as soon as he learned earlier.
He forgot it right away.
You guys studied together.
You were good.
He was nodding
as he wanted to please the teacher.
"Okay."
- Gosh. Sae Ho...
- He did write them down though.
should've created
a good environment to learn.
He was yawning.
His bad breath distracted me.
- My nose and my eyes were burning.
- I don't have bad breath.
- My eyes were burning.
- I brushed my teeth so many times.
I couldn't focus.
What do you mean I have bad breath?
I brushed my teeth. Are you saying
that I should see a doctor?
- That's enough.
- Probably because he lost weight.
Really?
It's important to know the image of
a company to earn money from stocks.
- Yes.
- Right.
That's why we prepared
this second seminar.
It's What Image training
for gaining insight.
- What Image?
It sounds fun.
It is similar to "Like Image."
However,
we'll show you a person,
which is the keyword of the round.
And you should defend yourself
using the image of the person.
(The member who was attacked
should defend with the image.)
For example, I said Kim Jong Kook.
And I went, "Jae Suk, four."
Then you should go,
"muscles" related to him.
And the next person who was attacked
should do the same,
using another image of Jong Kook.
Really?
It sounds difficult.
We'll divide you into two teams.
- Team Young Ji and Team Sae Ho.
- Really?
Young Ji,
pick four members you want.
- Four?
- Four.
A person with an image you can come
up with many words from is nice.
First, Se Chan.
- Me?
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Him?
Good.
For your information,
Jae Suk sucks at this game.
- Yes.
- Then I choose So Min.
So Min.
I'm sorry, but don't we usually
take turns to pick members?
- If she picks all the members...
- Right.
- Stay still.
- Just let her choose.
- Ji Hyo.
- Nice.
And my teacher, Suk Jin.
Suk Jin is bad too.
I think you chose the wrong members.
Okay. I like it.
It's good.
- It's good.
- I like it.
- I like it, Sae Ho.
Let's go.
I think you chose the wrong
combination of members.
- No.
- It's fine?
I think we can do well
as we're calm.
The ones who always insist
are in this team.
What do you mean we insist?
- Insist? That's too harsh.
- We're logical.
These guys are experts
at making a scene.
- Sir.
- You guys are experts at it.
- What scene?
- We're just capable.
What scene did we make?
They make ridiculous claims.
- We're logical and persuasive.
- Of course.
They're strong.
Yes. They're strong.
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
Sae Ho will go first.
The first person...
- is Se Chan.
- Se Chan.
That's neat.
(Keyword: Yang Se Chan)
- It's about Se Chan.
- Se Chan.
- If it's four... Wait.
- This is hard though.
That's right.
There are only four beats.
Ssaebssaeb.
- Should we go?
- A fool.
- We can't overlap, right?
- No, you can't.
It can be a long word.
- Okay.
- It can be a sentence.
- Good.
- Nice.
- I got you.
- Let's go.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- Bring it up.
- What image
Ji Hyo, two.
Protruding mouth.
Sae Ho, five.
Five? Okay!
(Sae Ho, five?)
This is it.
- I'm sorry about this.
- This is it. Okay.
Excuse me. You know...
- This is not it. I was thinking...
- We won.
- of the strawberry game.
- They'll lose anyway.
Ji Hyo lost it after the quiz.
You said that yourself.
Let that go please.
- No.
- We can't do that.
- Let that go please.
- No.
Mr. Kim. We can't do that.
Play it right. Come on.
We'll start with Ji Hyo.
I'm going first.
The next person is Kim Jong Kook.
Kim Jong Kook. Okay.
- Kim Jong Kook.
- It has to be now.
- Let's do this.
- Okay. Good.
- What image
Jae Suk, three.
Jong Kook.
Come on.
(He suddenly calls Jong Kook.)
What's wrong with you?
Attack Jae Suk from now on.
- Attack Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk, three.
He got everything wrong.
- "Jong Kook?"
- Seriously?
- I wasn't expecting it.
- Just say muscle.
I wasn't prepared. I'm sorry.
Why weren't you prepared?
- Why weren't you prepared?
- I'm sorry.
(Jae Suk starts apologizing.)
- What were we doing?
- It's my fault.
I will never do that again.
Focus.
Yes, sir. I am sorry.
I will never do that again.
- At least one.
- You can do it, Jae Suk.
- Yes, sir.
- Think about two things.
- Sit down.
Jong Kook is feeling better
with his apology.
Yes, sir.
He's nervous
about this game the most.
- Let's go with yours.
- Yes.
The keyword is still Jong Kook.
Here we go.
Image
- What image
- Image
(The intro is getting long.)
What image
- Image
- What image
It's not Lee Mi Ja
Let's get the beat first.
- Who are you
- What image
Who are you
I'm Ji Suk Jin
Hurry up
Whatever it is, hurry up
Lee Mi Ja also watches Running Man
Does she? Hello
(Suk Jin suddenly says hello.)
Please join our show
We want to see you
We're your big fan
- Come on
- What image
Jae Suk, four.
- Jong Kook...
- Seriously.
(Jae Suk says the name again.)
- No.
- It's boring.
It's boring.
- Wasn't that weird?
- Jong Kook again?
You got the beat though.
I am sorry.
- You were...
- My bad.
- practicing just until now.
- It's my fault.
- I will never do that again.
- Why would you say Jong Kook again?
- He's driving me crazy.
- The rally doesn't go on.
- No.
- Let's play among us.
- Gosh.
They keep coming after me.
- That's why...
- Then you should be prepared.
- Prepare yourself.
- Go say something to them.
The next keyword is So Min.
- So Min.
- It's So Min?
- Think about So Min's images.
- Okay.
Innocence.
- So Min.
- Go.
What image
- What image
Young Ji, three.
Slim.
Jae Suk, three.
Slim...
Come on.
Hey!
(It's Jae Suk again.)
This is not fun.
- Hang on.
- It's getting annoying.
Come here.
Do it for at least once.
Play without me.
- This is too much.
- Go on without me.
- Jae Suk is terrible at it.
- Play without me.
He's terrible.
I want to play the game.
- Play without me.
- Jae Suk. Go lie down.
Go lie down in the back.
Gosh.
- This is wrong.
- Come here.
I told you to think about one.
I told you to think about two,
didn't I?
- He's terrible.
- He's so bad.
I could say ribbit.
- I told you to prepare two things.
- I should've said ribbit.
- Why did I do that?
- There's more.
Why did I do that?
- But...
- Why didn't I say ribbit?
Gosh.
Let's try So Min again.
- It's So Min again.
- It's So Min. Go.
- What image
Suk Jin, three.
(Keyword: So Min)
Cute.
(He barely defends himself.)
(Laughing)
(He's lost for words.)
- Good job.
- What's wrong with you?
Good job.
- What kind of game is this?
- Gosh.
This is no image game.
- It's over.
- How come I never get to play?
It's over.
Let young people play without them.
- Let young people play.
- Let's play without them.
- Can only the MZ Generation play?
- Jae Suk.
- Your face turned red.
- Only the MZ Generation.
- I...
- Why did you turn red?
Let them have some coffee.
The rest of us will play.
Let's start.
- Let's start.
- I can do it now.
The next keyword is Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk.
- That's me.
- Jae Suk's image?
- Se Chan. You go first.
The keyword is Jae Suk.
Image
- Image
- What image
Haha, two.
Bug. Se Chan, one.
Nipples.
(Jae Suk didn't expect nipples.)
Sae Ho, two.
Grasshopper. So Min, three.
Low nipples, Sae Ho, two.
Nation. Suk Jin, three.
- MC.
- You got it.
Jae Suk, two.
Kyung Eun.
(Jae Suk did it.)
Young Ji, three.
(Keyword: Jae Suk)
(She fails to defend.)
(They did it.)
- That was fun.
- Hey.
- We did it this time.
- We did it.
- Good job.
That's how you play.
Jae Suk is amazing.
We said nipples three times.
And he endured it.
- I don't mind. They're mine.
- You don't mind?
We still won.
- That was more like it.
- Good job.
That was tense.
- We did it.
- That was a good one.
I got goosebumps. I never thought
it'd go on for that long.
We did it.
- Yes!
- Let's do this.
The next keyword is Young Ji.
- Young Ji.
Young Ji? Hold on.
Go.
- What image
Suk Jin, three.
(It's getting faster.)
KARA. Sae Ho, two.
Second. Se Chan, four.
Cute. Jae Suk, four.
(Keyword: Young Ji)
(Four...)
What was that?
I was thinking New Zealand.
- No.
- New Zealand.
New Zealand.
- Look.
- That was a good move.
- New Zealand.
- That's too long.
New Zealand.
She studied in New Zealand.
Then just say study abroad.
Okay. I'll do that next time.
But you can't.
How bad is it?
- Play like the last time.
- Yes.
Okay. I'll play like the last time.
Next person is Haha.
- Let's go with Haha.
- Haha?
- Me?
- Yes.
- Do I go first?
Image.
Image, what image
- What image
Jong Kook, three.
Byul. Suk Jin, four.
- Suk Jin, four.
- Dream...
(Dream...)
- Suk Jin.
- Okay.
Were you introducing him?
Dream!
Why?
- Next is...
- What about him?
- Right back at me?
- Of course.
Suk Jin. Why are you so nervous?
- Dream!
- Next is Dream!
- Calm down.
Gosh. Fine. Bring it on.
- I can't take it anymore.
- The next keyword is Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
Hang on.
- Jong Kook will start first.
- Do I start?
- What image
- Young Ji, four.
- Zoned-out Ji Hyo.
Sae Ho, three.
Short hair. So Min, two.
Mapo. Jae Suk, four.
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook.)
Se Chan, three.
Woman. Jong Kook, one.
Big eyes. Se Chan, four.
Double eye lids.
(Se Chan succeeds in defending.)
Jong Kook, two.
(Jong Kook, two.)
- Wait...
- Okay.
(Jong Kook fails.)
That was a good one.
Go blame him.
I was thinking.
- I can't repeat the same word.
- Do you think I wasn't thinking?
Because I can't repeat
the same word.
You think I didn't know that?
Jae Suk is raising his voice.
- That's not it.
- You need to do better.
Some...
Why are you quiet?
- I agree.
- Am I right?
- I was losing focus.
- Yes.
Why are you quiet
when Jong Kook got it wrong?
- But...
- Don't you agree?
Right? Am I wrong?
- You're not wrong.
- See?
The next keyword is Sae Ho.
- Sae Ho.
- An image about me.
- Yes.
- Let's do this.
- What image
- Ji Hyo, four.
- Designer brand.
Jong Kook, three.
Show off. Se Chan, four.
(He's off beat.)
- Hang on.
- He ignored it.
You took it too far.
- What?
- You ignored it.
- You took it too far.
- It's serious.
- Jong Kook.
- That was wrong.
Why are you all quiet?
- Why are you quiet?
- He was completely off.
- You let that go?
- Why are you quiet?
It was iffy.
It wasn't iffy at all.
- Jae Suk. Why are you quiet?
- It was iffy.
- He just pushed me.
My goodness.
- "Show off."
- Look.
If I was wrong, say I was wrong.
I didn't say anything
because it was iffy.
Why are you quiet?
- It was iffy, wasn't it?
- "Show off."
Let us try it one more time.
- Apologize.
- It was iffy.
- Sorry.
- Suk Jin.
Do you have to cross your arms?
- It's not that serious.
- I said I'm sorry.
He just apologized.
Get up
and bring your hands together.
- Why should I?
- Why do you demand it?
Sit down.
He's old enough.
I'm old enough.
Get up.
Sit down. Why are you up?
- Choose one.
- Choose what?
Are you going to get up
or should I sit down?
- Sit down.
- Okay.
- He's listening to you.
- There.
- He's obedient.
Currently, it's 7 to 7. It's a tie.
- I know.
- No way.
- I love this game.
- This is the last round.
- Let's do this.
- Let's win.
Since it's the last round,
the keyword is Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk. Good.
- Really?
- Okay.
(Jae Suk's image will
determine the winner.)
(Which team will it be?)
Wait. I have to choose one.
Let's go.
- What image
(The last round begins.)
(Keyword: Jae Suk)
Suk Jin, four.
Mapo.
(He fails in the speed of light.)
- Come on.
- What was that?
Let me go again.
- It was a sudden attack.
- Let me off this once.
- He was in a daze.
- What was "Mapo?"
- What was that?
Let me off this once.
You let him off.
If they accept your apology,
we will let you off.
Apologize then.
We can't let him off.
- Apologize.
- I will apologize.
Apologize formally.
Sorry.
- Apologize formally.
- We can't accept that.
What did you say earlier about
how an apology should be?
- Apologize sincerely.
- How should you apologize?
I have a suggestion then.
Apologize to us like this.
"I am terribly sorry."
"I won't do it again."
(Hopping)
- That's a good idea.
- Apologize like this.
- Go ahead, Suk Jin.
- Go outside the door like that.
- Hurry up.
- We can accept that apology.
Hurry up and do it.
We can accept that apology.
Wouldn't it be better to lose?
- No.
- Of course not.
- It's too much.
- The result depends on it.
- He should do that much.
Please do it.
- That's right.
- Think of it as a comedy skit.
- "I am terribly sorry."
- Please do it.
- "I won't do it again."
- Then hop away.
- Do it politely.
- Don't show your back.
- That's right.
"I am so sorry."
I am sorry.
- No.
- Put your hands together.
- For goodness' sake.
- Think of it as a comedy skit.
"I am so sorry."
"Misters, I am so sorry."
"I won't do it again."
My goodness.
(He becomes soft-spoken.)
I didn't know this would happen.
I am so sorry.
My goodness. I am sorry.
You have to do everything here.
- That doesn't count.
- Come on.
- It should be good enough.
It should be good enough you punk.
- That doesn't count.
- What else do you want me to do?
Why did you hit him?
Why did you hit me?
- It should be good enough.
- No.
Don't be absurd. That doesn't count.
- Forget it.
- We won then.
- Won't you accept his apology?
- We won't accept it.
- But he apologized.
You won.
- Okay.
- You guys did nothing!
- It wasn't anything hard.
- What was that?
- You should have done it properly.
- You ruined it.
- You just had to do this.
- Why didn't you do it?
Seriously.
Why didn't you do it?
"I am terribly sorry.
I won't do it again."
- Why didn't you do it?
- It wasn't anything hard.
I am not the type to bow to someone.
- Forget it.
- That's a lie.
Thus, this team will receive points.
- We don't have good energy.
- Seriously.
You must be hungry...
- due to the busy seminar schedule.
- Yes.
To help you get adjusted,
we prepared a local meal.
- Is it pizza? Burger?
- I think it's pizza.
- The food will be brought in.
- Bring it in.
But Sae Ho is...
a model for a burger brand.
Really?
- So he has to eat separately.
- What?
Are we eating burgers?
- No.
- We aren't eating burgers.
- The contract covers Western food.
- Really?
You should have divided the terms
into smaller categories.
I am not that influential yet.
- Those are ribs.
- The dishes look so tasty.
- My goodness.
- Outback Steakhouse.
(It's a meal
for the hungry investors.)
It's my favorite dish, garlic steak.
- I love steak.
- Garlic steak.
Sae Ho, please step aside.
Sae Ho.
- Step aside.
You should have prepared
Korean food or something.
(The menu is up to the advertisers.)
- It's nice.
- Thank you for the food.
- Seriously.
- Sae Ho, you can't be in the shot.
- Really?
(The model of the burger brand
gets chased away.)
- It's the tenderloin.
- I experienced the same thing.
A Korean meal. It's nice too.
Enjoy the food comfortably.
- It's nice.
- Thank you for the food.
- This is the New York steak.
- Yes.
Look at the meat. Look at this.
- Try this one.
- Dip it in the sauce.
- This one.
- This one?
The steak is so tasty.
(The monsters of product placement
are actually impressed.)
It's so juicy.
- It's still good.
- It's tasty, right?
- Gosh, it's nice.
- Outback Steakhouse is the best.
The soup is nice.
It's no wonder
the chain is number one.
Is Sae Ho receiving a penalty?
This is the tenderloin.
It's nice. The soup is really nice.
(He enjoys the hot soup by himself.)
Isn't it customary to prepare
a different menu...
if you know about
a guest's limitations?
I get that we are in New York,
but there must be other dishes.
- Be quiet. Let us eat in peace.
- I am sorry.
My goodness.
Jae Suk, please eat
the Toowoomba pasta.
- This one?
- Yes.
- We are eating so much.
- What's the name?
- Toowoomba pasta.
- The sauce is thick.
- It's a dish I eat by myself.
Don't be ridiculous.
We can share it.
No. If you butt in,
they will have to film it again.
No way.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- It's true.
(It's true.)
- My goodness.
- That's funny.
- You can't eat it.
- Hey. Don't be ridiculous.
- I need to eat it by myself.
They need a shot by myself.
(The advertisers want a shot
of Jae Suk by himself.)
Choowoom...
- It's Toowoomba pasta.
- Toowoomba, not Choowoomba.
I ate Toowoomba pasta so often
back in the day.
- Do they do deliveries?
- Yes.
- Like this? Do they do deliveries?
It would have been nice
if Sae Ho could eat with us.
Look at this.
Why are you not blending in
with us today?
- Will you keep doing things alone?
- Seriously.
Will you keep eating alone
like an A-list celebrity?
The soup is nice.
(The celebrity who loves
seaweed soup finishes eating.)
The flight to New York
will leave in a few hours.
- We will finally leave.
- This makes me a bit excited.
- New York
- I am excited.
- New York State of Mind
- Your points have piled up.
- Okay.
Now comes the last schedule.
It's called the Ants' Photo Time.
- Photo Time?
- The Ants' Photo Time.
The Running Man members
have tried something similar.
- You need to be in the angle.
- I know what it is.
Do you see this camera?
What it films
will show up on the monitor.
The camera will spin.
Then it will stop
in the count of three.
- We need to be in the angle.
- All the members of your team...
need to be in the angle.
- Okay.
- It's a team competition again.
Among eyes, nose, and mouth,
two need to show.
- Two or more.
- Okay.
One team will go at a time.
The number of teammates
who are in the shot...
- will be the points you receive.
- Okay.
But half of the opposing team
can disturb the process.
- Really?
- It won't be easy.
- Not many people will succeed.
- The disturbers in the shot...
will be counted for the points.
So they need to disturb
without appearing in the shot.
- We just need to be in the shot.
- Yes.
- It's over.
- Jong Kook's team will win.
I won't be so aggressive.
May I pick the teammates this time?
No. There is a separate rule.
- Stop getting ahead of yourself.
- Why are you acting up?
- Leave it up to the producer.
- Can't I ask a question?
Why are you acting up?
- Isn't that what the show is about?
- Acting up?
- Of course not.
- This show is about the quiet talk.
- That's right.
- Manners.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Do you think we acted up?
- You should just be quiet.
I didn't mean it like that.
As for the teams,
they will change for each round.
(The teams will change
for each round.)
We will ask you a question
with two possible answers.
People who choose
the same thing will be a team.
- Okay. It's about the character.
- That's nice.
That's really nice.
- What's so nice about it?
- Sae Ho.
What's so nice about it?
Your reactions are too much.
- It's nice.
- They are too over-the-top.
All right. Here comes the question
that will divide the teams...
- for the first round.
- What is it? Let's hear it.
- You will sit down or stand up.
- Okay.
- Please imagine the situation.
- Imagine.
Whom would you choose
as So Min's husband?
- So Min's husband?
- So Min?
- Sit down for Se Chan...
and stand up for Sae Ho.
(Whom would you choose
as So Min's husband?)
(Sit down for Se Chan
versus Stand up for Sae Ho)
- Both are good options.
- Do I choose as well?
- I choose as well, right?
- Yes.
- Come on.
- So Min's husband.
Why do we keep choosing
So Min's husband...
- among comedians?
- Why are my options so bad?
- I will stay quiet.
It's a bit strange.
- Why are they all comedians?
- So Min has no interest.
- It might be her fate.
- Right.
Sit down for Se Chan...
and stand up for Sae Ho.
Hold on.
- I don't know whom to choose.
- Think about it.
- Okay.
- Sit down for Se Chan.
- Stand up for Sae Ho.
- My husband.
- It's a matter of pride.
What do you think?
I need to think about it.
One,
- two, three.
- This is driving me crazy.
Five people chose Se Chan.
Why didn't you choose yourself?
(Disappointed)
I thought Jong Kook would stand up.
- Why didn't you choose yourself?
- I thought he would stand up.
Me too.
Se Chan,
the fact you stood up means...
- you want her to marry Sae Ho.
- Hey.
- You always told me to date So Min.
- But...
in this situation, it's Se Chan.
- Five people should come over here.
- Will they date now?
- Please put this on.
- Yes.
Okay.
What kind of a question was that?
Please share your reasons.
Sae Ho...
- is full of self-love.
- Self-love.
- He loves himself more.
- Yes.
- His character isn't compatible...
- That's right.
with So Min's.
You have a point.
- But Sae Ho...
- But once I date someone,
I get rid of self-love.
Can you give us an example?
Tell us about something you did.
- For example...
- Okay.
Have you ever been
in a relationship?
- He isn't lying.
- Come on.
You know what it means
to be in a relationship, right?
You share...
- lovely moments.
- She and I kissed, okay?
Sae Ho once dated a girl
from Suncheon.
I heard that he showers women
with gifts.
My first love
I dated at the age of 20...
was from Suncheon.
- Ms. Suncheon.
- A long-distance relationship.
- I had a missed call,
so I called and said,
"Honey, you called."
"Mister, what are you up to?"
- Did her father answer the phone?
- Yes.
- Her father.
- No. It was her.
- She is from Suncheon.
- "Mister, what are you up to?"
- Wasn't it her father?
- Did she say that?
- Yes.
- She said that.
- "Hello."
"Mister, what are you up to?"
- "Really?"
- "Did you have a meal?"
"Yes, I did. Did you?"
"Yes, I had Korean dishes."
- Really?
- Yes.
- "I miss you a lot, mister."
- Are you serious?
- Did you date a middle-aged woman?
- No.
- She used...
- She was his age.
- a dialect.
- Was she his age?
She asked me what I ate
and I told her that I had pasta.
"You shouldn't eat pasta."
"Your health comes first, okay?"
- Are you serious?
- I am serious.
- Was she younger than you?
- She was my age.
That's Sae Ho's love.
- That's right.
- He is sweet.
One time, he was seen
at Apgujeong-dong.
He was seen with a model.
Yes. He was seen with a model.
He walked like this.
You put your arm around her.
- Yes.
- I wanted to stand out.
I wanted to stand out.
(He barely managed
to put his arm around her.)
Don't lie. There is no way
she was that tall.
How did you kiss her?
I jumped.
I told her to close her eyes
and jumped.
(A brief kiss required
some serious jumping skills.)
- He is warmhearted.
- You could keep kissing her.
- He has kissed someone.
- He is warmhearted.
It couldn't be
a serious kiss though.
I am touched
that he has kissed someone.
In conclusion,
- don't date anyone in this circle.
- Why not?
- Then...
- You are out of their league.
- Then where will I meet someone?
- No, she isn't.
I will introduce you to someone.
- You?
- Like who?
Your younger friends
are in their 50s and 60s.
How will So Min date someone
in his 50s or 60s?
- Hey.
- That's worse.
My younger friends
aren't in their 60s.
They are in their 60s.
I am 100 percent sure
he will ask So Min,
"Miss, did you have a meal?"
(The man who is her dad's age
will surely do that.)
- "Where are you?"
- That won't work.
That's right.
- "What do you like?"
- He should be in his 30s or 40s.
- That's right.
- Seriously.
- All right. Get ready.
- This is ridiculous.
The three members
can disturb them together.
Can they begin right away?
- All right.
- Look after Young Ji.
Let's begin. Move the camera.
Be ruthless.
- Let's go.
- Don't go easy on them.
Protect Young Ji.
All right. One,
two,
- three.
- Where is it?
- Three,
- two,
- I can't see.
one.
- What?
- Is this allowed?
Young Ji and Se Chan succeeded.
(Team Sae Ho got 2 points!)
- Okay.
- Is this allowed? He covered...
- So Min.
- He covered my glasses.
More people succeeded
because you lifted up the camera.
Really?
The shot covers a wider area
than I expected.
Is covering the face allowed?
- Two people can disturb.
- Two disturbers.
- Two.
- Camera.
- Let's begin.
- Let's go.
- The shot covers a wide area.
- Go.
- No. Get in there.
- Go. Which way is it facing?
- Okay.
- One,
- Here.
- two,
- three.
- It's here.
- Three, two,
- one.
- It's here.
- There we go.
- Okay.
Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, and Jae Suk.
Three members succeeded.
- Three.
- We won.
I covered his face.
- Here comes the second question.
- Okay.
You are having a get-together
for the first time in a while,
so you need to pick
the person you will sit with.
Sit down for the nagging Jae Suk...
and stand up
for the harassing Jong Kook.
(Sit down
for the nagging Jae Suk...)
(versus Stand up
for the harassing Jong Kook)
It's hard.
Sit down for nagging?
Sit down for the nagging Jae Suk.
Stand up
for the harassing Jong Kook.
Follow your heart.
- One,
- This is hard.
- two,
three.
(6 people choose Jong Kook
and 2 people choose Jae Suk.)
Three.
(Sighing)
Haha sat down.
Jong Kook, Haha sat down.
- Sit down.
- I didn't sit down.
- You sat down.
- I almost sat down.
- Sit down.
- You sat down.
Three people chose Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- The rest chose Jong Kook.
- Really?
- Do we play by ourselves?
Yes. The three of you are a team.
- I see.
- Really?
Let's hear about your reasons.
When I am drinking happily,
- I don't want to be harassed.
- I don't do it continuously.
It will kill the joy of drinking.
You say that
because you haven't experienced...
- Jae Suk's nagging.
- That's right.
- Have you experienced it?
- Does his nagging tire you out?
It doesn't tire me out,
but he calls me.
He calls me on Sunday morning.
"Where are you?"
"I am at home in Mapo-gu."
"Hey! You are a young man!"
"You shouldn't be holed up
in the house."
"You should go out
and enjoy the beautiful weather."
- "Go out and run."
- I don't do that.
- "Okay."
I hurriedly put on my clothes
and go outside.
"Where are you?"
"Jae Suk, I came outside." "Hey!"
"Don't you care about fine dust?
Go back inside!"
It's the way we bicker.
- That's right.
- Thus,
we talk on the phone
3 or 4 times a day.
- We do that.
- Morning...
- Morning, afternoon, and evening.
Then there are special occasions.
- Do you ever fail to pick up?
- What?
Do you ever fail to pick up?
He keeps his phone on silent mode.
- Have you ever screened his calls?
- Silent mode.
- Yes.
- Yes or no.
- I bet he does it.
- Sit down for "yes..."
- And stand up for "no."
Have I ever screened his calls?
Yes.
(He has screened his calls.)
Of course. Yes.
- I have done it once.
- Of course. It's understandable.
- It was because of work.
- Of course.
- I was in the middle of a shoot.
Haha, why did you choose Jae Suk?
- I don't say much to you.
- To be honest,
I could pick neither.
But you do the same.
- Do I nag?
- That's right.
- You nag the younger ones.
- Me?
- You nag so much.
- You nag the younger ones.
You don't know what
they are sick and tired of, right?
They are sick and tired of you
talking about life.
You little punks!
- He talks about his struggles.
- I did it for your sake.
- Seriously.
He doesn't stop.
- He talks about money too.
- That's right.
It sounds like
he wants to borrow money.
- Me?
- Don't talk about money.
He talks about money.
Hey, don't make things up.
Don't make things up.
I don't like it
when Haha pretends to be cool.
He pretends to be nice.
- "Yaman!"
- He pretends to be hip.
- He always does that.
Seriously.
"You can call me anytime."
I am sorry.
- The six members will go first.
- Okay.
- Two...
- Here.
- Which way is it facing?
- Check the camera.
- Three.
- Where is it?
- Three,
- Let go.
two, one.
Only So Min succeeded.
(Only So Min succeeded.)
- Okay.
- Why...
You were too close to the camera.
- You blocked everyone.
- You did well.
- Hey.
I had to be in the angle.
You should have backed off.
- You blocked everyone.
- Hey,
- you did well.
- Only So Min succeeded.
- Only Haha succeeded.
- Okay.
I should have covered his face.
We did well.
- It's the last round.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Choose the one you would rather be
stranded on an island with.
Suk Jin, the burden
who complains a lot.
So Min, the distraction
who has no survival skills.
(Stand up for So Min
versus Sit down for Suk Jin)
- All right.
- Which option is sitting down?
Sit down if you would rather be
with Suk Jin.
Stand up if you would rather be
with So Min.
I would be a better choice.
This is...
This is very simple.
Just see them as individuals.
Don't think about the gender.
You will be stranded
on an island with this person.
Sit down for Suk Jin.
One, two, three.
(Will it be Suk Jin
who complains a lot?)
- Okay.
- Three.
- So Min would be better.
- Go to an island with him.
So Min would be better.
- Let's hear about your reasons.
- Why?
It would be nice to be with me.
- I would talk all night long.
- I chose him for that reason.
- Me too.
- I would talk all night long.
It would be like listening
to a radio show.
But he would laze around...
- while you work.
- He would complain a lot.
- He wouldn't do anything.
I know Suk Jin too well.
Toward the end...
"Suk Jin, we should do this."
"No, I am just going to die."
"I am just going to die."
(Suk Jin will be too bothered
to live.)
- "You do it."
- "Go on without me."
"This is it for me."
- It would be so sad to bury you.
- "I can't do this any longer."
"It would be so sad to bury you."
I would cut down wood
and make a raft.
I would do my best to escape.
You would use that raft
for his dead body.
(He would pass away on the raft.)
- Now comes...
- Okay.
- the last round.
- Let's win.
We can win.
Suk Jin and Sae Ho will be
the disturbers.
Okay. Here we go.
(Team So Min will go.)
So Min, don't move to the front.
Let's begin.
- Study the camera.
- Take it slow.
We don't need to move now.
- Don't move to the front.
- We have three seconds.
Are there only two disturbers?
(Screaming)
Suk Jin.
(This old man can't do much.)
What's up with him?
One,
- two...
- Suk Jin.
Go in front of Jong Kook.
- Two,
- Go in front of Jong Kook.
three.
- Three, two, one.
- I was disturbing the wrong person.
You got three points.
(Team So Min got 3 points.)
Two,
- one.
- I was disturbing the wrong person.
(The old man used his power
on his teammate.)
- Are you okay?
- You got three points.
Hey, who hurt Sae Ho?
Sae Ho is hurt.
- What's wrong?
- It's okay.
- Are you okay?
- What's wrong?
(One-eyed)
I think a thumb entered
my eye socket.
- It was an optical illusion.
- Hey.
An optical illusion?
It wasn't an optical illusion.
Can you see it?
- All right.
- I can see it.
Who will be the three disturbers
from this team?
- All right.
- Three men should go.
- Okay.
- Haha too?
Three men? Isn't that too cowardly?
That's too cowardly.
Not at all.
The camera will move now.
- Not yet.
- Form a scrum.
Form a scrum.
(Each member gets taken out.)
What's this?
Let me go in front of the camera.
- One,
- What is this?
(The cheerleaders steal the shot.)
two...
(Even the cameramen watch.)
(They are held tight.)
Let me go in front of the camera.
Three.
What are you doing?
Let me go in front of the camera.
Three.
(He gets pushed out the door.)
What are you doing?
(They couldn't even go
near the camera.)
The end.
- You got zero points.
- Nice.
We did it.
- We did it.
- Okay.
- It's over.
- He went out?
- The three in the front...
What was that?
- He went out.
- My gosh.
You can't push me out like that.
- What?
- He pressed...
- my temple like this.
- Are we allowed to do this?
- What did I press?
- Where did you go during the shoot?
Someone... My goodness.
- You went out.
- What's wrong with you?
This is too harsh.
- My gosh.
- How many people?
It was zero.
It's done.
The three of you
should go to a deserted island now.
Go to a deserted island.
The three of you
to a deserted island.
My goodness.
So each of you got your points.
- Okay.
- I didn't earn many points.
I will announce your points
when you get to New York.
- Okay.
- Let's go to New York.
I'll see you in New York.
- Let's go to New York!
- New York
(They get on the flight
to New York like that.)
(And they arrive at New York.)
(The financial center
of the world, New York)
(And the most fierce place of all)
(Wall Street in New York)
(A large sum of money is
going around in a second.)
(And there's a stock trading firm
for Koreans on the outskirts.)
(Running Stock
Investment Club is here.)
Let's go.
- This is nice.
- It's a perfect day to invest.
- My gosh.
- My goodness.
- Hey, Michael.
- Gosh.
(Are there Americans?)
- Hi.
- Michael, long time no see.
(This place looks
like a global financial center.)
(Welcome to RM
Investment and Securities)
- The company.
- Thank you for the chart.
(The traders seem familiar
as if we saw them on "Surprise.")
- But it's 136.
- No.
- Sell all.
- All right.
(RM Investment and Securities
only deals with petty stocks.)
(But things are fierce
just like Wall Street.)
I'm sure it will soar next month.
(Welcome to Wall Street.)
(And RM Investment
and Securities is here.)
(Long time no see.)
- Do you even know who he is?
- Are you from Hong Kong?
- Yes.
- Hong Kong.
- Hi.
- It's been a while, Michael.
What is going on?
- Hey, James.
- Hi.
(Chris, Sam)
- This is so...
- Long time no see.
- What am I supposed to do?
- Hey.
Hi.
My name is Sae Ho.
(Laughing)
Are you up for the challenge?
John?
- Are you up for the challenge?
- Yes.
- Yes? Okay.
- Good.
- All right.
(He's fluent in English.)
My name is Young Ji.
- Young Ji? I see.
- Young Ji. Yes.
- I don't like you.
- All right. Investors.
- Yes.
Has it begun?
- What do we do?
- Now you will start...
investment with 500 dollars.
- We get 500 dollars?
- Okay. It's finally beginning.
You will trade in dollars.
- Okay.
- It sounds great.
- This is...
- My heart is beating high.
(The US...)
(stock market...)
(is opening!)
(One said...)
(that investment resembles life.)
What is a foreigner doing here?
(English is the one
that catches up with them.)
(If you're prepared
for the US stock market,)
(make good use of the information.)
- Enemy.
- Enamel?
(If you don't have information,)
(follow your guts.)
(Money goes its way
by fair means or foul.)
(And time never stops.)
(If there's a record low,)
(there must be a record high.)
(Once the bell rings,)
(the rise and fall
of your life change.)
(Who will be the one
who laughs in the last?)
(The year 2022.)
(The stock prices of this year.)
(Please open it.)
(The Genius Investors:
Go to New York 2)