Gosh, that was hard.
This is crazy. Jae Suk.
We're back to square one.
Let me catch my breath.
Let's warm up here.
- What, Jae Suk...
- Come on and warm up.
Okay.
- Gosh, this is...
- I need to stretch my back.
Stretch your back.
Where is it? It's not here.
So Min, you should try this.
(They exercise on the street.)
This feels really good, So Min.
People would think...
"What are they doing
as soon as they got off the bus?"
We took the bus for a long time.
One, two.
- First...
- Do we eat?
Are we eating?
- But...
- Jae Suk, are we going?
Considering many things...
What about that place? The cafe.
- Or gimbap.
- There's a gimbap place.
Why don't we have some gimbap?
- So Min.
- Yes?
We're far behind the other team.
Something simple.
- What do you want?
- Ramyeon with gimbap.
- If...
- What time is it now?
- If we do that...
- I knew he'd fall for that.
- He loves ramyeon.
- It's 12 p.m. now.
Let's leave at 12:30 p.m.
What about this?
Why don't we eat after one step?
- Because... For now...
- Just in case.
There are many reasons.
It's lunchtime now.
So we won't be able to shoot...
- in a crowded restaurant.
- We can't do that.
I don't think
the gimbap place is crowded.
We can just eat ramyeon and gimbap.
You must be really hungry.
- All right then.
- Ramyeon and gimbap?
- Yes, ramyeon and gimbap.
- Let's decide by majority.
- Are we going or eating?
- Okay.
Raise your hand
if you want to eat gimbap.
- Raise my hand?
- Raise your hand for gimbap.
Since we are far behind
the other team,
we need to catch up.
We should go before we eat?
- Yes. We need to move once.
- Move once.
I'll ask then. Gimbap.
One, two, and three.
(So Min wants to eat gimbap.)
All right then.
- We should go.
- We should go first.
(Jae Suk and Se Chan
want to move first.)
- So Min.
- Don't be upset.
- It's not like that.
- So Min, we have no choice.
If you were going to do this,
you could've just told me so.
- Why did you give...
- It's not like that.
such a long speech?
- Come here, So Min.
- Let's take a bus.
Or let's take a taxi.
Jae Suk, what do we do?
Taxi.
Since your number is 1,
you can take a taxi for 1 minute.
- We can't do that.
- We will pick a number again.
- Let's do that.
- We should pick it again.
- So Min, you pick it.
- We have 8 and 5.
- Which is better?
- Eight is better.
Once you pick a number,
you have to follow it.
- Okay.
- Of course.
- Hang on.
- Pick eight.
- You're not supposed to look.
- I just checked the numbers.
- To see if there are three numbers.
- Don't look.
You can't see the numbers.
I was going to break it here.
Let go. You want to break this?
(He tries to manipulate it.)
We can't do that. I'll pick again.
- All right.
- I'll go with this.
- Did you pick one?
- Yes.
- It's eight.
- Eight.
(It's 8!)
- It's eight.
- Okay.
You can take a taxi.
- Let's take a taxi.
- A taxi or a bus?
- Let's take a taxi for 8 minutes.
- Take a taxi for 8 minutes.
- For eight minutes.
- Okay. Cross the street first.
Jae Suk, should we go downtown?
(Team Jae Suk chooses
to take a taxi for 8 minutes.)
(Jae Suk crosses the road
at the crosswalk.)
(The younger tortoises follow him.)
Should we cross the street?
Jae Suk, do you know where to go?
- He doesn't know.
- What are you doing?
- It's not here.
- Jae Suk, this is a parking lot.
Hey, this is...
You're wasting time.
- So Min.
- I thought this was a crosswalk.
But this is a parking lot.
So Min, come here.
- This is for bikes.
- We should go this way.
- This is where bikes are parked.
- There's no way out.
There's no crosswalk.
- You're wasting time.
- My goodness.
This is a parking lot.
A parking lot for two-wheeled vehicles.
This is crazy.
- We should hurry and go. Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
(They go back to where they were
feeling embarrassed.)
- So Min.
- Jae Suk, we should go this way.
- Let's go over there.
- We should cross the road.
So Min, this is a mess.
Jae Suk, don't lead the way.
No matter what show I do,
my team always struggles.
- I think you have the energy.
- This is strange.
My gosh. This is hilarious.
- Anyway...
- Hang on.
- We should take a taxi there.
- Yes.
Jae Suk, we should go this way.
Then we will take
the Olympic Expressway.
If we go this way...
- Is it Yeongdeungpo?
- It goes downtown.
- Is it Mok-dong this way?
- Then...
(They keep looking around,
but it looks confusing.)
- I think it's faster this way.
- We should go this way,
but we can't take a taxi here.
On this road.
(Blank)
Hey, we can't do this today.
Jae Suk, let's just eat
something delicious.
Let's just eat.
Let's just goof around.
- Jae Suk, we can go shopping.
- My goodness.
- Let's do that.
- This is driving me crazy.
I have the production crew's card.
- Let's have fun.
- Let's have some jeongol.
- Right.
The other team picked
the bowling mission,
so you should do
the karaoke mission.
I said there would be two missions.
Did they pick that?
They picked the bowling one,
so you have the karaoke one.
Let's take it easy.
- Let's just go.
- Let's cross the road first.
If we go to a karaoke room...
- Let's go to a coin karaoke.
- Okay. Let's do that.
(Dangsan Station, Myeong-dong)
This goes to Soon Chun Hyang
University Hospital.
- Okay. That sounds nice.
- Hello.
(Team Suk Jin took a bus
at Myeong-dong after eating.)
- Hello.
- Should we sit in the back?
- Yes.
We barely managed to stay in Seoul.
- We're lucky.
- It was so close.
If we went one more stop,
we would've ended up in Pangyo.
It could've been Pangyo.
- Gosh, fortunately...
- We could've...
taken a nap after lunch.
- Fortunately...
- If we went to Pangyo,
we would've given up.
We should give up there.
"We lose."
Fortunately, we got off at
Soon Chun Hyang University Hospital.
- We can take a taxi there.
- We should take a taxi then.
(They are getting closer
to Apgujeong.)
- We're here.
- Thank you.
- Gosh.
- Oh, dear.
Let's take a taxi now.
Our number is four, so...
It's three.
Right. It's 3, so we can take
a taxi only for 3 minutes.
- Let's switch it to nine.
- Okay.
Three is
the smallest number we have.
What if we pick three again?
(They've got nothing to lose,
so they pick a number again.)
(Team Suk Jin's numbers:
3, 7, 8, 9)
Okay.
- Let's go right away.
- I'll open it right away.
(They need to pick a big number.)
One, two, and three.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Eight.
- Eight minutes.
- Eight is really good.
- Okay. It's eight.
- You pick 8 a lot.
- It's good that I wrote 8.
I keep getting number eight.
- He picks it a lot.
- Eight.
Should we take a taxi?
Why don't we go to a cafe and
have the eighth drink on the menu?
- Sounds good.
- Let's go to a cafe and try...
- the eighth drink.
- Let's do that.
- We have enough time.
- Let's go.
- We will have the eighth drink.
- Is that all right?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Go.
I saw one over here.
There's also Blue Bottle Coffee.
There it is.
The eighth drink on the menu.
Okay.
There's something. It's the menu.
- It's a latte.
- The eighth drink.
It's a latte.
- Clove latte.
One of us should go in
and buy the coffee.
- I'll go buy it.
- Okay.
I want soybean milk for my latte.
- I'll try.
- Okay.
(Ji Hyo receives the orders
and goes in the cafe alone.)
- Hello.
- Where do I place my order?
Ji Hyo is not used to new stuff like this.
Why did we send her?
I once asked Ji Hyo
if she had been to a drive-through.
- And she said, "A dry booth?"
- Right.
- A dry booth.
Could you please
write down your name here?
(Ji Hyo is having a lonely battle
with the new culture.)
When your name is called...
(After a long struggle,
she manages to pay.)
It's here.
(Number 27, Song)
Things are going so well for us.
- Let's see where they are now.
- Okay.
I'm a little anxious though.
Right. Just a little.
We can't be all relaxed.
Didn't they catch up with us?
I don't think so. Probably.
- Seok Sam.
- Hey.
- Where are you?
- Us?
- Yes.
- We're at Apgujeong Rodeo Station.
We have some time to spare,
so we want to grab a bite.
It's so obvious that he's lying.
- What?
- Did you play bowling or not?
Bowling?
- Yes.
- Bowling...
We just finished bowling.
Suk Jin, you're looking
for a bowling alley now, right?
No, we just finished it.
I think I just hit the nail
right on the head.
(Seok Sam is caught
that they didn't play bowling yet.)
Where are you, Jae Suk?
- We are...
- Yes.
We're in Sinsa-dong now.
- My gosh.
- Sinsa-dong, Eunpyeong-gu?
That's enough.
Aren't you staying
in Sinsa-dong for too long?
You said you were
in Sinsa-dong before.
Didn't you say you were
in Sinsa-dong an hour ago?
(Laughing)
- Okay.
- We have to cross the street.
- Let's go.
Let's hurry and go.
Hurry, So Min.
Hurry and come, So Min.
Hey, hurry.
(They suddenly start running after
finding out about Team Suk Jin.)
- So Min.
- Yes.
Jae Suk, let's take a taxi here.
Hurry.
- It's coming.
- It's done.
It's here.
- Hello.
- Thank you, sir.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Sir.
For eight minutes...
We need to go to Apgujeong.
- I'm sorry, but...
- You should set the alarm.
Should we set the alarm?
All right. Good.
- All right.
- Thank you, sir.
- Start.
- We didn't ask for this in advance.
But we're communicating well.
- You should press start.
- Press start first.
(They met a driver who understands
the mission very well.)
- It's done.
- Thank you, sir.
Thank you so much, sir.
The driver is quick-witted.
Right. He set the alarm right away.
You're like one of our members.
- Thank you.
(The 8-minute drive
begins to get to Apgujeong.)
How much can we go in eight minutes?
We can't get there, can we?
Sir, how far
can we go in eight minutes?
We should go to Yeouido.
- Yeouido?
- We should go to Yeouido.
(It's Yeouido again.)
Yeouido? Isn't that
where we started the race?
Yeouido...
Do you need to go somewhere else?
- No.
- No, it's all right.
That's the only way.
- So are we going to Yeouido?
- My gosh.
- Are we starting again there?
- I think so.
- It's reset.
- Right. Yeouido is...
- where we started the race.
- Really?
- The bus stop?
- Yes.
My gosh. We left at 10 a.m.
After two and a half hours,
we're back here.
This is ridiculous.
It's like a dream.
It feels like I'm in a dream.
Right. It takes about 30 minutes
to get to Gangnam from here.
Eight minutes isn't enough.
- We need to go to Apgujeong.
- How can you get to Apgujeong...
in eight minutes?
The woman sitting next you
told us to do that.
Oh, dumplings.
So Min, you must be hungry.
- We should eat something.
- I think I am.
There's a Starbucks.
So Min, you're hungry.
Jae Suk, there's a pork restaurant.
We're in Mullae-dong now.
- Near the Yeongdeungpo Market.
- My gosh.
Sushi.
(She's hungry, so all she can see
are restaurant signs.)
There's a market.
So Min, there's a sundae alley.
Se Chan.
- We should eat when we get off.
- Right.
I don't think I should be
here with you.
So Min, we will eat something
when we get off.
- So Min seems really hungry.
- Right.
What's the name of this show?
- We are...
- It's Running Man.
- It's SBS.
- It's Running Man on SBS...
which begins at 6:30 p.m.
on Sunday night.
(Running Man is on at 6:20 p.m.
starting from January 1.)
It's not 6:30 p.m. yet.
- It's not changed yet.
- Not yet?
That's why you run around places
all the time.
- Yes.
- Right.
Have you watched Running Man before?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
When I watch TV shows like
"The Fishermen and the City,"
I see people cook
with what they catch.
I went to the alley that was on
"A Walk Around the Neighborhood."
I can tell
you don't watch Running Man.
(I can tell
you don't watch Running Man.)
If you watch
"A Walk Around the Neighborhood..."
I can tell
what kind of TV shows you prefer.
- But still...
- You don't like Running Man.
I watch it with my children.
I guess you watch our show
with your children or family.
Sure. It features Kim Jong Kook.
- That's the show, right?
- Yes.
I watch the reruns
from time to time.
(In the taxi driven
by the hidden viewer...)
There it is. That's it, So Min.
There it is, So Min.
This is where
we walked with Suk Jin.
- We are starting all over again.
- My goodness.
We have 30 seconds left.
Gosh, how is it...
I'm worried.
What if we go to Gimpo again?
- Please go straight, sir.
- Okay.
We can't go there
if we hit the red light.
My goodness.
- We won't go to Gimpo again, right?
- Count down.
Ten.
Nine. Eight.
- Seven. Six.
- Six.
- Five. Four.
- Five. Four. Three.
This is it.
- Time's up.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
We're really here.
- My gosh.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
Stay healthy.
- Have a nice day.
- Yes. Stay healthy.
Bye.
So Min. This is it.
This is horrible.
We took the bus here
and went this way.
- What if we go to Gimpo again?
- What's happening?
You see the taxi over there.
That's where we walked.
We did that right over there.
(They danced "Hype Boy" here.)
We danced "Hype Boy" here.
(They danced around in excitement
without knowing what would happen.)
I think I will fall asleep before...
- watching the World Cup match.
- I don't think you can watch it.
- You won't be able to come.
- I think...
I'll fall asleep before watching it.
I just can't do this.
- They all have coffee here.
- Do you want some coffee?
- What's our number now?
- It's eight.
Jae Suk, what's our number? Eight?
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, and eight.
- Jae Suk, it's cafe mocha.
- It's cafe mocha.
- Cafe mocha is not bad.
- What are our numbers?
- One and five.
Number five is a latte.
Number five sounds good.
Shall we give it a try?
If we pick number five,
we should stick to the number.
(If we pick number 5,
we should stick to the number.)
What's number eight?
- Cafe mocha.
- It's mocha.
Chocolate and coffee.
- Let's pick number five.
- I don't like mocha.
- Let's try picking number five.
- Can we pick a number?
- Mocha is too thick.
I have the numbers.
- We need number 5.
- What we want now is...
- number 5.
- Number 5, latte.
Latte sounds better.
That's a basic menu.
- What's the number?
- Mocha.
My gosh.
(They pick number 8 again
for cafe mocha.)
Let's have cafe mocha.
- But mocha is too thick.
- Let's have some...
- We have no choice.
- We can't help it.
We will have three cups
of iced cafe mocha.
- Hello.
- Iced Americano?
- No, iced cafe mocha.
- Cafe mocha.
- Ma'am.
- Yes.
I'd like my mocha very weak.
- Me too.
- Make it weak?
- Not so sweet.
- Make all three weak.
Okay.
So Min, you seem to be
in a good mood today.
Why am I feeling good?
You look really...
- Do you think this is a date?
- No. I think So Min wants...
to show off her new hair.
- But...
- "I got my hair dyed."
I think
So Min likes stuff like this.
Walking around the streets
and taking busses.
I like taking busses.
It feels like I'm on a trip.
I wish it wasn't a game.
She's hanging out
with a close friend...
- and a guy she's interested in.
- Right.
And it's so romantic that there's
a coffee truck in the downtown area.
- It's romantic.
- It's so pretty.
She doesn't care about the missions.
- So Min.
- We need to do the mission.
We should go to Apgujeong.
- Really?
- Don't forget about the mission.
- I'm just feeling good.
- You think this is a date.
This is the financial district
in Yeouido.
And it's lunchtime now.
That's why
there are a lot of people.
They're here to have some coffee.
I'd like to ask them something.
When will the stock market recover?
What?
Should I buy stocks now or not?
- Buy or not?
- Should we buy stocks now?
Should I buy stocks now or not?
(Asking the question
in the Yeouido financial district)
Buy stocks or not?
(Should I buy stocks now or not?)
- Buy.
- Buy stocks now?
(Buy?)
- They say that in Yeouido.
- Buy now?
I got the news
in the Yeouido financial district.
- Buy?
- We should buy? Okay.
Buy now?
- It's not my money, so whatever.
- Buy mine.
- "It's not my money, so whatever?"
- "Buy mine?"
"Buy my stocks?"
- What...
- He wants us to buy his stocks.
"It's not my money, so whatever?"
This looks good.
- Have a nice day.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Let me ask you again. Buy?
- Buy.
- Buy?
- Are you sure?
Because it's not your money?
(They give bold advice
because it's not about their money.)
- Buy or not?
- "Buy it with your own money."
There's a bakery down here.
Why don't we go to the bakery
and buy the eighth bread?
Right. The eighth one on the menu.
What do you think?
- I'll be back soon.
- Wait here.
- The eighth bread on the menu.
- The eighth one.
(The lucky number: 8)
Hello.
- Is this the menu?
- It's over here.
- Is this it?
- Yes.
Is this the menu?
- It's ice cream.
- Is it just ice cream? I see.
Where are cookies?
(Obviously, they are trying
to pull some trick.)
All right. We'd like to buy this.
(The letters on the menu are small,
and he can't find cookies.)
Suk Jin, they're selling this.
But we have to pick
something on the menu.
Let's figure out a way to buy this.
Hey, they're behind us.
- They are watching.
- They are watching us now.
- Okay.
- All right.
(They give up quickly
after hesitating a little.)
I think there's
another store in here.
Should we go in there?
- You want something sweet, right?
- Yes.
Why do they want to eat bread?
We have to go bowling now.
- Right.
- We're running late.
We should hurry and go bowling.
(While Team Suk Jin is
looking for some dessert...)
- That's...
- That's Bus 841.
That goes to Mok-dong though.
It's five.
(The lucky number: 5)
You will take a bus
that includes five...
- and get off at the fifth station.
- Okay.
- It's coming now.
- It's Bus 503.
All right. The race begins now.
Are you sure this is the beginning?
- What if we come back again?
- This is the beginning.
Are you sure?
If we win this race,
it will be really thrilling.
- He's right.
- It will be so thrilling.
You never know.
(They plan to turn the tables slowly,
but diligently.)
Right. The bus needs to stop.
Right. It was weird before.
That bus never stopped.
It's not a bus until it stops.
I used to eat a lot here
with Suk Jin when I was a newbie.
Where?
I went to all those restaurants
with Suk Jin.
Really?
You have a lot of memories
with Suk Jin.
Yes,
because I didn't have many friends.
There's a good
buckwheat noodle restaurant.
- I want buckwheat noodles.
- That's a famous restaurant.
- The buckwheat noodle restaurant.
- I like buckwheat noodles.
It's right around the corner.
We're getting off at the next stop.
Do you want to go there?
- Yes.
- Good.
The next stop is
Yeouido Sibeom Apartment.
Sibeom Apartment.
Do we get off here?
(Finally, it's the fifth bus stop.)
Let's get off here.
- Let's get off here.
- Scan your card.
I did.
I can't get away from Yeouido today.
The pit of Yeouido.
Exactly. I can't get away from here.
- The pit of Yeouido.
- I can't stay away from it today.
We're still in Yeouido
after five stops?
Last time,
we got to Gimpo after one stop.
- Jae Suk. We got here from there.
- But last time,
we got to Gimpo after a single stop.
Look, So Min.
We came from there.
We're still in Yeouido
after five stops?
Jae Suk. Will it end before today?
What? We're almost there.
- I can't believe we're here.
- This place is really good.
- Is it famous?
- Their udon is really good too.
Fishcake meal is number one.
- Fishcake meal.
- Fishcake meal is number one.
Udon is fifth.
Gimbap is eighth. It's not bad.
I want the buckwheat noodle combo.
This place is known
for its buckwheat noodles.
- Look at the number.
- Let me draw it.
But the buckwheat noodles...
It's a buckwheat noodle restaurant.
We have to have
buckwheat noodles here.
This is crazy.
You don't need to draw it.
- Right?
- It's five right now.
We could try
the spicy buckwheat noodles.
It's the fifth if you go horizontal.
- One, two, three, four, five.
- Can we do that?
Wait. One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
It's gimbap again.
- Gimbap is always the eighth.
- Yes.
Whether I go horizontal or vertical.
The owner was smart with the menu.
- He was smart.
- It's a bingo.
Whichever we go, it's always gimbap.
Whether we go horizontal or vertical,
it's always gimbap.
- It's hilarious.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Thank you.
- Hello.
- Let's sit here.
- It's been a long time.
We'll get
three spicy buckwheat noodles.
- Three spicy buckwheat noodles?
- Yes.
- Spicy?
- Yes, spicy.
- Okay.
- That's all we can get.
She was curious
why we were getting spicy noodles.
Because that's not
the signature menu.
You have to try
the buckwheat noodles here.
How many buckwheat noodles?
- Three.
- Three buckwheat noodles?
Spicy.
It's not spicy.
- That wasn't spicy.
- I wanted it.
- It's here.
- Thank you.
Can you smell it?
It smells so nice.
I'm glad we had a good number.
Yes.
(The sweet and sour spicy
buckwheat noodles...)
(make up for their sufferings.)
It's good.
- It's good.
- It's really good.
Ma'am. This place was always good.
I can cheer up now.
Let's win.
- Let's do it.
There must be a bakery.
- There's one for sure.
- There must be one.
- Egg and bacon. Here.
- Good.
- Here.
- Let's get some bread.
Please.
- There is bread.
- Finally we found the bakery.
Let's get bread.
The eighth bread.
- Eighth bread horizontally.
- They'll decide it.
What's the first bread?
- We can only get the eighth bread.
- What?
- Eighth?
Is this number one?
This is number one?
No. This should be number one.
- Isn't this number one?
- This should be number one.
Here.
- Is this number one?
- Yes.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- Done.
- This one.
- This is not bad.
- I like this bread.
- Good.
- It's nice.
Let's go. This is awesome.
- Finally, we got what we wanted.
- One.
Two.
(One chocolate bread is enough
to make them happy.)
Let's draw eight.
- Let's draw eight.
- And get a cab.
I think we should exit
at the National Cemetry.
(They plan to take Olympic Blvd
and get near Banpo.)
- We need to draw eight.
- If you draw one...
(They must draw 8
to make their plan possible.)
- Can I draw it?
- Yes.
Can you feel it?
No.
(Their fate is up to Se Chan.)
I'll draw it and show you.
(Will it be the lucky number 8?)
One, two, three.
- It's eight.
- Okay.
One, two, three.
- It's eight.
- Okay.
(8 gives Team Tortoise a chance
to turn the tables.)
This is awesome.
- We're safe.
- It's one of the three.
- Finally we get to leave Yeouido.
- Finally we can.
How long has it been?
Three? Four hours?
We bought it.
- I can't believe it.
- We somehow bought it.
What did you buy? A cheap one?
- We got the good one.
- Oh, that bread.
- Do you know this place?
- We bought this.
Let's go bowling.
We have to hurry up.
We don't have much time.
We'll run out of time.
Hi.
- Hello.
- Do you like Running Man?
- Yes.
- So much.
- Thank you. Did you run to see us?
- Yes.
Who's your favorite on Running Man?
- I guess it's not us.
- It's not us.
They can't answer me.
- It's here.
- Bye, kids.
- Bye.
- Bye. Take care.
(When it was getting awkward,
the cab arrives.)
- Hello.
- Hello. Sorry.
We're going to Apgujeong-dong.
Can you take Olympic Blvd?
We have a mission.
We can only take the cab
for eight minutes.
- So can you take the exit nearby?
- Drop us on the way.
(Laughing)
I'm sorry.
- Sir.
- Then I have to check the time.
- You're on our side. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- It'll be 54 minutes.
- Fifty four.
Sir. Imagine you're in this with us.
Please help us.
Does this happen often?
- No.
- I see.
- He's firm.
- It never happens.
- Never?
- It never happened before?
- Never.
- Then you should join us today.
- Okay.
- Please hold my hand.
- We can do it.
Let's drive together
for eight minutes.
Did you have lunch?
- No, not yet.
- Not yet?
I'm going to take a nap
and watch soccer.
You need to watch soccer.
We had buckwheat noodles.
You should try the other restaurant.
Oh, that restaurant.
That place is good too.
We all made a good reaction.
- We're cheered up after the meal.
- Yes.
And we're kind
to all kinds of topics.
- Yes.
I can accept everything
with generosity.
(The buckwheat even makes them
nice people.)
We're finally leaving Yeouido
after five hours.
- We're finally leaving Yeouido.
- Yes.
I can't believe we went to Gimpo.
It's unbelievable.
As long as there's no traffic jam,
we can get to National Cemetery.
- See? There's no traffic.
- There's no traffic at all.
- It's empty.
- We could get far at this rate.
- Of course.
- We could win.
It's time now.
- Look at the time. It's over.
- It's perfect.
It's perfect.
Nice timing.
- Thank you.
- It's awesome.
- Thank you. Take care.
Have a good day.
- Hey.
- We got very far.
We got very far.
- At this rate...
- We got very far.
That was successful.
Let's walk...
towards Banpo.
(Destination)
We're walking to Banpo?
We have no choice.
There's no bus stop.
It's going to be a long walk.
We have eight.
We should take the bus
and go eight stops.
Okay. Let's go eight stops.
And if we take a cab there,
we'll arrive in eight minutes.
- And we'll go to the karaoke.
- We go.
Sing, take a break,
go and we succeed.
Okay.
We have to walk a lot, don't we?
- To where?
- To Express Bus Terminal.
We don't have to go
all the way there.
There's a bus stop
across the street.
I feel like I'm going around
different neighborhoods today.
(They walk and walk again.)
I'm going around
different neighborhoods.
(But it never ends.)
We're walking so much.
It's painful that we can't leave
the neighborhood right away.
(Suddenly singing "Rope of Love")
- Why tie with a rope?
- It's her song.
(The original singer's
concert banner)
- Oh, so love can't leave?
- That's right.
- Tie your love with a rope.
- It's Kim Yong Im's song.
(While singing about tying...)
- So Min.
- Hey.
- Prostate.
That should be tied too.
- It happened to say prostate.
- Prostate.
Tie the prostate with a rope?
Why did it say prostate
when we were singing the song?
Gosh, today is...
- It's really tough.
- It's tough.
It's so tough.
(Tie with rope)
(So Min must've liked the song.)
- She's...
- She has the excitement.
- Yes.
How does the original dance go?
- How does it go?
- You turn around.
(Terrible dancers are
teaching each other.)
- Tie with a rope
(The bad dancer is reacting
to the song.)
(The street troupe is going crazy.)
It sounds like
it's tying the prostate.
My goodness.
Why did the prostate suddenly appear?
Let's go.
Oh, I know this place.
I know this place too.
There's a creek, right?
Look.
- It's that place.
- He's wearing...
only the sleeveless shirt
for his girlfriend.
- That's so cool.
- You're so cool.
So cool.
- Jae Suk.
- My gosh.
This won't do.
I should take off my shirt.
- I should take off my shirt.
- Now...
- He's so cool.
- So Min.
- Now...
- That's cool.
How cool is that?
He's so cool.
He doesn't care
about what others think.
I know.
He's wearing sleeveless.
- It's December.
- Not to make her hair wet.
- It's almost December.
- To protect her hair.
Now...
He's that romantic
to do that in December?
That's amazing.
I'm so touched.
- Why?
- He's so cool.
Is that possible?
Se Chan.
Do you want me to take my shirt off?
- Isn't it amazing?
- What are you wearing inside?
Gosh.
He was wearing sleeveless.
- That's so cool.
- He put his shirt over her head.
He wrapped her hair perfectly.
- Like a baby.
- He wrapped her hair perfectly.
- Is that love?
- That is love.
Even when we were passing by,
- he didn't react at all.
- No.
- He wasn't distracted.
He was so focused.
Jae Suk, is there a bus stop
if we go this way?
No. Go straight.
(They finally arrived at Banpo!)
Right.
It's over there.
- It's over there, right?
- Yes.
We're finally here.
The 148 bus is coming.
I think it goes to Apgujeong.
- The 148 bus.
- Right.
It says "Apgujeong Station."
We should take this.
We should take 148 bus.
It says "Apgujeong Station."
Then we don't have
to change the number.
No, we don't.
It's 412. Bus 4318 will go there too.
Let me check.
- It's 148.
- As far as I remember...
Eight.
- One, two, three.
- The one on the top.
Four, five, six, seven, eight.
It stops at Apgujeong.
It goes to Apgujeong.
148 bus is perfect.
We're going to the bank.
We should just go to a karaoke then.
- We're tortoises then.
- What?
- We're tortoises.
- It has come. The 3rd one.
- The 148 bus has come.
Hello. For three people, please.
For three people, please.
We can play bowling,
but how can we win?
Those people who come...
- to enjoy bowling...
- Yes.
would be quite good.
- They'll be better than us.
- Right?
Where should we go?
- It's over there.
The bowling alley is over there.
We finally found it.
It wasn't easy to come here.
It's nice.
- It's nice. Hello.
- Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
They look like pros. Hello.
We should play it quickly and go.
- Yes. We don't have time.
- We don't have time.
We should win quickly.
What should we do? We're in trouble.
What should we do?
Should we play eight rounds?
- If you keep number eight,
- Yes.
you should win eight rounds...
against other people.
If it's eight rounds...
Does 1 round
consist of 10 frames and more?
- Yes. That's one round.
- We don't have enough time.
Then you should pick number three.
We should pick number three.
We can win.
Yes. We can do it.
We must pick number three.
- Good.
- He's picking the number.
- Pick one.
- We need number three.
- Three. Please.
- Otherwise, it'll take too long.
(What number did Suk Jin draw?)
My number. Three.
- Three.
- We got it.
- What?
- Hey.
Wait. Is the difference three?
- Three.
- Is it three?
- So we should play 3 rounds.
- It's 3 rounds.
- Three rounds?
- It's actually long as well.
Let's play three rounds.
Three rounds? Should we call others?
You should find people to play with.
Gosh, this is...
Everyone looks like they'll be good.
I think they will be good.
I think
they're the only other group here.
- We can't. They're good.
- They're good?
- They're too good.
- They're so good.
- We can't do it.
- They're good.
- Are you a professional player?
- I'm a 12th grader.
- What?
- A 12th grader.
- You're a 12th grader?
Are you going to college
with bowling?
- No. It's just a hobby.
- And you're here, not at school.
- Is the class over?
- It's the final exam day.
Try throwing it.
This guy.
- Yes. Let's see how it throws it.
- But we're...
- Let's see what he's got.
- They must've heard we were coming.
Yes. The steps are...
- Okay. Pass.
- This guy...
Do you want to play a round with us?
If you have time.
Are you okay with that?
- Let's go together.
- Thank you.
This is doable.
Can we play
with two employees here too?
Do you want a 4-on-4?
- Okay. Just one more person.
- Yes.
- One person.
We need one more person
to play together.
- One?
- Yes.
Then I'll...
- Okay.
- I'll go then.
(They recruited an employee.)
(He's bringing his own gear.)
- What should I do?
- This is hard.
- Who are you?
- I work here.
- What's your average score?
I'm not bad.
I think you'll be really good.
No. I'm not good.
Let's do it quickly.
- It's okay if we do it quickly.
- Let's do it. We don't have time.
Let's go.
Should I play first?
- You got 15 minutes...
- They're wearing the same clothes.
- What's that?
- What?
I feel like you're professional.
Right.
Producer, I think we need this rule.
We all should play with the same ball,
not the custom one.
Right. I don't think it's right.
Suk Jin has custom balls too.
I have custom balls at home.
He even has his own balls.
I have six balls.
Let's talk about it.
Is he allowed to wear it?
- I have many wristbands too.
- He got 100 at home.
But still...
We'll let you do that.
Let's try first.
You will play in lane 15.
They will play in lane 17.
- Okay.
- Got it. I'll go first.
Good luck.
- You got this.
- Okay.
Here I go.
Jong Kook.
That's nice.
- That's good. Turn more.
- Turn.
- It's good. You can make a spare.
- You did well.
It had to go in the middle.
You did well.
Throw it as if it's the first ball.
(Haha tries to make a spare.)
- Hey. He was timid.
- No.
(The ball went sideways.)
- You can do it.
- In 1, 2, 3. We got this.
- We got this.
No matter what...
- You can play first.
- Okay.
(From Team Citizens,
a student plays first.)
Okay. This guy is so good.
He just threw it.
It was nice.
(He knocked over 9 pins.)
He just threw it.
(What is this?)
- What's this?
For how many years
have you played bowling?
It's not been long.
So how many years?
Since I was an 11th grader.
- Then it's a year. It's a lot.
- It's over a year then.
- So anyone of us can make a spare?
- Yes.
- I hope he does it.
- All right.
- Okay.
- He should do it.
Then I'll throw 1st
for the 2nd frame.
Okay.
It's like a dance.
- What? It's going in.
- He threw it weirdly.
- Okay.
I'm relieved.
- This is it.
- We caught up with them.
Well done. His steps were gentle.
He's good.
I'm not sure if I can make a spare.
I'll throw it for the second time.
- Just throw it to the center.
- Yes.
- To the center.
- You got this.
She was good.
- She threw it too hard.
- Not that way.
- Shew threw it too hard.
Oh, my gosh.
- Throw it gently.
- It's like the first ball.
- It's the first ball, Suk Jin.
- I'm going crazy.
- Throw it gently.
- Do it gently. That was too hard.
- I'm in trouble. It'll be fine.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Gosh.
Where are you going?
It's...
- We can't do it.
- This is us.
- Let it slide just this once.
- We're this bad.
So you don't have to go hard.
I know.
We're this bad.
It has to be a close game.
This is not fun.
He's left-handed.
- No, it won't work.
- It won't work.
What's going on?
(What's this?)
- This is not working. It's no fun.
- It's impossible.
You should say, "You got this."
He's a pro.
- Is this a prank?
- What are we doing?
- Did you see the spin?
- Are you mocking us?
- Do it.
- He's a professional.
Haha, you throw the ball first.
This is too much.
Our skills have
to be on the same level.
- Do it slowly and gently.
- He's so good.
- There you go. Well done.
- That's nice.
- It's okay.
- It's good.
(He knocked over 6 pins.)
Good luck.
Why is he throwing it first?
- We're taking turns.
I see. But you're a pro.
What's your name?
Hong Jin Ho.
- Jin Ho?
- Jin Ho? How about you?
I'm Cho Han Jin.
- Hwan Jin?
- And your name is?
- It's Han Jin.
- Han Jin.
- I'm Park Kyung Shin.
- Kyung Shin.
- Yes.
It says Park Kyung Shin
won the game.
- It went out.
- Last year...
Hey.
- Why?
- "King of Bowling Park Kyung Shin."
- He won.
(King of Bowling Park Kyung Shin)
Are you kidding me?
What's that?
He's the King of Bowling.
Be the referee.
Do you want to play with amateurs?
That's too much.
I was just asked to play.
- You're the King of Bowling.
- What are you doing with kids?
Last time,
you played at our bowling alley too.
Really?
- That's good.
- For "Infinite Challenge..."
with Kim Soo Hyun.
- I see.
- Yes.
I taught him.
Actor Kim Soo Hyun?
- Soo Hyun?
- You taught him?
Yes.
- This won't do.
- Get out quickly.
- This is a scam.
- This is too much.
It's the first game anyway.
- We'll just give up.
- Yes.
- Let's give up the first game.
(It's student Han Jin's turn.)
Look at him. His steps are so...
- That was nice.
- You did well.
- I like you.
- You're good.
- Han Jin.
- You're one of us.
- I like you.
Han Jin has a good personality.
Throw it comfortably.
Don't throw it hard.
- There you go.
- That was nice.
- It went to that side.
- It's okay.
You can make a spare.
This is the first ball. We never know.
We got 21 points.
The posture is...
- And they got 34 points.
- This is...
Kyung Shin.
- You came to play with kids.
- Sir.
The King of Bowling.
So he's standing diagonally
like that.
I think it will go in the gutter.
- Get out.
- Come on.
- What's this?
(What's this?)
- What are you doing with newbies?
Why did a professional player come?
Then I'll throw the ball
with the other hand next time.
Okay.
- Yes.
- With your right hand?
- Your right hand?
- Yes.
- Are you right-handed?
- No. I'm left-handed.
- Are you left-handed?
- Yes.
I really can't throw it
with my right hand.
- You can't? Okay.
- No.
(How good is the King of Bowling
with his right hand?)
- What?
He threw it in a weird way.
What are you doing?
(He said he wasn't good
with his right hand.)
I threw it with my right hand.
You didn't even put your thumb...
- into the hole.
- You're right.
He didn't even put his thumb in the hole.
Did you see that?
It's a trend these days.
- They don't use their thumb?
- Just the middle and ring fingers.
- It's a trend these days?
- Yes.
- Then I should follow it.
Do people actually throw it
like this?
Yes. It's called thumbless bowling.
It's a popular style these days.
- So the ball spins like that.
- Yes.
- Hey.
- Gosh.
(Strike)
- Nice.
- You go in.
This is...
Hey.
Don't do this.
You should think about us too.
Han Jin,
go with the thumbless style.
- Han Jin, you can do it.
- One, two.
- Good.
- It went in.
- Nice.
(Even the bad one got better now.)
Hey.
- Get it together.
- What's wrong?
What is it?
Why are you so good suddenly?
This is not like you.
They're good.
Team Citizens won round one.
- But...
- It's so...
he's not a regular citizen.
- He's...
- He's not a regular citizen.
- He's so good.
- He's the King of Bowling.
He's a professional.
You can't do this.
It says
"King of Bowling" over there.
"King of Bowling Park Kyung Shin."
Let's go to a karaoke
near Apgujeong Station.
(Team Jae Suk is going
to Apgujeong by the 148 bus.)
It's near exit four
of Apgujeong Station.
- Let me see.
- There's one.
Here.
The dentist
I go to is right in front of here.
I should get my braces.
Jae Suk. Hold on.
- Why? Do you want to go there?
- We're going down anyway.
- I'll get my braces real quick.
- He wants to stop by the dentist.
Your braces?
Do you still wear braces?
When will you be done?
- Are you wearing braces?
- Let me see your teeth.
Your teeth are...
Are you still wearing braces?
Gosh.
- I'm...
- Are you wearing braces?
I was done.
That's the most unexpected news
I heard in the past year.
- You're still wearing them?
- I was done.
But because I didn't
wear braces often,
- my teeth started to go back.
- I see.
That's why I'm doing it again.
When will you be done?
It'll be over soon.
I should just go to the dentist twice.
So is this the final look?
Is it the final look?
It's not perfect,
but I'm very satisfied.
(It's surprisingly
the best they can do.)
This stop is Kookmin Bank,
Apgujeong Station.
It's here.
- We should get off.
- We're there.
Thank you.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
(After going to Gimpo,
they came a long way to get to Apgujeong.)
- We're in Apgujeong.
- So...
we should go there, right?
It's behind the building.
- It's your neighborhood.
- Yes.
It's my neighborhood.
- Jae Suk...
- Do you walk around here?
- I walk around here.
- He's walking around...
with a mask and a cap.
I walk around
pretty much everywhere here.
I think people pretend
not to recognize him.
- It's obviously him.
- They don't recognize me.
- No. It's so obvious.
- Not with a mask.
- Jae Suk and I...
- Look.
Do you know which body part
they recognize?
Our mouths.
Because it's my neighborhood,
if I have a shoot in this area,
Kyung Eun's acquaintances
text her immediately.
Really?
- Yes. Many of them are here.
- So your wife knows immediately.
(It's a real-time report system.)
- I'm sorry.
- Hanam Pig House. It's over there.
- Okay.
- Oh, my gosh. It's Yoo Jae Suk.
Yes. Hello.
(As soon as he said it,
the report system is activated.)
- It's here.
This is the karaoke.
- Yes. Dudeurim.
Okay.
We suddenly came to a karaoke,
leaving Yeoui Island.
- It's so...
- We went everywhere.
From Gimpo to here...
It sounds like the title of a trot song.
"From Gimpo To Apgujeong."
- Hello.
Well...
- We should drink the 8th one.
- The 8th one.
- It's 1, 2, 3, 4...
- No.
It's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
- It's beer.
How about in the other way?
One, two, three, four...
- five, six, seven...
- I want to drink this one.
It's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
It's the same this way. One, two...
(He keeps counting numbers
in front of the fridge.)
Seven, eight. This is it.
I want to have this one.
Do you want this one? Then...
It's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
- It works.
- It's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
This works, right? It makes sense.
- We count numbers like this.
- Yes.
- It's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
It works.
(It works!)
(They got coffee like that.)
We should get 80 points.
Oh, my. Now, it feels better.
- What did you get? Coffee?
- Coffee.
Is it latte?
- Yes.
- We had no choice.
I should sing "Emergency Room"
after a long time.
- Your current number is eight.
- Okay.
- Your score should be 80 to 89.
- From 80 to 89.
- We pass then, right?
- From 80 to 89?
- Hey.
- It's hot.
Let's sing something
we'll get 80 to 89 points with.
There is definitely
a song like that.
What's this? "Cleo?"
("Good Time" by Cleo)
Is this the right song?
(She starts singing
without hesitation.)
(She likes going to a karaoke alone
and this is her go-to karaoke song.)
(Why is she doing this?)
So Min...
It's the last song she sings
when she's with her crush.
- The ending song.
"With you."
Look at the lyrics.
(I want to stay with you tonight)
(I need permission from my parents)
(But tonight
I want to spend with you)
(She doesn't give up singing
even after singing off tune.)
Let's go.
- Go.
- One, two, three.
(Co-ed band Frog and Protruded Brothers
is formed.)
(Sub vocalist and dancer)
(Main vocalist and center)
(I want to spend)
(The main vocalist's forte
is singing off tune.)
- It's over.
(What are the scores?)
- Let's get 80. Look at this.
- What?
- Well...
- I was really bad.
- No. Jae Suk.
No. You should not have a hint
of excitement in your voice.
I should've sung it even worse.
- Jae Suk, do you want me to do it?
- You do it.
It was close.
(Team Jae Suk seems to understand
the scoring system after a song.)
You should sing worse than this.
- What are you going to sing?
- I should sing a song...
that I will get just 80 points.
He's a professional.
You can't do this.
It says
"King of Bowling" over there.
- It says "King of Bowling,"
- We can't play against him.
"Park Kyung Shin."
- Then...
- Yes.
- Instead of the total score,
- if you play a 1-on-1 game...
- Yes.
- and get higher scores than him...
- We should win?
just three times.
- Okay.
- Just three times.
Playing a 1-on-1 game?
- So we should win 3 out of 10.
- Okay.
- I got it.
- It sounds good. We can do it.
- Let's begin now.
- Yes.
- Get higher scores 3 times. Yes.
- Out of 10.
You don't have to bend too much.
- I can just drop the ball.
- Yes. Just do it gently.
Like you're shaking hands.
- Shaking hands?
- Yes.
- Like I'm shaking hands?
- To spin the ball.
- We got this. It's the last time.
- It's the last time. Let's go.
I'll do it.
It's a practice.
(He practices throwing a ball
as he learned.)
That's nice.
That's how you do it.
That's right.
- This is it.
- Yes.
- This is much easier.
- And you won't get hurt either.
- I won't get hurt either.
- That's why many people do this.
- Is there a professional...
thumbless bowler?
- There are a lot.
- There are a lot?
Even professional players
do it like that with two hands.
- Two hands?
- Yes.
- Jong Kook should go first.
- I'll go first.
- If you win three times, it's over.
- Yes.
We should decide
on the order wisely.
- You got this.
- Here I go.
(Jong Kook starts first.)
Okay.
Let's go.
- My gosh.
- That's nice.
- That's nice. It's done.
- That's nice. It went to it.
Darn it.
- That's nice. It's done.
- That's nice. It went to it.
Darn it.
- It's always the middle one.
- It's so annoying.
It's always the middle one
that is left.
- That one pin.
- I'm going crazy. I'm frustrated.
Let's just win three times.
- I'll make it go in.
- Han Jin.
You're going to do it first, right?
- He'll go first.
- No. I'll go first.
Aren't you trying too hard to win?
No, I'm not.
- Let's make a spare first.
- Yes.
Let's go with the spare.
(Jong Kook tries to make a spare.)
- It's good.
- It's sliding.
- Go in.
- It slid.
- What's wrong?
That's nine.
What's wrong with me?
(Jong Kook, 9)
- That was close.
- I'm usually good at it.
Park Kyung Shin.
(He uses the other hand again.)
(He already knocked over 9 pins.)
That one is hard.
Look at that.
- It's easy. The one at the end.
- You can't do this.
That's the easiest one.
That was nine, so we could be tied.
Right. We could be tied.
Come on.
- Okay.
- We're tied.
- But it doesn't matter.
- A tie or a loss...
- It's nothing.
If we're tied 3 times,
let's make it 1 win.
- It's related to number three.
- Right. That sounds good.
If we're tied three times.
Okay. We'll approve it.
If you're tied three times,
- it's one win.
- Thank you.
(They agreed to consider
3 ties as 1 win.)
(Seok Sam who learned a new skill
is up.)
You should do it.
You must do it.
(Will he be able to do it well
just like when he practiced?)
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin. What's...
What's wrong with you?
I learned it,
but I didn't master it.
(Seok Sam is bad
at the actual game.)
- Choose a lighter one.
- This is light.
How should I...
(New ones)
Don't rush it.
Just...
Okay.
- No way.
- I still managed to get nine.
Is this how you do it?
Get nine and you'll tie.
You've got this.
I've gotten the hang of it now.
(Suk Jin versus Jin Ho)
All right. Just get nine for now.
Okay!
As long as he misses the spare...
I'll win this frame
if he only gets one.
- Please.
(Suk Jin versus Jin Ho)
- Okay. I tied.
- Good.
(0 wins, 2 draws)
We tied twice.
Two draws.
- I'm up next.
- You?
(It's the Little One's turn.)
I tied.
- Still...
- Han Jin's next, right?
Yes.
I'm going to beat him.
- Good!
- Darn it.
- Nice. That was good.
- It's fine.
Why won't it swerve
toward the middle?
You might be able to land this.
It's doable.
There's always an option to tie.
Three draws are worth a win.
(Haha's 2nd attempt)
He's got it.
- It looks good.
- Looking good!
You got it.
Darn it!
(Haha gets 9 in total.)
- It's all right. You did well.
- You got nine.
Nine...
- Han Jin's beatable.
- Han Jin!
It'll be hard
for him to get more than nine.
Send it right down the middle...
- Look at that.
- It's off course.
- Okay, good.
(He gets 6 on his 1st roll.)
- You might win this frame.
- You'll win.
You've got this.
- We'll get a win.
- Don't try too hard.
Han Jin, you have a wedgie.
- What?
- Sorry about that.
I couldn't help myself.
(He plays dirty against a teenager.)
- Oh, no.
- Okay!
Okay!
- We're good.
- Okay!
(Haha wins.)
That's one. We won one frame.
- Good job.
- Thanks, Han Jin.
You have 1 win and 2 draws.
We have 1 win and 2 draws.
We can't afford to lose anymore.
They've suddenly gotten better.
Nicely done.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
Here I go.
We can't afford to lose anymore.
Okay, looking good.
- It's always so close.
- Not again.
- This time...
- I'll earn a spare.
- This...
- We only need one win,
and you're almost there.
I'll get it done.
Just roll it like you don't care.
There. We're good.
- This will work.
- You'll get this.
Nicely done.
(He earns a spare.)
Good shot, nice shot.
- Nice.
- Okay!
I couldn't get it to spin earlier.
- This is who we must beat.
- The clock is still ticking.
We're good as long
as we win this frame.
Winning this frame
will get us to three wins.
(Team Suk Jin
is close to completing the mission.)
(Jong Kook versus Jin Ho)
- What?
- Please don't let it be a strike.
(Strike!)
Nice!
- They tied.
- It's a tie.
- Who's next?
- Okay.
- Unbelievable.
- Did you have to score a strike?
- If we had won...
- Why you...
You'll grow up
to be a fine young man.
After what it took to score a spare.
- You did well.
- It's all right though.
(Seok Sam's up next.)
He has lost his touch.
He knocked down a lot though.
It's not so bad.
(Seok Sam's ball
keeps finding the gutter.)
You know, I've gotten used to...
- I see.
- not putting in my thumb.
Hold it with the thumb, then.
Like shaking hands.
- I think you got it.
- Wait.
- Please.
- It won't hit.
That's seven in total.
- You've got this.
- Suk Jin.
This isn't the time for training.
It's your time to prove yourself.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Should I switch grips?
Yes, go back to your original grip.
You're supposed to prove yourself,
not train and learn.
- Don't you get that?
- All right.
(Meanwhile, Team Jae Suk
needs an eighty-something score.)
("Jintobaegi" by Lee Chan Won)
Let's get a score in the 80s.
He's been correcting his teeth.
Se Chan has been
correcting his teeth.
(Let's party.)
Here we go.
Don't sing it too well.
(Jintobaegi)
(He's in the zone.)
(He sings passionately...)
(despite saying
that they shouldn't party.)
(What's their score?)
- Cut the song.
- Okay.
- All right.
- What's the score?
- It's too high.
- What?
(Mr. Straight Teeth
gets a score of 95.)
- Let's not party.
- Don't sing too passionately.
You got a score of 95.
Let's not party, okay?
Don't sing too passionately.
Unbelievable.
- Jae Suk.
- You're liking this way too much.
I'm having a blast.
- She's the best.
- I'm having the best time.
This is the best.
Seeing So Min having fun
is cracking me up.
What are you going to sing?
"At Andong Station."
- Good.
- That's a good one.
I'll sing in a way
that'll get me 80 points.
("At Andong Station" by Jin Sung)
(A hat performance)
(Toot-toot)
Let's do this.
(The Yoo San Seul train
leaves the station.)
Let's go to Andong Station!
My singing is way too good.
(He forgets about the score
and sings while in the zone.)
(His nasal voice comes through.)
Jae Suk,
you're singing it way too well.
Okay, let's do this.
- Hurry.
- We're running out of time.
We only have two frames left.
You need at least win once
or tie once.
(They must win or draw one frame
to get 3 wins in total.)
One win or draw. That's doable.
All right.
- In 1, 2...
- Get a strike, Jong Kook.
(Team Suk Jin's best bowler
Jong Kook)
- Looking good!
- Please go off course.
Get a strike, Jong Kook.
- Looking good!
- Please go off course.
- Oh, no.
- It's going down the center.
- No!
- It's a split!
- That's the trickiest.
- What a relief.
It was dead in the center.
- Isn't that the trickiest?
- It requires a spin.
- The pins...
- It'll be hard to get a spare.
- This is impossible.
- The pins will have to ricochet.
That's right.
Like billiards.
A pin must take out other pins.
This is a tough shot.
- Nothing's easy in life.
- I had such a good chance.
This is a tough shot,
so just go for the pins on one side.
Will it go down the center?
- No.
- It shouldn't.
- He got 2, so that's 8 in total.
- We only need 9.
(He managed to take out
2 more pins.)
(If the citizens get more than 9,
they'll move on to the next frame.)
Getting nine isn't that easy.
- Scoring nine points isn't easy.
- What's his name again?
- Jin Ho.
- Jin Ho?
Jin Ho!
(Jong Kook versus Jin Ho)
- Head for the gutter!
- Don't!
- Oh, no.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook versus Jin Ho)
- Nice.
- This isn't so bad.
- It's not bad.
- He'll go for the three.
- Aim for the three pins.
- This isn't so bad.
Send it down the middle.
You must knock down
those three pins.
You can't afford to miss.
(Team Suk Jin will win
if he can't take out more than 3.)
- Get only one.
- We could tie.
Jin Ho, just get the one.
This is the time to gamble.
Aim for the three.
- We can tie to win.
- I bet he's nervous right now.
- Just get one pin.
- I bet you're nervous.
Aren't you nervous?
- The gutter couldn't seem wider.
- I bet you are.
- Oh, no.
It's heading for the gutter.
- I bet you're nervous.
- The gutter couldn't seem wider.
- I bet you are.
- Oh, no.
(Jong Kook versus Jin Ho)
(Will he only get 2?)
It's heading the other way.
(He manages to strike 3.)
(Darn it!)
- Are you kidding me?
- Seriously?
I can't believe he made the shot!
(That was so close.)
I was too excited just now.
- I...
- Darn it.
- You.
- Hey.
You scored a strike earlier
when we could've tied and now...
I doubt you're normally this good.
(They must play the final frame.)
I'm going back
to the grip I'm used to.
I must prove myself,
not spend this time to train.
- Twelve pounds.
- Stick to your usual grip.
The twelve-pound ball is mine.
(If they fail,
they must begin all over again.)
Okay!
Let's do this.
Good.
(He holds the ball
with his usual grip...)
(and bowls.)
- This...
- You've gotten used to it.
- Darn it.
(Team Suk Jin knows
that they might lose.)
It was a close game.
- Just one.
- Let me win this frame.
- I could score a spare.
- Of course.
I could score a spare.
Of course.
Do it comfortably.
Push it straight. That's right.
- That's right.
- Great.
(Will it go well?)
Do it comfortably.
Push it straight. That's right.
- That's right.
- Great.
(He scored a spare.)
Great!
(Ji Seok Sam proved himself!)
(They got 3 wins!)
I told you. It went in.
You succeeded in getting 3 wins!
Okay!
The final one went in.
What a relief. Thank you.
Great job.
Thank you.
- Great work.
- You taught me briefly but well.
- Good work.
It was difficult.
Thank you so much.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
You completed the mission.
The other team already picked
their mission.
- Really?
- So...
- there's only one mission left.
- Okay.
If we succeed this one and move,
we win, right?
- Yes.
- What will it be?
(What mission is left?)
What is it?
(Team Suk Jin read their mission.)
We can do that before the ending,
right?
- That's right.
- Yes.
Let's go to Apgujeong first.
- Let's go.
It arrives in seven minutes.
I don't think we'll make it.
(Team Jae Suk and Team Suk Jin)
(Team Jae Suk is still trying
to get a high score.)
I sang it really well.
This is crazy.
(He got 100 points.)
You did too well.
How could I get 100?
Why did you sing like that?
I did it too well.
I also think I sang so well.
Jae Suk.
Jin Sung will get shocked
when he watches this.
You got 100 points.
I thought this was "Mr. Trot."
- You sang so well.
- I thought it was a recording.
Why do I sing so well?
How did you improve so much?
This is crazy.
I love the song.
- It was great.
- Your condition is good.
This won't do.
I sing too well today.
I never thought
I'd score 100 points.
We shouldn't go for exciting songs.
We should go with simple ones.
You should sing a simple song.
Let's sing "Emergency Room."
- "Emergency Room."
- "Emergency Room?"
Let's sing "Emergency Room."
It's 80 points.
But this one scores well too.
You can sing it.
Don't get immersed in it.
("Emergency Room" by Izi)
This reminds you of the old days.
- Get rid of your emotion.
- Get rid of it.
(Sighing)
I'm regretting
(He's already soulful.)
We won't be able to leave this room.
What do we do? We sing so well.
(He said he'll sing
in a simple way.)
Because of my stubbornness
(No, I didn't mean it, you fool)
You meant it!
I don't know!
(Overly emotional couple)
Then why did you do that?
(Please don't leave me)
(Please leave me)
(Dumping him)
Leave.
So Min. What's the score?
- You are a singer!
- Look at that.
- Hey.
- We can't do this.
We have to get rid of all emotions.
I should sing a song
that I can't sing.
This is crazy. Is there no solution?
Sing a song
that's really difficult to sing.
Sing a pop song.
We might get the score then.
I think it'll work
if you sing a pop song.
- Let's sing a song we don't know.
- A song we don't know.
- Let's just press any number.
- Okay.
- Press any number.
Give me any two numbers.
- Two, four.
- Three.
- Five.
- Seven.
- I don't know this song.
- I don't know it too.
We're supposed to sing a song
that we don't know.
Why are you trying to find
a song you know?
- Let's do it one more time.
- One more time.
- Four, five.
- Seven.
- So Min.
- One.
("I Like Love" by Hong Jin Young)
- "I Like Love?"
- I don't know this song.
We're not choosing a song we know.
We're just pressing any number.
We still need to know a little.
Let's sing something fun.
Something fun?
- What do you mean? Fun?
- What about "Barefoot Youth?"
- "Barefoot Youth." It's fun.
- Okay.
Then I want the wires gone.
I want to dance.
There are a lot of wires.
Then how will you sing?
I want to dance,
but there are a lot of wires.
- We should sing "Barefoot Youth."
- It's so fun...
to be in a karaoke.
I'll raise one more key.
- Let's start.
- Okay.
("Barefoot Youth" by BUCK)
Great.
Let's go.
(They're still energetic.)
One, two.
(Let's go.)
(Making a fuss)
(Hoo! Ha!)
(Panting)
Let's go.
(They keep singing
even though they're tired.)
(His face is getting red.)
(He's still excited.)
Goodness.
Hold on.
This is crazy.
- Let's do something short.
- Yes. Something short.
Let's harmonize.
Why is this...
I think it's because we danced here.
Should we not dance?
Does it evaluate the dance too?
Are we doing it wrong?
- Does it sense that?
- Then...
I think I get it.
We shouldn't get hyped up.
- We shouldn't.
- Let's not get hyped up.
- Also...
- We shouldn't get so excited.
we should sing something difficult.
- We should sing "Resignation."
- What?
- By Big Mama?
- Yes.
(Full of high notes)
Good.
(It's a difficult song to sing.)
(They tortured the ears
of the listeners.)
(Jae Suk and So Min
sings a duet song.)
(Disharmony)
(They put in high notes
to show off too.)
(She got excited and sings "Tears.")
Good. It's in the 80s.
- What?
- This is driving me crazy.
Why?
Why were you showing off?
Why can I sing high notes today?
This is crazy.
Good.
(They scored 100 again.)
- This is crazy.
- Jae Suk.
How could they give this 100 points?
- But this...
- What do we do?
Let's do this one.
"The Train to South?"
"Does Anyone Love?"
- "Sorrow."
- "Chalangchalang."
- Chalangchalang.
- It's 2689.
At this rate, we might have to ask
for 20 minutes of extra time.
- We need more time.
- We've...
been singing here
for more than 30 minutes.
We need to ask for more minutes.
- Let's sing "Chalangchalang."
- What's wrong with us?
Why do you seem glad?
It's so fun.
(Shaking)
Let's go.
It's "Chalangchalang."
(Lost in the music)
(Twitching)
Everybody chalangchalang.
(Chalangchalang)
You shouldn't sing too well.
(Like whiskey in a glass)
(Whiskey Ballantine's)
(Psychorus is back.)
(The cheesy girl is showing
some steps.)
Let's go.
(His gum chorus is energetic.)
Are they on a date?
(It's a mess.)
(A couple on a date,
each doing what they want)
Guys.
Are you...
(It was a great song.)
(They finally got a score
in the 80s.)
It's done.
- We got it.
- We can leave!
You guys...
You two...
I thought you two were in love.
This is great.
It's against us too.
- It's against us.
- Mission completed.
- Let's go.
- Let's leave.
- It's too hot.
- My throat hurts.
- Mine too.
I sang too much.
I think it became dark.
- Hurry up.
- We have no time.
- Let's take a taxi.
- It's this way.
There's a taxi.
- It's coming.
- Thank you.
We're going.
- Hello.
We're going to Dosan Park.
We'll just go for five minutes.
- Okay.
- I'll start the time.
The driver is driving well.
Yes.
The traffic is helping us.
- The traffic lights are on time.
- Good.
We are passing through
all the traffic lights. How nice.
- Really?
- Okay.
That team hasn't done one mission.
I hope we win.
- If we lose, I will feel dejected.
- But...
(Team Jae Suk has a chance
since they have done both missions.)
- We are nearly there.
- Yes. We are doing quite well.
Look at the timer. The time is up.
- It was perfect.
- Thank you.
The song ended too.
(They arrive at the destination
on the 5-minute mark.)
Sir, thank you.
- Thank you. Please stay healthy.
- Thank you.
Where are we? Hold on.
- We have 100m left to go.
- We turn left here.
We turn left down the road.
- Where is the location?
- Where is the location? Here?
We are here.
- They aren't here yet.
(They begin to run.)
Where is it?
Isn't the other team here yet?
(If they arrive first,
Team Jae Suk will win!)
- Wait for me.
- So Min.
Are they here?
- Hurry up.
- Gosh.
- We won.
- Hurry up.
(Team Suk Jin arrived
at the ending location first!)
What's wrong with you guys?
- This is the worst.
- Why didn't you pick up the phone?
(They thought Team Suk Jin had
a remaining mission.)
What could it be?
(Team Suk Jin chose
the second mission.)
(They picked
the second mission ball.)
What is it?
"Take a photo with an acquaintance
you called recently."
One of you will pull up
the call history.
- Your lucky number is three.
- Yes.
Meet up with the third person
and take a photo with him or her.
- For me, it's Se Chan.
- What?
Please show us.
- Is it really Se Chan?
- You are the fourth person.
(Se Chan is Haha's 3rd person
in the call history.)
It's Se Chan.
- Doesn't it give us an advantage?
- It does.
We just need to take the photo
before the end, right?
- That's right.
- Take a photo with Se Chan.
- I can sneak up...
and take a photo with him.
We need to take it...
- right before they enter the place.
- That's right.
(They set out to take the photo
right before the end.)
They haven't arrived yet.
- They haven't arrived yet.
- We need to catch them.
- Where are they?
- We need to complete the mission.
- We need to catch them.
- Did they arrive?
Jong Kook,
let's come up with a plan.
(Hurried)
- Haha, turn on the camera.
- What?
Here. Would you take the photo?
- I will do it.
- When I put my arm around him,
- take a photo from afar.
- I will do it.
- It doesn't need to be a selfie.
- It just needs to show the faces.
- Let's do it when he enters.
Let's do it when he passes
the entrance.
This is nerve-racking.
- Very nerve-racking.
- I know.
- It's understandable.
- It isn't nerve-racking, Haha.
It needs to be a shot
of two people, right?
It just needs to show the faces.
It's a success
if we take the photo, right?
I just hope
they don't enter as a group...
and block Se Chan's face.
Team Jae Suk will win
if they enter...
before you complete the mission.
(Team Jae Suk will win
if all members enter first!)
- Haha and Se Chan's faces.
- Isn't the other team here yet?
- So Min.
- You guys took so long.
Are they here?
- Hurry up.
- Gosh.
- We won.
- Hurry up.
What's wrong with you guys?
- This is the worst.
- Why didn't you pick up the phone?
- You guys took so long.
- Haha.
- What's wrong with you guys?
- We went to Gimpo.
What?
(Haha is waiting at the entrance.)
- What's wrong with you guys?
- We went to Gimpo.
- What?
- We went all the way to Gimpo.
(Team Suk Jin must take the photo
before So Min enters.)
- You guys took so long.
- Haha.
- What's wrong with you guys?
- We went to Gimpo.
- What?
- We went all the way to Gimpo.
(Jong Kook has the camera ready.)
- Then...
- You called me many times.
(The result of the mission
will decide the winning team!)
- What's wrong with you guys?
- We went to Gimpo.
- What?
- We went all the way to Gimpo.
- Then...
- You called me many times.
(The second mission: Complete)
Then we went back to Yeouido.
My goodness.
- I took it. Here.
- Yes!
(So Min hasn't entered
the place yet.)
- It's a success.
- What?
When did you get here?
(They completed the mission
before Team Jae Suk entered.)
- You completed the mission.
- It's unmistakable.
Team Suk Jin succeeded in
completing the mission.
Since they arrived
at the ending location first,
- they won.
- It's unmistakable.
We completed the mission just now.
- Really?
- The second mission.
Had you entered faster,
you would have won.
What was the mission?
Taking a photo with Se Chan.
Really?
Had you entered faster,
you would have won.
Had So Min entered
with the other members,
- then you would have won.
- You would have won.
We hadn't completed the mission.
We lost
because you entered belatedly.
We shouldn't have sung
that last song.
We sang so many songs
at the karaoke.
- Your mission involved singing.
- We partied so hard.
- A score in the 80s.
- We spent nearly 50 minutes there.
- Did you go to Gimpo?
- We went all the way to Gimpo.
- Gimpo?
- We almost went to Pangyo.
- We got off one stop before Pangyo.
- That's right. Seriously.
Thank you for working hard...
- and coming all the way here.
- We really worked hard today.
- Seriously.
- The four-member team won.
- It was close.
- How disappointing.
- It's understandable.
- You entered without thinking,
- but we were really nervous.
- Yes. It was nerve-racking.
"What if we fail to take the photo?"
We wouldn't have gotten...
- another chance.
- Seriously.
To see if the lucky numbers
that led you here...
are truly lucky,
we will have the Lottery Game.
- This is important.
- This is important indeed.
The lottery box contains...
the lucky numbers
each team has used so far.
If you used five multiple times,
there will be
multiple number five balls.
So keep that in mind...
and put five numbers...
- on the lottery ticket.
- Five.
- The numbers we used today.
- Yes.
Regardless of the order,
you place 1st
if you get 5 numbers right.
You place 2nd
if you get 4 numbers right.
You place 3rd
if you get 3 numbers right.
There will be
appropriate prizes too.
- Okay.
- Understood.
- The numbers can overlap.
- Okay.
Since the 4-member team arrived 1st,
they will get
two lottery tickets each.
Since the 3-member team arrived 2nd,
they will get 1 lottery ticket each.
Okay.
- This is the real deal.
- We can still win a prize.
- This is the deciding game.
- Team Tortoise.
- Yes.
It's important
to choose the right numbers.
We are bound to get eight.
We should put down multiple eights.
What were
Team Suk Jin's lucky numbers?
They were one...
- Five and eight.
- Five.
- Seven was picked three times.
- Really?
Did we pick one?
- We didn't, right?
- We did. Once.
We did pick one.
We picked five once too.
All right. Let's go.
(They finished filling out
the lottery tickets.)
- No one will get all five numbers.
- I am sure of it.
- It's too thick.
- Who will draw the balls?
For the lottery drawing,
- we invited a specialist.
- Who is it?
Kang Chan Hee, please come on out.
He is the richest cameraman.
The master among cameramen.
- Yes.
- Please draw five balls.
- The ancestor among cameramen.
- Let's see the odds.
- Look.
- Two?
- What's the number?
- I want to place first.
- Eight.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Eight.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Eight.
- That's one.
- Okay. This is great.
- Okay.
- Eight.
(Ji Hyo went all in
on number eight.)
- Eight.
- That's one.
- Okay.
- We got eight.
- I hope we get eight again.
- Seriously.
Let's see another eight.
- Okay.
- We got eight.
- I hope we get eight again.
- Seriously.
Let's see another eight.
- Seven.
- I don't have it.
- Was there a seven?
- For goodness' sake.
- Seven.
- Was there a seven?
- For goodness' sake.
- I crossed out seven.
- No way.
No way.
(Only Suk Jin and Haha had 7.)
- I crossed out seven.
- I crossed it out.
- Seven.
- I don't have it.
- Was there a seven?
- For goodness' sake.
It was their lucky number.
It's too bad.
(Amidst the disappointment,
Chan Hee picks the next ball.)
- What?
- Nine.
- I don't have it.
- What?
- Nine.
- I don't have it.
We don't have nine.
I changed 9 to 8.
I have all the numbers.
- I just need three.
- Gosh, Chan Hee.
Please give me another eight.
- I need 8 or 3.
- I need 5 or 3.
- I need 8 or 3. Please 8, 3, or 5.
(The next ball)
- Eight.
I need 8, 3, or 5.
- This is great. Okay.
- Okay.
Now comes the last number.
- Eight.
- For goodness' sake.
- Now comes the last number.
- I should have kept 9.
- Why aren't we getting 3?
- Three.
- Three or five.
- We need 3 or 5.
- Seriously.
- Give us 5 or 3.
- I need 8, 5, or 1.
(What will be the last number?)
- Give us 5 or 3.
- I need 8, 5, or 1.
- Three.
- It has to be three.
- Eight.
- Eight?
- I knew it.
- I need 8, 5, or 1.
- Three.
- Eight. I got 3 numbers.
- Why didn't I add another 8?
Three eights.
- I never get lucky.
- I got three numbers right.
I never get lucky.
- Three.
- It has to be three.
- Eight.
- Eight?
- I knew it.
(Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, Suk Jin, Haha)
Are we done?
One of these should have been nine.
- Chan Hee, thank you.
- Thank you.
- I got three numbers right.
- Same here.
Had I kept 9,
I would have gotten 4 numbers.
Who got three numbers right?
- Here.
- I am glad you did it, So Min.
- Did anyone get 4 numbers right?
- I got 3 numbers right.
- Three.
- Three?
- Did anyone get four numbers right?
- No.
Can Se Chan and I combine
the numbers?
- I changed it at the last minute.
- Can we do that?
You wrote down the same numbers.
(They wrote down similar numbers.)
We will give you
the prize for third place.
You remember
what your lucky number was, right?
- Yes. Mine was 3.
- Mine was 9.
The prize suits the lucky number.
Please bring it in.
- What's the prize for first place?
- What is it?
Does it suit the lucky number?
- I guess it's different...
- What's this?
for each number.
Although the package is big,
- the actual prize might be shabby.
- I know.
- Shabby.
- You know,
you shouldn't have voiced
that thought.
- I could hear you from here.
- Suk Jin.
Mine was seven.
- Mine was 5.
- Mine was 7.
This is for nine.
- This is...
- Mine was seven.
- Thank you.
- What could it be?
- It was the lucky number race,
- Yes.
so we prepared a gift set
that is full of your lucky number.
- My goodness.
- They look strange.
- Are these So Min's?
- My goodness.
- Was that her lucky number?
(Miscellaneous items
with the lucky number)
- How pretty.
- So Min, they are nice.
- My goodness.
- Was that her lucky number?
My goodness.
- How pretty.
- So Min, they are nice.
(How pretty.)
- How nice.
- What are those?
I don't want them. What are those?
So Min, this is...
- How pretty.
- In my life...
So Min, they are very pretty.
In my life,
- I have never worn this color.
- Seriously.
- Jae Suk, we are the winners.
- Look at this.
- We are the winners.
- When I have a daughter,
- I will give this to her.
- We are the winners.
Had you gotten four numbers right,
you would have received a pork set.
- What?
- Had you gotten five numbers right,
- you would have received beef.
- Really?
- It's too bad.
Everyone looks unhappy.
- Everyone looks unhappy.
- It's too bad.
- Why did I take out nine?
- How nice.
(Dissatisfied)
Does anyone not like
his or her lucky number?
- Anyone?
- I am sorry,
but this isn't even my size.
- It won't fit me.
- It's too small.
Give it to Na Eun.
Na Eun should wear it.
- Na Eun?
- Yes.
Na Eun should wear better clothes.
He has a point.
- It's a nice top.
- Look at Jae Suk's reaction.
- It looks nice.
- Thus, today's race ended.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Give us the real prize now.
Hello.
(A week later, N Studio in Hanam)
Mr. Hairtail is here.
We aren't dressed
for a party, but a gig.
When else would I wear
such an outfit?
Good morning.
(The stars in fancy outfits enter.)
- Their outfits are no joke.
- It's a nice day.
- How nice.
- The perfect day for fish cake.
- Have a glass of wine each.
- Hey, we got fish cake.
Is it coke? Grape juice?
It doesn't go well with sandwiches.
Look at that tropical fish.
The tropical fish will eat.
- Tropical fish.
- Eat with the hairtail.
- Fish.
- Let's eat.
- They are fish.
- Fish.
- They are fish. He is a hairtail.
- I am a hairtail.
- He is a tropical fish.
- Is he a tropical fish?
He is a tropical fish.
(Eating fish feed)
- He is a tropical fish indeed.
- It's tasty.
Nemo's friend.
- We are having a party.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Are you going to work?
- What's up with the two of you?
- I am at work.
- He is going to sing at a wedding.
- Don't be ridiculous. What's this?
Running Man is work.
- I guess our outfits are weak.
- I know.
- Suk Jin said...
- I see why Suk Jin is annoyed.
- We will accept your criticism.
- Yes. We will accept it.
I didn't expect that reaction.
(Suk Jin picked a fight
and ended up looking bad.)
Are you the skinny Zhu Bajie?
- He looks like it.
- Seriously.
- That's right.
- The skinny Zhu Bajie.
- "Sun Wukong, what's wrong?"
- You are spot on.
- "Sun Wukong, what's going on?"
"Sun Wukong, what's wrong?"
- Zhu Bajie went on a diet.
- "Don't be like that."
He really looks like Zhu Bajie.
- "Sun Wukong, what's going on?"
- Zhu Bajie who lost weight.
He has Zhu Bajie's face.
He really does.
I see the resemblance.
- A piranha.
- Today, Ji Hyo dressed up.
Ji Hyo, you and I
look good together.
- You and I?
- Yes. Our outfits go well together.
Suk Jin, take off your coat.
- What?
- Take off your coat.
- Come on. Take it off.
- It's cold.
- Take it off.
- It's too cold.
- No.
- You stayed true to your character.
- I mean...
- You lead a fake life.
- Everything is fake.
- Fake.
You lead a fake life.
- Everything is fake.
- This is your outfit.
Everything is fake.
- He can't sit down in this outfit.
- What's that?
What's this? A barricade?
No.
- Did you barricade your body?
- It accentuates the look.
It's cold.
The hairtail is cold.
- The hairtail.
- Yes, I am a hairtail.
- The coat completes the look.
- Suk Jin...
was so cold that he said,
"Yes, I am a hairtail."
Gosh, Suk Jin!
- Fur went into her eyes.
- Fur went into my eyes.
It was fur from your coat.
Did you take it out?
It must have been hard
to find a suit like that.
I am wearing an ordinary outfit.
So Min, are you filming
a period drama?
- My outfit is a bit...
- Look at So Min's shoes.
So Min,
aren't your shoes too pointy?
- What?
- They are an eyesore.
You could kill a person
with those shoes.
- Aren't they pretty?
- Let me borrow those shoes later.
- Why?
- I need them to eat tteokbokki.
- She looks like...
- Skewered rice cake.
- a woman in "The General's Son."
- Yes.
- Namiko?
- You look like Namiko.
- Seriously.
- I can see the resemblance.
Zhu Bajie.
(Haha captivates attention.)
- Zhu Bajie.
- That's so funny.
- He really looks like Zhu Bajie.
- Zhu Bajie who lost weight.
- Anyone would agree...
- He really looks that way.
that he looks like...
- the skinny Zhu Bajie.
- Seriously.
Zhu Bajie who went on a diet.
For the stars who attended
the year-end party,
- we invited two more stars.
- Okay.
Let's welcome the first star.
Please come on out.
Who is it?
- You know, the temperature...
- The temperature is below zero.
- Okay.
- "Counting Stars."
"Counting Stars."
(Singer, BE'O)
(The hip-hop Zhu Bajie
begins to groove.)
BE'O.
(Counting stars,
Pearls in the night sky)
I love it.
Zhu Bajie.
Zhu Bajie, get out.
(He averts his eyes.)
(Pay attention to me.)
(Even the hairtail joins in
and acts like a hip-hop musician.)
Hey, get lost.
(He suddenly asks
for a diss battle.)
Why are you picking a fight?
(He is showing his professional side
since it's quite hard to perform.)
(Shoving his face)
- What are you doing?
- Get out.
(He shows off his fake fur coat.)
BE'O.
(Counting stars,
Pearls in the night sky)
Don't you hate the way...
- he acts like a hip-hop musician?
- I hate it.
(Absorbed)
Isn't this Louis Vuitton fake?
- It's fake.
- It's a fake Louis Vuitton.
It's a fake Louis Vuitton.
- It's fake.
- It's a fake Louis Vuitton.
- Say hello to Zhu Bajie.
Haha's outfit is fake.
- Fake?
- BE'O.
He is Zhu Bajie who lost weight.
He is Zhu Bajie who went on a diet.
- BE'O.
- Fake.
- He is a hairtail.
- Yes, I am a hairtail.
He is a tropical fish.
- He is a tropical fish.
- Yes.
- Party time.
She is Namiko.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- He is a trainer at a gym.
- Hello.
He is a trainer.
She is in the wholesale business.
- She is a madam.
- He is a guide.
- I am a guide.
(He exchanged greetings
with the celebrities at the party.)
- BE'O.
- Hello.
(The real hip-hop star, BE'O)
BE'O finally visited the show.
I love BE'O.
Would you please sing "Complex?"
- Okay.
- The power of elementary schoolers.
- Please sing "Complex."
- I like "Suddenly" too.
- Shall I sing it right away?
- Please sing "Complex" a bit later.
A bit later?
We need to listen to "Complex..."
- right away.
- The second star is waiting.
- The second star.
- It's cold.
- Okay.
- Let's wait.
I am so happy since BE'O is here.
The elementary schoolers
will go wild.
You seem awfully happy to be here.
Isn't that right?
- Don't be like that, Suk Jin.
- I am really happy.
- Right?
- You wanted to be here, right?
- Yes. Totally.
I wanted to see you too.
All right.
- It's nice to see you happy.
- Just a moment ago,
he was like, "Who is the guest?"
(Fake)
- For goodness' sake.
- You didn't know who was coming.
(The boisterous greetings end.)
It's time to welcome
the second star.
- Please come on out.
- Who is it?
He is a close friend of mine.
- There we go.
- What?
My goodness.
(A star appears.)
Jukjae is here.
- There we go.
- What?
(Singer, Jukjae)
Jukjae.
("Let's Go See the Stars" by Jukjae)
it's the song So Min loves.
It's a festival.
Grand Mint Festival!
I went to Grand Mint Festival.
- He must have been cold.
- I know.
(The melodious guitar sound...)
He is handsome.
(suits the year-end party.)
- He can sing live in the morning.
- He is cool.
(Where are you? What are you up to?)
- Here!
- Me?
- Let's go!
(Let's go see the stars)
- Suk Jin.
- I will go with you.
Me too.
(Come out of the house
for a short while)
Really?
I am not wearing any makeup.
Is that okay?
(These middle-aged men enjoy
the sweet song in a homely way.)
We are such middle-aged men.
This is an old dance.
(The second star
also has trouble performing.)
(We won't go anywhere far)
We are such middle-aged men.
- It's okay.
- I love it.
Let's go somewhere far.
(But I will hold your hand tight)
- Hold it tight. Don't let it go.
- Let's kiss as well.
- His voice doesn't waver at all.
- I know.
(He wraps up the performance
perfectly.)
- You are cool.
- Jukjae.
- Let's go see the stars.
- That was incredible.
You are so cool.
(I am incapable)
(I am lacking)
- Jukjae is a unique character.
- He is slow.
(Is Jukjae really lacking?)
We don't have time.
(It has been a while
since people told me that I can't)
(But there are things
BE'O just can't do.)
(No!)
(Not everyone can enjoy
the year-end party!)
(A famous singer picks up a guitar
because he is hungry.)
(Thank you for the song request.)
Can you play a song?
(Thank you
for the 2nd song request.)
(Thank you for the food.)
(Can you sing two songs for a coin?)
He can do it.
(A music discussion
with the singers)
(When the members become absorbed
and fight without any logic,)
(a guest becomes flustered.)
It could be a new encounter.
(Is Jukjae a player?)
It contains my sincerity!
(It's a party with all the spectacles.
How will it end?)
(The Year-End Party With Stars)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)