Somewhere in Korea.
(A night in Korea when everyone is asleep)
There's a lonely place...
that's off the beaten track.
Do you remember
the Card Shark Association there?
Asura balbalta.
(One summer day in 2020)
Two years ago,
card sharks from
all over the country gathered...
and founded the Card Shark Association.
We have rules here.
It feels like...
(That's how
the Card Shark Association was founded.)
(The 1st chairperson Ji Suk Jin)
The first chairperson
of the association was Old Man Ji.
Yoo Jae Suk.
(The 2nd chairperson Yoo Jae Suk)
The second chairperson
of the Card Shark Association...
was Yoo Jae Suk.
(I'm nothing like the former chairperson.)
(The 2nd chairperson showed
his true colors seeking to make changes.)
(I need to collect the membership fees.)
(He exploited the members
and embezzled their money.)
But since he came to power,
the Card Shark Association...
has gone down a path of destruction.
And during the New Year's party in 2021,
Chairperson Yoo ended up getting impeached.
Kim Jong Kook who used to be a thug
was elected the new chairperson.
(He led the association
with his leadership of trust and revenge.)
But shortly thereafter,
he handed over his position to Haha.
(The 4th chairperson Haha)
(Chairperson Ha got to lead
the association with his leadership.)
And a year after that...
(A day in January, 2022)
(The association found a new hideout
with the R money they had saved.)
My day has finally come.
The symbol of greed,
Chairperson Ha is holding...
the third regular meeting.
(The 4th chairperson Haha, 168cm)
(The card sharks are gathering around.)
- Is this someone's house?
- What is this?
I think I've been here before.
Hey, guys.
- You will be searched first.
- All right.
- Search?
- Yes.
Well... You don't seem to know who I am.
You're just a weak man.
You're nothing.
Why are you pretending to be tough?
- What? Are you having a gig?
- No.
- I'm Aekku.
- All right.
(A gypsy is here to give a performance.)
- I don't have anything strange.
- You may go in.
All I've got is my fists.
- All right.
- Nice to meet you.
- Have you been doing well?
- Yes.
Oh, dear.
So we're here again.
You'd better be punctual.
(The members of the association
are meeting again in a year.)
I don't think
we need to introduce each other.
You're here, weasel.
- What's this?
- Gosh. Hang on.
- How dare you...
- What's all this?
- Can't you see this?
- What on earth?
- What is a beggar doing here?
- What?
A beggar?
I'm Ryoo Seung Bum
from "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks."
- "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks?"
- Ryoo Seung Bum?
- I'm Aekku.
- Hey.
Aren't you a primitive man?
- This is...
- Where's your hair?
What's with you?
Hey, you've been...
- You've been trying really hard.
- Gosh.
Is this because
you're afraid of Jong Kook?
- Are you afraid he might nag you?
- Are you satisfied now?
Your costume is just too much.
Let's sit. By the way,
why are you the chairperson?
Is he the chairperson?
He was the last chairperson back then.
- When?
- I see.
Kwang Soo and you lost the race.
Who's Kwang Soo?
He's in jail now.
Is he in jail?
(Lee Kwang Soo is arrested.)
(Long Legs was put behind bars
because of his habit of stealing.)
Your hair has grown a lot.
I know. My hair has grown long.
I have a new character now. I'm Aekku.
Gosh, this is...
You look like a deep-sea fish.
Did you say a deep-sea fish?
A deep-sea fish?
You look a lot like a deep-sea fish.
I'm Ryoo Seung Bum.
(While the lowers are
fighting a war of nerves...)
(A card shark who looks like a thug
shows up with a swaggering gait.)
The half-thug is here.
It's been a while, Mr. Half-thug.
Can't you come on time?
Who's talking over there?
Someone just told me to come on time.
- My gosh.
- What?
Someone just told me to come on time.
(A mysterious rocker shows up.)
- My gosh.
- What?
You are...
This isn't just right. My gosh.
What?
- This isn't just right.
- Suk Jin, this is...
- I'm Aekku.
- No, I'm Aekku.
You're Ppikku.
- Oh, dear.
- What's wrong?
- Aren't you a rocker?
- Right.
Park Wan Kyu.
This is Aekku. I'm Ryoo Seung Bum.
No, I'm Aekku.
You're just a rocker.
Give me an honest opinion.
- This is just...
- This is too much.
a rocker who is past his prime.
Now he just...
- He runs an LP bar as a diversion.
- Exactly.
He plays some music.
He runs a rock cafe in Misari.
That's not true.
This is Lee Yoon Seok from Hurricane Blue.
- This isn't right.
- Hey.
So have you been doing it lately?
- What's this?
- What do you mean?
What is he doing?
What do you mean?
Have you been flipping over
some cards lately?
Are you two from the same family?
Anyway, let's do this.
- Let's work together.
- All right.
He does look like
a business owner in Misari.
Are you a cop or something?
- He acts like a cop.
- You're like that every time.
- It's not like that.
- You are terrifying us.
- What?
- Let's have a seat.
- Your hair...
- Jong Kook, he's trying hard today.
I see. What did you do with this?
- Let's just sit.
- What's with your hair?
- Hey!
- What's that?
- What's this?
- What's with your hair?
What are you supposed to be?
He doesn't want you to nag him.
So what is this?
- My gosh.
- He wants you to notice.
He wants your praise.
He tried harder than when he was
on "How Do You Play?"
I bet he will look like this
when he's old.
- Right?
- I think so.
- This is how he will age.
- Stay quiet.
What are you doing?
- Hey.
- Haha is losing his hair anyway.
- This is your future.
- I draw some hair on my forehead.
Anyway, listen to me.
Have you been doing well?
- Not really.
- The thing is...
- Now...
- You sound so awkward.
We are meeting again in a year.
- It's been a year, right?
- Has it been a year already?
Did you get a script or something?
- Yes.
- What's going on?
- I'm trying my best.
- He's doing some skit.
Two of our members...
They got killed?
- They went to prison.
- What?
(They went to prison.)
- Are you serious?
- They are not in prison.
They are staying at home.
- They're home.
- They are in self-quarantine.
- They're in quarantine anyway.
- I warned them.
They're gone. He's right.
- Anyway, I'm glad you've survived.
- Okay.
Today, we will have
our last gamble and leave.
Are we a team?
Today, I brought a guy
who's known to be a pushover.
A pushover?
- A pushover?
- Good. We need a pushover.
My gosh.
We should extort money from him.
Suk Jin, this isn't a historical drama.
That sounds like a historical drama.
- You and I look like...
- He's so bad at things like this.
- You and I should work together.
- When he was younger,
he was often scolded
by his senior comedians.
The pushover is coming.
You have to do things right.
- Okay.
- Who is it?
I'll pretend to be innocent.
(He looks just like a pushover
with a lanky frame.)
I bet he's quite tall.
- It's Joo Woo Jae.
- That's him.
(The symbol of pushover, Joo Woo Jae)
(The card sharks are excited
to see the pushover.)
It's Joo Woo Jae. My gosh.
- You look so ugly today.
- My gosh.
(A surprise attack)
He looks like a loser.
What's with you? You look horrible.
He's Lee Yoon Seok.
You look so ugly today.
- You look terrible today.
- Are you wearing long underwear?
You look like a farmer
from the countryside.
I'm sure he's wearing long underwear.
Hey, Woo Jae.
Isn't it supposed to be a skit?
Why are they doing this?
Go ahead and do it.
- What?
- Are you Earwax or what?
I'm Hearing Aid from Gangnam.
Aren't you Earwax?
- What kind of name is that?
- Hearing Aid from Gangnam?
Isn't that the name I had the other day?
You're not wearing the padded shorts.
(You're not wearing the padded shorts.)
- What?
- Does he wear padded shorts?
- He has flat buttocks.
- I was surprised to see that.
- They are worse than Kwang Soo's.
- They are totally flat.
He's got no buttocks.
They are like silken tofu.
Silken tofu. They are so soft.
- What is going on?
- Totally.
- As soon as you show up...
- I mean...
- Let's have a seat.
- All right.
He's our new member.
- Okay.
- What?
His name is Lee Yoon Seok.
Yoon Seok.
How could you say something so harsh?
- Let's see.
- Woo Jae is here.
Is he the pushover?
He's known to be a card shark.
A card shark? Is he?
I'm worried about Woo Jae's health.
- Aren't you ill?
- I'm healthy.
Are you sure?
- There he goes again.
- Did you have a medical checkup?
- I didn't.
- You should have one.
You should do that.
- I'm sure you have some polyps.
- I think so.
What? Polyp?
- Is he that old?
- I'm sure he has one.
I think so.
- He needs to have it removed.
- You should get it removed.
- Well...
- I have a headache.
- You should also take anthelmintic.
Do you take anthelmintic or not?
- I do.
- You do?
You should take anthelmintic.
You have straight intestines.
Anything you eat comes out right away.
- I often have diarrhea.
- I knew it.
- That's why he's so skinny.
- Stay quiet.
- Let me take your pulse.
- Hey.
I bet he's healthier than you.
(The chairperson worries about him
with a jaundiced face.)
- I suffer from cold hands and feet.
- You do?
I also have reflux esophagitis.
(The triple crown of weakling:
Diarrhea, cold hands, esophagitis)
- You don't have a serious illness.
- That's good.
I'm sorry, but it seems like...
you don't have a body.
You look like a clothes hanger.
- This is like a clothes hanger.
- He's all skin and bone.
Do you want me to flex my muscles?
(He sounds quite confident
for his weak body.)
Flex my muscles?
- He thinks highly of himself.
- Right.
What makes you so confident?
- Because...
- Because of you,
people call me Round Shoulders.
My shoulders...
- My shoulders are my everything.
- Are you serious?
Your shoulders are covered with dust here.
- Hey, stop that.
- Get him a duster or something.
That's enough.
- You're covered with dust.
- My gosh.
Look at him.
- You look as if...
- I knew it.
You look like a guy
who eats meat in the mountains.
- He's a primitive man.
- The man of nature.
- You're embarrassing me.
- Do you run a YouTube channel?
- Seriously, who are you?
- That's how you look.
- I'm Ryoo Seung Bum.
- My gosh.
I look like Ryoo Seung Bum.
I look like Aekku.
You are from the movie,
"War for the Planet of the Apes."
(You are from the movie,
"War for the Planet of the Apes".)
(An ape from
"War for the Planet of the Apes")
- My gosh. He's...
- An ape?
- You are...
- He's just...
- What about you?
- You are...
an ape from
"War for the Planet of the Apes."
"War for the Planet of the Apes"?
They both look scary.
Okay. I'm glad to hear that.
You look really strange.
So this is the regular meeting
of the Card Shark Association.
With our new member, Pushover Joo,
you will have a race called
Through the Card Sharks' Minds.
- You start with 20 caramels.
- We get 20 caramels.
As always, you will earn
more caramels after each mission.
And the two winners with
the most caramels will get the prize.
And one member chosen
by the winner will get a penalty.
The winner gets to pick one.
I should win favor with the winner then.
The current chairperson
of the association...
is Haha as he was elected last year.
The chairperson has the power
just like he did last time.
But he is given more power
that's upgraded today.
What is it?
On each mission,
he can reset one round of a game...
whenever he wants.
- The chairperson?
- He can reset the results.
- Reset.
- He can nullify the results.
He just goes all in.
- And if he loses, he can reset it.
- What if I lose?
Then the game will go
back to the previous round.
- That's huge.
- That's amazing.
- Go all in? Okay?
- That's a huge power.
If the members don't like the chairperson,
they can collect 20 caramels
in the proposal box...
to have the chairperson impeached.
And one of the members who
turned in caramels will be elected.
- Good.
- Okay.
Now I will give you 20 caramels each.
Okay. You know I'm a pacifist.
- Good, Woo Jae.
- Nice, Woo Jae.
- You should do things like this.
- Sure.
- He's good.
- He's good at this.
Jae Suk, are you eating it?
Of course.
Are you a thug or what?
- What are you trying to pull off?
- He's got guts.
Are you eating it?
- This is...
- My goodness.
You are unbelievable.
Once 20 caramels are collected,
there will be a new chairperson.
(A surprise attack)
This is...
- What's going on?
- Can he do this?
- Is it okay to do this?
- What is he doing?
- Is he a mugger or what?
- Can he do this?
Is it okay to do this?
Is this really okay?
- This is just...
- Can he do this?
- Hey!
- Give me half of them.
(He takes the whole bag
of Suk Jin's caramels.)
- Hey.
- Here.
Guess which one is yours.
(Guess which one is yours.)
(He starts swindling
caramels out of Suk Jin.)
(Headache)
It's 19 caramels.
One bag has 19 caramels in it.
And the other has 20.
- It's so confusing.
- All right.
What do you think?
He's really good.
If you want to survive in this world,
you must have some guts.
It's not easy to survive in this world.
But I'm a card shark.
I can pick out the good one.
With my deduction.
(Ppikku's Find My Caramels)
I bet mine is all wrinkly.
Because he rubbed it a lot.
(Rubbing fiercely)
(Ppikku's deduction is meaningless.)
I don't know what to pick.
Suk Jin, you're not supposed
to say that out loud. He heard you.
I was talking to myself.
(His plan is revealed to the whole world.)
Seriously, Ppikku is tender-hearted.
If I were him, I would've gotten mad.
If I were him,
- I would've poked him in the ribs.
- I just like a moment of choice.
That's what I do.
I love it when I'm supposed
to make a choice.
- Choose one.
- Make a choice.
(Which bag does Ppikku choose
with his gambling instinct?)
- What's your choice?
- Which one is it?
I'll go with this.
Okay.
- He hands it over right away.
- No.
(Did he manage to pick
the bag with 20 caramels?)
Two, four, six, eight, ten
Two, four, six, eight
Why does it have only 18 caramels?
(Why does it have only 18 caramels?)
(2 caramels are missing.)
Isn't it supposed to have 19 caramels?
- I don't know.
- Hang on.
It should have 19 caramels.
It has 18 caramels.
Two, four, six, eight, ten
Two, four, six...
Two, four, six, eight
- You're good at counting numbers.
- They are 19.
A YouTuber who counts numbers.
Two, four, six...
It tastes so good.
So our Ppikku is back.
He's finally back.
I'm Aekku.
- It's okay. It's just one caramel.
- It tastes so good.
- Let's start the first mission.
- Okay.
It's hilarious.
(The first mission with the card sharks)
Come on up.
(The place for the first mission
has cards and a green blanket.)
From the beginning...
- My gosh. This is...
- Oh, dear.
Are we dealing the cards
from the beginning?
- Okay.
- Don't you dare pull tricks.
My blood is boiling.
- Good.
- Okay.
- Today...
- Today, you might lose your hand.
- Be careful.
- I'll get to deal the cards today.
The table has gotten so small.
(Sitting awkwardly)
The stool is too low.
And I'm facing the front.
- Hey.
- Why?
You have nothing to hide.
What's the problem?
- What did you say?
- What are you trying to hide?
You have nothing to cover.
No one finds it strange.
- You have nothing to cover up.
- Just stay confident.
- I do have something to hide.
- Why do you think you're there?
I have a lot to hide.
Hey, you should do this.
It's not like that.
He's known to have nothing.
He's got nothing to hide.
That's why you two are sitting there.
Two guys covered with dust.
- I can't believe this.
- Those with flat things.
You weaklings.
- You are so feeble.
- Those with flat things.
This is the first mission
for the Card Shark Association.
The proposal box is always open.
- Once 20 caramels are collected,
- Really?
One of the members who turned in
the caramels will be elected.
I didn't do anything wrong though.
- You'll see. Just wait.
- The chairperson gets...
to reset the game.
(The chairperson has a huge power
to reset the results of a game.)
(How long will
Chairperson Ha's time continue?)
This will be fun. What do we do?
For this mission,
you will need good strategies
as well as good luck.
It's called Asura Balbalta,
Do You Want More Caramels?
- I see.
- Asura Balbalta.
I guess we get to pick things randomly.
Each member gets...
cards that say 30, 20, 10,
- plus 1, minus 10, and minus 20.
- Okay.
You will hand out the cards
to the members.
I know what it is. It's random.
It's not like you just hand out the cards.
You just put the cards face down
in front of the members you want.
Once you're done distributing the cards,
the six of you will play
Card Game of Wits.
You're supposed to stand up
and shout someone else's name.
(They should stand up
and shout someone else's name.)
- Ha Dong Hoon.
- Yang Se Chan.
Just like that.
But you can't call the same name.
- The same name?
- Yes.
If someone fails,
he should turn in caramels.
If you manage to shout a name,
you will pick one of the cards
that the person you called has...
and get the caramels accordingly.
(If they succeed, they get a card
from the one whose name was called.)
Okay?
If you gave good cards to someone,
you would want to call his name,
so you could get a good card.
- For a higher winning rate.
- I see.
- Isn't that obvious?
- It's a battle of wits.
- We'd need good strategies.
- It will be on my face.
- All right.
- I'll just do it randomly.
Please go ahead and distribute the cards.
All right.
I'll just do this.
I'll hand them out randomly.
I'll do that too. I think that's better.
Knowing the cards wouldn't help.
- You can have better chances.
- If I know positive numbers,
I'm more likely to win.
But other members will
try to pick the cards as well.
That's right.
So I should call the name first.
- Just do as you want.
- We don't know that.
Since when did we use our brains?
(The old men don't
like to use their brains.)
In math, there are
probability and statistics.
They can be very helpful.
- Listen, Woo Jae.
- Yes?
There's no one here who knows...
- what that even means.
- We just go with our guts.
- I can just see through you.
- Hey.
- I've been doing this for years.
- You'll see.
- We just go with our guts.
- Exactly.
- I'll show you how important it is.
- All right. We'll see.
- Just go with your guts.
- I'll see my cards.
- I'm looking at my cards right now.
- I caught so many that way.
- I'm looking at my cards.
- We don't need that method.
He's acting up
just because he majored in...
- engineering, but we'll see.
- Exactly.
- See how we win in our way.
- This is just the beginning.
I'll show you how I win
by following my hunches.
- Math never betrays me.
- Hey.
- You're wrong.
- I believe in math.
- Math will stab you in the back.
- Right.
- I'm sure of it.
- I used to hate math the most.
- My math score...
My math score on the CSAT...
- was 4 out of 100 points.
- I just slept through the exam.
- Did you hear me?
- I just slept.
- All right.
- That's so funny.
- Here.
- I'll give the cards randomly.
- Se Chan, what's your problem?
- Did you see how I threw the cards?
You might lose your hand.
- Jong Kook, did you see your cards?
- Okay.
Don't you dare try to pull a trick.
Asura balbalta.
Are you trying to pull a trick?
- Do you want to be rich?
- Here you go, Woo Jae.
- That's for Suk Jin.
- This is such a simple game.
- How many cards should each have?
- Here.
You saw me how I distributed
the cards, right?
Here. Jong Kook, here's one for you.
- Jong Kook, did you see your cards?
- Okay.
You gave Jae Suk half of your cards?
Here you go.
- Why did you give me so many cards?
- Gosh.
- Pardon?
- That's not how you should play.
- You shouldn't do that. How many...
- You shouldn't.
- should each of us have?
- I picked the cards to give him.
Woo Jae, this is for you.
You didn't see your cards, right?
I gave out my cards randomly too.
- Me too.
- All right.
It's similar.
If more than one person shouts
at the same time...
he loses three caramels,
and so does the last person remaining.
- The last person remaining?
- Gosh, that's harsh.
- Okay.
- Let us begin.
It begins when I blow the whistle.
- I'll go first.
- I'll do the same.
- Here we go.
- I'll stand up right away.
- Woo Jae.
- Jae Suk.
Okay.
- Woo Jae.
- Jae Suk.
(Haha and Woo Jae will lose 3 caramels.)
- Nice.
- Hand in your caramels.
- Okay.
- Don't you know...
- that you can win if you wait?
- They shouted at the same time.
I'll go first no matter what.
I should be careful.
- Okay.
- I'll go first.
I'll go first this time
because I don't think he can.
- I'll go first. I'll do it.
- So will I. Go ahead.
- I'll show you. I'll go first.
- I'll do the same.
I'm the chairperson. Just remember that.
- I don't care.
- I'll go third.
- Here we go.
- I'll go first no matter what.
Suk Jin.
- Se Chan.
- Jae Suk.
- Haha.
- Jong Kook.
- He said Jae Suk's name.
(Two of them shouted Jae Suk's name.)
(Jong Kook who shouted Jae Suk's name
again will lose 3 caramels.)
- What?
- Woo Jae shouted his name already.
- He shouted his name already.
- Oh, I see.
- Is that against the rules?
- All right.
(Card sharks always pretend
they don't know the rules.)
- Doesn't only the timing matter?
- No.
- You shouldn't pick the same name.
- All right.
- I really didn't know that.
The four of you who won can take
a card from the person you picked.
- Okay.
- I picked Suk Jin.
I picked Haha.
- Jae Suk.
- I shouted your name.
- This is great.
- Gosh.
- Asura balbalta.
- Se Chan...
- Did you pick him?
- Yes.
(The old card sharks who have
no strategy get their 1st cards.)
- Asura balbalta.
- Se Chan...
- That's not allowed.
- Se Chan... Gosh, seriously.
- What is it?
- I took a card from Se Chan.
- I didn't know that.
- Gosh, seriously.
- What is it?
Minus 20.
Asura balbalta.
(He picked the worst card
from the beginning.)
- I'll pick one of Haha's cards.
- Okay.
(Next up is the primitive card shark.)
- Asura balbalta.
- I wish I'd picked a better card.
- What? Minus 10? Gosh.
- Minus 10.
Okay.
(Se Chan will lose 10 caramels.)
- Great.
- Gosh.
This explains why probability is
important in this game.
Whichever card I pick here,
I will win caramels. Watch me.
- Really? Let's see.
- I'll just pick one randomly.
Go ahead.
- You're all that.
- As I said, math always wins.
We must win this.
(This is the normal way
to play this game.)
- We can't let him win.
- We can beat him.
- Please pick a minus card.
- We will never let him win.
(Following Woo Jae, Haha will pick
1 of the cards Suk Jin has.)
Oh, that's a plus card.
- Oh, that's a plus card.
- No, it's a minus card.
Asura balbalta.
Plus one.
(Haha picked a plus 1 card.)
He looks happy.
I must say, he never wins big.
(He seemed confident,
but he won only 1 caramel.)
- Why did you throw it on the floor?
- That was unexpected.
What was that?
- Haha.
- Gosh.
- This is so you.
- You...
- You're so adorable.
- Indeed.
- It's so little.
- That was funny.
(The bald chairperson is adorable.)
It's a shame. Okay.
It's so little.
(Only Woo Jae who gave Jae Suk
all the plus cards won big.)
- He gave me...
- Let's begin.
- many good cards.
- I'll go first this time.
- I will. I have nothing to lose.
- I'll go first.
- I'm serious. You know me, right?
- Remember that I'm the chairperson.
We must not let him go first.
I'll go first.
Guys, let me go first this time.
- I'll go 1st.
- Let me be the 1st.
- Let me go first just this once.
- I have no choice.
- Haha, will you go first?
- Yes.
I'll give you 1 caramel
if you let me go 1st.
- Deal.
- Okay.
Suk Jin, I'll go first too.
Give me a caramel too.
Or else, I'll go first. I'm serious.
- You weren't going to go first.
- I'll really stand up.
Go ahead then. I'll get up.
- Just give me a caramel.
- Then give me one too.
- Or I'll go first no matter what.
- I'll get up no matter what.
- I'll let you go first.
- If you want to get a plus card...
You see, I can win 20 caramels
if I go 1st, right?
- That'll be awesome.
- Of course.
- I'll let you go first too.
- I'll do the same.
I won't get up if you give me one.
- I won't get up. You can trust me.
- Suk Jin, listen.
- I'm in first place right now.
- Then...
- That doesn't matter.
- Okay.
I'll give each of you a caramel.
So let me go first.
- Sure.
- Okay.
I hope I'll get more than I spent.
Here you go.
- I really want to go first.
- Of course you will.
I'm giving away five caramels in total,
but if I win 20 caramels, I'll be okay.
- Jae Suk, are you eating it?
- My gosh.
Aren't you going to save any?
But I have 20 caramels.
- But...
- Hey.
(The gutsy card shark wastes
his caramels with no plan.)
Hey, you guys won't get up, right?
Okay. I won't go first.
(Ppikku made sure he would be
the 1st to go in the end.)
Let's begin.
Woo Jae.
- Let's see.
- We're ready.
Woo Jae.
Don't do that. Hey.
- I'm warning you. Seok...
- Woo Jae. I wasn't...
(Se Chan shouted
right after the whistle was blown.)
(Was he shouting his own name?)
- They got up at the same time.
- I wasn't the first one.
- You two got up at the same time.
- Suk Jin said his own name.
- He said his own name.
- You got up too fast.
Suk Jin said his own name.
- You punk. How could you...
- Why?
What is your problem?
Why did you do that? Hey.
- It wasn't my intention.
- That was so mean.
- They got up at the same time.
- Don't you think that was too mean?
That little...
What a jerk.
Why won't you guys criticize him?
By the way, why did you say your own name?
Well, I was taken aback.
I saw him standing up and got flustered.
Darn it. I shouldn't have trusted
those punks.
- Suk Jin.
- I'll go first this time.
- I'll go 2nd.
- I'll go 3rd.
- I said I'd go 1st.
- I'll go 2nd.
- Remember that I'm the chairperson.
- Okay.
- Don't say the same name, okay?
- I'll go first no matter what.
You'll be in trouble if it goes wrong.
- I want to go first this time.
- I'll do it no matter what.
No, I'll go first.
(Jae Suk walks
toward the corner quietly.)
What is he doing?
He wants to drag me down?
(He put his caramels in the proposal box.)
The chairperson will be replaced.
- All right. Okay.
- Good.
- Really?
- There will be a new chairperson.
- Okay.
- Really?
(20 caramels have been handed in already?)
(Earlier on, while Chairperson Ha
was raising his voice,)
(these 2 card sharks gave each other
signals secretly.)
(They gathered 20 caramels
and handed them in at once.)
- What's going on? Really?
- All right.
Get lost.
- You're not the chairperson. Move!
- Move.
- How dare you?
- Come here.
- Give me that.
- Get lost.
- You arrogant punk.
- What's going on?
- Okay. That felt good.
Which of you two is the new chairperson?
- They'll choose one of us.
- We don't know yet.
I knew they were cooking up a scheme.
This is great.
- I didn't see that coming.
- Let's see who will be picked.
(Which of them will be chosen
as the new chairperson by lot?)
- I picked one.
- Okay.
(The chairperson has been chosen.)
Please show us.
- Either of them will be annoying.
- I hate both.
- The new chairperson is...
- Who could that be?
(The new chairperson is...)
- Jae Suk.
- Great.
(Jae Suk has been chosen
as the new chairperson.)
- Chairperson Yoo.
I contributed ten caramels...
to help you.
- Hey.
- Congratulations.
(The notorious former chairperson
is back.)
- Hey, guys.
- Congratulations.
The dictator is back.
All right.
This is for you.
What is this?
- Remember I gave you that.
- Okay.
- I'll put it around your arm.
I don't like having a boss.
Then you shouldn't be here.
- I like having a boss.
- Right.
I like having a boss too.
- I like it so much.
- I like serving a boss.
- Let's officially begin the game.
- Okay.
- Before we begin,
- No way.
- for the newly established...
- Right.
- He won't say that.
- He won't.
- No way.
- It's too soon.
- Let's chip in ten caramels.
- No way.
- Right after he was elected?
- We'd better hand in caramels.
How many do you want?
Rather than giving him three,
- it's better to hand in three.
- Let's gather our caramels.
- Wouldn't that be better?
- Let's gather 20 caramels.
- Will 3 be enough?
- Give me three caramels for now.
- Wait.
- If we contribute three caramels...
- Three... Hold on.
- Woo Jae, what do you say?
- Hey.
We might as well gather our caramels.
- Hey, 3 times 4 equals only 12.
- We're 5 people.
- We'll have 15 caramels.
- Let's do that.
- We can replace him with one more.
- That's right.
- Exactly.
- Why should we give him caramels?
- You can give me just two.
- We have to... No.
Why should we give him our caramels?
- He got scared. He's demanding 2.
- Give me just 2 caramels.
- He got scared. It worked.
- It worked.
- Why don't you forget about it?
- You can demand three.
He got scared.
- One caramel.
- We're not the ones we used to be.
- Or else, we'll replace you.
- One caramel would be reasonable.
- Let's settle it.
- Why should we give him any?
Just receive one.
Three caramels.
- But...
- Let's gather our caramels.
- You can give me only one.
- Let's do this.
(You can give me only 1.)
(Oh, really?)
My gosh.
Let's do it without him.
- Let's do it without him.
- Okay.
- You can give just one too.
- Just one?
- Give him the caramels, you punk.
- Let's do it without them.
- Okay.
- This is ridiculous. Let's do this.
- Just give him your caramels.
- One, two, three, four, five...
- You two can go ahead and try.
- We'll do it without them.
- Yes, we'll do it.
- Two, four, six...
- One of you can hand in two.
- Here you go.
- Me.
(They handed in caramels right away.)
(Ppikku ran to the chairperson
to pay the tax.)
Come on. I want the deduction too.
- Look at me.
- You should hand in four caramels.
- Hand in four caramels.
- I'll give you caramels.
- You should give me four caramels.
- Come on.
- Give me four caramels.
- You have no choice.
- Four.
- Okay. Give me just three.
I was upset since you demanded
caramels right away.
- Just hand in the caramels.
- Won't you see me again?
- Just give me your caramels.
- I'm happy although I gave him two.
- Three?
- I'll give you two.
- Three.
- Okay. Give me two for now.
Here you go.
- You should be careful.
- Gosh. He's really something.
- I'm at your service.
- Good.
- Now, Chairperson Yoo, let's begin.
- Let's begin.
Okay.
Okay!
(Haha got lucky
and picked a plus-30 card.)
This is awesome.
Okay. I'll reset this round.
- What? Hold on.
- Why?
- Okay. That's good.
- Okay.
- Give me back the card.
(The card sharks feel happier
seeing others lose than winning.)
- Didn't he pick a plus one card?
- Darn it!
(They continued playing the game
with no strategy.)
- I'll announce the result.
- Okay.
We deducted three caramels...
- every time you got caught.
- Yes.
Haha won 20 caramels in total.
- Impressive.
- That's not bad.
- Se Chan won 23 caramels in total.
- Great.
(Se Chan won 23 caramels.)
- Good job.
- Woo Jae...
lost 11 caramels.
You're doomed.
- That's the thing about math.
- Right.
- Math never betrays you?
- See?
Hey, Math Boy.
(Probability and statistics are
useless on Running Man.)
- Jae Suk...
- I bet he lost caramels.
lost 41 caramels.
What? He lost 41 caramels?
- Did you say 41 caramels?
- Calm down.
- Really?
- I mean...
- He advised me on how to play it.
- That's shocking.
- Don't worry.
- Let's replace him.
- He lost 41 caramels?
- Now that we've used him,
- let's replace him.
- It's time to replace him.
- I'll find a way...
- Let's replace him.
- For your information...
- Put your hands in front of you.
Suk Jin won 32 caramels in total.
- I can replace him with 20.
- That's amazing.
Jong Kook won 18 caramels in total.
Okay.
- We can gather 12.
- Give me 5 caramels...
as a membership fee.
- No. We'll drag you down.
- We'll replace you.
(No. We'll drag you down.)
- You should pay me first.
- We'll drag you down.
- No. We refuse to do that.
- We won't give you any.
Will you make us?
- What? You have no power now.
- Now...
- Hey, let's... Right.
- Let's collect caramels.
I'll contribute ten caramels.
Yes. Then I'll contribute five caramels.
- Good. Chip in five caramels.
- Okay.
- You should contribute that much.
- I'll contribute too.
- How many? Ten?
- Shall I contribute five? Okay.
- Yes, five caramels.
- What did you say?
- Contribute just three caramels.
- How many do you have now?
- I handed in one caramel too.
- We won't accept yours.
(Surprised)
- You're the current chairperson.
- I already put it in the box.
You can't do that.
- I'm handing in one caramel too.
- Yes, I can.
- I handed in one too.
- Right.
- I handed in one caramel too.
- All right.
- Why did you do that?
- We all contributed.
- I contributed the most.
- I'm so upset.
I gave Jae Suk one caramel.
- Hey.
- I can't stand this anymore.
- We should've done it quietly.
- He's right about that.
- I hope I'll be chosen again.
- You see...
I want to make this
a peaceful organization.
- I hope Jae Suk will be chosen.
- Then we'll replace him again.
Jae Suk contributed just one.
Is it Jae Suk?
- That'd be hard to believe.
- Who is it?
That won't happen.
The new chairperson is...
- I contributed the most.
- It'd be awesome if it was me.
Please.
It's Woo Jae.
(Chairperson Joo Woo Jae)
- Gosh.
- What's wrong?
- Why?
- What's the matter?
(Woo Jae seems to be on edge.)
- Why?
- What's the matter?
How many caramels do you have now?
- What?
- How many do you have?
- Why?
- I have none.
- How many do you have?
- I have no caramels.
How many caramels do you have?
- We don't have to give him.
- That's right. We don't have to.
- Why would we?
Who are you to demand caramels?
- Hey.
- Who do you think you are?
- Isn't this how it works?
- Hey.
(Intimidated)
Not everyone can handle the job, Woo Jae.
- What are you talking about?
- That doesn't come with the job.
- Wait.
- You should win them over first.
- If we hold out a little longer...
- Then to celebrate...
- Yes.
- that I became the chairperson,
- give me just one caramel.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Just one?
- We'll let you keep your job.
- He's right.
- Okay. Fine.
- Hey.
- Just keep your job.
- Are you giving up?
I'll see which of you will
give me a caramel.
- I'll see.
- Hey.
Jong Kook, if things go well
for you in the next game,
- I'll reset that round.
- Okay.
- Hey, go ahead. I don't care.
- Just give me one now.
- Give you what?
- Then I won't do that.
- You messed with the wrong man.
- Hey.
- You made a big mistake.
- I will...
let you keep your arm,
so you can wear that armband.
(I will let you keep your arm,
so you can wear that armband.)
(Frozen with fear)
- My gosh. That's so scary.
- Hey. Don't ask for more.
Come on. What was that?
- You know what I mean.
- Will he get killed later?
- I mean...
- Will he get killed...
- at the end?
- As if we owed him something.
- You punk.
- You know...
- But...
- Stay out of this.
It's not like we're obligated
to give him caramels.
- But as you know,
- Why would he...
- he came here to help us.
- You punks.
- You know I'm right.
- Why would you scare him?
- I didn't intend to scare him.
- It's a matter of life and death.
You're too fainthearted...
- to be a chairperson.
- Just give him one caramel.
- How many caramels do you have?
- None.
Then how will you give him a caramel?
- He has nothing to lose.
- He has no caramels.
- Don't worry.
- It's lunchtime.
You will go downstairs 1 by 1...
and choose 1 of the 3 rooms.
And the people in the same room...
will evenly share the given caramels.
- Hold on.
- He has no caramels.
Can I nullify the result of that too?
You can nullify the result if you want.
- Can I?
- Of course you can.
Yes. You're the chairperson.
If you do, all of you will have to
come back and start over again.
- That sounds great.
- Right.
You should take advantage of
your power like this.
Don't be too greedy
and say you'll choose the 20 room.
Then we won't go into that room.
I'll choose the 40 room.
- The 40 room?
- You'll choose the 40 room?
- Don't be...
- He calculated the probability.
- You can reset it only once.
He's being too greedy.
- Is this for us?
- Can we eat this?
Take one bowl with you
when you go downstairs.
- Oh, we take it with us?
- I see.
- I'll eat jjamppong.
- I'll eat jjamppong too.
(I'll eat jjamppong.)
- Then I'll eat jjamppong today.
- I choose jjamppong too.
- Okay.
- Oh, dear.
(All 5 bowls of jjamppong were taken
in an instant.)
- We can be a little mean sometimes.
- I prefer jjajangmyeon.
- Do you?
- Yes, I always choose...
- jjajangmyeon over jjamppong.
- Really? Okay.
Hey, I didn't know Woo Jae was
so fainthearted.
- See you later, Woo Jae.
- He's too weak.
- I'll go into the 40 room.
- Okay.
- I can reset the result.
- Go ahead.
All tenacious people like us would
choose the same room.
- Choose wisely.
- I wouldn't say "tenacious".
I would say that we know too much
about variety shows.
- Like moths flying into the fire.
- We've been doing this for so long.
Estimate the number of possible outcomes.
(The 30 room)
(He won't go into the 30 room.)
(The 40 room, the 20 room)
If I choose the 40 room,
everyone will come
since this is the first round.
If I choose the 40 room,
and they all choose the same room...
And none in there.
I choose the 20 room.
(I choose the 20 room.)
(He told everyone that he would
choose the 40 room.)
Now that I'm in the 20 room,
all I can do is
hope that they all choose...
the 40 room.
Detective Kim, you go first.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Come on.
Since Woo Jae said
he would choose the 40 room,
I'll respect the chairperson's decision.
He said he'd choose the 40 room, right?
Then I'll choose the 20 room.
(Then I'll choose the 20 room.)
I clearly remember him saying
he'd choose the 40 room.
He didn't choose the 20 room
like a coward, right? Let's go.
(Jong Kook chose the 20 room.)
What? He's really not here.
I'm impressed. Woo Jae must have...
Oh, gosh.
I knew you'd choose this room.
Come and sit down.
- Let's say no one else comes here.
- Okay.
But the others might choose the 30 room.
- No, I don't think so.
- They won't do that.
They all... Hey, listen.
They're all reckless and awfully greedy.
Make a decision
when you find out the result.
(As Detective Kim predicted,
all the others chose the 40 room.)
I'm not that kind of person.
Everyone has made their choice.
There are 4 members in the 40 room.
(There are 4 members in the 40 room.)
See? I was right.
- Just as I expected...
- Is this scripted?
(The pro card sharks always choose
the biggest room.)
- Did you all plan this?
- No.
- It's the same anyway.
- Each will get ten caramels.
- Each of us will get ten.
- Yes.
It wouldn't be so different.
- Especially in this situation.
- You're right.
- You should always be bold.
- It's so good.
(They started eating in peace
after getting 10 caramels each.)
Woo Jae decided to reset the result.
- What?
- Woo Jae decided...
(The chairperson used his power
to reset game results.)
He's so stupid.
Say that you'll choose the 20 room...
and that they can choose
between the other rooms.
Do as I say.
Will you reset the result?
Yes, I want to reset the result.
(Chairperson Joo reset the result.)
Should we go upstairs right now?
- Gosh. Woo Jae, that punk.
- We should go now.
- He keeps calculating.
- Will you go first?
I'll go first. I'll tell you
which room I'll choose before I go.
I'll go into the 30 room this time.
- Okay.
Do whatever you want. You can go now.
He won't stop calculating.
You learned the wrong math.
- Where did you learn that?
- It's useless on this show.
Don't act like you're highly educated.
- Go on.
- You only ended up losing.
We want others' failure
more than our own success.
You misjudged us.
At least take a risk.
Don't try to predict our next moves.
That's not possible.
- I'll go to the 30 room.
- All right.
(The 30 room)
(He just said that he was going to
choose the 30 room.)
(What could be his choice?)
(Woo Jae has chosen a room.)
Okay. I'll choose the 20 room
no matter what.
I hope he didn't choose this room
again unlike his words.
There's no way he came here.
No, he's not that stupid.
(Did Woo Jae go into the 20 room
again this time?)
Right? Okay. Good.
(Relieved)
- I have an idea.
- What is it?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors
to pick one of us...
to go to the 30 room.
And the rest of us can choose the 40 room.
The rest three of us. Okay?
Even if Woo Jae is there,
you can get 15 caramels.
- Right?
- Exactly.
You can go first, Jae Suk. Go and eat up.
- Let's let him go first.
- Okay then.
- Which room will you choose?
- I'll choose the 40 room as I said.
(He chose the 40 room as he said.)
Yes, I knew it.
Of course, no one came here.
Right. It's too soon to tell.
(Following Jae Suk, Suk Jin comes in.)
Okay, good. It's just the two of us.
It's just us, Jae Suk.
I'm going to the 30 room.
- The 30 room?
- Do you want to go instead?
I thought that was the case.
Why you though?
Because you said so.
So what will it be?
- Will you go to the 30 room?
- Yes, the 30 room.
- Then I'll go to the 40 room.
- Okay.
- I...
- You really are exhausting.
Is this the main event today?
(They're sick and tired of each other.)
Se Chan, that brat.
- Darn it.
- Of course.
(Haha steps into the 40 room.)
Okay, good.
Where will Se Chan go?
- The 30 room.
- Right?
Why is everyone
coming to the 40 room though?
I could ask you that myself.
- Jae Suk...
- Tell me.
One can dream, right?
A chance could open up for me.
- Did anyone order food?
- Seriously?
(Se Chan enters.)
(Startled)
- Unbelievable.
- What are you doing here?
Haha, why are you here?
You said you'd go to the 30 room.
I told you multiple times
that I was going to the 40 room.
- You said you'd go to the 30 room.
- How many of you are in here?
(Woo Jae joins the party.)
Tell me how many of you are in here.
What on earth are you doing here?
Are you kidding me?
Why are you here?
- So no one is in the 30 room?
- Why are you here?
- Is no one in the 30 room?
- No one's there.
Going to the 30 room would mean a jackpot.
What on earth are you doing here though?
(He failed to calculate
the right probability.)
You two shouldn't be here at all.
Why did you come in here?
Jong Kook, how many do you have?
- Unbelievable.
- Twenty?
- Did you go to the 20 room?
- Yes, 20.
- I can't believe it.
- So the 30 room is empty.
- How...
- There are five of us in here.
Woo Jae.
This is what math really is.
This is the math
that applies to Running Man.
This is the math known in Running Man.
(The Running Man math isn't
taught in engineering classes.)
I lost everything I had.
Woo Jae ruined everything.
I'm ruined.
(Card Shark Association)
(The card sharks
move on to their next game.)
I really need to do better.
Exactly, but when will it happen?
After the show ends?
Woo Jae, you shouldn't
mention math at this show.
- But...
- Normal math doesn't apply here.
I can win, you know.
There's still a window of opportunity.
- Woo Jae, math...
- I mean it.
This is what math is.
- Woo Jae.
- Right?
Woo Jae,
you shouldn't be using your brain.
- Let your heart guide you.
- Exactly.
Look here, Woo Jae.
Jae Suk, they said it all.
- They already said everything.
- Math is irrelevant here.
- Woo Jae, take it slow.
- They said it all.
Just watch how I make it happen.
Aren't you at minus 30?
There's no need to fret.
- Guys.
- Yes?
You're now entering the second match.
- Right.
- Sure.
During the lunch break,
- all 20 were received.
- What?
- No way.
- Who was it?
- Who had enough?
Haha, Suk Jin, and Se Chan.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
Guys, listen up.
The three of us
should pay enough right now...
and have one of us become a candidate.
Okay, good.
Let's do this!
- If I...
- I will only ask...
for one from each of you.
We're a union.
- A union.
- I'm curious though.
You said you'd only ask for one.
Why must we pay up though?
Just know that I don't intend to pay you.
- Same here.
- That means none for me, right?
Just know that
I don't have any to give out.
The chairperson doesn't have
a lot of authority.
It can always be nullified.
- That's all we need frankly.
- All right.
It must be Suk Jin.
Today's third...
No, you're already
at your fourth chairperson.
Today's fourth chairperson is...
No way.
- That's true.
- Let it be Suk Jin.
- It's Suk Jin.
- Nice!
(Suk Jin is chosen.)
Mr. Ji, congratulations.
- Mr. Lee.
- I will not forget what you did.
Suk Jin, we're a team.
- I won't forget.
- The chairperson...
I will turn the tables.
I'll aim for the last election.
Do whatever you want.
As a membership fee,
I'll accept ten.
What a joke.
(What a joke.)
Seriously?
Don't let them be this way.
- Why?
- How does this make sense?
It's not fair.
(They're not going to participate
in the collection of funds.)
- He asked for 10, not 1.
- Exactly.
As if we'd pay ten each.
- But the chairperson...
- Do something about them!
- What?
- Why?
When you two are elected as chairperson,
we get into character and pay up.
- But...
- How is that fair?
- I'm a veteran myself, you know.
- Pay up!
- But...
- Ten!
Why should we pay up though?
Because I'm the chairperson.
- That's not a reason.
- That doesn't make sense.
Okay, fine.
I'll give you a 50 percent discount.
- Hear me out.
- No way.
Unless the chairperson
does something for us...
Of course I'm an influence.
In my case,
I will leave the association
unless I'm paid five.
I'll leave the association.
He's asking me to pay up instead.
- That's a good idea.
- Right?
You should pay up.
I'll form another association.
He's threatening to form his own.
You should tell him that it's not allowed!
The chairperson collecting money
isn't in the rules either.
Shut it!
After all the money I paid them?
- There are no perks.
- This is hurting our pride.
- We should make them pay.
- Our pride is on the line.
- I'll form another association.
- You only have to pay one.
You...
- You're broke, right?
- No.
- Aren't you broke?
- I'm not.
- You have none.
- That's not true.
How many do you have?
I can't tell you that.
Debt is categorized as an asset, you know.
Debt is categorized as an asset!
You're even worse than Jong Kook.
- Bring it on!
- Why?
Then let me suggest a deal.
- Sure.
- Go ahead.
I'll offer two and you'll do the same.
We'll then play rock-paper-scissors
and the winner will take everything.
(Winner takes all?)
- What do you say?
- That's...
So what you're suggesting is a fair game.
- You suggested a mini game.
- Right.
We...
Does that serve a purpose though?
- Of course.
- So we should play a game?
I'm challenging you.
So you're suggesting a mini game.
- Yes, a mini game.
- Are you kidding me?
- With two each...
- We can do that at any time.
Let's drag Jae Suk down.
- Three of his...
- Jae Suk...
- He'll even crawl at your feet.
- He'll accept the deal.
Offer three and
he'll crawl between your legs.
- Jae Suk...
- Make him our minion.
Join us and we'll give you two.
- How many?
- Two.
- Two isn't enough.
- Then three?
No.
- Then...
- Ask how many he wants.
- The number will keep going up.
- Don't give him any.
- How many do you want?
I'll move for five.
You'll be our minion though.
Bring us our water.
- Okay?
- Okay, deal.
- Is five enough?
- Yes.
- Okay!
- Nice.
- Okay.
- How adorable.
You adorable punk.
- You little...
- Okay.
- What's with them?
We have our new minion.
- Get us some water.
- Get the water.
As if I'd ever do that.
Are you kidding me?
- Hey.
- You need to pay back your debt.
Pay what back?
(Pay what back?)
Must he pay you back right away?
If you think about it,
your assets get frozen, right?
You must pay back the debt right away.
- This is infuriating.
- Jae Suk never gets to keep one...
in his pocket.
Where do you think you're going?
Stand back here.
Your place is at this far end.
We'll begin the next game then.
For this next game,
luck must be in your favor.
This is All-in for your Victory.
How will it go?
We have already set four rounds
of 1-on-1 games for you to play.
While two of the sharks go head to head,
the others...
will place their bets on who they think...
will win the game.
The winner will take twice the amount.
Okay, good.
So here are the games.
Round one. Jae Suk and Haha.
Arm wrestling.
The winner will be obvious.
Round two. Suk Jin and Se Chan.
Elephant trunk spin and flag race.
Round three. Woo Jae and Se Chan.
One-legged fight.
Round four. Jae Suk and Jong Kook.
Bottle cap flicking.
I'd do well if it were a normal lid.
We'll then begin with the first round.
Jae Suk and Haha's arm wrestling...
- will commence in three minutes.
- Three minutes?
Do the winners of the games
get something as well?
The winners of the games
will receive a prize of one.
- Just one?
- One?
The rest will take one of these.
- Later, you will place your bets.
- Our bets?
Who has the upper hand?
- Jae Suk, of course.
- It's a best of three.
- Haha can't win.
- Of course not.
- Haha's strong as well.
- It won't happen.
His arms are too short.
- It's better to have shorter arms.
- I'm good at arm wrestling.
And arm wrestling isn't what I'm good at.
Is he not good at arm wrestling?
There's no way he'll lose.
- Jae Suk, right?
- Yes.
- But...
- And he won't want to lose.
He doesn't even lift weights
when he works out.
I lift kids instead.
I lift kids for a living.
That doesn't really count though.
- You have no idea.
- My gosh.
- Let's see.
- Can his arms be mushier?
His arms aren't muscular at all.
We should check their status
like jockeys check their horses.
- I'm not that bulky either.
- Let's see.
- I'm not bulky.
- But still...
- Okay.
- Do we bet on who'll win?
Bet your desired amount on
who you think you'll win.
Write it down.
You can keep it with you.
(The bets have been placed.)
- It's a best of three matches.
- I placed my bet.
- But this...
- You never know though.
You never know.
Besides, their pride...
- hangs in the balance too.
- Of course.
I'm going to win no matter what.
- Go.
- This is to protect...
- their dignity.
- Haha is strong in the arms.
(That hurts!)
Sir, come on.
What do you think you're doing?
It won't make you stronger.
- He's gambling again.
- Loosen up a little.
Haha has the losing grip.
- Okay.
- Ready, set, go.
Look at how strong Jae Suk is.
Jae Suk's strong.
(Right away, their hands
swing over to Jae Suk's side.)
No! Hey!
- Nicely done.
- Haha, don't!
No...
(The bald player is holding out.)
- Haha lost. It's over.
- He lost. The game is over.
It's over!
Jae Suk is really strong.
- All right!
- Jae Suk wins!
- All right. I got it.
- Hey!
- How could you lose?
- Look at this.
Good job, Jae Suk.
- Suk Jin.
- That was great.
- He's really strong.
- He's tough to beat.
Gosh, look how desperate he was to win.
All right. I got it.
What's wrong with you?
You said you could win.
(Right then,)
(Detective Kim approaches Jae Suk.)
I'll beat him.
I'll give you five.
You should lose deliberately.
(A dark proposal by a corrupt detective)
(Jong Kook, who bet on Haha,)
(suggested Jae Suk to lose deliberately.)
I bet a lot on you.
You can do it however you want.
Just beat him.
I'll give you five right away
if you beat him.
But Jong Kook offered me five as well.
- If you lose?
- Yes, if I lose.
No, you must beat him.
What kind of a deal did they offer him?
You'll lose everything you have
if Haha loses,
- so offer Jae Suk five.
- What?
Jong Kook said
he'd give me five if I lose.
If what?
- Jong Kook...
- He offered me five.
- In that case...
- said he'd give him five.
- You...
- You should give him five too.
If you win, I'll give you five.
That means you'll get ten.
- You should win.
- Okay? You can do it!
- Okay, I got it.
- You should beat him right away.
Gosh.
(Player Yoo settled a dark deal.)
Get ready. Let's play.
Grab his hand.
Get ready.
One, two, go!
- Go!
- Go.
Haha.
He's determined.
- Go!
- Go.
(The indebted card shark
is guaranteed 10 caramels.)
Go.
It's over.
Finish him!
- Nice!
- All right.
- All right!
Jae Suk wins!
Now, please reveal your betting results.
- All right.
- Should I go first?
I bet 20 on Jae Suk's win.
All right. Se Chan won 20 caramels.
Next, Woo Jae.
- Four.
- Four?
Let's check out Jong Kook's.
I bet five on Haha.
You need to pay up five caramels.
I bet 30 on Jae Suk.
All right. Suk Jin wins 30 caramels.
Se Chan wins 20 caramels.
- Woo Jae wins four caramels.
- I'll give you some.
Jong Kook, pay up five caramels.
Here are five caramels.
You don't have to give him any.
All right. Round Two...
is between Suk Jin and Se Chan.
It's getting a flag
after elephant trunk spins.
But I'm not good at it.
The winner can take three caramels.
- Three?
- I think...
- Wait, why didn't you give me any?
- Oh, right. I should give you one.
- Just one?
- Didn't you also win one earlier?
- You're so obsessed with it.
You should eat it like you did before.
- Try it.
- I'll have it later.
He has to survive with one.
- I know now that it's useful.
- You can't eat it?
- I should make use of it.
- I'll give them to the rest of you.
- Come here.
- What do we do?
Whom should we bet on?
I think this round will be a draw.
We need to form an alliance.
Join our alliance.
Listen up, Jae Suk.
- It's all about betting.
- Do you want me...
to do the elephant trunk spin or not?
- Of course you should.
- Okay, then.
- What does he mean?
- Then you should...
He said, "Do you want me to do
the elephant trunk spin or not?"
You should give me three each.
I'll do my best.
- If you give me 3...
- Will 3 be enough?
But if you bet on me, you'll win.
It's up to you.
I'm telling you, I'm not good at spinning.
- We know that.
- I think I'll lose.
We all know that.
- But he could lose on purpose.
- He could lose deliberately.
Because he could make
the others lose their caramels,
although he doesn't win any.
- The thing is...
- But why would I do that...
- when you'd give me the caramels?
- You're capable of that.
I'll play properly for real.
If he acts up, he could lose on purpose.
(Elephant trunk spin and flag race)
(Jae Suk bet 16 caramels on Se Chan.)
Give me some first. Give me three.
I bet 16 caramels on you.
On me?
- I'll give you three.
- Okay. Give them to me first.
But you must do your best.
- Jae Suk, I will.
- Okay.
All right. Three caramels.
I'll not lose for sure.
I should lose on... What?
You should lose on purpose.
But I'll lose anyway.
I know that, but...
I'll give you half if you lose.
- Really?
- Yes, I bet mine on Se Chan.
(It looks like Woo Jae will bet
on Se Chan as well.)
Please wrap up your bets.
(Are you going to win or lose?)
(I'll win.)
Oh, that could happen.
Se Chan could lose on purpose
after accepting a deal.
If they bet on me...
That could happen.
Who are you talking to?
Is there anyone here?
(The betting time is over.)
Are you done with the bet?
- Yes, I am.
- I'll start from here.
(The player who spins 5 times
and grabs the flag first wins.)
All right. That's it.
I'm already dizzy.
- Let's play.
- Hey.
It's five spins.
- Se Chan.
- I went all in for you.
- Are you ready?
- I'm not sure about Se Chan.
- I'll play in earnest.
- Let's do this.
You can start spinning
as soon as I blow the whistle.
- I should spin fast.
- Please count for us.
Ready.
(The game starts.)
One.
- One.
- He's doing his best. Look at him.
- Two.
- Three.
- Suk Jin, yours is two.
- Four.
- Five.
- Gosh, I'm so dizzy.
Go, Se Chan.
- Why that punk...
- Hey.
Go, Se Chan.
- Why that punk...
- Hey.
Are you kidding me?
Seriously.
- Hey.
- Hey. Do a proper job.
- Are you serious? Hey!
- Hey!
- Gosh, I'm so dizzy.
- Hey.
- Hey!
- Get a grip.
- Don't joke around.
- Hey.
- I bet they won't reach the flag.
- I'm going to kill you.
- Seriously.
- Gosh!
- I'm going to kill you.
- I'm going to kill you for real.
- Se Chan.
- That's a water bottle.
- Hey.
- Come over here. Hey.
- That's a water bottle.
- Hey.
- I knew he'd do this.
- That rascal.
- Stop it.
- Se Chan!
- Hey.
- Hey, I bet all my caramels on you.
- Se Chan, I bet all my caramels.
- Hey.
I bet all my life on you.
Hey, that's a camera.
- That's a camera.
- I'm going to kill you.
- Hey, are you serious?
- Hey! Se Chan!
- This is driving me crazy.
- Hurry up.
- Se Chan.
- Come over here.
- The flag is right here!
- Hey.
- This is the flag.
- Suk Jin.
- It's here.
You are almost there. Both of you.
My gosh. He's unbelievable.
- I even took out a loan to bet.
- Se Chan.
Se Chan. Hey.
- Hey, I...
- Suk Jin.
Think wisely.
You'll get just three even if you win.
- If you lose...
- Hey, Se Chan.
Gosh, this is...
- Hey!
- Seriously.
(Suk Jin wins.)
This is because...
He wouldn't have grabbed it
even if we gave him an hour.
- Gosh. I'm so dizzy right now.
- You know...
I'd rather have them ruined
than to get a few caramels from you.
You see? I knew this would happen.
It's better that I won.
Please reveal your bets.
- Hold on.
- I...
I knew he'd act up.
I told you. You should've bet on me.
He bet 16.
I bet five on Se Chan.
I told you.
You should've bet on me to win.
- Next.
- I knew Se Chan would do that.
I knew this would happen,
so I bet one on Suk Jin.
(Haha bet 1 on Suk Jin.)
Got it. What about Woo Jae?
- This is because...
- I thought Suk Jin would lose,
- He...
- and that Se Chan...
- would give a twist.
- Woo Jae, it'd have taken long.
I was dizzy!
- You try it!
- What? You bet 28?
You bet that many?
Gosh, I'm so sick of him.
- But this was...
- Gosh, seriously.
- Se Chan...
- They are such jerks.
Seriously.
- Hey.
- You try spinning at this hour.
I bet you'll be dizzy too.
Be quiet.
I couldn't see it for real.
Se Chan, you're seriously...
You must be on
"The Story of That Day" next week.
Goodness, I still can't see it.
All right.
Round Three is a one-legged fight...
between Se Chan and Woo Jae.
- Right away?
- The prize is five caramels.
- Gosh, Se Chan...
- Se Chan will win for sure.
Se Chan will win if he plays properly.
But I can't trust him.
(Se Chan has the key
to the game once again.)
- Do you think he'll win?
- But in this condition...
Listen. I'll do this.
I think I'll win if we go at each other,
but if we retreat,
I don't think I can manage to win.
I was too dizzy.
(Should we believe him or not?)
I promise you. I'll play earnestly.
Get lost.
If you give me two caramels each,
I'll beat him.
- Do you have a death wish?
- I mean it.
You're seriously...
Seriously. You...
Can't you get it?
Jae Suk is really upset.
He's really upset.
Jae Suk is upset for real.
He was frustrated with me earlier.
He went,
"Of course, you should bet on Se Chan."
What's worse is that
he gave me three caramels.
This time... I'm serious.
I'll return the three caramels
you gave me earlier.
Here.
You should go all in.
I'm not kidding. I'll play earnestly.
(You should go all in.
I'll play earnestly.)
I'll play earnestly.
There's nothing I can do in this round.
Are you going to do your best?
I'll beat him for real.
Gosh, I'm not sure about this.
I know that Se Chan will lose for sure.
- Se Chan will lose for sure.
- That's true.
I'll lose right away,
so give me ten caramels.
Hold on.
Gosh, Se Chan...
I'm confident that I can lose.
- I'm confident that I can lose.
- I see.
- Your knees should...
- Give me ten.
You can bet everything
on Se Chan and give me ten.
I'm not confident that I can win.
But I'm confident that I can lose.
But you must lose.
Of course. I have nothing to lose.
I have nothing.
This is all I have.
All right. This is great.
- I made my bet.
All right. Are you done?
I'm going to beat Se Chan here
since I couldn't...
on "Love Me Actually."
(Pushover Joo met his old enemy.)
For your information,
I bet all 30 of my caramels.
- Really?
- Yes.
This is so nerve-racking.
But I...
They're deceiving all of us.
I have nothing to lose.
All right. I made my bet.
(It looks like they all bet big
in this round.)
You'd better do well.
- Get ready.
- Let's do this.
You should at least bump into each other.
Get ready.
(The game starts the moment
their knees touch each other's.)
(They'll start with the starting posture.)
You got this.
Gosh, I hate the way he talks.
Are you going to fall off on purpose
as soon as we start?
- I'm going to play for real.
- Okay.
I think we'll need a VAR.
Here it comes.
His face says that he's going to lose.
His face says it all.
He's thinking of how to lose.
(The moment they touch each other,
the game starts.)
They haven't bumped into each other.
They haven't?
- Gosh.
- It'll only start after they do.
- I'll get five if I win, right?
- Go bump into him.
Play hard, you guys.
(They bumped into each other.)
(You should go all in.
I'll play earnestly.)
(Exclaiming)
Yes!
(Se Chan loses.)
Woo Jae wins!
(Pushover Joo wins.)
I was going from below,
but he hit me from above.
Please reveal your bets.
- You're seriously...
- Gosh, I bet on Woo Jae though.
- I bet one.
- I bet 30 on Woo Jae.
- Give me one.
- That was one great bet.
- That was incredible.
- Give me one.
- Gosh, Se Chan.
- I should've bet five.
- I knew Se Chan would lose.
- Really?
- I bet two on Se Chan.
I bet 1 on Woo Jae. I should've bet 10.
I did my best.
(Se Chan claims he did his best.)
- Are you going to beat him?
- I'll lose.
- I'll fall as soon as we clash.
- You'll lose?
I'm confident.
Move over. Don't talk to them.
- What? I'm talking with them.
- Move.
I'm going to give it my all.
(I'm going to give it my all.)
How was I supposed to attack him
when he attacked me from above?
- I should've bet ten.
- You are...
Gosh, this is amazing.
- All right.
- Okay, fine.
I'm going to bet it all on the last round.
All right, you're going to get
as many caramels...
as the numbers here.
I'll start.
It's out.
(Did Jong Kook make a mistake on purpose?)
(Jong Kook unexpectedly lost
when he's obsessed with winning.)
- What was that?
- What?
We are...
- All right!
- Yes!
Please reveal your bets.
- Yes! I bet 30!
- Yes!
(Suk Jin and Haha
won 30 caramels from their bets.)
I also bet 30!
(Se Chan also won 30 caramels.)
I'm going to reset the round if I lose.
Oh, you're thinking of resetting it?
- That's why I'm betting all.
- Oh, right. He's the chairperson.
- I should've stuck with him.
- You're right.
We should bet all 30.
(He only shared the info
with Haha who listened to him.)
It was a piece of cake to make the bet.
I knew it. He's only bad with stocks.
Gosh, I should have one.
- Goodness, I lost so many.
- Right now...
If you join me,
- this is what happens.
- I know. That was so cool.
- What's the point of betraying?
- Thank you.
You can have it all.
- The chairperson...
- We should change the chairperson.
I think we should change the chairperson.
Suk Jin, we're on your side.
- I'm on your side.
- We won't change the chairperson.
- Gosh, those punks...
- It's okay.
- I'm joining you.
- It's meaningless.
- We even took photos earlier.
- This is great.
- It's meaningless.
- This is a nice mix.
Family!
You automatically formed teams.
- This is great.
- All right.
Those with makeup and without makeup.
Let's finish them.
The last mission...
is something you all claim are good at.
It's Card Game of Wits.
- That's going to be fun!
- Bring it on!
The one where we stick a card
on our forehead?
- I'm good at it.
- We're finally playing it.
- I'm good at this.
- We should do this well.
(A card game to determine
the true card shark)
This game is really nerve-racking.
No, it's not nerve-racking at all.
(A card game to determine
the true card shark)
It is nerve-racking.
By the way, we have more than
20 caramels in the proposal box.
(There are more than 20 caramels
in the proposal box?)
Jae Suk, Woo Jae, Haha,
and Se Chan paid up their caramels.
- All right!
- I paid for mine too.
- Jong Kook paid up too.
- Right. Jong Kook did too.
I... Darn it.
We have a one-fifth chance.
- This will be our final bet.
- Gosh.
Make me the chairperson.
(It's time to pick a new chairperson.)
All right. I'll draw one now.
- Please...
- This is it.
- You can totally win.
- Because you can turn the table.
I think it'll be me.
This round is a big one.
- I'll go all in.
- You'll play with ease.
- Then you can go all in.
- It's me.
It's me.
- The second chairperson.
- Please...
Jae Suk won't be picked again, will he?
(Everyone waits for the result
with bated breath.)
- Jong Kook.
- All right!
(Kim Jong Kook)
(Jong Kook becomes the next chairperson.)
- It'll be advantageous for him.
- I got this.
It's completely advantageous for him.
- Gosh, this is...
It's advantageous for the chairperson.
- It is advantageous.
- Everyone.
This is the last round
for the card sharks.
I must do well.
It's Card Game of Wits
with your pride at stake.
(It'll be carried out
with 4 people in a group.)
(There are red and blue cards with
numbers 1 to 10 written on them.)
(Stick one of the red cards
on your forehead.)
(Check the blue card on your own.)
(After betting your caramel,)
(the player with a higher
combination of numbers wins.)
If one goes broke,
Haha will join the table.
Okay.
If no one goes broke,
the player with the least caramel
will be eliminated,
and Haha will join.
The experienced ones know the game better.
I just need to be good at it, right?
- Of course!
It's a matter of probability in the end.
Now, please stick a card on your forehead.
Gosh, this is...
Don't look at the card,
and stick it on your forehead.
Just stick a random card.
- Let's do this.
- A random card.
(They'll pick a card and stick it
on their forehead.)
- All right.
- Do I stick it like this?
Here we go.
(Carefully picking a card)
Let's see.
- Time's up.
- All right.
(They're done putting
the card on their forehead.)
Check the hidden card on your own.
The hidden card.
This is the important part.
The chairperson will go all in.
(It's important to keep a poker face
no matter what number you see.)
- Gosh.
- All right.
(It's important to keep a poker face
no matter what number you see.)
(They all carefully
check the hidden card.)
Chairperson Kim, who should start first?
I'll start first.
How many should we bet at first?
Everyone should bet one each.
- One each?
- I see.
Here we go.
If you throw it in the wrong box,
then that's it.
Of course.
All right, then.
- I'll bet 1 first.
- He's betting 1.
- Just one?
- I'll go all in at the end.
Did you bet only one,
Chairperson Kim? My gosh.
Here he goes again.
He's going to start betting everything.
- Goodness.
- I bet eight.
- Woo Jae, it's your turn.
Come on, guys.
(The math lover was on about probability.)
I bet...
(How many will he bet?)
- I bet five.
- Five? No, that's not it.
Since he bet eight, you should bet higher.
- You should bet at least six.
- Oh, really?
(He dropped one in Se Chan's box.)
And since you dropped one
in Se Chan's box,
you can't take it out again.
- You saw that?
- Yes.
- We all saw it.
- I thought you didn't.
- We'll let it slide.
- Please let it slide.
- Are you going to bet?
- I will...
- You can bet on top of that.
But you have to bet
more than eight caramels.
- Then I can't.
- You can't bet lower than that.
- You have to bet 16.
- That's right.
- He's bad at math.
- He is.
Eight times two is sixteen.
- He's an empty head.
- He really is.
- How did he major in engineering?
- What's 8 plus 8?
- It's 16.
- Then...
- I just bet eight, didn't I?
- Then just say, "call."
- Call.
- That's it.
I'm out.
(I'm out.)
(He gives up fast.)
You're out? Come on.
- Gosh, he was Ppikku.
- He's Ppikku.
- Hey!
- How could Aekku play like that?
- I knew I'd lose.
- You're out?
I'm out.
I'm out too. I can't bet more.
My number was too low.
Since you both called for it,
you can open your cards now.
Jae Suk, you guys
need to open your cards.
- Are we revealing this card first?
- That's right.
The two of you...
It's seven!
- It's 6 and 7.
- It's 7?
- It was pretty high.
- It was.
I don't think he knew.
(Jae Suk is ahead by 1.
What is his hidden card?)
Woo Jae called for it.
You should show yours first.
- Seven.
- Seven and seven.
- It's 14.
- Woo Jae won.
(Jae Suk's total score is 14.)
(Woo Jae's hidden card needs to be
higher than 8 for him to win.)
- What is it?
- I think it's ten.
(Which player will take
all the caramels to himself?)
- Come on!
- Yours was five?
- I won.
- I think it's ten.
(Jae Suk wins.)
- He's bad at it!
- He's so bad at math!
How did he get into Hongik University?
We discard these, right?
Yes, you should discard
the cards you used.
- I'm so glad the number was low.
- All right.
He's an empty head.
He really is a pushover.
- He's a bit...
- All right, now.
(They move on to the next round.)
- All right.
- He's got this.
(Pushover Joo picked 9.)
Please check your hidden card.
- He looks relaxed.
- My card...
The line...
(The line...)
- The bottom bar.
- Oh, is that so?
(It must be hard for him to read numbers.)
That fool.
- He's so dumb.
- You actually revealed...
- It's either 6 or 9.
- the number you picked.
You fool. Gosh.
- It's either 6 or 9.
- Oh, right.
I got this.
- My hidden card...
- This is...
(It's 10!)
(Keeping a poker face)
Woo Jae should go first since he lost.
(Woo Jae starts the bet.)
(Everyone's eye is on Woo Jae
as the card on his forehead says 9.)
(Pushover Joo goes all in.)
(He bets all 35 caramels.)
- How many are they?
- That's 36 caramels.
No, I bet 35 caramels.
- He bet 35 caramels.
- I'm out.
(I'm out!)
- Gosh, you are...
- Aren't you going to play at all?
It's too low! I couldn't make a bet.
Then the numbers you'll pick later
will be high.
It will be crazy high.
He bet 35 caramels?
Let's go all in!
Hold on.
It's because...
I must bet on a big round.
- Do I have enough?
- Just put it on top.
Call.
All right. That's 36 caramels.
It could go beyond that.
Or won't it?
- All right. It's Jae Suk's turn.
- I should bet at least two.
- Gosh, this is...
- It's Jae Suk's turn.
Go for it.
- Here comes the beggar.
- It's just one round.
- Here comes the debtor.
- I can't join this round.
It's because we join after seeing the bet.
- Jae Suk can't do this either.
- I can't join the round.
- No.
- We join after seeing the bet.
- There are only two of them.
- Woo Jae.
I think he made his bet
because the number is high.
- Let's check your hidden card.
- You'll open your cards, right?
You should open yours first.
The card on your forehead is high.
- It's nine.
- What's your hidden card?
I think it's ten.
(It's 10?)
- What's your hidden card?
- I think it's ten.
(The total is 19.)
I lost. I can't beat that.
I lost.
Let's reset this round.
(Let's reset this round!)
(The chairperson resets the round.)
Let's reset this round.
(He'll reset this round?)
Let's reset it.
- All right!
- Let's reset it.
- Wait a minute.
- Please discard your cards.
- Please think again.
- We need to discard the cards.
Discard your cards.
Discard the good cards.
- You must discard them.
- Discard the good cards.
- You too.
- This is hilarious.
Okay, let's take back the caramels.
- This is what Running Man is like.
- We need to make our winning moves.
- Let's play!
Let's play!
We need to make our winning moves now.
It's all about one big shot. You know it.
Jae Suk, it's all about one big shot.
I'm waiting for that big shot.
- Let's play.
- Stick the card on your forehead.
- But this is...
- This is fun.
- It's really fun.
- Let's see.
It's fun just watching from the side.
Jong Kook can't reset
the round anymore, right?
- He can't.
- I can't.
(Checking Jae Suk's card)
Check your card.
Right. Did you check yours?
Shall we begin?
This is the important round.
- Yes.
- Woo Jae, please go first.
(Chuckling)
He is determined.
(The man with number 1
wants to win this time.)
I can't help but laugh.
- It's such a funny sight.
- This is insane.
All right.
- Shall we begin?
- Yes.
It's entertaining to watch them
from the side.
(Pushover Joo bets first.)
Look at Woo Jae.
- He can't reset the round anymore.
- No.
He is annoyed.
Ten caramels?
No.
(10 caramels? No.)
I will bet 15 caramels.
- Look at that.
- You will bet 15 caramels.
- Do that.
- He is nice.
All right.
It's your first time to bet, Ppikku.
(Ppikku enters the game
for the first time.)
That's new.
It's your first time to bet.
Why are you calling me Ppikku
before the game?
- Why are you betting?
- Did you smell something?
Here are 15 caramels.
It's Ppikku's first time to bet.
- And...
Six, eight, ten.
- Ppikku.
- Two...
- Six, eight, ten.
- Is this a race?
- I will bet 20 more caramels.
- So 35 caramels in total.
(Se Chan submitted 15 the 1st time
and 20 the 2nd time.)
The number he checked must be ten.
(Ppikku bet 35 caramels in total...)
(while maintaining a poker face.)
I fold.
- You will fold.
- Yes.
- I will fold.
- You will fold.
Woo Jae, you need to go all in.
Can I keep playing if I go all in?
- Go all in.
- Do you have 20 caramels?
I have 20 caramels.
- Two, four, six, eight, ten.
- Go all in.
Two, four, six, eight...
- I will fold.
- Okay.
(He suddenly folds.)
- Are you serious?
- You folded.
- You fool!
- Are you serious?
You can't do math.
- Come on.
- Check the cards.
- What's your card?
- You should have gone all in.
(My goodness.)
(Was it number 8?)
- What's this number?
- Why can't you do calculations?
- My goodness.
- Are you a fool?
- What's this number?
- Why can't you do calculations?
- My goodness. Why did you...
- Are you a fool?
(He folded even though he had number 9.)
(Woo Jae's total was 17.)
- Why did you...
- What's his total?
It's 17.
- Why did you fold?
- What's your total?
- Were his numbers 8 and 9?
- Yes. They were 8 and 9.
My total was 15.
His total was 15.
Why did you fold?
(Woo Jae's total: 17
Se Chan's total: 15)
Why did you fold?
- That's too bad.
- Are you a fool?
Gosh, this is sweet.
- You should have studied people.
- What is up with you?
Woo Jae.
Thank you.
This is an allowance from Woo Jae.
This is sweet.
- This is sweet.
- Let's eat it.
- My goodness.
- It's tasty.
- Woo Jae.
- Why didn't you go all in?
- Are you a fool?
- It's tasty.
I had already used 9 and 10.
- You should have taken a chance.
- It's mathematics.
(The novice gambler chickened out.)
- Hey.
- How many...
What are you really good at?
(What are you really good at?)
How many more did you need to bet?
- Shall we go?
- He is really bad at this.
- The loser will get eliminated now.
- Okay.
- The forehead.
- It will be Woo Jae or me.
I will put a number on my forehead.
Woo Jae or...
Will I be able to do well
and win some caramels this time?
(Everyone put a number on his forehead.)
My goodness.
- The hand card.
- Yes. Check the card.
(Jae Suk has 19 caramels
and Woo Jae has 20 caramels.)
Please.
- Please let me succeed this once.
- I need number nine.
- Come on.
- I can't get eliminated.
(They check the hidden card
that is important in placing a bet.)
Five caramels.
(Five caramels.)
(Ppikku bets in a daring way.)
When you are rich...
Why do I always get a small number
for my hand card?
I want to join that round.
- I will fold.
- Wait for the next round.
- Next is Jae Suk.
- As for me...
How many caramels do I have?
- He will bet caramels.
- Of course.
On top of five caramels...
- Will you bet everything?
- Yes.
- Six.
- He is serious.
I will bet 14 more caramels.
(Jae Suk submitted 5 the 1st time
and 14 the 2nd time.)
He bet 14 more caramels.
You need to bet 19 caramels.
- Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae, go all in.
You won't get to play the next game
if you fold this time.
You will have
the smallest number of caramels.
- So you have to go all in.
- No.
- No?
- If Jae Suk loses, I will survive.
- That's right.
You are good.
I will wait...
for the next round. I will fold.
- The next round?
- Yes.
- If Jae Suk wins this round,
- Is that your decision?
- you will get eliminated.
- That's right.
What happens if I fold now?
- Then Woo Jae will get eliminated.
- He will get eliminated.
(If Se Chan folds,
Jae Suk will win caramels.)
What did he do?
(What did he do?)
You should have betted caramels.
I wasn't going to bet more caramels.
What did you do? You folded, right?
- Is that possible?
- Of course.
- If you have the smallest number...
- He is right, Woo Jae.
- You folded already.
- It's up to Se Chan's decision.
(Se Chan's decision
will determine the loser.)
I will fold.
- Really?
- Will you fold?
(I will fold!)
- In that case...
- Listen.
Woo Jae got eliminated.
- No.
- I folded.
- Woo Jae got eliminated.
- Number two?
- He had number two.
- That's right.
- Was your total only 6?
- I had number 1.
- I am back in the game.
- Good job.
- Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae, go home.
- Go.
Get him a taxi.
- Go away.
- Why didn't you listen?
- You got eliminated.
- Woo Jae.
- He kept talking about mathematics.
- Pushover Joo, go away.
Woo Jae, you are unbelievable.
Woo Jae, give me your hat.
- You need to give him the hat.
- Give me the hat.
And bring me water.
Woo Jae.
- Yes?
- Would you bring me a latte?
- What?
- Latte.
- Do you need anything?
- I have water.
- Woo Jae, bring me water too.
- "Woo Jae, bring me water too."
- Latte.
Is there a latte?
This is the semifinal.
Now, it feels like...
- the real deal.
- The real gamblers have gathered.
Put a number on your forehead.
Now is the time I place a bet.
- Now is the time.
Now is the time.
I will place a bet
without checking my number.
(Checking)
I will place a bet
without checking my number.
- Woo Jae.
- You checked the number.
- What are you saying?
- I won't check my number.
- Didn't you check it?
- You checked it.
- I didn't check it.
- Go ahead.
- I'm sure you did.
- Jae Suk will go first.
I will bet five caramels.
(Jae Suk submitted 5 caramels.)
(Solemn)
- There he goes.
- He is ready to bet.
Grandpa will bet.
On top of five caramels...
(On top of five caramels...)
"All of us will die."
- I will bet ten more caramels.
- Okay.
- What?
- Let's get a new chairperson.
(Let's get a new chairperson.)
I submitted caramels in advance.
I will submit 20 caramels.
(While Pushover Joo was suffering,)
(Haha quietly submitted caramels.)
I will change the chairperson
when I enter the game.
He submitted caramels in advance
to change the chairperson.
Will you be the new chairperson?
- It's meaningless.
- I will fold.
I will fold.
(Se Chan decides to fold.)
I will fold too.
Follow me.
(Provoking)
Even if you win caramels...
- The chairperson will reset it.
- That's right. He will reset it.
There is no reason to enter
a round with the chairperson.
- Really?
- Of course.
- It's best to fold now.
- Yes.
Just let him take back his caramels.
If you have a high number,
you should keep going.
- I bet five caramels already.
- Then you should keep going.
- We have a new chairperson now.
- Hey!
I will change the chairperson.
- I bet five caramels already.
- Then you should keep going.
- We have a new chairperson now.
- Hey!
(They have a new chairperson now.)
- Give it to me.
- This is great.
I will bet ten caramels.
- Bring it.
- I placed a bet.
- Hey.
- Good timing.
We are on the same side!
- Let's go.
- Haha.
You little...
Why are you doing this to me today?
- What did I do wrong?
- It's not like that.
Tell me one thing.
What did I do wrong?
- You were too boastful.
- What?
I didn't like your boastful tone.
- Good job.
- For goodness' sake.
He only comes after me.
- Good job.
- Do you only have eyes for me?
I am set.
- Good job. Nice timing.
- Sit down.
How dare you?
- Nice timing.
- I am the chairperson.
Let's reveal the numbers.
Okay.
It's a match between Haha and Jae Suk.
- Let's reveal the numbers.
- I will check the forehead card.
- The number is big.
- Is it big?
Yes.
It's big.
His number is too small.
His hidden card might show a big number.
The hand card.
(The hidden card might make a difference.)
One, two, three.
Take the caramels.
Two, three.
- Take the caramels.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk won.)
(Haha lost more hair.)
I did it.
It's over.
What?
It's the rule. Sit down, old man.
You little punk. That's no way to behave!
- You are such an old fossil.
- I will get back at you.
- Let's go.
- I am so annoyed.
He is so annoying!
What is up with you today?
- It's just that I like you.
- Hey.
- He drives me crazy.
- Hey,
- put a card on your forehead.
- Let's smile.
- Let's smile, okay?
This is no joke.
- Let's smile.
Let's smile.
(They reveal the forehead card
with a smile.)
Smile as you play the game.
- Let's see.
- The hand card.
Haha is the worst at this game.
- Seriously.
- I don't know why he criticized me.
For goodness' sake.
(Jong Kook's hidden card is number 1.)
What is up with my luck?
(Se Chan, the chairperson,)
- You know...
- I will bet ten caramels.
(bets 10 caramels.)
(Chairperson Yang bets freely
since he can reset the round.)
Vroom.
(Solemn)
- Will you change the chairperson?
- Hold on.
I will change the chairperson.
(Will you change the chairperson?)
- Bet as much as you want.
- That's good.
- Really?
Suk Jin became the new chairperson.
Bring it.
What did I do wrong?
- Suk Jin.
- Bring it.
I thought you were my gganbu.
- Your boastful self is an eyesore.
- I thought you were my gganbu.
Bring it.
- Unbelievable.
- Listen.
I still have caramels.
- You really brought a latte.
- Latte.
Did he bring a latte?
You really brought a latte.
- Yes. It's a latte.
- Thank you.
Hey, kid. Bring me patbingsu.
(Kid?)
Hey.
Here is a tip.
(When Haha throws a caramel,)
(Kid Joo picks it up without hesitation.)
Woo Jae, I am sorry.
It's tasty.
How many caramels are you betting?
I am betting ten more caramels.
- Ten more caramels?
- Yes.
My goodness.
(He hesitates
because Haha's forehead card is 10.)
Bring it on.
- Will you place a bet?
- Yes.
Let's see the numbers.
I have no other choice.
I think I will lose.
There is a big difference.
Your number was one.
Se Chan.
It was one.
- My other number was ten.
- Here.
(Se Chan trusted his hidden card,
but his forehead card was one.)
It was a good match.
Here. It was a good match.
Good job.
- Is the total 15?
- He did well.
With number ten, he was bound to win.
Hey, kid.
(Take this.)
Would you like condensed milk
or regular milk with your patbingsu?
- What?
- This won't do.
- Shall we begin?
- Hey!
What are you doing?
Let me join the game.
He is a thief!
- What?
- What do you mean, "What?"
It's good as long as you don't get caught.
He got caught.
Did he get caught? Then he is a thief.
Let's go.
How did I get ten?
(Both of them have number 10!)
Let's go.
(Even Se Chan has 10!)
(3 people's forehead cards
show number 10.)
The numbers aren't very big today.
This will be fun.
It's your turn.
(Everywhere he looks,)
(there is number 10.)
(He can't help but laugh.)
He is like an old man
you see in a cartoon.
(He just laughs.)
All right.
Let's go.
(The weak gambler goes first.)
- Five caramels.
- Will he go all in?
It has begun.
Five caramels.
I will go all in.
(He goes all in even after seeing
Jong Kook and Se Chan's number 10!)
- He will fold.
- I will fold.
Will he bet caramels?
I will fold.
Se Chan, will you place a bet?
You should.
No. I will fold.
You should have placed a bet.
(He checks his forehead card.)
- What's your total?
- Why did you...
- Hey.
- What's your total?
It's 17.
(Se Chan's total is 17.)
What was my number?
(Jae Suk checks his card as well.)
- Your total is higher, right?
- Hey.
All 3 of you had 10.
- Really?
- What was your hand card?
Jae Suk, what was it?
- The hand card.
- I can't tell you that.
His total must be smaller than yours.
My hand card has a small number.
This is driving me crazy.
You know, it's annoying...
that I can't join the game.
(Regardless of Suk Jin's wait,
the game continues.)
I will enjoy the caramels.
He went all in,
so Suk Jin should join the game.
- Did he go all in?
- Suk Jin should join the game.
- I will join the game.
Se Chan went bankrupt.
You guys are weak.
The real gambler is here.
It has been a while since I played cards.
He was desperate to play this game.
I was about to go crazy.
He waited until you guys went quiet.
I was full of regrets.
I waited all day long to play this game.
It wasn't even about the shoot.
He wanted to play this game.
Old man, you got a haircut.
- Yes.
- I see.
- He shaved his head.
- Let's begin.
Put a card on your forehead.
Let's begin.
All right.
- I should be a chairperson.
- Chairperson.
You can't change the chairperson now.
Let's begin.
(Woo Jae became the chairperson
for the fair game.)
Don't do that now.
The winner will become
the Card Shark of the Year.
- The Card Shark of the Year.
I really want that title.
Let's go.
(Jong Kook, Jae Suk, Haha, and Suk Jin)
I waited a long time.
One caramel.
I will bet five caramels on top of that.
He is cool.
One, two, three, four, and five.
- "And five."
- I will fold.
Me too.
(Haha gives up as well.)
You guys are weak.
My hand card had a small number.
Is this all you can do?
That wasn't a fun round.
Is it a good idea to show the cards?
- It doesn't matter.
- All right then.
His numbers were 5 and 4.
- They were 5 and 4.
- Those numbers are out.
He won three caramels.
It doesn't matter.
Suk Jin, you should give away
one caramel.
He won three caramels.
Kid, eat one.
Okay. Let's begin.
He won two caramels.
He gave away one.
You have to wait for the right time.
(The second set of forehead cards
is revealed.)
Let's see.
Do I bet first?
Yes. I will bet three caramels.
Maybe I should bet five caramels.
- Five.
- Bet more caramels.
Bet more caramels
to liven up the atmosphere.
- I just feel bad for you.
- Bet more caramels.
Okay. Ten.
Two, four, six, eight, ten.
- Ten caramels.
- Okay.
(He bets 10 caramels.)
- Jong Kook.
- I will fold.
- I will fold too.
- Me too.
It was a good round.
- I will fold too.
- Me too.
It was a good round.
(Did everyone fold this time as well?)
- Hey.
- My numbers were too low.
(The second game was so boring
that it almost got edited out.)
Bet enough caramels
to liven up the atmosphere.
Aren't you going to place a bet?
- He really wanted to play the game.
- Hey.
Why did you fold when my number was three?
Go.
(It's time to compete.)
I am ready.
- I won't check the hidden card.
- All right.
- I won't check it.
- All right. Don't do it.
All right.
(He puts a card on his forehead.)
Don't look at it.
- Don't do that.
- Won't you check it?
Check the hidden card.
Won't you check it?
I won't check it either.
All right. I won't check it.
- Put it in front of you.
- I...
I will check it.
- I won't check it either.
- I won't check it.
- I will check it later.
- Put it down afterward.
All right.
- Okay.
- I won't check it either.
I won't check it. I will check it later.
Put it down afterward.
- I won't check it either.
- It just weakens your resolve.
Jae Suk will bet first.
- Jae Suk.
- Okay.
All right.
(Jae Suk submitted 1 caramel.)
On top of that, I will go all in.
Why would you do that?
Sit back if you aren't going to go all in.
What's your forehead number? Let's see.
Did you check your hidden card?
No, I didn't.
- Mister, chicken out if you want.
- Yes.
Go all in.
This is your last chance.
- Chicken out if you want.
- Do that.
- Why would you check that?
- You can't do that.
- Chicken out if you want.
- Do that.
(Taking a peek)
You can't do that.
That was the condition.
- That was the condition.
- Why did you look?
- You said you won't look.
- That was the condition.
- Give me a break.
- Why did you look?
- Give me a break. It's my choice.
- That was the condition.
- That's ridiculous.
- You can't do that.
- I won't place a bet.
- Why did you look?
- Hey.
- I won't place a bet.
- Think about it.
- Seriously.
Why did you look?
Who places a bet
without checking the card?
- Why did you look?
- Only a fool would do that!
You promised to play the game
without checking the card.
Don't corner him like that.
You won't look cool.
- I don't care about that.
- Suk Jin.
This game involves two cards!
I went all in because you said
you won't check the card.
Just fold then.
- For goodness' sake.
- All right. Take out the caramels.
Is this mustache fake?
What are you doing?
For goodness' sake.
I can't believe you.
What?
Don't check the card.
Be cool and just place a bet.
- Why would you check the card?
- That's the real match.
He checked the card.
I didn't check it.
I swear that I didn't check it.
I will make a decision based on
their reaction to the card.
- Okay.
- No. Show me the card.
Come here.
The two of you placed a bet, right?
- Stay there.
- Listen.
Stay there. I will show you the card.
- Okay.
- You can't show anyone else.
I bet 34 caramels.
If you keep getting angry,
I won't play the game.
Don't be ridiculous.
You guys are the absolute worst.
Mister.
Listen.
Mister, did you say
that you won't check the card?
- Yes, I did.
- Then you shouldn't check the card.
- You said it yourself.
- So I made a compromise.
I will make a decision based on
their reaction to the card.
- Come on.
- Mister.
You said it yourself.
- I swear that I didn't check it.
- Okay.
Listen to me.
- I swear that I didn't check it.
- Okay.
(What?)
Mister.
- Whatever. I will place a bet.
- You said it yourself.
I will go all in.
- I placed my bet.
- Let's go.
I bet more caramels.
Didn't you check your card?
- I really didn't.
- Jae Suk.
You saw my number, right?
- Hold on.
- Suk Jin.
Why did you show me?
(He belatedly realized
that he showed everyone.)
Why did you show everyone?
Seriously. Why did you show everyone?
- Everyone saw it.
- Seriously.
He was supposed to show us only.
- I didn't see it.
- Everyone saw it.
He was supposed to show us only.
- You saw it, right?
- No.
- I didn't see it.
- Everyone saw it.
Why did you show me?
I must be insane.
I doubted my eyes.
Why did you show me?
Why did you see it, you punk?
What kind of a question is that?
You are the one who showed me.
Why did you see it?
You showed me.
You should have closed your eyes!
That makes no sense.
- We should have closed our eyes?
- Come on.
- Why did you show us?
- I don't know.
You guys shouldn't place a bet.
I will place a bet.
Will you place a bet?
- Didn't you check your card?
- No.
This is driving me crazy.
- Place a bet.
- I would be strange...
- if I don't go all in.
- That's right.
They are set.
There is someone who went all in
after revealing his card.
Seriously.
That's impressive.
I checked my hidden card.
- Let's check the forehead cards.
- The forehead cards.
The number
on your forehead card is too big.
- What's mine?
- Eight?
- My number is 8.
- Mine is 8 too. I didn't check.
- I didn't check either.
- I didn't check.
- Wait.
- Their numbers are too big.
You are out.
- Why?
- My number is eight.
- No.
- Suk Jin, you are out.
No. He doesn't know his number.
- He doesn't know.
- He checked his card.
No. He doesn't know yet.
Suk Jin's total is five. Wait.
His number is eight.
- Jong Kook.
- We should reveal them together.
You should go first.
- We are in the same position.
- That's right.
- That will be more fun.
- We should reveal them together.
- One...
- Shall we reveal them together?
- One, two, three.
- One, two, three. Ten!
(Who will win and become
the Card Shark of the Year?)
- Two, three.
- Ten!
- I won!
- It's 6.
- It's 8.
- Two, three.
- Two, three. Ten!
(Haha won.)
- It's 6.
- It's 8.
My total is 14.
- It's 10.
- Your total is 13.
That was close.
That was incredible.
(Haha had a dramatic victory.)
I should have picked this card.
Is it over?
Haha's winning move was successful.
He placed first.
Haha placed first.
With 1 caramel, Woo Jae placed 2nd.
- What?
- Why?
- Did he place second?
They went all in.
They went all in,
but you have one caramel.
I can't believe it! I placed second!
- You have one caramel.
- I will get the prize.
- Right?
- I didn't want to go all in.
I have two in my bag.
- You said you'd go all in.
- You went all in.
(You said you'd go all in.)
All right. What?
We prepared gold bars
for 1st place and 2nd place.
(The winners get gold bars?)
- Real gold bars?
- You guys...
Go ahead and open the cases.
You're pretty good at games.
Gold is expensive these days.
- My gosh.
- Darn it.
(Red bean jelly bars)
- Why?
- What?
- I really want to eat this.
This is sweet red bean jelly.
I will look like a real old man
if I hold this in my costume.
Suk Jin likes it.
(Yoom)
And Haha will...
get to choose a member
to get a penalty today.
All right.
Hey.
Beggar.
(Beggar!)
- You.
- What?
- Aren't you Korean?
- Yes.
(The penalty is
getting hit by a wet tissue.)
(He throws wet tissues
as hard as he hates Se Chan.)
That's hard.
Jong Kook is serious about this.
(The mischievous card sharks
love stuff like this.)
- Here I go.
- Woo Jae.
(Next up is Pushover Joo.)
- Okay.
- Gosh, what was that?
You can't do anything right.
- What is it you're good at?
- You sit there too.
- I can't let this slide.
- There's nothing...
- you can do.
- Sit here.
- Nothing's going right for me.
- I know.
This looks perfect for you.
(Slapping)
You look cute.
He wants you to keep your mouth shut.
After preying on the pushover like that,
they are seeking to revive
the Card Shark Association.
What will happen
to the Card Shark Association then?
(What will happen
to the Card Shark Association then?)
(They want to pat Seok Sam...)
(as much as they love him.)
(We can't take it anymore.)
(A special episode
for Seok Sam to vent his spite)
(Seok Sam's backup, M.O.M)
(A meeting is finally made between
Running Man and "How Do You Play?")
(What's Suk Jin's date of birth?)
(An unprecedented battle...)
(to take Ji Suk Jin)
(Is he Ji Seok Sam?)
(Or is he Byeollu-Ji?)
(Of Ji Suk Jin)
(By Ji Suk Jin)
(For Ji Suk Jin)
Hey, our viewers might believe that.
(As Ji Wishes)