- Hello.
- Hey.
This is Hyung In's first day,
so I'll try hard today.
Hyung In, why am I a slave
from the beginning?
We have three birthday people
in August.
(The table is loaded with a feast
for the members' birthdays.)
- Should I scoop rice?
- Here?
- Should we spoon-feed them?
- Yes.
- Feed them?
- Spoon-feed them?
- It's not like...
- My gosh.
In the Joseon Dynasty...
- It's soup. It looks delicious.
- Even in the Joseon Dynasty,
- they ate things by themselves.
- I know.
This is kimchi.
- Look at So Bal.
- So Bal.
I can tell you rarely do this.
- No, this is hard.
- This is really cool.
- Scrape it.
- You should scrape the bottom.
It must be delicious.
- It does look delicious.
- By the way,
slaves don't get to eat a lot.
Once the aristocrats get here,
I'll put on a show with the kimchi.
(Yoom)
Kimchi tastes good
when it's cut by hand.
- Se Chan, you should do this.
- It's so tasty.
Suk Jin, you can't eat it.
It's for the aristocrats.
They don't know
how many pieces we had.
I'll tell them.
Jong Kook, we should roll him
in a straw mat and beat him up.
I know.
- No, we need two.
- Se Chan.
- Is it good?
- Yes. No one will know. Eat.
You know what?
The aristocrats should taste...
the kimchi shredded by Slave Yang.
I'll do that for them later.
- Here.
- I'll shred it for them.
- All right.
- No one will know.
- Just eat.
- They can't tell?
- Then I should eat.
- They wouldn't know.
Who cooked this?
- Right.
- Gosh, this is so good.
The jeon is delicious.
The aristocrats are here.
- They're here.
- Gosh.
- You're here.
- Hello.
- How are you?
You all work hard.
Why are you wearing sunglasses
in a historical play?
- Go away, Seok Sam.
- Who are you?
- I'm just...
- Don't be silly and go away.
I'm serving the rice.
- Seok Sam, stop it and go away.
- This is...
- I mean...
- I'm telling you again.
The Joseon Dynasty...
had a caste system.
- Okay.
- Hey!
How dare you open the lid?
Go away.
- All right.
- We have gifts for the aristocrats.
- Is it money?
- It's coins.
You can give the coins
to slaves who work hard...
or make them fight for the coins.
You can use them as you please.
Will the aristocrats
make us fight? My goodness.
But the coins will be important
in today's race.
You should remember that
when you distribute the coins.
All right. Today is Hyung In's
first day as the Team Producer.
- Congratulations.
- So I texted...
- Hyung In earlier.
- What did you tell her?
I said I would make her...
feel anxious during her first shoot.
- Why would you do that?
- I'll mess things up.
Why would you do that, sir?
- Because...
- He will mess things up.
I said this on purpose. "Hyung In,
for our first shoot,"
"I'll have things my own way
without listening to you."
How dare you...
How dare you stand
between the aristocrats?
- She's right about that.
- You're a slave.
- Go away.
- I got hit in the back of my head.
- Get away from me.
- Come over here.
- Come here.
- Go.
- You...
Aren't you supposed to stand here?
- We have a caste system now.
- It's a caste system.
- Do you not know the caste system?
- The caste system!
- She even hit him.
- You just bought your class.
- What did you say?
- You bought it with money.
Bought it with money?
Okay. I'll work hard and buy one.
So I told Hyung In...
- that I would be reckless.
- Reckless?
"The shoot will go well
only when you feel comfortable."
- This is what she said.
- Really?
So I got really upset.
You're the one who's being anxious.
- He's the one who's suffering.
- I found it really upsetting.
He hates responses like that.
I hate it so much.
- My gosh.
- When she's being calm.
- I know.
- He wants her to be mad.
It's no fun to tease her.
Please enjoy the birthday party now.
- Let's enjoy the feast.
- Please enjoy the food.
- All right. Don't come up.
- First, eat your food.
- We have many delicious dishes.
- Go away.
- Don't come up.
- Please go ahead.
Hello, sir.
- I heard you got enteritis.
- We have many dishes here.
The sun is setting.
Hey, go away.
- You, go away.
- Mr. Haha,
- please take off your sunglasses.
- Jong Kook.
Drag him down.
- I want to eat.
- Bring him.
Drag him down.
- Hey, wait.
- Ssaebssaeb.
- Can't you pick up on the cues?
- Lift his legs.
- Where are your shoes?
- Bring him.
Get up.
Hey, get up.
(Slave Jeon suddenly
makes a deep bow.)
- Where are my shoes?
- Your shoes.
- Let's sit then.
- Get up.
How many bows are you making?
I'm performing an ancestral rite.
All right then.
- The food looks great.
- Kimchi.
(It's time to taste the dishes made
with the slaves' sweat and blood.)
It's really good.
Gosh, I haven't
tried this in a while.
The airplane is taking off.
Here it comes.
It's an airplane.
(It's an airplane of rice cake.)
Is there an airplane?
- Open up.
- Wright brothers weren't born yet.
(Sticking out his tongue)
- What are you doing now?
- By the way,
is he So Min's son?
- There's nothing good for you.
- Why don't we...
I'll give you just one dish.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes.
- Come and massage my shoulders.
- That sounds great.
- This is my spot.
- Gosh. I get it.
- Go over there.
- Wait.
I'm serving her now.
Why do you meddle in?
(Slave Ji wants to join them.)
You might choke.
You look like a character
from an animation movie.
I don't want you
to choke on the food.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes.
- Come and massage my shoulders.
- That sounds great.
(Slave Kim is confident
in using his strength.)
- That's what I'm good at.
- All right.
You know it well.
I'm serving her now.
This feels good. A little lower.
- A little lower?
- Yes.
(He presses the shoulder blades hard
to get some coins.)
- Here?
- It's coming out.
- It's right there.
- This is it.
- That's it.
So this is it.
- Jong Kook, here.
- Oh, dear.
- Thank you so much, sir.
- I couldn't help it.
What are you doing? Wait.
(Slave Ji starts
to massage him abruptly.)
Hey.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes.
- Drag him out.
- Drag him out?
The thing is, Seok Sam is...
very enthusiastic,
but he doesn't know what to do.
Gosh, I'm so upset.
You want this?
- Seok Sam.
- Yes.
Since it is our birthday,
I want you to go over there...
and dance for us.
Yes, sir.
Seok Sam, I just want you
to try your best.
I like Seok Sam.
Look at me
(Embarrassed)
What is he doing?
As if I'm a flower
blooming in winter
- Hey. Seok Sam.
- Please look at me
- Here comes Arari
- Not like that.
The thing you did...
when you were in the military.
Dancing Bear.
What? Is that a thing?
- What's that?
- Really?
- Back then...
- You should do that.
That's what his superior called him.
"Hey, Dancing Bear."
"Yes, sir. Corporal Dancing Bear."
A bear?
(Corporal Dancing Bear)
Dancing Bear.
- What's that?
- This is what I did.
Anywhere, anytime.
Once his superior called him...
"Hey, Dancing Bear."
"Yes, sir. Corporal Dancing Bear."
(He starts dancing right away.)
- That's real.
- I did the dancing.
- That's nice.
- I like that.
- I do like that.
- It looks nice.
I love it.
- So...
- My gosh. Thank you so much.
- I want to use my strength.
- Thank you, sir.
- Jong Kook is...
- All right then.
- You should sit and eat now.
- Have a seat and eat.
- Shall we?
We should eat when we're told so.
- Seok Sam.
- There's no bowl.
Come and sing for us.
Gosh, it's hot.
(Gosh, it's hot.)
It's really hot.
Seok Sam.
Stop making a fuss.
Look at you. I thought I had
no customers at my tavern today.
I guess that's because you were
having a birthday party here.
Gosh, Mr. Se Chan.
Mr. Jong Kook,
why did you not call me?
- Me?
- I don't know you.
Yes, you do. You are my darling.
- Darling?
- Of course, you know me.
- Hey, you...
- Hey.
You have Slave Jeon.
(Slave Yang's date,
Slave Jeon steps up.)
No, wait.
(Clanging)
Did you call me darling?
Honey, who is this woman?
- "Honey?" Excuse me, ma'am.
- My gosh.
(Slave Yang was dating two women
before he knew it.)
That's a strange woman.
- Let me tell you why I'm here.
- Okay.
I'm known to be good
at card readings in this village.
I will make it cheap,
so let me know if you want
to have your fortunes read.
- So Min likes stuff like this.
- Right.
I have one coin.
So Min would want to ask her
about her love life.
Read So Min's fortunes first.
Okay.
- Bring one to me.
- Okay.
All right. First...
What do you want to know?
Will I be able to start
seeing someone within this year?
If you'll be seeing
someone within this year?
- I don't think it can happen.
- Let me see.
Here's what you do.
Pick two cards.
(The two cards
will decide her destiny.)
Two cards?
Don't open them yet.
- Is this how it works?
- She picks the cards.
All right. You picked two cards.
Let me see.
- Why are the cards...
- All right.
Let me tell you what these mean.
About your love life...
Things will work out well.
You'll meet someone
within this year.
The bird will bring you good news.
- I see.
- She seems really good.
The bird will bring me good news.
It will bring you good news.
And this is about what he's like.
He's quite playful.
You're likely to meet
someone very playful.
Playful?
(If he's playful...)
It's Yang Se Chan!
Yang Se Chan is my darling.
I don't even know you.
Why would you say that?
What are you talking about?
We went to Jeju Island together.
(What are you talking about?
We went to Jeju Island together.)
I knew it!
- What?
- I can't believe this.
That's her.
She's the one.
Who wants to go next?
- I want to do it.
- Se Chan?
- Ask her about our compatibility.
- All right.
Sit next to him.
Make yourself comfortable.
All right.
You will pick one card each.
Don't open the cards yet.
Just pick one.
- I pick this.
- This one.
(They carefully pick one card each.)
Pick one.
Good.
- So here's the first card.
- I picked it.
- The image you have about So Min.
- Her image.
And the card you picked shows
the image you have about my darling.
Is this real?
- I think she's real.
- I see.
- The image you have about So Min.
- Her image.
(What does So Min mean to Se Chan?)
What is it?
Is it dung?
(Dung)
Hey!
Am I dung to you?
- He thinks you're dung.
- Am I dung?
- Why?
- What is it?
- No, wait.
- Am I dung?
- Am I dung to you?
- It's a dung card.
- He thinks of me as dung.
- I didn't see this coming.
I picked a poop card.
- Wait. You might've picked one too.
- I said you weren't for each other.
- Poop in dreams means good luck.
- Exactly.
- Let's see what she thinks of him.
- She might've picked a poop card.
(What could Se Chan mean to So Min?)
- It's a poop card!
- My gosh!
(A poop card next to a poop card)
- And it's a double junk card.
- It's a double junk card.
- She picked a poop card too.
- We didn't plan this.
- We both picked a poop card.
- Unbelievable. Another poop card?
(It means
they're meant for each other.)
She thinks of you as poop
more than you do.
(She thinks even more badly of him.)
You think she's a bad one...
- while she thinks you're the worst.
- What are the odds?
- This is unbelievable.
- I think she's a bad one,
- and she thinks I'm the worst?
- You're the worst.
- It's so hard to believe.
- It's unbelievable.
I told you, I have spiritual power.
- Please sit here.
- Okay. I'll try it.
The poop cards made Ji Hyo
believe her.
- I got offered a role.
- You got offered a role?
- Pick two cards.
- Okay.
- This one.
- Good.
- And this one.
- Okay.
Here we go
- It's a September card.
- It's a blue ribbon card.
First, this card symbolizes
a drink or a drinking party.
Also, if you think of the time,
it means an evening or a night.
(A chrysanthemum card means
a drink and a night.)
So you'd be at an advantage if you
shoot a movie or a drama at night.
- Hey, you have a shoot tonight.
- Today is the day, Ji Hyo.
- Exactly. It brings you good luck.
- A night shoot?
- It tells me you're a night owl.
- Yes.
Who's next?
Does anyone else have a question?
- Seok Sam, why don't you try it?
- Okay.
Seok Sam, you should ask
about your life span.
Right, his life span or health.
When will I die?
- When will you die?
- Yes.
Seok Sam, don't ask her about that.
Let's check his life span.
- Please pick one card.
- Okay.
No. You shouldn't open it yet.
Let me look at the card you picked.
I think she's a real fortune teller.
- She must be a real fortune teller.
- Is this for real?
- Here we go
(December, rain)
You chose a rain card.
This card means...
- December. I see.
- Yes, it's a December card.
- This card symbolizes a new guest.
- What?
I think that the Grim Reaper will
pay you a visit.
- The guest must be the Grim Reaper.
- You mean, this year?
- You mean he'll die in December?
- When will that be?
- Seok Sam.
- It's only a few months away.
The Grim Reaper could visit you
within this month.
- There may be someone...
- Just don't follow the Grim Reaper.
- hidden around you.
- Don't follow the Grim Reaper.
- I know.
- Exactly.
Does it have something to do
with the show?
Right.
What is it?
(Does it have something to do
with today's episode?)
- The King's command!
- What is he doing?
What is it?
- What is the King's command?
- What is it?
"Whatever Penalty Project?"
- "Whatever Penalty Project."
- We just got here.
We just got here.
Why must we get a penalty?
- A penalty?
- Is it a long-term project?
- Yes.
- What is this?
Today,
we'll begin a four-week project...
with legendary penalties
on the line.
(The Running Man penalties
with a long history)
(From bungee jumping
with no cord...)
(The scariest swing in the world,
the Nevis Swing)
(To the 90-degree roller coaster...)
(in Taiwan that's called
the roller coaster to purgatory)
- This is so unexpected.
- It's a four-week project?
- Hyung In, I thought better of you.
- I wonder what the penalties are.
You will receive penalty stickers
throughout the four-week race.
- Two of you will get a penalty.
- Two of us?
- Not 1, but 2?
- Oh, man.
The members to get a penalty are
those with the most stickers...
and one of the remaining members...
except for the member
with the least penalty stickers.
- Since it's a legendary penalty,
- It must be intense.
we'll receive recommendations
from the viewers...
for the next two weeks.
We'll give you a few examples.
- Activities we can do in Korea...
- What is it?
- First, it's a penalty...
- Is it the sky bicycle?
- that will make you feel fear.
- What is that?
- It's the sky bicycle.
(The scariest penalty that can
give you an adrenaline rush)
- Riding a bicycle in the air?
- Yes, riding a bicycle...
- in the air 50m above the ground.
- Did you say 150m?
- You ride a bicycle on a rope.
- It's suspended in the air.
- Why would you ride it on a rope?
- What's that?
- I can never do that.
- It makes no sense.
- Here's the second example.
- What's that?
It's an upgraded water slide jump.
- Should I jump?
- Oh, that?
You slide down a water slide
and fall from 7m into the water.
- You fall into the water?
- Yes, and the pool is 3m deep.
- Is that a water slide in Korea?
- Yes.
- Hyung In... I mean...
- I saw that on social media.
- I thought she was a nice person.
- What's wrong with her?
Next up is the sky glider
that enables you to fly in the air.
You glide at a height of 125m
above the ground...
at a speed of 80km per hour.
- Look at Haha. He's already scared.
- I don't understand.
- What's her problem?
- Oh, it's suspended in the air.
- You should've discussed it.
- Why did you decide on your own?
She's crueler than Bo Pil.
Also, there's a penalty
that can be a hassle.
- That would be better.
- Yes, that'd be better.
It's to go to Hwacheon
in Gangwon Province...
and mine gold dust
for the other members.
- Come on. That's ridiculous.
- Mining gold dust?
(They've mined gold dust
eight years ago in Australia.)
- I've tried it before.
- But in Korea...
- There's no gold dust in Korea.
- I couldn't find any gold dust.
- What's gold dust?
- I've tried it before.
- Gold. It means mining gold.
- But in Korea...
- Gold?
- I couldn't find any gold dust.
- It's real gold, right?
- I couldn't find any.
- Are you sure we can find gold?
- Yes. We've done the research.
- So we can find gold dust?
- But it's only an example.
If the viewers suggest better ideas,
we'll choose one of them.
The viewers will find something
even more intense than those.
- We might walk into a fire pit.
- Let's do something easier.
- Let's go with the Nevis Swing.
- What's wrong with them?
- Hey, you don't have to do this.
- Hey, this is...
- She must have lost her mind.
- This is too much.
Today's race is
Whatever Penalty Project, Part One,
Ghostly War of Coins.
You have to get
as many coins as you can...
- to increase your winning chance.
- Got it.
Two of the losers will be given
penalty stickers.
- Let's move to the first mission.
- Okay.
Hyung In, why are you doing this
to us? Are you serious?
I felt dizzy for a moment.
I feel suffocated.
I can never do that.
Gosh, those penalties...
I'd rather mine gold dust.
Getting tanned would be better.
It scares me too much.
Hey, would you go with
the Nevis Swing again?
I'd rather choose the Nevis Swing.
- Really?
- Yes.
Yesterday, I watched the episode
where you rode it.
You should ride it.
- I strongly recommend it.
- No, I would never ride it.
- You should...
- Seok Sam.
You see... Lord Yoo.
My gosh.
Lord Yoo, would you choose
the Nevis Swing or bungee jumping?
Well... I hate both.
We thought the aristocrats would
give the slaves some coins.
- They didn't give us any coins.
- We would never do that.
- We were wrong.
- Come on.
- What do you take them for?
- What are you talking about?
- Don't you know how they can be?
- What do you take us for?
I'll just...
- run away.
- Making money isn't easy.
- I'll run away.
- I gave out the most among us.
- They didn't give out any coins.
- I gave them a few coins.
But you're too stingy.
Besides, you revealed
how intense our penalty could be.
- They'll be even more stingy.
- That's right.
- Of course.
- Okay.
- What should we do to get a coin?
- Give him a coin.
(Right then)
My gosh. That scared me.
(Everyone is
scared out of their wits.)
(Two mysterious men came out
through the wall.)
- Don't come near me.
- My gosh.
- That was scary.
- They scared the life out of me.
(The mysterious shadows
slowly approach the members.)
Are you Ji Suk Jin
from Running Village?
Yes, that's me.
Your time has come.
- I've come for you.
- Me?
(Suk Jin's time has come to die?)
- His time has come.
- Wait.
I'm not ready yet.
(The Grim Reaper gives him
something.)
(Joseon Book of Fate)
(The book where the life span
of people in Joseon is written)
- What's going on?
- For real?
- He said your time had come.
- Suk Jin.
- But...
- Are you leaving?
I guess so.
- Where are you going?
- "Ji Suk Jin..."
I guess I'm going to die at 8:50 p.m.
(Ji Suk Jin's life ends
at 8:50 p.m.)
- Are they Grim Reapers?
- I think so.
- She said he would die soon.
- I guess I'm going to die.
The fortune teller said
I would die soon.
But I'm not ready yet...
- I thought he was Kim Joon Hyun.
- He startled me.
- I thought he was Kang Ho Dong.
- That was scary.
- It was okay when it was dark here.
- The fortune teller said it too.
They must be embarrassed
since it's bright now.
- They look cute under the light.
- Under the light...
- I can tell who they are.
- Joon Hyun.
Their job is to eliminate
the members who are about to die.
- Suk Jin is going to die soon...
- Let's save him. We'll save him.
- Why?
- Please save me.
The time you just checked
in the book is...
- It was 8:50 p.m.
- the time when you get eliminated.
- What time is it now?
- Will he get eliminated?
It's 8:03 p.m. right now.
- I still have 47 minutes left.
- Yes.
The other members' times of death
have also been decided.
The anger disorder that has been
going around Running Village...
influenced each member's life span
greatly.
The anger disorder?
(Estimated time of elimination:
10 p.m.)
(Slave Ji was picked on
even from the opening.)
(Estimated time of elimination:
9:50 p.m.)
(He had to hold back his anger
even when he was hit in the head.)
(Estimated time of elimination:
9:30 p.m.)
(His life span was shortened
whenever he held back his anger.)
Oh, that's why my life span was
shortened?
Jae Suk, I bet you'll live long.
- I guess I'll live long.
- So will Ji Hyo.
- I'll live long too.
- Now...
The time of death is written
in each member's book.
(Each member's life span is written
in the Book of Fate.)
When your time comes, you get
eliminated and become a ghost.
(When the time comes, the member is
eliminated and becomes a ghost.)
You have to go and find your book
where your time of death is written.
The books are hidden
in two different places.
It's scary.
It's too scary for me to go alone.
Also, there are coins
hidden in different places.
- You can keep the coins you find.
- I'm worried.
You'll be divided into teams
to search for the books.
- I'm relieved.
- The members of the first team...
are Jae Suk and So Min.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are
on the second team.
I went into the Haunted Hospital
with So Min.
Both of us were so scared.
All right.
So Min, let's go.
- Jong Kook, let's go.
- Okay.
I really hate things like this.
I'm worried.
Gosh. I hate this the most.
Can I take it out?
Gosh. It looks scary
now that it's dark outside.
(It looked peaceful during the day.)
- Gosh. I'm scared.
- Oh, man.
- This is driving me nuts.
- All right.
We have to go out there.
We just have to find our books,
right?
Correct.
We'll see them anyway.
I'm sorry,
but am I allowed to hit the ghosts?
How should we find the books
when it's so dark?
There must be a way.
(They can't come back
until they find their books.)
There will probably be some ghosts
around the thatched cottages...
reading a book or something.
We should check if it's ours.
This is why
the staff members hate you.
- Why?
- Don't predict what will happen.
- It's not like that.
- Think of the staff members.
We have to think
about what we might face.
- Don't go too far.
- That's what they hate.
- You see the red light, right?
- We should go and check it.
- What? Let's go over there.
- Oh, gosh. That looks so scary.
I'm sure
we can find our books there.
- Look at that. It's so red.
- Let's check it out.
- It's so red.
- But we...
- Hey, Ji Hyo, how could you...
Jae Suk, let's go together.
- Let's go.
- Let's go and check it out.
- Gosh.
- We don't know where our books are.
- Let's go.
- Look at the red light.
I don't think I can go in there.
Hurry up, guys.
Hey, this is the place...
- The props are so scary.
- It's a shaman's shrine.
I'm afraid something might come out.
- What is he doing?
- What?
- He thinks he's a tour guide.
- There's a shrine...
- Why is he acting up?
- It's not like that.
- That's a shrine.
- What?
This looks so creepy.
- Hurry up and come up.
- My shoelace got untied.
- So Min, what's wrong with you?
- Jae Suk.
- Is it because of the disease?
- So Min, hurry up.
- I'm not lying. My throat is...
- I can't see. I need a flashlight.
(Screaming)
- You scared me. What's going on?
- What's wrong with you?
- What was that about?
- I'm sorry.
(Screaming)
- You jerk!
- Hey.
- Now, let's go.
- I feel dizzy.
- Let's go.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
Why did you curse at him?
- Hey, Ji Hyo, why...
- Gosh, you. Don't do that again.
- Let's go.
- Ji Hyo, why would you curse?
- Don't do that. I'm warning you.
- All right. Come on.
- I hate him.
- Hurry up.
- He must be out of his mind.
- What's his problem?
- My gosh.
I hear music.
Why? What is it?
(Meanwhile, it's being broadcast
live for the other members.)
- Jong Kook is...
- What's this? Shall I take it off?
Jong Kook is pretending
he's enjoying it, right?
I bet that So Min and Jae Suk won't
be able to find their books.
- It's over for them.
- We don't know where the books are.
Gosh, I have enteritis.
Why today of all days?
Haha, just let it go.
Let us know if that happens.
We'll bring you clean pants.
- You should shoot inserts though.
- No wonder why...
- Let them shoot inserts after that.
- Pee your pants.
Young Jin brought
an extra pair of underwear for me.
I asked, "Will I get wet today?"
Then he said, "I think you will."
Or do you have a cork,
by any chance?
(He's going to plug it
if it's necessary.)
I'm not joking. I couldn't
get out of bed for three days.
In my bedroom,
just like Niagara Falls...
Do you think they blocked it?
So Min,
I don't think I can go there.
I'll just die.
(I'll just die.)
- We have to find coins too.
- Hurry up.
- Jae Suk.
- Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
- Hurry up.
- A yellow pouch...
(The tour guide is acting up again.)
- Jae Suk, hurry up.
- A yellow pouch.
- What is...
- I'm afraid of dying too.
- The Grim Reaper will show up.
- There's something over there.
- What's that?
This is too scary.
- You should go first.
- Hurry up.
Your reactions will be funnier.
- Gosh. What is this?
- Where is it?
- Gosh. Let go of me.
- There...
- I see some objects tied there.
- Ji Hyo.
- That startled me.
Then...
(Slave Kim leaves them alone
at the entrance.)
- Good luck.
- So Min.
- Hey.
- Let me go with you, Jong Kook.
- Good luck.
- Let me go with you, Ji Hyo.
- So Min.
- I don't want to be with him.
- Jae Suk.
- He's such a scaredy-cat. Oh, gosh.
I hope...
(Gosh! What's that?)
- Gosh! What's that?
- Oh, man.
- Kim Jong Kook, that punk.
- He startled me.
- Good luck. Let's go.
- Don't you just...
Don't you hate the sight of him?
- Let's go.
- My goodness.
I hope you make it back alive.
Let's meet again alive.
(Left: Aristocrat's House,
right: Ghost's Room)
- Let's go to Aristocrat's House.
- Aristocrat's House?
(The cowardly siblings are left
alone together.)
Jae Suk, you go first.
Touch the objects
to see what they are.
I'm warning you.
I'll leave once I find my book.
I'll leave you here alone and run.
- Do you understand?
- When I find my book,
- I'll leave you...
- Oh, gosh.
- You scared me. Hey.
- It's just a leaf.
- I'm sorry.
- I won't let you off.
Jae Suk.
Should we go inside?
What are we supposed to do?
I think we should go inside.
- It's so dark in there.
- What's this?
There's a phone here.
Who is Jung So Yeon?
Leave it.
(She talks nonsense
because she doesn't want to go in.)
Gosh.
I really don't want to go in there.
- Are they still outside?
- Come on. Please.
- When will you go in?
Gosh.
I'll show you a rare video.
(Seok Sam offered to show them a video
when they were getting bored.)
Here. Watch this video.
It's interesting.
- It's a swing.
- It's being moved by the wind.
- Yes.
- Hey!
- Gosh! Darn.
(Screaming)
My gosh. What's wrong with him?
(Happy)
(His sphincter muscles relaxed
for a moment.)
That was so funny.
I'm sorry,
but can you give me wet tissues?
That was terribly scary.
(He ended up peeing his pants
even before going outside.)
Won't you...
- Won't you go with us?
- This place looks so scary.
- It means we should go in there.
- Won't you go with us?
Won't the cameramen go with us?
Jae Suk, what will you...
Jae Suk, what...
(He kicked in the air.)
We have no choice but to go in.
Seriously, this is driving me crazy.
Oh, gosh.
(The hallway looks eerie.)
I think we have to go in there.
Oh, gosh.
(I think we have to go in there.)
Let's go in there.
That wasn't it.
Right. We should go in there.
But I can't. It drives me nuts.
Won't you go with us?
They turned off the lights.
Gosh, I feel like I'm going crazy.
Let's go.
(They have to come in here
without the staff members.)
- Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
- Exactly.
(But they have no choice
if they want to find their books.)
This is driving me nuts.
(Jae Suk reached the entrance.)
Gosh. This place is too scary.
- Gosh!
- That startled me.
- What was the noise?
- I'm so scared.
I heard a weird noise in there.
Gosh. I feel like I'm going crazy.
(Snorting)
Cameraman, please come with us.
Please come inside with us.
- I can't go in there.
- I heard a weird noise.
Come on. Please come with us.
No, I can't.
(He begs the cameraman
who's working hard.)
(The situation is being broadcast.)
Gosh, you punks.
Will you shoot the show all night?
Gosh!
Hey, set a time limit.
Right. Tell them they failed.
- Are they idiots or what?
- What?
- Aren't there... Oh, they're alone.
- Are they idiots?
- Aren't the cameramen with them?
- I see.
No, they're not with the members.
- Then I understand them.
- I wouldn't be able to go in.
Then I wouldn't be able to go in.
- There's no camera. I understand.
- Exactly.
- I'd go in if they go with me.
- The cameramen aren't with them.
- Really? Then it's understandable.
- They're not in there.
In that case,
we should understand them.
- I fully understand them.
- That's too scary.
What did you prepare
for today's episode?
Jae Suk, come on. Lead the way.
(The cowardly siblings go back in
since they have no choice.)
- It won't end if we don't go in.
- Gosh.
Do you understand?
It won't end if we don't go in.
Then what should we do?
- Gosh.
- I really don't think I can go in.
This is the worst.
- I can, but I don't want to.
- I feel...
That means you can't go in.
- No. I can go in, but...
- Then you should go first.
I can go in, but I don't want to.
It's a little brighter in here.
(The herbal medicine store is
covered with blood.)
(Grunting)
I feel like something will come out.
I can't go in. What should I do?
What's this?
(But she must go in
to find her book.)
Right. I'll think of this room
as a drama filming set...
Oh, I get it. I know now.
- What do you mean? Yes.
- We saw a phone out there.
Ms. Jung So Yeon, please come out.
- She must be in here.
- What was that? Quiet down.
Ms. Jung So Yeon, please come out.
She must be in here.
I think
she put her phone out there...
because she had to come inside.
- Don't you think so?
- Stop talking and come inside.
Come on in. Come over here.
Hurry up.
Hurry up and come here.
Let's go together.
(After a quarrel, they entered
the first course at last.)
Gosh. I don't think I can go.
What should I do?
Gosh.
Oh, my gosh!
I told you not to do that.
I really hate
being scared like that.
- Gosh. What do I do?
- Hey...
Don't do that.
- I really hate this.
- Seriously.
- What should I do? Gosh.
- Oh, man.
- My goodness. Sir.
- Gosh, seriously.
Thank you for your hard work, sir.
He touched me as he left.
My goodness.
- Gosh.
- I'm so scared.
- I'm sorry, sir.
- He scared the life out of me.
- Sir...
- Come here, So Min, will you?
- Sir, I'm sorry for getting angry.
- Hurry up.
- Come here.
- You must've been surprised.
Really? That must be...
There are trees around it.
That's a place
where rituals are held, right?
This is where...
You pray with
a bowl of water, right?
- It's a shrine.
- This is the place.
- This is it.
- The spirit that protects us.
- People pray here.
- Stack three stones, bow thrice,
and spit thrice for good fortune.
Why don't we try it?
Stack three stones.
- Stack three stones.
- Right.
Like this.
(They suddenly decide
to say a prayer.)
Three stones.
There we go.
And bow thrice.
(With respect)
And spit.
(Spit!)
- Hold on a second.
- Hurry.
Is this allowed to be aired on TV?
(After an embarrassing attempt,
they head out to find the book.)
I'm sure luck will find us now.
Who knew folk village
would be this scary at night?
What's this?
Wouldn't there be something here?
What is this?
- This...
- Open it, Jong Kook.
What if something jumps out?
- Open it.
- This?
Open it.
(Slave Kim's voice goes up a notch
when he sees something suspicious.)
There's something here.
- Really?
- There is.
(Flinching)
Where are you going?
(She runs for her life.)
(Screaming)
I wish they get so startled
that they kiss.
(I wish they get so startled
that they kiss.)
You be Ji Hyo,
and I'll be Jong Kook.
"Get over here."
(Kissing because they're startled?)
- They have a reason to kiss.
- Right.
"Let's go that way."
(The father of three
enjoys his fantasy.)
Why are you coming to me?
You jerk!
(You jerk!)
Ji Hyo's showing her temper.
Leave me alone, will you?
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook
ended up separated.)
(She hears the sound
of drumming bats.)
There it is.
Miss.
(She cautiously moves closer.)
(Tap)
(Peek-a-boo!)
(The granny's face is the same
as the back of her head.)
(Screaming)
Jong Kook!
(She ran away
without putting her shoes on.)
(The granny adjusts her wig.)
You frightened me once
which is enough.
Here you go.
Just pass me the book.
Thank you.
Stop...
(Screaming)
You're too scary.
(Where's my bat?)
I'm going to go home.
(Ji Hyo still managed
to collect the book.)
Darn it.
Are you kidding me?
(Fooled you!)
Give me the real one.
(Some books are fake.)
Where's the real one?
(While Ji Hyo wanders
to find the book...)
- When will this be over?
- Darn it.
Look for the book, Jae Suk.
So Min, why is this so long?
- What...
- I can't go any further.
I hate this eerie sound.
So Min, I'm stuck.
So Min, I'm stuck!
Stuck where?
I'm stuck. Help me out of this.
- Help.
- How?
- This snapped.
- What is it?
- What?
- This snapped.
- Where?
- This got caught and snapped.
- This...
- This got caught.
- You startled me.
- Darn it.
Did someone grab you?
- No.
- Did it get caught?
- Yes, this got caught.
- You startled me.
- Are you good now?
- Yes, I'm good.
You need to film this though.
(Hi!)
Just a second.
(Screaming)
(Jae Suk, So Min)
Just a second.
(They make a U-turn
only after taking a few steps.)
Oh, no. What are we going
to do with your camera?
- Put it back together.
- Hold on.
Wait a second.
(They still maintain
their professionalism.)
How can the camera
be the issue right now?
My survival is more important.
Still, we should...
This actually broke.
It must have snapped.
This is killing me.
- I'll film you instead.
- This will do.
This got caught here.
- What now?
- She's still here.
She's looking at us.
- I can't go any further.
- She's looking at us.
We'll move past her.
We'll just walk past you.
Ma'am, please. I'm terrified enough.
No, don't. Please don't do this.
- I'm sorry.
- Please.
Let us walk past you.
(Hand shoots out.)
I told you not to do that.
(Seriously?)
(What the...)
The ghosts are too scary.
(Jae Suk makes a fuss
even though the ghost did nothing.)
Let's take a breather.
Oh, no.
- Come this way.
- No, I won't.
- I won't!
- I can't do this.
- Come this way.
I won't.
Tell her that I won't go.
- Come this way.
- We won't.
- We won't!
- We won't go over there.
- Come this way.
- No!
- We don't want to.
- Come this way.
- We won't go there.
We have no choice though.
Come this way.
- That's enough.
- Come this way.
That's enough.
(Jae Suk is beginning
to get annoyed.)
- I don't want to go there.
- Come this way.
Come this way.
(Darn it!)
Jae Suk!
(They even drop the camera.)
That really frightened me.
- My gosh. I can't believe it.
- Seriously?
(Groaning)
My gosh.
- Are you kidding me?
- My gosh.
Unbelievable.
(Wailing)
Jae Suk.
You need to pick up your camera.
(Darn...)
My gosh.
Pick up your camera.
- Jae Suk, let me take a breather.
- So Min.
- I can't do this.
- This is impossible.
- The hallway's too long.
- I'm exhausted.
My throat's already hoarse.
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo is
searching the house.)
Where is the notebook?
Come out here and I'll smack you.
I mean it.
Why are you in my house?
What are you here to steal?
You... How dare you.
You... Get lost.
- Get out!
- The notebook!
Fine. Just leave.
Go!
I'll take this though.
I'll take this.
I'll leave with this.
I'm taking this!
(Ji Hyo finds the book
after a hand-to-hand combat.)
I'll kill you all.
See how angry I am.
This is insane.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook searches
another house.)
(His eyes widen.)
What's this?
Who's there?
(Groaning)
- Who's there?
- My gosh.
Right. So what now?
- Leave.
- Should I leave?
But I can't.
I need to find something first.
You look really scary though.
I need to find something, okay?
Hold on a second.
I need to find something.
(They're playing pat-a-cake.)
- Rock...
- Sorry?
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Again. Rock-paper-scissors.
Is "rock" what you can only play?
- Leave.
- How about a best of three?
A best of three.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay, good.
Okay.
(Fine. Take it.)
Thanks.
Thank you. Allow me to take a look.
I'll use it for good.
I'll find the book
and use it for good.
Hold on a second.
This...
(Jong Kook finds his Book of Fate.)
Here we go.
Why didn't you tell me?
Leave.
Right. Thank you.
I'll get going now.
The others will be in shock.
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook
find their Book of Fate.)
Gosh.
(Screaming)
This is super annoying. I hate this.
I can already picture the scene.
There's no reason for me
to go in there.
- I already found mine.
- He should find the coins alone.
I don't want any of the coins.
That'll take you one step closer
to receiving the penalty.
- I'm good with that.
- You'll be at risk.
- I don't want the coins.
- The others are taking too long...
which means you only have
a short amount of time to live.
What happens when you die?
Will I get dragged away?
You'll become a ghost.
Darn it!
(He's close
to turning into a ghost.)
Darn it!
I want to live though.
(He'll be reborn as a ghost.)
- Is it over for you?
- I mean it.
What's the time?
- Get going.
- I barely lived my life.
This is bad.
- Why don't you...
- Just so you know,
I'll die in 15 minutes.
Seriously. How is this fair?
Suk Jin, I can't see
the lower half of your body.
- Oh, no!
- Where did my legs go?
- Where did they go?
- I'm already dying.
I only have 17 minutes left to live.
Why can't we see any of the books?
As if. Just get back here, will you?
- Let me at least get some coins.
- It's over for him.
One shouldn't be broke
when entering the afterlife.
- Jong Kook's back.
- Here you go.
It was a blast.
(Slave Kim returns.)
- How was it?
- How did it go?
You'll split up
even if you go as a group.
- Really?
- I see.
But Jae Suk and So Min
are still together.
Yes, I know.
- Why did we split up?
- Please...
- Seriously?
- Bye, Suk Jin.
- Me?
- Suk Jin will leave us.
Is it time?
- But the time...
- They're taking too long!
Should I go?
Your upper body has disappeared.
I still have time.
- Are you a ghost?
- I can see your face only.
Joon Hyun and Sung Kook...
came and...
- I can't see them.
- This is driving me crazy.
Why can I see your face only?
- Do you want to see something cool?
- Yes.
Watch this cool video.
It's interesting.
It's the wind that moves the swing.
The wind.
(A ghost will appear in 3 seconds.)
(Flinching)
Wait. Jong Kook.
Joon Hyun in the back
was really surprised.
(Surprised)
(A ghost surprised by another ghost)
Is Joon Hyun a Grim Reaper?
The Grim Reaper flinched.
My stomach hurts. Did he do that?
He...
flinched like this.
It kind of relieves me
hearing that he was surprised.
- He's a human.
- He's so cute.
(Grim Reaper Joon Hyun
is so much like a human.)
Why is his flinching so funny?
My stomach hurts. It was hilarious.
It's funny.
Tell them to come quickly.
Excuse me, do you know
where the Book of Fate is?
(The scaredy-cats are still moving
like a snail.)
(The ghost who can't stand it
anymore rushes them.)
So Min.
Why is it so long?
(They didn't even have a glimpse
of the Book of Fate.)
Look at this.
Save me.
- I found it.
- Is it yours?
(Jae Suk found the Book of Fate.)
(I found it!)
- No. Don't go.
- I found it.
- Please don't go.
Don't go. Is it yours?
- It's mine.
- Isn't it mine?
- Don't go.
- Okay, So Min. I found it.
I found it, So Min.
- Please don't go.
- What did you say to me?
I'm telling you. If I find it,
I'll leave by myself immediately.
- I'm sorry. I was wrong.
- What did you say to me?
- I was wrong. Don't go.
- You said you would leave.
I'll treat you better.
You told me not to stop you.
Please.
Don't go, okay?
(She calms down for now
and starts moving.)
Let's go for now.
- Let's go for now.
- Where is mine?
Let's go for now.
- Let's go for now.
Where is mine?
- What is this?
- It'd be where I can see, right?
What's this? Oh, my.
(Screaming)
- It's alive.
- Jae Suk.
- Oh, my goodness. Wait.
- It's alive.
- Oh, my goodness.
(Running away as fast as they can)
Wait.
(Coming back to the room
where they were right before)
I thought it was a doll.
This is driving me crazy.
Why is the Book of Fate his
and not mine?
- I'll leave.
- No, Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk. Please.
- I'll go.
- I'll go if you talk like this.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay?
- I'm sorry. I did wrong.
Oh, my goodness.
Until when will they get surprised?
Those punks.
My life is about to end.
Suk Jin.
(Current time: 8:49 p.m.,
Suk Jin: 8:50 p.m.)
Your lifespan is over.
(His lifespan ended.)
Now, you became a ghost.
- Oh, no.
- Hey.
- Suk Jin.
Take care of Hyun Woo, my son.
(Seok Sam died
even before the real race began.)
- Hey.
- Suk Jin.
Hey.
- Seok Sam.
- Suk Jin.
Gosh, how did this happen?
I couldn't even enjoy my life.
(The scaredy-cats unintentionally
ended Seok Sam's life.)
- It's still not over.
- When will this end, So Min?
(They're still wandering around.)
My goodness.
When will this be over?
It's here.
- Oh, my.
- Gosh.
It's here.
(Frightened to death)
What should I do?
(Locust jumped back out of fear.)
Hey.
Hey, it's here. So Bal's book.
(But he found
So Bal's Book of Fate.)
(Book of Fate, So Min)
- Hey.
- Oh, my.
- Jae Suk.
- Come out quickly now.
- Hurry up.
- Wait for me.
Hurry up.
We should go out quickly now.
(They obtained two books.
All they have to do is go out!)
(A shaman ghost was guarding
the way to escape.)
Please.
- Please.
- I'm so scared.
(Swinging)
She told us to go out this way.
- She told us to go out, but how?
- How?
- How can we go out?
- It has just begun, you punks.
- What?
- What has begun?
- What is it?
- What...
It has just begun, you punks.
- What?
- What has begun?
(The exorcism began.)
The door won't open.
- The door won't open.
- This is annoying.
What is going on?
- The door won't open.
- Oh, no.
- What's this?
- Hold on.
- Hold on. Open the door for us.
- What's this?
The door won't open.
(Shouting)
- Be careful.
- Oh, my gosh.
I really can't go.
(The search for
the Book of Fate ended.)
Gosh, please don't do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm so tired.
I'm so upset. What should I do?
- Hey. You honestly did nothing.
- My shoulders hurt so much.
No, that's not true.
I picked up all the books.
(So Min did nothing.)
Hold on.
It was so scary.
I almost tripped when the old lady
was coming after us. I was scared.
- It was so scary.
- The door is so scary.
My voice is gone.
Haha, Se Chan, please go.
It's completely dark.
I want to show a new side of me.
Being too dramatic
on a variety show is...
actually...
Haha, will you scream like this?
No. That's kind of shameful.
(They set off shamefully.)
You can't start doing it
at the entrance, Haha.
I can't see anything.
How can I go?
Go to the place where
Chinese characters are written.
- "Patients?"
- Chinese characters.
Kick it.
Here? There must be one here.
- Right?
- You go first.
(Shouting)
You punk.
- Hey, you.
- Go.
- You go first.
- Hey.
Hey.
(The cheating instinct took over.)
As I went in once, you should...
(Emergency escape)
- I'm here.
- I'm not doing it.
- I'm not doing this with this guy.
- All right.
- He's hopeless.
- Okay.
He's hopeless.
I'm not doing it with him.
- Okay.
- I'm not doing this.
I was looking at you.
- I quit.
- Okay.
Seriously. You go first then.
Okay, I will.
Are you happy now? Come.
Come.
Just walk.
Keep going.
Just go.
Do you know
how good fighters we are?
- Beat them.
- He was the best in Dongducheon.
- Bring it on.
- Got it?
Do you know how scary we are?
(Screaming)
I'm sorry.
(A quick apology)
Put candles.
- Sorry?
Candles.
(They listen well.)
I'm so scared.
What? Why?
(They're startled just by the sound
of the door opening.)
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
Where are the coins and my book?
I need to find them.
My neck hurts. I'm sorry,
but you're human, right?
We're looking for books.
Can you find them for us, please?
- She told me to go out.
- I'm sorry.
My neck hurts.
It's because I'm so scared.
- You do it.
- I'll do it. Let's do this quickly.
What's there to be scared of?
- Darn it.
- You darn...
Why?
(The door closed behind their back.)
My neck.
Just pass by. Go.
(Shouting)
(Screaming)
(Crying out)
(They're passing by quickly,
screaming shamefully.)
Come here.
(They got to the next room.)
What's the matter?
- I want to poop. Why?
- Oh, gosh.
Why? What is it?
What's the matter, Se Chan?
- You go first.
- Why, Se Chan?
Wait. I want to poop.
Hold on. Let me fart once.
(Darn it!)
Next to us.
- I saw it too.
- Next to us.
- I'll go. My goodness.
- Oh, my.
- Isn't she the kid from earlier?
- Yes, she is.
- I'm sorry. Let us go.
- Let us pass.
Please...
Do you have something in your hand?
No, she doesn't.
I'm sorry.
I can't see. Don't do it.
- Should we go this way? Hey.
- It's here.
- Hey.
(He found a book.)
Is this not it?
- Whose is it? Let me see.
- Wait.
(Book of Fate)
It says Haha.
(They found Haha's Book of Fate.)
Wait for me, Haha.
Search for your book here.
There must be one.
- I don't think there is.
- It must be there.
- What?
- What? Why did you call me?
- Why did you call me?
- I got a cramp.
Do I go this way? Where do I go?
Tell me the direction.
- I got a cramp.
- Where do I go?
Come here.
Don't do that. I'm sorry.
I got a cramp.
Haha, wait for me.
(Another dirty trick)
Don't leave me.
Wait for me. Help me find it.
What's this?
That was scary.
- Come here.
- What?
(What?)
Come here.
- What?
- To where?
(Screaming)
Gosh.
(Screaming
as if they're practicing singing)
That was so scary.
(That was so scary.)
Se Chan. We have to find yours.
I've improved though.
Haha. You're wonderful.
I can't find the coins.
We still need to find yours.
I know. Help me find it
or I'm going to die.
(Screaming)
I'm sorry. That was darn scary.
I admit it.
I almost peed my pants.
Hurry up and pass me.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
- Before I move.
- Hello.
(She's sitting on
Se Chan's Book of Fate.)
(He missed it.)
Where's mine?
Okay.
- Help me find mine. Where is it?
- I'm trying.
- Haha. I need to fart.
- Wait.
- I need to fart.
- Go ahead.
- I farted so much too.
- Are you still here?
We're moving.
- I was farting.
- We're going.
- Ma'am!
Ma'am.
What is it?
It's moving.
- What's moving?
- That's moving.
(Fart booster on)
(The fart brothers
escape successfully.)
- Good work.
- I couldn't find mine.
(However, Se Chan is empty-handed.)
You should've gone
through the bookshelf.
What? I couldn't find it.
You should've gone
through the books.
- Did you find your book?
- Yes.
- Did you find yours?
- No.
Then you have to go back in
and find it.
Don't be ridiculous.
(Don't be ridiculous.)
(He fails to keep calm.)
- Hey.
- Hold on.
Don't be ridiculous.
That's nonsense.
- What did you just say?
- Calm down.
- Hey.
What are you talking about?
Are you telling me to go in there alone?
By myself?
He should go alone.
That's up to you.
Right? You should go alone.
- Come here.
- Oh, my goodness.
You forgot this.
- Oh, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- You forgot this.
- Oh, ma'am.
(Se Chan's Book of Fate)
Ma'am. Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Bye.
- This is great.
- Thank you so much.
Where did you find it?
I was sitting on it.
I see.
That's cheating.
Good work.
Here.
(They all checked their lifespan
in the Book of Fate.)
- Gosh.
- Sushi.
Did you all check your lifespan
in the Book of Fate?
- Yes.
Now, let's start the race.
As soon as your life is up,
you're out and become a ghost.
(As soon as your life is up,
you're out and become a ghost.)
Two of the ghosts will...
receive the penalty sticker today.
Do your best to survive
as long as you can.
There are two bets
to expand your lifespan.
Okay.
You can bet your life
as much as you want.
If you win, your life will expand
as much as you bet.
If you lose, your life will reduce
(If you lose, your life will reduce
as much as you bet.)
I see.
Okay. If you're confident, bet more.
If the ghost wins the bet,
he can reduce one human's life.
(If the ghost wins the bet,
he can reduce one human's life.)
I could lose the bet on purpose.
(I could lose the bet on purpose.)
If you lose the bet...
- I should win, right?
- You have to win to reduce it.
(He doesn't understand the rule
even after becoming a ghost.)
You should just rest today...
in the nearby grave.
Leave the game to humans.
- Right.
- Go to a nearby grave,
- Go for a walk.
- and take a break.
Fine. I'll reduce your lifespan.
I'll reduce yours. Just wait.
- Okay.
- The more the ghosts,
the better it is for them.
- They need to take us with them.
- Yes.
You should take someone
with a short lifespan.
- Her.
- Yes.
- Her?
- Me? Why me?
Not only the coins are hidden,
but also a way to end the race...
- before your life is up.
- Really?
(There's a way to end the race
before your life is up.)
(There's a hidden mission
to end the race.)
You should look carefully.
I should go for that.
(What's the secret of today's race?)
Let's get started.
Let's go.
If you don't have much time left,
I'll go pick you up.
Let's stay together.
What do you say?
- The three of us.
- Are you brave?
Yes. Let's go.
Let's go.
We need to find coins, right?
- Yes.
- We just need to find coins.
Let's find the coins
and go for the bet.
- Where do we go?
- I'm so sweaty.
I'm soaked too.
That's pretty. Let's go over there.
- We...
- I haven't been there yet.
- It's pretty.
- So Min. Don't go there.
- Stop.
(Hushing)
- Then I'll go this way.
- But it's pretty.
Wait for me.
(Screaming)
(Scared for real)
Hey!
I was only rushing to find coins.
You scared me.
So, don't go alone. I'm scared.
I'm scared too.
I found it.
(Screaming)
(Trembling)
(Falling)
Se Chan. You still found it.
(It was so hard to get the coin.)
- Let's go in there.
- The coin.
Why are you such a coward?
What's so scary?
That was frightening.
I should make you a ghost.
- Me? Try to recruit me.
- Yes.
I need to recruit you, but I have
a feeling you have a very long life.
Me? Because I never hesitate
to say what's on my mind.
(He's never stressed.)
What's that?
(At that moment,
Jae Suk spots something.)
Is something here?
- Where?
- What's my position?
- Bet.
- It's the bet.
Ten coins for ghosts,
seven coins for humans.
I only have two coins.
Are you going to bet?
(The price for a bet is 10 coins
for ghosts and 7 coins for humans.)
I don't have seven coins.
I don't have ten coins.
Where can I get ten coins?
- Hurry up and find them.
- Find them?
Right. They must be somewhere.
- I'm scared.
- What's this?
I want to do it now.
(Rich Lord Yoo tries to expand
his lifespan now.)
Oh, gosh.
Someone's here to bet?
That scared me.
Listen to the sound I make,
and guess what it is.
(1. Happy to take revenge)
(2. Dumbfounded be dead)
I'll bet ten minutes.
(3. Happy to meet a human)
(1. Happy to take revenge)
(2. Dumbfounded be dead)
(3. Happy to meet a human)
(4. Looking down on Suk Jin)
What's the answer?
(3. Happy to meet a human)
(4. Looking down on Suk Jin)
Happy to take revenge. Number one.
(1. Happy to take revenge)
What a shame. It's wrong.
What's the answer?
That was number four.
- Looking down on Suk Jin.
- Don't be ridiculous.
(Lord Yoo loses 10 minutes of life.)
That's ridiculous.
You can't control your life.
(After reading the lines
in the script,)
Bring more coins.
(she leaves.)
Jae Suk. Did you get ripped off?
It's impossible to win.
- The bet?
- It doesn't make sense at all.
- Did you try it?
- I'm going to do it now.
I can't believe it.
There are a lot of coins there.
- Really?
- Yes.
What's this?
Suk Jin.
There's the Nine-tailed Fox.
- What the?
- Where are the coins?
Ms. Fox.
- Suk Jin.
- Ms. Fox.
- We're both ghosts.
- You're both ghosts.
- Can you give me one?
- How should I...
address her?
Give me one please.
- Suk Jin. Come here.
- Yes?
- What?
- It looks like something's in here.
It's guaranteed.
Right? Go check it out.
How? Do I take my shoes off?
My goodness.
It's 100 percent.
- It's...
- Suk Jin.
- Look.
- Something must be there.
(Scared)
It's just a cameraman.
Anything?
(They found coins.)
Gosh.
- Coins.
- There's nothing in here.
- Nothing?
- It's empty.
(Jong Kook lies
and takes the bag himself.)
My goodness.
There must be fake ones.
- I...
- Suk Jin. There's one.
- There's one.
- Where?
- Money.
(They meet a ghost.)
(He meets another one
while running away.)
(Screaming)
(Laughing)
Why am I surprised to see a ghost?
You're so fast.
My shoes.
Stop it. I'm your colleague.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook...)
(Seizing the ghost with an arm bar)
Wait. I should take that money.
Good work.
I'm so drained.
Suk Jin.
I'm a ghost. Why was I surprised?
They're my colleagues.
There's nothing.
(Holding onto his heart)
- I think...
- They're all fake.
the one the Nine-tailed Fox
is holding is fake.
Let's close it for other people.
This place is scary.
That was scary. My voice is gone.
(That was scary. My voice is gone.)
I'm so full. I had too many muffins.
(Out of context)
I'm so full.
(Running away for the 2nd time)
(It's too much work for the heart.)
I am full. This is driving me crazy.
- What? Give me some coins.
- What are you doing?
- No. These coins are mine.
- Give me some coins.
- I need them for plastic surgery.
- These coins are mine.
- I got more coins. Hold on.
This is nice. Okay.
- What?
- It's nothing.
You got startled, right?
I got some coins.
(While the weak ghost walks around
without much gain,)
(Jae Suk looks for coins
after losing coins in a bet.)
Gosh!
(Jae Suk's cameraman
screams as well.)
Hey.
Hey, Sung Ho.
(The cameraman ran away.)
Hey.
How could you get startled?
(Jae Suk's cameramen
are known to get scared easily.)
Now that Kwon Ryeol isn't here,
he is causing me a headache.
(Jae Suk's cameramen
are known to get scared easily.)
I am stressed out.
(The cowardly Lord Haha
is looking for white lights.)
I don't want to get a penalty.
(The cowardly Lord Haha
is looking for white lights.)
My goodness, Suk Jin.
He passed away...
and turned into a statue.
Suk Jin.
I never treated you to a warm meal
while you were alive.
Suk Jin.
It's scary to imagine
the statue moving.
(Cowards imagine things
and get scared.)
Imagine the statue moving.
I will find coins...
(The old ghost is determined
to shorten the members' lifespans.)
and shorten people's lifespans.
This won't do.
(The old ghost is determined
to shorten the members' lifespans.)
How much time
does Jae Suk have left?
I will play for 30 minutes
of Jae Suk's life.
- Thirty minutes of Jae Suk's life.
- Maybe he has 15 minutes left.
- Understood.
- Yes.
- The rules are simple.
- What are they?
- I will take a photo of you.
- Okay.
While you get your photo taken,
- keep your facial expression blank.
- I can do that.
It's easy.
- I will take a nice photo.
- A blank facial expression.
- Okay.
I will take it now.
One, two, three.
(Startled)
For goodness' sake.
This is so annoying.
Gosh.
All right. Suk Jin failed.
It was too scary.
(He lost his coins and failed.)
You should have gone easy on me.
This is so scary.
(Se Chan walks around by himself.)
How many minutes do I have left?
What time is it now?
(The current time is 9:20 p.m.)
What?
Hold on.
(Se Chan only has 20 minutes left.)
I have 7 or 8 coins.
(He plans to use his coins
in order to extend his life.)
I will need to do the mission
and extend my life.
Where will I find the coins?
(So Min doesn't have
much time either.)
I don't have much time left.
Only 20 minutes remain of my life.
(She needs to collect coins
in order to extend her life!)
I feel dizzy.
I really feel dizzy.
(She needs to collect coins
in order to extend her life!)
This is bad.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan arrives
at a betting place.)
(1. Sad to see a ghost
that looks better than her)
(2. Annoyed because people
keep getting surprised at her face)
(3. In pain because she fell down
while avoiding the Grim Reaper)
(4. Touched because the food
at the ancestral rite is very tasty)
Number two, annoyed because people
keep getting surprised at her face.
It's correct!
(It's correct!)
(Se Chan succeeded in winning a bet
by guessing the answer.)
You succeeded in extending your life
as you wanted.
(Se Chan's life got extended
by 30 minutes.)
Thank goodness I earned time.
(Se Chan's life got extended
by 30 minutes.)
Ji Hyo, do you want
to go there together?
Let's go over there.
I was so scared.
- Ji Hyo, the two of us...
- Haha, go in there.
I am too scared to go in.
We can do it. Let's go.
Okay. I will go in.
(The entrance with the red light
looks spooky.)
Haha, go in there.
I will look for coins.
Okay.
(After pretending to be brave,
he stops in front of the gate.)
All right.
(After parting ways with Haha,
she places a bet with her coins.)
Here you go.
(After parting ways with Haha,
she places a bet with her coins.)
What time is it now?
(The current time is 9:35 p.m.)
(Squeaking)
What a sound.
(Creeped out)
The sound is so scary.
Hey!
(Laughing)
Open the door!
- For goodness' sake.
- What?
- You startled me.
- Aren't you a ghost?
- I am, but things are scary.
- What's wrong with you?
I don't know.
Why are things so scary?
Look at them. They are on their way
to get someone.
- Right?
- Someone died.
They are on their way
to get someone.
(Grim Reapers appeared.)
- Someone died.
- Who died?
Hey, Joon Hyun.
Sung Kook.
You startled me.
(He won a bet and extended his life
by 30 minutes.)
- Why?
- Let's go.
(But the Grim Reapers came
before 30 minutes passed.)
All right. Go easy on me. It hurts.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
It hurts.
- Se Chan.
- Did you do it?
- Hurry up and join me.
- Did you reduce my life?
What?
- Let's join forces.
- I will be back soon.
Gosh, you startled me.
Don't grab me so hard.
Se Chan, let's join forces.
Okay. I will be back soon.
Okay. Come back soon.
(Did Suk Jin reduce
Se Chan's lifespan?)
(Se Chan got eliminated at 9:40 p.m.)
Your life has ended.
(So Min begins to run hurriedly
upon seeing something.)
(Grim Reapers appeared here
as well.)
(So Min extended her life to 10 p.m.)
(She still has 15 minutes left.)
(Ji Hyo is in the middle of a bet.)
Grim Reapers are following me.
Save me, Ji Hyo.
So Min, I need to do ssireum. Wait.
Ssireum?
Your life has ended. Let's go.
(So Min got caught
amidst Ji Hyo's indifference.)
Ssireum.
You seem to be out of breath.
(So Min got eliminated
in a mysterious way as well.)
I am out.
I have no regrets.
(Did Suk Jin take out two people?)
It was a nice life.
Bye.
Let's find some coins.
(Se Chan came back as a ghost.)
(Glancing over)
Are there no coins?
My goodness.
You were one tempo late.
Gosh, that hurts.
Do you have any coins?
Help me out!
Give me coins!
My throat is hoarse.
Don't you have any coins?
I am a fellow ghost.
Please give me some coins
if you have them.
I need to turn more people
into ghosts.
(He needs to collect coins
and reduce people's lifespans.)
I need to hurry up.
I should go to that lazy ghost
who is lying down.
Mister.
Do you have coins?
Do you have coins? No?
You shouldn't sleep here.
You have coins, right?
It's convenient
now that I am a ghost.
(The second newbie ghost)
I look scary, right?
It's no joke.
I hope someone sees me.
(Happy)
If someone comes...
(The newbie ghosts
are absorbed in their roles.)
(The current time is 10:10 p.m.)
Let's play a game.
Cham.
(Those who place a bet
to extend their lifespans)
My goodness, are you okay?
I will extend your life
as you wanted.
Who is next?
You need to bet someone's life.
I will play for 30 minutes
of Jae Suk's life.
Okay.
Thirty minutes of Jae Suk's life.
I should look for hints.
Placing bets to extend your lifespan
isn't the answer.
(While explaining the rules
of the race)
(There is a way to end the race...)
(before their time runs out.)
(A way to end the race?)
What's this?
(Jae Suk goes in search
of the hidden secret.)
(At that moment,)
(he finds
a suspicious-looking book.)
What's this?
What does this mean?
The Joseon Book of Fate has
records of everyone's lifespan.
The time of everyone's death
is written in this book.
At that time, Grim Reapers
with five horns go to the person.
In Running Village, there is
a total of three Grim Reapers.
("Veritable Records
of the Joseon Dynasty...")
"In Running Village, there is
a total of three Grim Reapers."
(Three Grim Reapers
are in Running Village.)
(Glancing over)
Lord Yoo.
- What...
- It seems like you found something.
- What?
- Why don't you help me?
- What is this about?
- It seems like you found something.
- What do you mean?
- What's this?
This is... I can't tell you.
How much do you need?
(How much do you need?)
What are you doing?
(Slave Kim joins them.)
Did you find some coins?
I found only one coin at a time.
I know.
(Glaring)
- So it has begun.
- I know.
- This race has a secret, right?
- What do you mean?
Okay. I get it now.
- I will get going now.
- Okay.
(They part ways.)
Where should I go?
(Jae Suk takes out the book again
after everyone leaves.)
What does this mean?
"In Running Village, there is
a total of three Grim Reapers."
(Three Grim Reapers?)
(He saw two Grim Reapers earlier.)
Grim Reapers with five horns?
(Where is
the one remaining Grim Reaper?)
Does that mean one of us is a ghost?
It means one of us is a ghost.
(Is there another Grim Reaper?)
I need to collect hints.
(Lord Yoo becomes careful
upon finding an important hint.)
I think I can stop having matches.
That isn't what's important
right now.
I need to end the race.
What's this?
(He finds a scroll.)
"Only the Grim Reapers
can eliminate a person..."
"by taking off his or her name tag."
"If the Grim Reapers eliminate all,
they win."
"To beat the Grim Reapers,
rip off the name tag of the leader."
"But if humans suspect each other
and rip off the wrong name tag,"
"all humans will get eliminated
and the race will end. Be careful."
"Only the Grim Reapers
can eliminate a person."
My goodness.
Your time has come.
- I've come for you.
- Me?
If the leader takes off
the last person's name tag,
the Grim Reapers win.
(Suk Jin, 8:50 p.m.)
(Three humans have been eliminated.)
(Se Chan, 9:40 p.m.)
(So Min, 9:45 p.m.)
To beat the Grim Reapers,
rip off the name tag of the leader.
(To beat the Grim Reapers,
rip off the name tag of the leader.)
(Jong Kook found a way
to end the race.)
I knew there would be more
to this race.
Hold on.
I need to tell people about this.
The Grim Reapers
can take off our name tags.
(Jong Kook sets out
to share the knowledge.)
Hold on.
I am sorry.
- Seriously.
- Haha.
Seriously.
- Yes?
Come here. Who are you with?
Jae Suk?
Jae Suk.
- Stop it.
- You found something.
What is it?
- You...
- Hold on.
- I don't know what to do.
- Is there something strange?
You know...
What's that?
(They hesitate to share the hints.)
- There must be a twist.
- There is more to the race.
Open up.
- "Open up?"
- Yes.
For goodness' sake.
What's that?
What I have is too crucial.
- We don't have much time.
- What I have is too crucial.
What I have is the same.
Maybe we have the same information.
Let's see.
I think they are different.
- Here.
- It's crucial. We are in trouble.
What does it say?
- Here.
- "The Joseon Book of Fate..."
"There is a total
of three Grim Reapers."
We only saw 2 Grim Reapers,
so that means 1 is among us.
"Only the Grim Reapers
can eliminate a person."
I need to watch my name tag.
"If the Grim Reapers eliminate all,
they win."
"To beat the Grim Reapers,
rip off the name tag of the leader."
"But if humans suspect each other
and rip off the wrong name tag,"
"all humans will get eliminated
and the race will end. Be careful."
"There is a total
of three Grim Reapers."
One of the three is the leader.
- We saw two of them.
- Who?
The two who took Suk Jin.
- Are those the Grim Reapers?
- Yes.
- And...
- And one of them is among us.
- Thus, there are three.
- There is the leader.
- Yes.
- Hey.
- Right?
The leader.
Hey, I am not it.
- I got him.
- Hey.
- The leader.
Look. He is flustered.
- He is flustered.
- We caught the leader.
- Hold on.
- The leader.
- He must be the leader.
- It's fitting.
It's fitting.
- He is flustered.
- He did behave strangely.
Jong Kook, I am not it.
Sit down.
(Okay.)
- Sit down.
- I am 100 percent sure.
Will the race end
if we remove his name tag?
It will end
if we remove the leader's name tag.
But if he isn't the leader,
all of us will be eliminated.
You need to think about this.
Why are you changing the subject?
Listen. There are people
we haven't seen for a while.
You are right.
There are such people.
It means they could be working
separately...
to eliminate people.
Hold on. How many people remain?
- You, me...
- People got eliminated.
Ji Hyo is still alive.
Come forward and take the coins.
(She collected coins diligently.)
Please give me coins.
- Thank you.
- Go.
Thank you.
Who wants to place a bet?
It's me.
(Is Ji Hyo the leader?)
- Here is the important thing.
- We could end the race.
He isn't explaining himself well.
I am not a Grim Reaper.
I am a mantis.
- What?
- I am not a Grim Reaper.
- That wasn't funny at all.
- I am a mantis.
- That makes no sense.
The only explanation
is that he is nervous.
(Jae Suk didn't share his hint
with Haha earlier.)
(Is Jae Suk the leader?)
Okay. I got it.
- I am serious. I am not it.
- Go and do whatever you want.
This is driving me crazy.
"This is driving me crazy."
Go and do whatever you want.
- Gosh.
- My lifespan...
I think he will go
and place a bet...
to reduce my lifespan by 30 minutes.
This is driving me crazy.
They are suspecting me.
(Jae Suk leaves.)
Haha, we can't take off his name tag
if we become ghosts.
We should extend our lifespans.
Let's place bets.
Jong Kook, come here.
Let's go together.
- We need to place bets.
- I was so startled.
What time is it now?
I don't have much time left.
This is bad.
I will place a bet.
Hey, zombies.
I brought water.
Drink some water.
Here. Take a bottle.
(This ghost is selling water.)
Here is water. Thank you.
Thank you.
(Screaming)
Give me a bottle of water.
Are you a water ghost?
Why are you carrying water?
Give me a coin.
(Smacking)
(The vendor ghost
gets a smack on the head.)
- Hey.
- Give me a bottle of water.
What's that?
We are in trouble.
Why?
- Is there a spy?
- It's Jae Suk.
- I think it's Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk?
What's going on? Tell me.
- Well...
- Just sell water.
- Why? What's going on?
- Water vendor.
What's going on?
I did the blank expression mission.
- Keep your distance.
- Why?
You might be the leader.
Jong Kook.
Rip off my name tag then.
I can't do that. What?
I think they are here for me.
(Two Grim Reapers approach them.)
Haha is out.
No way.
- We are here to drink water.
- I see.
Thank you for your hard work.
Jong Kook!
Get him!
- Your life has ended.
- For goodness' sake.
- Let's go.
- Hey.
- It isn't me.
- Take the scroll.
Take the scroll, you punk.
(Jong Kook gets eliminated as well.)
My time isn't up yet.
It seems like
someone reduced my lifespan.
It's him!
It's Jae Suk!
(Jae Suk appeared
before Jong Kook.)
The Grim Reapers have five horns.
- It's Jae Suk!
- You are mistaken.
(He is unfazed
by Jong Kook's elimination.)
- It's Jae Suk!
- What's happening?
It's Jae Suk.
- Tell me what the race is about.
- Suk Jin.
I think Jae Suk is the leader
among the Grim Reapers.
- Is there such a thing?
- Yes.
(A Grim Reaper eliminated people
from Suk Jin to Jong Kook.)
(Suk Jin, Se Chan,
So Min, Jong Kook)
The leader is
among the surviving members.
(The leader is
among the surviving members.)
To beat the Grim Reapers,
rip off the name tag of the leader.
- Tell me what the race is about.
- Suk Jin.
I think Jae Suk is the leader
among the Grim Reapers.
- Is there such a thing?
- Yes.
Why doesn't he think it's me?
Edit this part to make things
more confusing.
I was speaking nonsense.
(This ghost wants more screen time.)
Hey.
You know that there is
a Grim Reaper among us, right?
Yes, I do.
It isn't me.
- Is it you?
- It isn't me.
- Who is it then?
- That's what we need to find out.
What's the story?
It's not like that.
- What's the story?
- Suk Jin.
He says there is
a leader of the Grim Reapers.
What's going on?
There must be more hints.
- You little...
- You startled me!
For goodness' sake.
(You little...)
(An old lady stops Jae Suk
at the gate.)
Are you a human or a Grim Reaper?
I am a human.
A Grim Reaper can't enter a place
that has deer antler,
fox head, and pig tooth.
What?
Deer antler,
fox head, and pig tooth?
A Grim Reaper can't enter a place
that has deer antler,
fox head, and pig tooth.
(Grim Reapers dislike deer antler,
fox head, and pig tooth.)
(They can't enter a place
with these items.)
I have no problems.
- Are you a human?
- Yes, I am.
Enter.
I...
(Jae Suk got past the gate.)
(Jae Suk is a human,
not a Grim Reaper.)
She is an incredible actor.
(Aristocrat's House)
A Grim Reaper
can't enter this place.
Then I just need to bring them here.
(Jae Suk decides to bring
the remaining members.)
Then I just need to bring them here.
Hey.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Haha.
- Jae Suk.
- What is it?
- Come here.
- Why?
What is it?
- There are rumors about you.
- You know,
(The members come
to the shrine gate.)
- An old lady told me this.
- Okay.
The Grim Reaper
can't get through the door.
(The Grim Reaper
can't get through the door.)
What?
Do you know what I mean?
- Try going in there.
- The Grim Reaper can't go in?
The Grim Reaper can't go in there.
You should try going in.
The Grim Reaper can't go in?
The Grim Reaper can't go in there.
- You should try going in.
- It's a false rumor.
- No.
- It is a false rumor.
- Hello.
- Come here.
- Is that what she said?
Ma'am, come over here.
- You come here.
- Did you really say that?
If he can't go through the door,
he's the Grim Reaper.
- Go ahead and get through it.
- I can go in.
But this is a lie.
- Come on in.
- You should be able to go in.
- Come in.
- Of course I can go in.
- Go ahead and come on in.
- I'm going in now.
I'm going in now.
(But Haha stops on the threshold.)
- I can go in.
- Go further in.
- I can.
- Come on in.
See? He wants to rip off my name tag
once I go in there.
No, I won't rip it off.
(Haha keeps stopping
in front of the door.)
No, I won't rip it off.
Come in with the ghosts.
- Come here.
- You can come with them.
(Right at the moment...)
(Haha goes in.)
You can come with them.
The lady said
the Grim Reaper can't come in here.
(That means
I'm not the Grim Reaper.)
That means I'm not the Grim Reaper.
Then it's Song Ji Hyo.
(Then it's Song Ji Hyo.)
Is Ji Hyo the Grim Reaper?
(Is Ji Hyo the Grim Reaper?)
The Grim Reaper can't come in here?
Ji Hyo... I mean,
did the old lady say that?
You and I are the only ones alive.
Did Ji Hyo die?
You're out once you become a ghost.
Actually, I didn't see Ji Hyo here.
I don't see her here.
Find Ji Hyo.
She's probably doing her mission.
Where's Ji Hyo?
Ji Hyo is the Grim Reaper.
She must be the Grim Reaper.
Gosh, it's Ji Hyo.
Is that Ji Hyo? Go find Ji Hyo.
Otherwise, we will be out,
and the race will be over.
- Ji Hyo.
So Min, hurry and come here.
Suk Jin.
Ji Hyo has horns on her head.
Otherwise, we will be eliminated.
(The Grim Reaper, Song Ji Hyo)
(This morning)
(The 3 Grim Reapers are here to take
people's lives in Running Village.)
That means there is a ghost
among us.
(Song Ji Hyo, the Grim Reaper leader
is in Running Village.)
(The Grim Reaper's goal is
to eliminate all the humans.)
(The card reading said
night brings her good luck.)
(And she's like a night owl.)
(As the night glides on, she starts
looking for the Book of Fate.)
Yoo Jae Suk.
(Ji Hyo's Book of Fate had
the lifespans of humans.)
(Ji Hyo could reduce the lifespans
of humans with bets as a ghost.)
(She started the bet
by shortening Se Chan's life.)
(Se Chan: 10:10 p.m.)
(Se Chan: 9:40 p.m.)
(That's why Se Chan got
eliminated 30 minutes early.)
(The Grim Reaper's
second target is Jong Kook.)
(Yang Se Chan 30 minutes,
Kim Jong Kook 30 minutes)
(That's how she shortened
their lives and eliminated them.)
(When she reached the entrance
to the shrine with Haha,)
(The Grim Reaper was too scared
to go in there.)
Okay. I'll show you how I go in.
(Ji Hyo left the place
saying she'd look for coins.)
(And there was a hint
that the humans missed.)
(Ji Hyo's portraits were
tied up to a tree in the shrine.)
(That's how the Grim Reaper was
taking human lives.)
(The only humans who can stop
the Grim Reaper, Jae Suk and Haha)
(It's 10:50 p.m. now.
Haha's life will end soon.)
Don't be ridiculous.
The ghosts are coming.
(Right at the moment...)
(The ghosts are rushing
to the entrance of the shrine.)
Let us in!
(The ghosts are
blocking the entrance.)
- Let us in!
- Help us.
What?
- The Grim Reaper.
- There's...
(They see someone
behind the ghosts.)
That's the Grim Reaper.
- Let us in!
- What?
They can't get in here.
They can't come in.
Where's Ji Hyo?
I don't know!
- Where is Song Ji Hyo?
- I don't know!
Move over.
(The Grim Reaper leader shows up
when the ghosts are gathered.)
Move over.
(The Grim Reaper leader shows up
when the ghosts are gathered.)
It's done. There's Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yoo Jae Suk, Haha.
(Yoo Jae Suk and Haha,
your lives are over. Come on out.)
Your lives are over. Come on out.
It's over.
Come on out. Come here.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Come here.
- Leader.
- I'm the leader...
- of the Grim Reapers.
- Leader.
- I'm the leader.
- Once the Grim Reaper rips off...
the name tags of the humans,
the Grim Reaper wins.
I don't have much time left.
I increased it a little though.
It's one between the two.
- We should... Hey, leader.
- We have to go out.
Go ahead and rip it.
Go and rip it off.
- Come on out.
- Come in here.
Just come out here.
Come on out before
you run out of time and die.
Hurry and come.
Do you want to die
when the time is up?
I know we will die
once the time is up.
- Hurry and come on out.
- Go and try holding her hand.
You two will have to go at her
and see who wins.
Hold your name tags tight.
Be careful.
Or just stall for time so they will
run out of time and die.
(At the moment...)
(The two Grim Reapers try
to drag the humans out.)
They're caught.
- They are being dragged.
- Go.
They're caught.
(They are dragged out!)
Ji Hyo, be careful.
(Ji Hyo takes the chance
and attacks them.)
- Hang on.
- They hold them for her.
- Gosh, that's tough.
- Wait.
- The Grim Reapers are strong.
- Go get them!
I can't get off of it.
(Ji Hyo has to rip off
the humans' name tags.)
They are really strong.
(At that moment, Jae Suk
and Ji Hyo grab each other.)
No.
- I took it off.
- My gosh.
- He took it off.
- He did it.
No.
- I took it off.
- He did it.
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Song Ji Hyo,
the Grim Reaper is out.)
- Did you rip it?
- Ji Hyo, are you all right?
Ji Hyo lost her name tag.
- Is it over?
- Are you okay, Ji Hyo?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- The humans win.
- He took it off.
- He did it.
It says the Grim Reaper.
What were you two doing?
- No, I tripped.
- We did it.
- Ji Hyo, are you okay?
- Yes.
You lost, but you fought well.
It says the Grim Reaper here.
All right.
The two humans won't get a penalty.
The first episode of
Whatever Penalty Project,
- Ghostly War of Coins is over.
- My goodness.
- I'll get a penalty today.
- That was the best one ever.
The Grim Reaper leader
who shortened human lives today...
- was Song Ji Hyo.
- My gosh.
- I had no idea.
- Hey, you...
- She's so cool.
- Why did you eliminate me so soon?
I didn't see her make a bet.
You just died.
I just died myself?
- You started with a short life.
- I see.
Since the Grim Reaper lost,
the humans who eliminated
the Grim Reaper at the end...
won the race.
So Song Ji Hyo, the Grim Reaper...
and one of the ghosts
will get penalty stickers.
Okay.
The member who will get
penalty stickers with Ji Hyo is...
We have a penalty box.
Ji Hyo will draw a name.
Me?
- Right. The humans...
- I hope it won't be me.
- The humans survived.
- This is the worst.
- I hope she doesn't pick me.
- Hey.
It will be the worst
if your name gets picked here.
- Who's picking it?
- Ji Hyo will get a penalty sticker.
- Ji Hyo.
- Shall we let the humans pick it?
- Let the humans pick it.
- Whoever wants to do it.
All right.
Jae Suk, mix them well.
Don't go with your first choice.
I got one.
(The first penalty sticker
from Whatever Penalty Project)
- Who is it?
- One name won't leave my hand.
Okay.
(The first gate
to the horrible penalty)
- It won't leave your hand?
- No.
Okay.
(Who will get
the first penalty sticker?)
- Let me see.
- That's strange.
- This name won't leave my hand.
- It won't?
- Let me see.
- That's strange.
- I hope it's not me.
- This name...
stuck to my hand the whole time.
You act like it's one of us.
- I wonder who it is.
- It's strange.
It's Kim Jong Kook.
My goodness. What's that?
- I wonder who it is.
- It's strange.
(Kim Jong Kook gets
the penalty sticker.)
- It's strange.
- It's Kim Jong Kook.
- My goodness. What's that?
- I knew it.
- You saw the name, right?
- No, I didn't.
- I think you did.
- I didn't.
Didn't you pray to the three stones
at the shrine earlier?
- What do you mean?
- Did you even pray?
I heard it would bring me good luck.
So I stacked three stones
and prayed to them.
Isn't it that you prayed
in the wrong way?
Jong Kook doesn't seem that way,
but he's quite superstitious.
- Congratulations.
- He's with Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
- You two are going together.
- Ji Hyo and...
- You're coming with me.
You two look great together.
- Good work.
- Good work today.
- Thank you.
The ghosts did a great job today.
(What's the comment
that makes your heart flutter?)
(I like your t-shirt.)
(Cutie)
(You're driving me crazy.)
(Why are you so cute?)
(You might feel like
some trivial things bother you.)
(Have confidence in yourself.)
(Be my girlfriend.)
(That makes me sick.)
(It's something
a man in his 40s would say.)
(I can't believe them.)
(They have to get votes
from the citizens.)
(A heated debate on dating
and generational conflicts)
(Am I more like
a friend or an uncle?)
(They receive real-time feedback.)
(And there are 7 penalty stickers.)
(It's a probability game where
only one member can get them all.)
(They have to stop the penalty
from coming to them.)
(Who is the member
with the worst luck?)
(Running Man Round and Around)