- So this is it.
- These are cereals.
- Hello.
- I should eat cereals.
- I will eat them too.
- I want cereals.
- Hello.
- What is all this?
- Look at this.
- Who sent this?
- It's from Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk bought it.
- Why?
- Why all of a sudden?
- To cheer you up.
- Hello.
- All of a sudden?
- For no reason?
I've never seen a coffee truck
that serves this.
I know.
- It costs a lot.
- This is...
- My gosh.
- Hello.
Those who live
in Apgujeong are different.
I drink iced Americano
no matter how cold it is.
Hello.
It's strange that
he's suddenly being nice to us.
Jae Suk got us a coffee truck.
If your husband is
suddenly nice to you,
that means he's having an affair.
Why is he doing this
all of a sudden?
Is Jae Suk your husband?
I'm just giving you an example.
Why is he being so nice?
What's with him? This is strange.
I paid for it.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- Hey.
(Suk Jin and the one who paid
for the coffee truck show up.)
- Hey.
- You look great today.
- I do?
- I like your cardigan.
Why are you saying that?
I'm just saying that
because it's pretty.
- He's conscious of what people say.
- It looks pretty.
And I like your white cap.
It looks good on you.
What's going on?
- Why are you...
- I like your outfit.
- That's enough.
- And you smell nice today.
Your shoes are pretty too.
Look at your pants.
- By the way...
- You look so cute.
- That's enough.
- Hey.
- It's true that it's pretty.
- It's true.
- Why are you being like this?
- I'm not joking.
I'm saying this because it's pretty.
As soon as you got off the car,
I was surprised to find out
that we're wearing the same color.
- Don't be so self-conscious.
- I was like, "It's pretty."
- That's enough.
- Suk Jin, I like your voice.
- You have a nice voice.
- My voice was always like this.
So yesterday...
Jae Suk, why did you buy this?
- Why is that?
- Why all of a sudden?
- You know what?
- Tell us.
He has nothing to spend money on.
- He's got nowhere to spend...
- I saw him...
looking for places
where he could spend money.
He doesn't buy clothes
or eat something expensive.
- He doesn't need money.
- The thing is,
I wanted to cheer up
our production staff.
Everything is going well.
- What's wrong with them?
- Everything's fine.
They are applauding.
I wanted to express my gratitude
at the end of the year.
Are you doing this to win
the Grand Award?
Then I would've sent it to the CEO.
By the way, Suk Jin, are you
expecting to win an award this year?
- Are you?
- You deserve one this year.
- Right. This year...
- The Grand Award?
- Just stay quiet.
- He deserves it.
- The Grand Award.
- This year...
I'm not doing this to win an award.
They are not doing this
for an award either.
Did I work hard
to win an award then?
- You deserve one.
- Even if I win,
it's not like I get a pay raise.
- You do get a pay raise.
- He got a raise.
- Suk Jin.
- He also got meal tickets.
I got a pay raise
after I won an award.
When I won
the Honorary Employee Award,
I only got four sacks of rice.
- Did you get rice?
- You did?
(Did you get rice?)
- I did.
- You did?
- You didn't get one?
- No, I didn't.
- I got rice.
- My gosh.
- Really?
- You got four sacks of rice?
Is that right, Hyung In?
You get four sacks of rice a year.
- That's true.
- The employees get it.
- That's what I got.
- Really?
Do the employees get rice?
- That's what I got.
That's the benefit
for the SBS employees.
That's nice.
And we got beef jerky from SBS.
That's from the director.
- It tasted really good.
- It was Korean beef jerky.
Right. The beef jerky
from the director.
You got the beef jerky
thanks to Running Man.
You don't get
things like that elsewhere.
It's only for major TV shows.
- Suk Jin.
- I sometimes get apples.
He has money to buy
his own beef jerky.
When I was sick
and got hospitalized,
I got a fruit basket.
- Really?
- From whom?
- From SBS.
- The director.
- Right. That's what you got.
- Really?
Yes. I got a fruit basket.
- That's Director Choi Young In.
- She's very thoughtful.
I'm so disappointed.
When I was sick,
she didn't send me anything.
- When were you sick?
- When was that?
She wouldn't send it
just for a cold or something.
- It's not like that.
- Were you sick?
- When I was hospitalized.
- When was that?
- When were you hospitalized?
- When were you so sick?
- Why were you sick secretly?
- I was hospitalized,
- so I skipped the shoot once.
- What? You did?
- When was that?
- When were you sick?
- Was it ten years ago?
- When Girls' Generation was here.
- When Girls' Generation was here?
- So you called me.
(It was 11 years ago.)
- Girls' Generation?
- It was like a party.
That was a long time ago.
It was like a party
when Girls' Generation was here.
I still remember them.
It was even before they joined.
It was before we joined.
Today, we are having the guests...
who will make some of you
go wild for sure.
- What?
- Really?
Really?
- Bring in the first guest.
- Is it me?
(The first guest shows up.)
- Someone's coming. It's a woman.
- Where?
- What?
- My goodness.
Is she from the drama,
"One Dollar Lawyer?"
(That's her!)
That's right. She's from
"One Dollar Lawyer."
- Look at her.
- She's Ji Eun.
- How did her hair get so long?
- Hello.
- I'm surprised.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hello. I'm a big fan.
- Nice to meet you.
(The heroin from the SBS drama,
"One Dollar Lawyer")
(She's a rising star who captivated
viewers with her lively charm.)
(Actress Kim Ji Eun)
- Hello.
- Her acting is brilliant.
Ji Eun. My gosh.
She's so good at acting drunk.
She had short hair in the drama.
- Right. I had short hair.
- This is amazing.
Did you get a hair piece?
- Yes. For another drama.
- I can't believe she's here.
We have the second guest.
- Do we have another guest?
- Really?
- I didn't get to see who it is.
So Min seems very excited.
- You don't know who it is?
- Bring in the second guest.
- Hello.
- Who is it?
- I just heard.
- She doesn't know the guest.
- They didn't let them meet.
- I won't go wild easily.
Someone's coming.
(Someone's coming.)
- Hello.
- Someone's coming.
That's Cho Sae Ho.
- My gosh.
- Darn it.
- What is he doing?
- Gosh.
- It's Cho Sae Ho.
- That's Cho Sae Ho.
- My gosh.
- Darn it.
- What is he doing?
- Gosh.
I thought...
I thought I smelled something sour.
Look at her face.
(She's the only one
who welcomes him.)
Why are you dressed up?
- Look at her.
- They said, "Darn it."
- What?
- Look at Ji Hyo's face.
Ji Hyo. These two...
- Does he have shares or what?
- Why is his jacket so tight?
- Why is he coming here so often?
- What's with his outfit?
Hey, he's wearing a school uniform.
My gosh. Even from over there,
- Why are you in a school uniform?
- I could hear your boos.
I could hear that even from there.
This is a Japanese school uniform.
Hello.
- Hello.
- What's with your outfit?
- What is this?
- That's a Japanese style.
- He's Japanese.
- Isn't this a Japanese uniform?
This is not acceptable.
Go get changed.
- This is a Japanese uniform.
- This is unisex.
Isn't this what G-DRAGON wears?
- This is a Japanese style.
- G-DRAGON wears this.
- This is not a Japanese style.
- This is Japanese...
- Is that Chanel?
- Look at his shoes.
- Nice to meet you.
- Aren't these your shoes?
Did you give him the shoes?
Am I standing here
when I'm the guest?
Sae Ho, come over here.
- Can I go there?
- You sent there yourself.
As soon as I got here...
- You went there yourself.
- Right.
This is Chanel.
- You look cute today.
- It's too tight for you.
I was excited to be on Running Man
after a long time,
- By the way...
- You look cute.
so I chose expensive clothes.
You look really lovely.
So Min, today...
- You're frowning.
- No, I'm happy.
I thought you weren't feeling well,
but that wasn't the case.
- Right. That's because of you.
- No, I'm happy.
I'm really excited to see him.
I'm sorry.
- I'm really glad.
- All right then.
We have Ji Eun and Sae Ho here.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- What brought these two together?
- Why is Sae Ho here?
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- What do they have in common?
- Did they do a drama together?
- Ji Eun.
I heard you rearranged your schedule
to be on our show.
Thankfully, I was supposed
to start my next drama right away.
But they agreed to wait.
I really wanted to be here.
- Seriously...
- So are you happy to be here?
- Yes.
- What?
- So are you happy to be here?
- Yes.
- Why would you ask that?
- What was that?
- I'm happy.
- This is what we do here.
- You can have fun.
- He sounds so mean.
- Why would you ask that?
- What was that?
He's being so mean.
- Stop it.
- My gosh.
How can I possibly stop it?
- Look at Jong Kook.
- She just got here.
Jong Kook tells him to stop.
Stop what?
- How can I stop it?
- That's enough.
I have to talk to him.
If there's anything
you want to say, just say it.
Go ahead and say it.
By the way, Ji Eun recently
finished her drama.
- That's "One Dollar Lawyer."
- That was amazing.
- She had short hair in the drama.
- That was...
- Right.
- It's "One Dollar Lawyer."
Did anything change
after the drama was over?
Yes. The drama was
loved by a lot of people.
So many people recognize me
even when I don't wear any makeup.
- Really?
- I see.
Wasn't it like that before?
No. Only a few fans
recognized me before.
But many people recognize me now.
Once you join Running Man,
people will recognize you
even when you wear a cap and a mask.
- Really?
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
You're right about that.
- You're right about that.
- Exactly.
- Stop it.
Listen to him carefully.
- Listen to him carefully.
- That's enough.
- He's right.
- Are you making fun of him?
Just criticize me instead.
- I like what you said.
- I said something silly.
- What you just said was great.
- My gosh.
Anyway,
even her family at home...
is treating her differently now.
They call me Actress Kim.
And my aunts asked me
for my autograph.
- That never happened before.
- That happens a lot.
- That's the change.
- All of a sudden.
They ask for your autograph.
I'm sorry, but do you want me
to stay out of this?
There's nothing
I can do in the middle.
- I just say, "Oh."
- What are you talking about?
- Please keep doing that.
- Okay.
- Please keep saying that.
- I'm sorry.
- Sae Ho, already...
- You are up next.
By the way, what are you doing here?
- Shouldn't you be in school?
- What school?
You know
which high school you go to.
Ji Eun's outfit and mine...
- are similar in style.
- No, it's not.
- In what way?
- We have similar patterns.
- The patterns are similar.
- I see.
So do you have
anything to do with Ji Eun?
- No.
- About Ji Eun...
Lee Dong Wook is
a close friend of mine.
- Right. I heard that.
- And Ji Eun did a drama with him.
It's called "Strangers from Hell."
- Did you watch the drama?
- I did.
Really? What was her character?
- Why are you doing this?
- You really don't know?
- Why are you upset?
- You can't be a star like that.
- Why are you being like that?
- I don't need to be a star.
- Why are you lying?
- Isn't that your goal?
- She was Im Si Wan's girlfriend.
- Exactly.
I heard a lot about you.
- Really?
- What did you hear?
- That they were close friends.
- I see.
And you two meet often
at the end of the year.
- That's true.
- Why at the end of the year?
I heard he was really fun.
- Dong Wook praised her a lot.
- What did he say?
This is it for today.
- You don't need the details.
- I want the details.
This is about Dong Wook.
It's okay because it's a compliment.
He says she works harder
than anyone else.
- And that...
- He's just making things up.
- Who wouldn't work hard here?
- Right.
He doesn't work so hard.
- Hey!
- You didn't work hard, did you?
(He got a blow after a long time.)
- He works really hard.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm just experienced.
- He's really hard-working.
- I just hit it and quit it.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm a pro.
- That's what he does.
- Okay. I get it.
- I hit it and quit it.
He does his own part.
By the way, the thing is...
Actually, the two people
I tried fixing up together were...
- Sae Ho...
- So Min.
- and So Min.
- Why does it have to be me?
- Why didn't it work?
- They both weren't interested.
Sae Ho refused it.
- Right.
- I don't like him either.
- I know.
- I hate it even more.
Why do you hate it even more?
(I hate it even more.)
Why would you hate
to go out with me?
- Why are you doing this to So Min?
- I hate it too.
How dare you not like her?
- Do I have to like her?
- Who do you think you are?
- I get it.
- That darn brat.
- Sae Ho is...
- All right.
- How dare you?
- This is what upsets So Min.
- She's not interested in him,
- Exactly.
but he refused her.
That makes her feel terrible.
- Right.
- How dare you refuse So Min?
If So Min really wants to go out
with me, I could give it a thought.
- But she's not like that.
- I hate this too.
I hate the way
he's thinking right now.
- Why?
- Why should I want to go out?
Then why are you
so dressed up today?
She got the wrong information.
- The information...
- She was misinformed.
I think she heard
Jinyoung of GOT7 would come.
Will you go out with me once?
I won't!
Go away!
"I won't."
(The tragic ending)
- I'll eat with Nam Chang Hee.
- "I won't."
- That's funny.
- That's hilarious.
Ji Eun became popular
with her line, "You darn jerk!"
- "You darn jerk!"
You darn jerk!
I heard she wanted to say that
to one of the members.
- The exact line?
- Ji Eun.
- It's the famous line.
- Who is it?
- You need a partner.
- What about Sae Ho?
What about Sae Ho?
- I think that would be nice.
- Okay. Good.
- Ji Eun, speak your line to him.
- Okay.
- But how...
- It's a famous line.
- It's from a drama.
- I know it's a famous line.
- I don't find it offensive.
- She doesn't mean it.
You darn jerk!
(Flinching)
- I like the tone of her voice.
- "You darn jerk!"
- You've got the vibe.
- She sounds like an old fossil.
- She's got the vibe.
- She's not just saying that.
- You're right.
It comes from deep within.
- That's explosive.
- She's different.
When Ji Hyo says that,
she even makes the face.
Ji Hyo, show us.
You darn jerk.
That's new. She's different.
- My gosh.
- She's good.
- She's a veteran actress.
- This is intenser.
- This is...
- It sounds a lot intenser.
- She didn't even yell.
- She's different.
- I have no hard feelings.
- I know that.
- This is what she sounds like.
- That's heavy.
Today, we are having
One Dollar Gourmet Race.
We prepared
all sorts of delicacies for you.
(They will visit many places
for all sorts of delicacies.)
And everything will be
only one dollar.
- What?
- My gosh.
Everything will be a dollar.
- What?
- My gosh.
And you can earn one dollar
during the race.
Today, Jong Kook, Ji Eun,
and Sae Ho will be the captains.
- Three captains?
- Why me?
We have three kinds of R money
with their faces on them.
- They look cute.
- Why did they do that?
- Sae Ho loves stuff like this.
- It's so cute.
I like it
when people do things with me.
So you will choose a captain
you want for each mission.
I see.
After a mission, you get the money
with your captain's face on it.
The value of the captain's money
goes up with the team's ranking.
It goes up together.
The value of money goes up.
After the money value is decided,
you can exchange your money...
and use it to pay for your meal.
- Each meal has different values.
- I got it.
You can move to another team
in each round considering the value.
- To pick the captain you want.
- I see.
Among the three kinds of R money,
you can choose 20 bills
at the beginning.
Now you can split up
and get the bills you want.
- Okay.
All right.
How would you like
to have your 20 bills?
I'll take Ji Eun's money.
- I'll give you 20 bills of Ji Eun.
- Okay.
I'll try hard anyway.
I'll take ten bills of my money...
and five bills of the other two.
My goodness.
If I do well and win the mission,
the value of my money will go up.
- So...
- Sae Ho, you're talking too much.
(Embarrassed)
- I'm sorry, but I need some time.
- What's taking you so long?
- I'm back after a long time.
- Okay. Go ahead.
It's nice to meet you. I'm...
Will you keep quiet?
I'm doing the shoot here.
I know.
- Why is he being so...
- All right.
Let's go to a secluded spot.
His comments are so lame.
Hey, are you sure you can do this?
I was going
to get your money, but...
Are you sure about this?
I'm sure. I'm feeling good today.
- My gosh.
- Let me make it simple.
Then...
I'll take 10 bills
of Ji Eun's money.
(Ten bills of Ji Eun's money)
And five each.
Ten bills of Ji Eun's money.
Nine bills of Jong Kook's money,
and one bill of Sae Ho's money.
(Ji Eun 10, Jong Kook 9, Sae Ho 1)
Sae Ho money has no value.
I can actually hear it drop.
You can trust me.
I'm feeling good today.
I'm all-in today.
You are done
choosing your seed money.
- Yes.
- Based on the money you have,
- you can choose a captain you want.
- Shall we?
- We can change teams, right?
- Yes.
One of them might not be chosen
by anyone.
- Yes, that's possible.
- Would that be okay?
- I see.
- That'd be funny too.
- Why would you look at me?
- Really?
If we complete the mission,
the money value will increase.
- We should work together.
- We know nothing about the mission.
- We can make our team strong.
- Okay.
- Shall I say it in front of them?
- Yes.
Really?
- Then let's start with Ssaebssaeb.
- In front of us?
- Can I join the team I want?
- Yes.
- Just as we all want?
- I pick Sae Ho.
- Really?
- Really? You picked Sae Ho?
- That's unexpected.
- All right.
- They're both comedians.
- That's true.
- We're both from SBS as well.
- We...
- Both of them are comedians.
- Right.
- He's my senior comedian.
- Yes.
- Okay. Next.
- I want you to treat me as one.
Ji Hyo, go ahead.
- I pick Sae Ho too.
- Oh, really?
- I'm surprised.
- Gosh, Sae Ho?
- I wonder why.
- Because he's easy to control.
- Oh, is that so?
- Right.
- If you can control the captain...
- If that's not the case...
- I'll pick Sae Ho too.
- Really?
- Are you serious?
- Go ahead.
- I want to join his team.
- Go.
- I pick...
- He...
- I picked him to ruin him.
- It'd be funny if he picks Sae Ho.
Me too. I have the least amount of
Sae Ho's money.
(They joined the team
to decrease the value of his money.)
We can't leave Ji Eun alone.
- I pick Ji Eun.
- I also...
(Suk Jin and Jae Suk chose Ji Eun
without hesitating.)
(If that's the case...)
- Then I'll...
- Haha, join our team.
- Well...
- No pressure.
- I mean...
- Go ahead. It's okay.
Hey, let's start over again.
Starting with me.
- Sae Ho, we...
- Then...
- I said, no pressure.
- I know. It's not like that.
- I'll go with him no matter what.
- No pressure, Minion.
- Hey, make up your mind.
- I already did.
- Which team did you pick?
- I picked Jong Kook.
- I'll make them all dirt broke.
- We're all quite young.
- Right. We're Generation MZ.
- We're Team MZ. Go, Team MZ!
- Team MZ!
- Go, Team MZ!
Sae Ho's feelings might change.
- Since they're on the same team...
- Right.
- You never know.
- He might develop feelings for her.
- "How about we have a drink later?"
- That's possible.
Stop it, you all.
I didn't say I wanted that.
- Seriously.
- What are your plans for tonight?
- I have no plans.
- I see. But I have plans.
- I mean...
- Why would you...
- do that to So Min?
- She got rejected by him twice.
- What is wrong with you?
- That's so mean.
- There's nothing wrong with asking.
- Come on.
- You punk.
- But you have plans.
- Why would you do that to So Min?
- I apologize.
Now that you've chosen your teams,
we'll go to have the first food
after you get changed.
- Okay!
(National Hangeul Museum)
- My gosh.
- Oh, you two are sitting together.
That's right.
Gosh, So Min. Why are we wearing
matching clothes like a couple?
- This is our team uniform.
- Oh, I see.
- They look like a newlywed couple.
- Right.
I guess
that's how I look from behind.
- That's how I look from behind.
- I can see the resemblance.
Se Chan, why are you sitting there?
- I always sit in the back.
- You two look great together.
- You see, I love romance.
- Yes.
- But you're not curious about them?
- To the point that I'm frustrated.
- I don't think it'll work out.
- I know how that feels.
Hold on. How old are you, Ji Eun?
I'm 30.
- She's Generation MZ.
- She's still young.
- You were born in 1993.
- Yes, I was.
- She was born in 1993.
- I see.
She's still very young.
She was born in 1993?
She's very young.
Ji Eun, do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't have a boyfriend.
May I ask what type of man you like?
- I care about their personality.
- But...
I care about their personality.
But Ji Eun, listen.
- Don't you care about appearance?
- You see,
- I hate that answer the most.
- unlike what she said,
- when she starts dating someone...
- Exactly.
- Right.
- I bet she'll date a handsome man.
- She'll date a handsome man.
- No.
- What I'm trying to say is...
- Appearance does matter, right?
- that even the flaws he may have...
- Remember Lee Na Young?
- Lee Na Young.
- She said that too...
- but married Won Bin.
- That's right.
- Exactly.
- Ji Eun.
Se Chan has a good personality.
- Indeed. And he's funny.
- Se Chan has a good personality.
I like a funny guy.
And when I start to like his flaws,
I fall for him.
When you start to like his flaws,
you fall for him?
- Yes.
- Do you see his flaws now?
I bet she does.
(Taken aback)
- See? Ji Eun, don't be like this.
- She couldn't answer that.
- Be honest with us.
- You shouldn't be like this.
- Ji Eun.
- If you don't like me, just say it.
- Wasn't I honest?
- I think...
- Se Chan looks quite charming.
- Indeed.
- He's cute.
- He's moderately good-looking.
- Se Chan is cute, indeed.
- Especially his eyes...
Considering only the appearances
of Sae Ho and me,
- which one of us would you prefer?
- Sae Ho...
(Yang Se Chan versus Cho Sae Ho)
Sae Ho...
- Sae Ho?
- Just be honest.
I think that Se Chan looks better
than Sae Ho.
- She sounds firm.
- Se Chan looks better than Sae Ho.
(Se Chan wins, and Sae Ho loses.)
- She sounds firm.
- I think that it's her way...
- of approaching me.
- She's playing hard to get?
Okay. All right.
- My, he's so optimistic.
- She did that on purpose.
- This is...
- She's trying to get my attention.
- This is the way an ugly man...
- Really?
behaves in front of pretty women
just as So Min said.
- Ji Eun, you're not good at it.
- This is...
She has a long way to go.
- He said she had a long way to go.
- My gosh.
- I like his positive spirit.
- He's handsome.
- You see, I heard...
- He's not handsome.
- that the ladies Sae Ho took...
- I'd say he's cute.
out on dates were all very pretty
although he's not dating them now.
- That's what I heard. Right?
- I heard that too.
- What's your ideal type, Sae Ho?
- He says I'm too small.
- We have never asked him about it.
- True.
- What's your ideal type?
- Exactly. You've never asked.
- We've never asked, right?
- What's your ideal type?
- I'll be honest with you.
- Okay.
- I do like pretty women.
- I see.
- I like pretty women.
- He's very honest.
- You like tall women too, right?
- I prefer pretty women.
- What about the height?
- Since I'm small,
- Tall women?
- I prefer tall women.
- Then she'd look down at you.
- He likes that.
- That's not a problem.
- Do you like it?
- "That's not a problem."
I actually had a thing going
with someone who was 178cm tall.
- I met her.
- That was it?
- Didn't you go out with her?
- Was that it?
- I held her hand.
- I see.
- I saw you putting your arm...
- You held her hand?
- around her waist.
- He saw that too.
- Oh, when he spent all his money?
- Yes.
After watching a movie, I wanted
to kiss her on the forehead.
- I went up one step of the stairs.
- Yes.
Then I turned around,
but I was still smaller than her.
That made me feel
a little embarrassed.
- That's a funny story.
- I felt...
- I felt a little embarrassed.
- That was good.
- Good. You're doing great.
- Was it good?
It was good.
Also, I like someone
who's pleasant and cheerful.
So Min is very cheerful and tall.
I'm small and gloomy.
I'm not your type, Sae Ho.
So Min is right.
- That's not true.
- I'm not a cheerful person.
- Ji Eun seems very cheerful.
- Just eat with him.
Yes, I'm quite cheerful.
You're tall too.
- I'm small though.
- How tall are you?
- I'm short.
- She doesn't want his attention.
- You're short?
- Yes, I'm short.
- But you seem tall.
- You don't seem short.
- I'm only 165cm tall.
- Oh, you're quite tall.
- You're very tall for me.
- I'm too short.
- You're tall for me.
- She's not interested in you.
- You should do better than that.
- That's funny.
- "You should do better than that."
- Right.
By the way, the smell of someone's
cologne is filling up the bus.
It's Sae Ho.
Gosh, seriously.
Oh, great.
This is a barbecue restaurant.
I'm so hungry.
I've been here before.
They serve top-quality Korean beef,
Sae Ho.
- The food is good here, Suk Jin.
- Right?
Oh, my. Something smells good.
- Great.
- Really? You've been here before?
- I don't smell anything.
- I've been here before.
The dishes on the first menu
that will fill your stomach are...
top quality Korean beef
and naengmyeon.
Naengmyeon.
Sounds great.
It looks nice.
(Cool naengmyeon
and fresh, tasty Korean beef)
- Do we have enough money for this?
- Is this okay?
The result of the mission will
determine the prices of the dishes.
So the money we have... I see.
Oh, we need enough money to eat it.
The first mission is
Calculating with a Shaky Hand.
You will use a calculator...
with a low-frequency massager
on one hand...
to answer the given math question.
- We can use a calculator?
- Yes.
- We don't calculate mentally?
- That's right.
Good. So Min, we can do this.
- We'll use our fingers. Right.
- Yes. So we can do this.
The fastest team...
- to get the right answer will win.
- Okay.
- There will be three rounds.
- Got it.
The team captains will go first.
We'll start with Sae Ho and Ji Eun.
- Okay.
- Go, Ji Eun!
- Let's do this!
- I'll try my best to win.
Sae Ho must be determined to win.
It's just a game,
so I hope you understand me, Ji Eun.
I enjoy using
a low-frequency massager.
That's great. We'll get to eat.
As long as you give me food to eat,
I won't ever leave your team.
- All right.
- I'll stay on this team forever.
- I'm good at games like this.
- You are?
- I'm okay.
- Oh, my gosh.
I'm good at games like this.
Endure it.
- Don't worry.
- Okay.
Ji Eun, let us have some meat.
- I know. I'm hungry.
- Good.
- Ji Eun.
- Let us have some meat.
I really want to eat some meat
and naengmyeon.
Of course.
- I'll make sure we'll eat the food.
- Good.
- Let's eat.
- Oh, gosh.
- It's too intense.
- Hey.
- Is it that intense?
- It makes your arm shake like that?
- It's too intense.
- Ji Eun.
- What is this? It's too intense.
- Ji Eun, remain calm.
Come on, Sae Ho.
- That'd make the game more fun.
- Oh, my. This is fun.
- My gosh. Is it that intense?
- Let's eat some beef.
- Ready. Go.
- Gosh!
(Round One begins.)
- Hold on.
- Ji Eun, start calculating.
- That's a lot of numbers.
- What's that?
My goodness. What's that?
- Let me count. Is it 100,000,000?
- It's difficult.
Should I use only one hand?
Am I allowed to use both hands?
- You can't use both hands.
- Only one hand?
(Falling)
(His hand keeps shaking.)
(His calculator fell off.)
- It doesn't seem easy.
- It seems difficult.
Hold on a second. It's too intense.
- Hey.
- You can't use both hands.
- Only one hand?
- You can use only one hand.
- Oh, no.
- It's 342 million and...
- I can't do it.
- That doesn't look easy.
Gosh. It's too intense.
Hey, Ji Eun.
Hey.
- He's struggling too. Slow down.
- Hey, Ji Eun.
All right.
(Be quiet.)
Ji Eun, get it together.
The last one. Take your time.
My gosh. It's so hard.
- How should I do that?
- It's hard.
- Keep your arm off the table.
- Ji Eun.
Really?
- That makes it even harder.
- How can I do this, then?
Sae Ho, hurry up.
What are you doing?
- That one is Ji Eun's calculator.
- I see. Ji Eun, you're doing great.
- Ji Eun.
- It's about enduring the pain.
- Oh, my.
- Ji Eun, focus.
How can I do this, then?
- Sae Ho, hurry up.
- Oh, I see.
(Ji Eun starts entering
the 2nd number 1st.)
(Team Ji Eun is doing great
from the beginning.)
- Oh, my.
- Ji Eun, focus.
She's going to win.
Zero, five, two, one...
Zero, five, two, one, one...
- Zero, five, two, one, one...
- Look at Sae Ho.
(Zero, five, two, one)
(Zero, five, two, one, one)
- Zero, five, two, one...
- Look at Sae Ho. He's confused.
- One.
- Sae Ho is confused.
- Minus...
- He's entering a different number.
- Two, eight, one, zero.
- Look at Sae Ho's face.
- Two, eight, one...
- What's with his lips?
- Zero, seven...
- He's really bad at this.
- Sae Ho entered the wrong number.
- Ji Eun, you're doing great.
- Ji Eun, keep going.
- Number nine is missing.
(He moved on to the 3rd number
without fixing the 2nd number.)
- Two, three...
- Sae Ho entered the wrong number.
- Ji Eun, you're doing great.
- One.
- Am I doing well?
- Ji Eun, keep going.
- She's doing really well.
- Nine, nine, one, zero.
- Nine, nine...
- Sae Ho is so slow.
- My, she's so fast.
- One...
- I think she's...
- Zero.
I didn't put my arm on the table.
- That's not what I meant.
- One, zero, four...
- Ji Eun, keep going.
- I mean...
I think mine is more intense
than hers.
- Ji Eun is doing so well.
- Mine is intense too.
- Four, two, three...
- It seems really hard.
- One.
- You're doing great.
- Sae Ho, you know you can do this.
- Keep going.
- It's 7, 3, 5, 6, 2, 7, 3, 4.
- Overcome it.
- It's 5, 1, 6, 8, 2, 3, 4, 3, 4.
- Oh, no.
Oh, no. What should I do?
- You can do it if you focus.
- One, two, three?
- I think I tapped the wrong button.
- Did you?
Why is that bracket there?
A bracket? Then delete it. Hurry.
- How do I do that?
- Go back and delete it.
How do I go back... Oh, no.
- Okay!
- Gosh.
- Hey, Ji Eun!
- How do I go back... Oh, no.
(She reset her calculator.)
- Hey!
- I'll do it really quickly.
- Three, four, two...
- Sae Ho, hurry up!
- Why did you do that?
Are you going to let us
starve to death?
- Eight, four, nine.
- Ji Eun!
Ji Eun, I'll teach you a lesson
if I don't get to eat.
- Come on. Seven, seven, two, zero.
- What should I tap?
Seven, seven, two, zero, three.
Two, eight, one.
- Two, eight, one.
- I'm done.
- Tap the equal button!
(Meanwhile, Sae Ho is done!)
I'm done.
- Seven, two, three...
- How do we delete a number?
(Incorrect!)
- Incorrect.
- He got the wrong answer.
- Okay.
- Start over again.
- Darn it.
- One, zero, four.
- Gosh!
Why is he so bad at calculating
when he's a calculative person?
- Why is it incorrect?
- Minus.
- Take your time.
- One, two, three, one.
- Two...
- Hey, Ji Eun!
- Take your time.
- Ji Eun, tap the "C" button.
Sae Ho is doing it all over again.
So take your time.
- Ji Eun, come on.
- All right.
Two, one. I didn't enter
the wrong number. Oh, dear.
Come on. Ji Eun, keep it together.
- The last one. Take your time.
- Plus.
- Five, five.
- Ji Eun, you've got this!
Sae Ho, divide the numbers
into four sections.
- Ji Eun, you've got this!
- She's almost done.
Eight, two, three.
No, it's 8, 2, 1.
- Eight, two, three.
- Eight, two, one.
- Four, three, four.
- It's 8, 2...
- It's 8, 2, 3, 4, 3, 4.
- That's good! She's doing well.
- Good.
- You're doing great!
- Ji Eun, we'll get to eat.
- Four.
- Ji Eun!
- Tap the equal button!
- Please get the correct answer.
- Three, four. Equals...
- Tap the equal button.
- The equal button.
- Is this correct?
(She's finally done!)
Tell us.
(Did she get the correct answer
on her second attempt?)
(Incorrect)
- Oh, gosh!
- Oh, no.
- Take your time.
- Start over again.
- Do it again.
- Ji Eun, start over again.
- Okay! Sae Ho, take your time.
- Start over again.
- The first number is wrong.
- He moved on to the next number.
- You're right.
- Three.
- Four.
- Hey, Ji Eun.
- Three, four.
- Seven, seven, two, zero.
- Three, zero, five...
- I'm done.
(Sae Ho is done again!)
- I think he got it right this time.
- Three, zero, five, one, two.
- He got the correct answer.
- Yes!
(Sae Ho got the correct answer.)
- Why don't you guys look happy?
- Hooray!
- Did you get the right answer?
- Yes, I did.
- Give us food, please.
- Why don't my teammates look happy?
- We're elated.
- What a shame.
(Disappointed)
- Why don't you guys look happy?
- Come on, Ji Eun.
- Please turn this off now.
- Ji Eun.
- Please turn it off.
- Why don't they look happy?
Come on, Ji Eun.
(Screaming)
- No!
- Oh, is it the opposite? Okay.
- All right.
- Ji Eun's reaction was so funny.
I like her reaction.
- I'm sweating.
- That wasn't easy.
- I feel bad. I'm sorry.
- It's so hard.
- By the way, Sae Ho.
- Yes?
- It wasn't professional.
- It was so intense.
- What?
- I can't believe you beat her.
What do you mean,
it wasn't professional?
- Good job.
- Thank you.
What a shame.
I gave her a chance.
- Where are your manners?
- Enjoy your meal.
It didn't hurt so much,
but it kept tingling.
- It keeps tingling.
- Shall we...
- I know how that feels.
- move on to the next round?
You look thinner now.
- Really?
- Yes.
Your face looks sharper now.
Shall we move on to the next round?
The second round is
Team Ji Eun versus Team Jong Kook.
One player from each team will
play the game.
- How about Seok Sam?
- Okay.
- What do you think?
- Shall I do it?
- Gosh.
- Don't you think...
- we should win this round?
- Yes, Suk Jin?
Let Haha do it.
Okay. Haha will do it.
I think he should go first.
- Only then will I have a chance.
- Okay.
- Haha will do it.
- I like to see them like that.
- Go ahead, Haha.
- Okay.
- Let's do him a favor.
- Jong Kook would say yes...
Maybe I'll win.
Of course. You'll win.
- I must win.
- Right.
- Right. You should win.
- I'll win so that we can eat.
Suk Jin, this feels great.
Jae Suk is enjoying it.
- Does it feel good?
- Yes.
- What is he doing?
- Are you getting therapy right now?
- I'm getting physical therapy.
- Exactly.
It's used for physical therapy.
- Hey, go away.
- I hope he'll win.
- Come on. I'm on your team.
- I know what you'll do.
I know you're going to increase
the intensity all at once.
I won't do that. Come here.
Wait. I'm afraid.
- Come on.
- No.
(Scaredy-cats always scream first.)
(And they overact.)
Gosh. It's no joke.
What's wrong with my arm?
- Increase it gradually.
- He's being a scaredy-cat.
I don't think it's as intense
as it was when I did it.
Gosh, I really hate this.
Hey, don't do that.
- Sit down. I should...
- Don't do that.
It should be the same as Haha's.
(He increases the intensity.)
- Stop it.
- Jae Suk is...
standing there... Jae Suk,
are you playing a game or something?
(Fiddling)
- Jae Suk?
- Increase it gradually.
He looks like a DJ.
- Are you playing a game?
- He looks like a DJ.
(He's enjoying low-frequency DJing
that makes Seok Sam dance.)
Gosh. Stop it.
- Come on, Haha.
- Come on.
- Stop it.
- Hey.
Gosh. I'm not faking it.
- It shouldn't be that intense.
- I'm not faking it.
- It's not that intense.
- Are you serious?
- I'm not faking it, Jae Suk.
- It's not that intense.
Haha, why is your left hand shaking?
- Hey, that's enough.
- I'm not faking it!
The intensity is the same. Look.
Hey, but...
(He's screaming
unnecessarily loudly.)
- What's wrong with him?
- It's the same as yours.
- I'm sure he's faking it.
- All right.
- Hey, how intense...
- Fine. Go back to your seat.
- Go back to your seat.
- Right. Give up.
(Embarrassed)
- There you go.
- I'm sorry.
- This is embarrassing.
- Go.
It was...
- Gosh, seriously.
- It was unbearable.
- Haha gave up.
- He can't play this game.
- He gave up.
- My gosh.
- I felt like I was going to die.
- What's wrong with him?
- Gosh, that scaredy-cat.
- I can't believe him.
Haha is the weakest of all.
- Gosh.
- Hey, Haha.
- He can't...
- Even Ji Eun did it.
Okay. That's just right.
- Are you two ready?
- It should be that intense.
- Hey, go easy on me.
- Keep your arm off the table.
- Ready. Go.
- Good. Go, Seok Sam.
- Gosh, this is...
- You must win.
Seok Sam, if you don't win,
we won't get to eat.
- One, four, two, one,
- One at a time. Take your time.
- You can do this.
- nine, four, five, six, seven.
- You must not use the other hand.
- Exactly.
- Jong Kook, don't hold the phone.
- Hey.
- You shouldn't do that.
- I'm not allowed to do that? Okay.
- Come on.
- Plus.
- What's wrong with you?
- Why are you being so sly?
- He entered the wrong number.
- How do I delete a number?
- And 2, 1, 3, 9, 4, 5.
(The digitally illiterate Jong Kook
faced a hurdle already.)
- Two... He's...
- Tap the arrow.
- The delete button.
- This one?
- In the top right corner.
- This one? I see.
- Three.
- Three, nine, four, five? Three.
- Suk Jin's is less intense.
- Two, one, three, nine...
- No, it's the same as Jong Kook's.
- Eight, seven, three, five.
- Gosh, it hurts.
- I'll read it for you.
- It's the same as Jong Kook's.
- Eight, seven, three, five.
- Eight, seven, three, five. Minus.
- Minus.
- One, four, five, six. Minus.
- Gosh, this is hard.
- Am I taking the lead?
- One, four, five, six, three.
- Jae Suk is reading it too.
- It's 1, 4, 5, 6, 3, 9, 8, 2, 7.
(Jong Kook is entering
the right numbers.)
Jong Kook, delete one more number.
- No, delete one more number.
- Behind that number.
- Five, six, three.
- One, four, five, six, three.
- Jong Kook.
- What?
I said, it was 1, 4, 5, 6, 3.
- Are you sure...
- No, delete it.
- Whom are you talking to?
- Delete it.
- Jong Kook is doing it right.
- That one is mine.
Oh, that one is yours?
I thought it was the other.
- Jong Kook is doing well.
- I was mistaken.
- I thought that one was his.
- What was that?
- What's up with him today?
- I'm sorry.
- What's the matter with you?
- Jong Kook is doing great.
Right. You're doing great.
- Plus... Minus?
- It's perfect.
- Minus?
- Put number 5 between 4 and 6.
- Delete.
- One, four... Oh, it wasn't seven.
- Delete the numbers.
- How do I delete it?
- Isn't there a button for deleting?
- Don't tap the "C" button.
- Tap the "C" button!
- The "C" button!
- Suk Jin, tap the "C" button!
- That's correct.
- You missed number four. Delete it.
- Eight, five, four.
- Darn it.
- Three, two...
- Eight, five, four, three, nine.
- Three, two, five, nine.
- Four, three, nine.
- Nine. Next.
- Seven, six, zero, zero, seven.
- Seven, one, nine, nine, four.
(Shaking)
(He can't move his finger
as he wants.)
- Seven, one, nine, nine, four!
- Minus.
- Five, six, four, two.
- Next.
- Four, four.
Zero, zero, one, one.
Four. Plus.
- Plus.
- One, one.
- Plus. Gosh, it hurts.
- Three.
- Is it correct?
- Three, two, five, nine, seven.
- Correct!
- Jong Kook got the correct answer.
(Jong Kook got it right.)
My gosh.
Darn it. Hey, you try it.
- Why couldn't you do better?
- Try it.
- Our team keeps losing.
- I'm worried.
You should've played in this round.
- I should've. I'm the ace.
- Exactly.
You can't be sure.
You're not the ace.
- My gosh.
- I'm the ace.
You would've done a poor job.
If you can't endure it, go home.
- What are you doing, Haha?
- Gosh, seriously.
- So Min.
- What's wrong with him?
Hey, Haha is doing great.
- Eight, eight.
- So Min, you made a mistake.
- Wait.
- So Min, delete the whole thing.
That's the wrong number.
Eight, eight.
So Min, delete the whole thing.
- Haha got the correct answer.
- Yes!
(Haha got the correct answer.)
- Hey, I'm impressed.
- He pulled it off.
- I'm proud of you, Haha.
- I pulled it off.
- Are you okay?
- Yes. I made it.
- I'm sorry. We lost.
- It's okay.
- We lost. What do we do?
- I'm sorry.
- You did better than me.
Each team will receive...
- How much do we get?
- twenty each.
How much is this?
We'll now reveal the exchange rate.
See? The money...
- But...
- Nice.
The exchange rate is high.
(Current Exchange Rate)
- You're right.
- To eat the Korean beef,
- we need to pay 60 bills.
- Yes, 60.
With that currency, right?
If we want to pay
with Ji Eun's notes.
How much meat will be served?
Not much, I guess.
The exchange rate
is the worst right now.
Let's wait until the rate improves.
The money...
- Sure.
- Let's not eat for now.
- Not at all?
- That's right.
- We should wait for a better time.
- Until the exchange rate improves.
This is so annoying.
What should I do?
(He's 5 bills short.)
- I only have 20.
- Let's do that.
What about the money
you received before the game?
I don't want to spend
all of it just yet.
I should've received Jong Kook's
when I had the chance.
- We can cash other things in.
- Who wishes to exchange...
- What's better?
- Se Chan, do you wear a watch?
Sae Ho, you can exchange
your watch for more money.
- Do they take watches?
- Luxurious watches,
- shoes, and...
- I can't believe it.
- You're right.
- You can cash it in for money.
And even gold.
I'm glad I accessorized today.
Why don't we sell a few things?
Maybe our shoes.
- Do you take gold?
- Yes.
We're only being generous
because Ji Eun's our team leader.
So Min, I'd like to exchange
what I have as well.
(He visits the exchange counter
when he's practically broke.)
- A dollar.
- The gold.
- Just a dollar? Seriously?
- Really?
Here.
- These are gold.
- I should at least get 50 dollars.
(He carefully submits
the brass cutlery.)
It's 14k gold.
- It's stainless...
- No, it's gold.
It's gold.
- What are you up to?
- I'm selling gold.
- Gold...
- Hold on a second.
- When did you steal these?
- You're selling cutlery?
- Is it not allowed?
- No.
Sae Ho...
How much is Sae Ho's watch worth?
- A dollar.
- A dollar?
- Is this worth only a dollar?
- Only a dollar?
- Everything's worth a dollar.
- Is that so?
- Come on.
- Really?
Will I get a dollar
for this 50-dollar bill?
- A dollar for a 50-dollar bill?
- Seriously?
(The price is knocked down
in the Running Man universe.)
I'm next.
(Ji Eun's at the exchange counter.)
- Just a second.
- I can't believe this.
Are you buying something?
- No, I'm selling something.
- I see.
Here's my smart watch.
(What she wishes to exchange)
That's two dollars.
Three dollars.
Four dollars.
(What she wishes to exchange)
Five dollars.
She took off all her earrings.
(She's submitting
all the jewelry she has on.)
Five dollars.
We can't take the smart watch.
I was told that you'd accept it.
(What fluctuates in price
can't be submitted.)
Are you sure this is gold?
Yes, it is.
They won't take your watch?
- They won't.
- Why not?
(Stealthily)
This is silver.
It's silver.
You won't take lip balm, right?
What else do I have?
(She even submits
the 50-dollar bill she has.)
(I'll give you 2 dollars
for everything.)
- Thank you.
- I can't believe you.
(With everything she had,
she manages to get 2 dollars.)
Why did you tell us
not to eat anything beforehand?
I can't believe these guys.
- Seriously.
- Jong Seo, here.
These pants are Calvin Klein.
Why not when it's a luxury brand?
(Urgency has him flashing
his chubby tummy.)
Guys, check this out.
Isn't Calvin Klein a luxury brand?
- It is.
- I wanted to exchange it, but...
It lost its value
when you put it on.
They wouldn't take it.
- You showed them that?
- Calvin Klein...
- Come on, Se Chan.
- I can't believe you showed him.
- Then I'll...
- Which brand is it?
- Armani.
Right, I know that brand.
Armani.
Why won't you accept underwear
from luxurious brands?
I'm also wearing Armani.
- I'll take this off.
- Armani.
- They won't take underwear.
- What about this?
He must've known in advance
to have this much gold.
- This is real gold though.
- Just so you know,
you won't get these back
once you have them exchanged.
You won't get them back.
- What?
- They won't give them back.
- Really?
- Viewers will criticize us...
- for not keeping things real.
- What are you talking about?
It doesn't make sense
for them to return these.
You shouldn't return
his gold bracelet.
(The nail in the coffin)
- This...
- That made him anxious.
You can't return his bracelet.
- You have to be genuine, Sae Ho.
- Hold on.
Why would I waste
this expensive bracelet here?
Then don't exchange them for money.
- Not those you want to keep.
- I'll hand in the bracelet.
Is a 50-dollar bill
worth a dollar too?
(Sae Ho exchanges his gold bracelet
for a dollar.)
- Are you not going to eat?
- No.
For some reason, I'm not interested.
(Team Jong Kook that's in 1st place
is the one to save up the money.)
It's better to save up the money
for later on.
Director, hold on.
(Jae Suk visits
the exchange counter.)
Can I buy the gold bracelet?
Can I buy it for a dollar?
Then I'll take it.
Jae Suk, here. Buy it with this.
- But that's my money.
- Buy the bracelet.
(They're hoping to put on
a fun show.)
- There.
- Thank you.
- Hey, you can't wear that.
- I bought it.
- Why would you buy that?
I bought it for a dollar.
Why?
It was only a dollar.
Hey, get over here!
Gosh, sorry about that.
- Let me help you.
- But I bought it.
You can't let someone else buy it.
- Good for you.
- Because...
- Nicely done.
I'd like to get this
for a dollar as well.
It's better to buy it
when it's cheap.
- The exchange rate might go up.
- Sure.
- Is it Jae Suk's now?
- I bought it for a dollar.
Do you have any idea
how expensive this is?
You shouldn't have sold it.
I'll take it back for a dollar.
- What?
- I'll sell it for two dollars.
(The gold is now
double its original price.)
- Nicely done.
- That's still a bargain though.
- If not...
- It's still cheap for two dollars.
I'll sell this for a dollar
and 40 of your bills.
- Because...
- Hold on.
Sae Ho's actually worried.
- But...
- No way, right?
- He won't give it back.
- I'm not kidding.
You sold it just now.
Giving you back the goods
could get us into trouble.
I'll give you two dollars for it,
then.
Right now would be preferable.
I can't believe we have people...
who are trying to profit
in the middle.
Why do we have people doing that?
Everything here
is worth a dollar today.
- Right.
- And Sae Ho handed in the goods.
(He hands in a 50-dollar bill
for another dollar.)
- At a bargain price.
- I made a purchase.
- I asked if it was possible.
- Good for you.
- And I was told it was allowed.
- It's so mean.
Give back my bracelet.
- Here.
- No way!
Will I get a dollar
if I sell this again?
(An exchange where
you spend two dollars to gain one)
- Don't buy it this time.
- But...
This is the definition
of creative economy.
- That's how you earn money.
- Don't just idly sit there.
- What an investment.
- Exactly.
I'll buy it again if I can.
- Then...
- Unbelievable.
Without doing anything...
- Naengmyeon.
- A bowl of naengmyeon...
and two portions of beef.
How's that?
- How's that?
- I love it.
Let's have our fill.
We're having a feast
despite finishing last.
Exactly. We finished last
in the game.
Aren't the other teams going to eat?
- No.
- No, we're going to save up.
- We don't have the money.
- We'll sit this one out.
- So Min.
- I'll sell my shoes for money.
Are we the only ones eating?
Just us?
- Hold on.
- Are you selling your shoes?
- I'll buy those too.
- What?
These won't fit you though.
Can I sell these?
- Of course.
- We need to retrieve those shoes.
I don't have a dollar though.
Can you lend me 20 bills?
- The Sae Ho bill?
- Yes.
I'll exchange 40 of the bills
for a dollar and buy the shoes.
- I really want those.
- Sure.
Thanks, So Min.
- How many do you need?
- Twenty will do.
Okay, good.
I can buy these back, right?
(Sae Ho sells his shoes
for a dollar.)
(There's a reason
he desperately needed the dollar.)
- There. So Min.
- Go ahead.
- Have the barbecue.
- Are you sure?
- Really?
- Go ahead.
Can I make a purchase?
- What's with him?
- What about you?
Go ahead.
I'm having barbecue
with a friend later today.
It's like I said. You never know.
- If he's nice...
- They've never been this close.
She might change her mind.
- People slowly grow on you.
- Exactly.
Ji Eun, what's your take
on men like that?
They impress me.
That sounded robotic just now.
- Ji Eun.
- You're the best!
- That sounded soulless.
- That's cool of him.
I'll buy the shoes.
I have 40. It's all there.
(Se Chan's at the counter
buying the shoes.)
Thank you.
These shoes aren't easy
to come by these days.
I can't believe it.
I have those too, you know.
Hold on. Him...
These shoes aren't easy
to come by these days.
Can you believe
that I got this for a dollar?
(Can you believe
that I got this for a dollar?)
(These shoes
aren't in stock anymore.)
They fit perfectly!
How did you pay for it?
You can get a dollar
for 40 of the Sae Ho bills.
That can get you these.
These are for us to keep.
- Se Chan, pay me back, okay?
- Try those on.
- Sure thing.
- Why would you lend him the money?
He badly wanted those shoes.
- Sae Ho...
- But I sold them for you.
- Why would you help him out?
- You can't take it back though.
- He badly wanted the shoes.
- He badly wanted those.
- He asked in an adorable way.
- They fit like gloves.
He expressed his wishes.
They'll look even cooler
if you fold them at the heel.
- Like this?
- Don't you dare.
- Don't.
- Okay, my gosh.
I'll have the Korean beef.
Forget it. Give it back.
You can't take back
what you gave me.
- I'll have the Korean beef.
- The Korean beef?
The shoes look great on you.
- Right?
- Please bring in the food.
- Let's eat.
- Let's do this.
Check out the naengmyeon.
This is crazy.
The marbling is a work of art.
Here we go. My gosh.
The beef already looks delicious.
- This smells like the holidays.
- The marbling is a work of art.
(He tries a bite.)
(So good!)
It's delicious.
This is to die for.
My gosh.
Have some of the naengmyeon.
(It was worth selling her jewelry.)
- Isn't it amazing?
- It is.
This is incredible.
- It melts in your mouth.
- This is unbelievable.
- The meat is incredible.
- It looks so good.
- My gosh.
- Unbelievable.
Why wouldn't you have this?
- It's so good.
- You should all have some.
- I'm not hungry at all.
- As if.
- He looks starving to me.
- You're not hungry?
Jong Kook,
you should eat when others do.
It's just that...
You know how I am.
I would eat if I was hungry.
Haha looks hungry to me.
I'd rather have
something better later.
- But this is to die for.
- Come on.
Don't be so calculative.
One should eat when one's hungry.
Just eat when you have the chance.
This is delicious.
- Try the naengmyeon.
- All right.
- What do you prefer?
- The spring onions.
- Spring onions?
- Yes.
I'd like more.
- This is more than enough.
- I love them a lot.
(The guilt has So Min
offering a wrap to him.)
This is incredible.
Here.
(Not you)
Enjoy.
Enjoy, Se Chan. Is it good?
It's good, isn't it?
I'm glad...
there's someone else
that has it worse than I do.
I'm glad Sae Ho's here.
Do you not have slippers at least?
Wear a plastic bag or something.
- Give me one and I'll wear it.
- Yes. Wear a plastic bag.
- It happened a lot in the past.
- Yes.
- Wearing plastic bags.
- Right.
- It happened a lot in the past?
- Yes.
- His shoe is cool.
- What's that?
But isn't it too big?
Do you not have a small one?
Are these boots or what?
Because it's winter.
- I'll do it.
- Sae Ho...
- Do you think he's trash or what?
- Give it to me.
- Isn't this a garbage bag?
Just put Sae Ho in it.
It's too big.
Are these long boots?
(They didn't save the material
when making long boots.)
Sae Ho has a sense
of fashion indeed.
But...
It's done.
- Let's go to the next spot.
- You...
- The plastic bag is...
- This is warm.
- That's cool.
- Is it okay?
It looks cool.
Let's go.
I got no shoes.
(The runway is connected
to the outside.)
I should just watch out for my feet.
Okay.
(A fashionista who can pull off
even unusual boots)
That looks cool.
You look like Puss in Boots.
We had meat thanks to Ji Eun.
We could have it thanks to Ji Eun.
I'll try to collect more gold.
- Ji Eun...
- I won't leave Team Ji Eun.
I guess you switched the team.
- Suk Jin, you too?
- Of course.
- I guess you switched the team.
- I got to eat meat.
You switched the team
when we weren't there. Oh, no.
Look at Ji Eun.
- Sae Ho.
- Yes.
This is not how you make
people laugh these days.
(What?)
Jae Suk.
Honey, people make others laugh
with their talk these days.
- This is not it.
- You wrapped it nicely.
- Why did he take off his shoes?
- What are you doing?
I'm a semi-professional.
Do you think I'd want to do it this way?
- Sae Ho is working very hard.
- I also want to be funny...
with my fancy talk.
- Honey.
- This is not what I intended.
You should make people laugh
with your talk these days.
My gosh.
Why are you sitting there, baby?
I...
- He became her baby.
- "Baby."
He doesn't know what to say.
- He's perplexed.
- She went for it.
- It's not like that.
- I should protect you from behind.
So MIn.
It's Se Chan who is in your heart.
- But you're using Sae Ho.
- I know.
It's a little...
I sold my shoes for meat.
You can't give money to Se Chan
for the shoes.
- What are you doing?
- We're best friends, you know?
Se Chan, it's amazing
how you got the shoes for a dollar.
But let me ask you one thing.
What if he calls me
after the shoot...
and tells me
to give them back to him?
- He can't do that.
- It's a little... Right?
- Because...
- It's a promise with the people.
That's... Yes.
- "A promise with the people?"
- It is. You got them for a dollar.
"A promise with the people."
I like that.
- It's nice, isn't it?
- Yes.
Ji Eun, don't you have
to get the earrings back?
- She's amazing.
- It's okay.
- Really?
- Yes.
I should join Team Ji Eun.
- She's so nice.
- No, I'm not.
Of course, she should be nice.
She's on the show.
- Don't be so mean.
- Suk Jin.
(He's criticized for being
habitually mean to guests.)
(Desperately looking away)
Honestly, you can't judge someone
when you've just met once.
- You don't know.
- That's true.
- Yes.
- Shut it, you jerk!
- Why?
- Stop.
I said you were right.
That's true, everyone, right?
- You don't know at first.
- Guys.
- But let me say this.
- That's true.
Ji Eun is highly likely
to be a nice person.
- Yes.
- Very likely.
You're going to see
how fake his life is, Ji Eun.
- Look at Suk Jin's fake life.
- I'm serious.
- You'll see.
- It's not like that.
What?
Floss your teeth as you ate meat.
- Floss?
- Why are you asking her to do it?
Because she had meat. Just in case.
- Gosh. Ji Eun.
- I'm fine.
Flossing on a variety show
is the first time.
- It's...
- Should I...
- show it?
- First time on a variety show.
I'll show you
if you're okay with that.
Yes. It'll be fine.
(Disturbance warning)
I can show you.
You should use floss.
I use that one too.
- What?
- It's the same one.
- I use that one too.
- Why is it not convincing?
- It's so forced.
- I get easily moved, but...
If he doesn't like it,
it means he really doesn't like it.
- Yes.
- Look at this.
You should use floss like this.
You said people don't try
to be funny like this these days.
You should be funny with your talk.
- Floss...
- This is subtle.
- Is it floss between his teeth?
- Yes.
Ji Eun is horrified.
- Ji Eun...
It's not the Jae Suk she imagined.
Floss.
- It's an interdental toothbrush.
- This is...
This is very...
- It hurts.
- Look at him.
Let me pull it for you.
(Stubborn teeth that don't let go
of the floss easily.)
- It's an interdental toothbrush.
- You got an interdental toothbrush.
It's not teeth special today.
(Laughing)
Jae Suk's teeth
are seriously misaligned though.
They're so misaligned.
How can they be like that?
So Min.
That's...
- Seriously,
- What are you talking about?
he must've worked so hard
with his teeth.
- They're so misaligned.
- He's a great guy.
I can still...
Even if his teeth are misaligned,
it's fine as long as he speaks well.
- I mean...
- He's good with that.
You wrapped two people
around your finger.
How many people
are you going to wrap?
And for Jong Kook,
as the World Cup season started,
starting from the game
between Uruguay and Korea,
he has a lot to think about.
- I do. Right. Thank you.
- So don't mess with him.
- Right?
- Yes.
Does he have anything to do with it?
- He should come up with strategies.
- I should make plans.
Why does he have to come up
with strategies?
- I should comment and stuff.
- Yes.
I need to talk about it.
I know a lot about soccer.
Suk Jin, what's your prediction
for this World Cup?
I'll make precise predictions.
First, we'll win the game
against Uruguay 2 to 1.
- Why?
- Korea never failed...
at the first game. Almost never.
We either won or tied.
I guess you didn't watch
World Cup Brazil.
What happened at World Cup Brazil?
(Fake)
(His fake life
is immediately exposed.)
This is how you do it.
- "This is how you do it."
- Did you not watch it back then?
- Did you not watch the World Cup?
- Do you think I didn't?
- He just doesn't remember it.
- And...
we will win against Ghana.
- We will lose against Portugal.
- We'll lose?
- Then it's 2 wins and 1 loss.
- We'll go to the round of 16.
At the second restaurant,
I'm going to eat no matter what.
Let's go to eat.
My stomach is empty.
I have a sour stomach.
It feels like they have good food.
Let's eat.
(Seafood soup restaurant "H"
in Gangnam)
As expected of Sae Ho.
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- Look.
- It looks so delicious.
The dishes we got this time are
raw lobster that melts in your mouth...
and spicy seafood soup.
(Meaty raw lobster
and spicy seafood soup)
Is this one dollar?
Per one piece.
One dollar for a bite.
Is this one dollar as well?
- I want this.
- This looks delicious.
I should eat lobster.
- I can't.
- I should eat lobster at least.
That's mine.
- Aren't the shoes pretty?
- They're so pretty.
- They're perfect for you.
- The shoes...
- suit you.
- The shoes look expensive.
Where did you put the insoles?
- I took them out.
- Where are they?
I paid for them too.
So where are they?
I have them. Why?
- Do you really have them?
- Yes.
(Threatening)
I should wear them for the shoot.
- Do you really have them?
- Yes.
(Threatening)
He's mad.
I bought them for a dollar earlier.
Don't make me look weird
in front of many people.
- But...
- You punk.
Producer, I got them for a dollar.
- Right.
- Do I give it back after the shoot?
- Stop.
- No, you don't have to.
- It's going to be a problem.
- It isn't how you make them laugh.
Sorry?
He said it isn't
how you make people laugh.
- Sit down.
- Honey.
- You should talk to be funny.
- I always talked.
That's not how you make people
laugh these days.
The audio director told you
to sit down...
as you keep making
rustling noises. It's loud.
(The guy in plastic bag boots
is so loud.)
(Quietly)
That's cool.
(The shoes most hated
by the audio director)
He looks like a hero.
If anyone wants to switch teams,
you can go to the team you want.
- But Ji Eun...
- All of us can be on the same team.
Ji Eun gave her earrings...
- for her team.
- Yes. You shouldn't switch.
My gosh.
Why do you want to come?
This is crazy.
What is it?
(So Min from Team Sae Ho
quietly gets up at that moment.)
- Ji Eun... Then you come here.
- Are you going to that side?
I'll give you my seat.
- You came here?
- Please sit on the next chair.
You came here?
Suk Jin is coming.
He's coming.
- Do you want it?
- Yes, we want it.
This is nice.
- This is cool.
- Ji Eun. This is for you.
It's okay. We'll be fine on our own.
- Did Ji Hyo come here?
- What's happening to Sae Ho?
- Is Sae Ho alone?
- He's by himself.
- Sae Ho.
- Am I doing it alone?
(The guy in plastic bag boots
is left alone.)
Is Sae Ho alone?
Then I'll go to his side.
Okay. Let's create a balance.
- We need to be balanced.
- Right.
- This is how you switched teams.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- I like it.
Let's have seafood soup.
- Let's do it.
- Let's cheer up.
- We can do it.
- I'll make sure to feed you.
- I'll sell something.
The mission for this round
is Water Splash in Silence.
Each team will play Cry in Silence.
Whenever you get the question right,
you can remove a stick...
from the water bomb hat
the leaders of other teams are wearing.
The game ends when you make
water bombs...
- for both leaders explode.
- Okay.
(They should make all water bombs
explode to succeed.)
Three teams will try it and will be
ranked based on the time they take.
Who is going to try first?
- We'll go second.
- Okay. Then Team Jong Kook first.
- Okay.
- We first?
(Team Jong Kook will try first.)
Gosh, this is complicated.
Oh, my, it's loud.
(Two teammates are wearing headsets
to play Cry in Silence.)
- I hear nothing.
- I really can't hear.
- Can you not hear?
- It might explode at once.
- No, I can't.
- Se Chan, scream.
- Okay.
Scream.
(Shouting)
- You got so many gold teeth.
- Yes.
- I should sell them.
- Get ready. Hey.
- Where should I look? That one?
- Hey.
- Okay.
- Get ready. Go.
- Go.
(MBTI)
(Jong Kook has to explain
what MBTI is.)
It's a personality test.
A quote from the Bible?
A test.
- A quote from the Bible?
- This is hard.
A personality test.
- A quote from the Bible?
- A test.
- "Sa."
- He can't hear anything.
- This is impossible.
- A quote from the Bible?
A personality test.
Seoul sightseeing?
This won't do. His eyes lost focus.
(His eyes lost focus.)
- Come out. Let's switch.
- We should switch.
- Switch.
- Switch?
You go in.
- This takes time.
- Yes.
(Urology)
Kkwachu.
Gwangju?
- Kkwachu Hyung.
- Gwangju Station?
(Urology)
Hospital.
- Hospital? One in Gwangju?
- Brother Kkwachu.
There are many hospitals in Gwangju.
Samsung Hospital?
- No.
- Severance Hospital.
- What?
- "Severance Hospital."
- Which department?
Which department?
- You visit the department often.
- Which department?
Cardiothoracic surgery.
- What?
- Cardiothoracic surgery.
- Think of Jae Suk.
- Urology.
(Correct)
- Correct.
- It was...
- He did well.
- Let's go.
- Thank goodness.
- I got goosebumps.
- Ji Eun survived too.
- What are the odds?
This is incredible.
Cho Sae Ho!
- Cho Sae Ho!
- Cho Sae Ho?
Cho Sae Ho!
- Cho Sae Ho!
- Cho Sae Ho?
He gained weight.
No. Losing weight...
- and gaining it back.
- I know.
Shoulders. Narrow shoulders.
Losing weight and gaining it back.
(Annoyed)
- Bloated. His face is bloated.
- No.
He was like this
after losing weight.
- He lost weight and gained it back.
- He gained it back.
- Right now...
- The yo-yo effect.
(The yo-yo effect is correct.)
- The last one.
- Okay.
- Correct.
- Let's do this.
- Why isn't it coming out?
- It isn't coming out.
- The last one.
- Okay.
- Correct.
- Let's do this.
(Ji Eun survived again.)
- Good.
- It isn't coming out.
This is incredible.
- Cho Sae Ho.
- What are the odds?
- Name.
- Cabbage.
- Yes.
- Okay.
(They continue to get
correct answers.)
- Ji Eun.
- It isn't coming out.
- What's going on?
- This makes no sense.
- Hurry up.
- Clogged toilet.
- What do you use then?
Plunger.
- Yes.
- All right.
They are good.
It's a 50-50 chance.
This makes no sense.
- Botox injection.
- Why do you get it?
Wrinkles.
- All right.
- The water needs to come out now.
(Haha finally removes
the last stick.)
- It's coming out.
- No.
It's finally coming out.
- It's coming out.
- All right.
What was the five-letter word?
The last stick did the trick.
- The water came out.
- It came out.
How did it hold out until the end?
It finally came out.
Until the end... I bet we won.
- The water trickled down.
- Seriously.
- Do we give the questions?
- We need to answer them too.
Ji Eun, will you guess?
I will guess the words.
- Get ready.
- What are we going to do?
- Can you do well?
- I will pick the sticks well.
- Set, go.
- They can't hear me.
(Blind date)
- A man...
- and a woman...
- meet.
Lovers?
The first meeting.
What?
- The first meeting.
- Things are getting complicated.
Marriage interview?
- The first.
- Marriage interview.
My goodness.
A man and a woman meet.
- It's an easy one.
- The first.
- Installment savings?
- Marriage?
- My goodness.
- I don't know what to do.
- She can't hear Ji Hyo.
She can't hear Ji Hyo.
- It seems that way.
- I don't know what to do.
She can't hear Ji Hyo.
- A man and a woman.
"Hello."
Be still.
- What?
- You can't act it out.
- It's prohibited.
- Keep your hands behind you.
- Be still.
- What?
- This is too much.
- Hello.
Hello.
(Bowing)
- You can't act it out.
- Hello.
- Marriage interview?
- You can't act it out.
- Seriously.
(Ji Hyo can't hear him.)
- Hello.
I am Song Ji Hyo.
Installment savings.
She keeps saying,
- "Installment savings."
- I am Song Ji Hyo.
This is funny.
This is how you play the game.
Just now...
- No.
- Pass.
- Ji Eun is so funny. "Just now..."
- It was an easy one.
- Pass.
- Pass. I can't hear anything.
It was an easy one.
- Someone...
- This is hard.
- who made a lot of money.
- Oh, no.
Someone who made a lot of money.
Someone who suddenly made
a lot of money.
- A rich person.
- Shrimp.
- An heir.
- Think of another name.
- Carrot?
(Nouveau riche)
(She heard "Carrot.")
- Carrot?
- This is funny.
- Secondhand market?
- Carrot? Secondhand market?
- This is funny.
- This is funny. Good.
- Secondhand market?
That's right.
- No.
- It's incorrect.
- Is it incorrect?
- You are good.
- This is great.
This is great. Ji Eun is good.
- This is funny.
- Someone...
- This is great.
- You are good.
(Other members love
how funny she is.)
- This is funny.
- Someone who suddenly made...
- money.
- Money.
- This person has a lot of money.
- Someone who suddenly made...
- Money.
- a lot of money.
- Yes.
Someone who made a lot of money.
- "Suddenly" is the key.
- This person uses it frivolously.
- Stocks.
- A wealthy person.
Think of another name.
"Suddenly" is the key.
- Suddenly.
- Grandma?
- Suddenly!
- Suddenly.
- Extremely rich.
- "Extremely rich."
- You are getting there.
- Filthy rich.
- Extremely rich.
- Don't give her clues. Stay still.
- Sit down.
- This person suddenly became rich.
- What's the word for it?
Lottery.
- This person suddenly became rich.
- Lottery.
- Totally rich. Totally.
Lottery.
Totally rich?
"Totally rich."
(She got fooled once again.)
(She is like a human sponge
who soaks in all information.)
- Suddenly!
- You are doing great, Ji Eun.
- Lottery.
- I don't know.
- Don't you know?
- Pass.
- Lottery.
- Someone...
- Pass.
- who suddenly made a lot of money.
She said, "Totally rich."
- We had it...
- in the morning.
- Jae Suk...
- Beef.
- Okay. Beef.
- Jae Suk...
sent us this.
Coffee truck.
(Coffee truck)
Take out a stick.
Shall I take out this one?
It isn't spilling.
(Both of them survived.)
- It will take some time.
- All right.
- Yesterday.
(Qatar)
The World Cup.
The...
The World Cup!
W...
- The World Cup.
- W...
- This time, where does it happen?
- This time.
Uruguay.
(Uruguay?)
(The hosting country
of the World Cup suddenly changed.)
- She is good.
- Seriously.
- There you go.
- Ji Eun is good at this.
There you go.
- She is good.
- Ji Eun is good at this.
Which country?
The host. The hosting country.
- Home.
- What's the hosting country?
- The hosting country.
- The hosting country!
- Home.
- The hosting country.
- The World Cup hosting country?
- The World Cup hosting country.
- How did she get that?
(The human sponge
succeeded in making out the words!)
The country that is hosting
the current World Cup?
- That's right.
- Which country is it?
Which country is hosting it?
(Which country is hosting it?)
My goodness.
(The sponge girl's basic question)
- She is good. Ji Eun is good.
- She is good.
- Ji Eun is good.
- She is the best.
- I don't know. Five syllables.
- Okay.
- It doesn't have five syllables.
Two syllables.
- Okay. Pass.
- Pass.
(Hotteok)
- Busan.
- This is hard.
- Seagulls.
- In Busan,
- this is famous.
- Vacation.
- Famous.
- It's a snack.
- Gelato.
- What?
Is gelato famous in Busan?
- I want to see her have a quiz.
- I was there yesterday,
- but I had no idea.
- Ji Eun is good.
Yes, she is. She is funny.
Snack.
Famous.
A light snack.
- A light snack.
- Yes.
- Where?
- Busan.
Busan. Hotteok.
There you go!
(A light snack in Busan: Hotteok)
- She did well.
- Is it famous in Busan?
This isn't it either.
- So Min, why are you so bad at it?
- This is bad. I don't know.
- This must be it.
- She is slow-witted.
- Her wits...
- Gosh.
- It's coming out.
- Is it coming out?
Why is there so much water?
Mine didn't burst. Okay.
All right.
- Stomach.
- Us.
Stomach.
- Stomach.
- Us.
- In our bodies...
- Stomach.
- She should say, "Medical checkup."
- Not that one.
- Liver.
- No.
- Intestine.
- Go on.
- Medical checkup.
- Large intestine.
- There you go.
- Small intestine?
- You look at the inside.
- Legs?
Stomach. Liver. Heart?
- Go down further.
- Come on.
Go down further.
- Medical checkup.
- Hospital.
Hospital.
Internal medicine.
- Time's up.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Second place.
- Ji Eun, it was funny.
- It was so funny.
- I am sorry.
Plucking out leg hairs.
I got it done.
- I got it done.
- Waxing.
Waxing.
Jae Suk heard him.
- It's coming out.
- Okay.
- I need to dance.
- No.
(Twerking)
- Dance.
- You can't dance.
- Twerking.
- Okay.
- Is it coming out?
- It's coming out.
- Okay.
(They speedily set off
Ji Eun's bomb too.)
- Okay.
- We are fast.
We are done.
- This is hard.
- I will announce the results.
Team Sae Ho took first place.
Good.
Team Jong Kook took second place.
- Team Ji Eun took third place.
- I didn't set off the bombs fast.
- Okay.
- You did well.
We are getting a lot this time.
Only the exchange rate is different.
Thirty bills.
All right. Okay.
(Depending on the ranking,
the exchange rate is different.)
Forty bills for a dollar.
For the 2nd place,
it's 50 bills for a dollar.
We can eat one dish, right?
Shall I eat the seafood soup
or lobster?
What happened?
Is the exchange rate out?
I want the seafood soup.
Do you want to change it
with Jong Kook's money?
- Ten bills of Jong Kook's money.
- Really?
- How many bills?
- Ten bills.
Why don't we exchange them?
Ten bills? Okay.
Hold on. Let me check.
- I won't change teams now.
- Really?
Who do I pay if I want to eat?
- Sae Ho.
- Yes?
Would you lend me six bills?
Well...
- Your money.
- I am sorry.
Don't say that.
I need 40 bills to eat.
Right.
Lend me six bills.
(Sae Ho pretends not to hear him.)
- Sae Ho, I need to eat.
- I don't have 50 bills.
- I think...
- Sell something.
- you should sell something.
- I...
I have five bills of Sae Ho's money.
Who wants to exchange them
for five bills of Jong Kook's money?
- I will do it.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Can you do that?
- Three, four, five.
- It's worth more,
- but I will give you a flat rate.
- Okay.
- You know what I mean.
- Thank you.
It looks like you are selling
gift certificates.
Something like that.
Other team members can switch teams,
but captains can't do that.
So I should collect my money only.
I am selling designer shoes
for two dollars.
I will give you two bills
of Ji Eun's money.
That doesn't sound very appealing.
I have five bills of Ji Eun's money.
Who wants to exchange
five bills of Jong Kook's money?
- Does anyone need Ji Eun's money?
- Forty bills.
- No?
- Five bills of Ji Eun's money...
for five bills of Jong Kook's money.
Ten bills of Ji Eun's money.
- Ji Eun's money for Jong Kook's.
- Two bills of Ji Eun's money.
- Why is everyone getting rid of it?
Things are quite active
at the over-the-counter market.
- Things are quite active.
The exchange rate is the worst
for Ji Eun's money.
- I will win the next time.
- Okay.
There is too much Ji Eun's money
going around.
- You know,
- Right now...
Ji Eun's money became so cheap.
There is too much of Ji Eun's money
going around right now.
Here are 40 bills of Sae Ho's money.
Exchanging 5 bills of Ji Eun's money
for 5 bills of Jong Kook's money.
- Here you go.
- You jerk.
(Haha exchanged 50 bills
of Jong Kook's money for 1 dollar.)
- I need to eat this time.
- Will you eat?
- Yes.
- Does seafood soup come with rice?
I will eat the next time.
I am not hungry.
(Jong Kook decides to eat
the next time.)
I don't need this. Can I rip it up?
I will give you one.
- Five for one.
- I will blow my nose...
- with Sae Ho's money.
- One.
- All right.
- Five bills of Sae Ho's money.
I am going to rip it up.
- Hey.
- I am going to rip it up.
I am going to blow my nose.
If you don't give me one,
I will rip it up.
- Cherish it.
- I will rip it up.
- Why would I give you one?
- Give me one.
- Rip it up.
- I will rip it up.
(Se Chan threatens to rip up
Sae Ho's money.)
Ji Eun, are you going to eat
something?
- You can't, right?
- I need to save up money.
- I don't think we can eat.
- I learned something today.
I will go all in Ji Eun's money
in the next round.
- Same here.
- I have a lot of Ji Eun's bills.
That's a good idea.
We will bring in the food now.
- Gosh, look at this.
- This is nice.
This is nice.
- We will eat now.
- Look at this.
- It isn't half bad.
- This is incredible.
- So Min.
- Can we eat?
- Okay. Have a piece.
- It's tasty, right?
It's so tasty.
Luckily,
I have been eating all the dishes.
Two more rounds remain, right?
I am very hungry.
Can I sell my silver ring
for a discount?
Aren't our jewelry enough
for a dish?
(They try to negotiate
with their silver jewelry.)
It looks tasty.
If everything fails,
- I will sell these shoes.
- You should sell them.
- You have that option.
- I am torn.
I don't know if I should sell them
here or on Carrot Market.
- Sell them on Carrot, of course.
- Five bills of Sae Ho's money.
- What?
- For lobster sashimi.
How big is a bite?
- Really?
- Five bills of Sae Ho's money.
- I only have three bills.
- Okay.
- Sell it for five Ji Eun bills.
- Thank you.
Give me a thick piece with sauce.
- It's thick.
- Give me a thick piece.
- Give me a piece of sashimi.
- Rip it.
- How many bills?
- Three bills of Sae Ho's money.
(Ji Eun purchases a bite
because she is hungry.)
It's tasty, right?
It's like shrimp sashimi.
Who wants the lobster shell
for decoration?
It's five bills of Sae Ho's money.
One bill of Sae Ho's money.
One bill? It's a deal.
Give me the bill and take this.
Okay. I will put it
on top of the shoes.
- Hey.
- Why?
- Why would you do that?
- I want to put the lobster shell...
- on these designer shoes.
- It will look cool.
- Right?
- I collected a lot of money.
- Let's go to the next location.
- Okay.
Let's refresh ourselves. Okay.
What do they sell here?
(The last place of the day)
- I feel bad for Jong Kook.
- This is the food.
Jong Kook hasn't eaten anything,
- but this place has dessert.
- It's dessert.
I haven't eaten anything.
- It looks tasty.
I want something sweet.
- What kind of food is there?
- It looks so tasty.
Coffee.
- Is it a bowl of rice?
- I...
What?
Isn't it a bowl of rice?
(Se Chan mistakes a cake
for a bowl of rice.)
For goodness' sake. My goodness.
- What am I going to do?
- Team Ji Eun.
- I want a meal.
- I starved all day.
but we came to a dessert place.
This is a day for me.
- I will stick with Jong Kook.
- I'm all in.
We need to place first.
- I need to join Team Ji Eun.
- Same here.
- Come.
- I only have Ji Eun's money.
- I will win this time.
- Everyone has a path to take.
Ji Eun, please win this time.
- Okay. I only have my money too.
- I will go all in.
So Min, aren't you going to come?
- I am going to stay here.
- Trust me.
So no one is joining Team Sae Ho.
- Sae Ho is alone.
- Really?
- Sae Ho's money is worthless.
- I am sorry.
- This is no way to treat a guest.
I visited after a long while
and got my shoes taken away.
It can't be helped.
I only have Ji Eun's money.
I can't join any other teams.
I have 65 bills of Ji Eun's money.
You have a lot of bills.
The last menu is the finale
of every gourmet experience,
- the sweet dessert.
- Okay.
Is this the last round?
Is there one more round?
After this one,
there will be a round for a prize.
- Really?
- That will be the last round.
This is the last round with food.
Se Chan and Jong Kook
haven't had any food.
Se Chan thought the dessert
was a bowl of rice.
- I thought it was rice.
- The last round.
- How did you see it as rice?
- Rice.
- It looks like rice.
- It does look like rice.
That's how rice looks
before making rice balls,
He must be so hungry.
This mission is...
- the Scary Slipper.
- The Scary Slipper.
Two members of other teams will sit on
both sides of the player.
- The player will get 20 chances...
- Okay.
to attack the member's shin
with the palm of his or her hand.
If the attack is successful,
the player gets one point.
You use the slipper.
- The game is Haha's idea.
- Haha.
- Haha brings many such games.
- He does.
Haha loves Running Man a lot.
He is an idea bank.
The team with many members...
- can switch out the player.
- Okay.
The rankings will be decided
by the earned points.
Let's win this time.
But I am alone.
You need to keep playing alone.
I need to keep playing alone.
I don't know if I am imagining it,
- but someone's feet stink.
- Whose feet stink?
The smell isn't coming from my feet
because they are wrapped up.
Right?
Whose feet stink?
The smell isn't coming from my feet
because they are wrapped up.
Right?
Ji Hyo, what are you doing?
It isn't you.
- Ji Hyo.
- It's Ji Hyo.
- It isn't me.
- Is it you?
It isn't me.
- My goodness.
- It isn't you, but this is...
- It isn't me.
- It isn't you.
We became very close.
It must be Sae Ho.
His feet probably became sweaty.
- No.
- Sae Ho.
- Didn't sweat pool at the bottom?
No.
Who wants to go first?
- We need action.
- I will sit on this side. Yes.
- I will sit on this side.
- Slap the shin for real.
- Like this.
- Yes. We should hear the sound.
(Slapping)
- Is that how you do it?
- You slapped too hard.
- But...
- The sound should be big.
Isn't that how you do it?
- It is.
- That's how you do it.
Is he supposed to hit my head?
- I mean...
- No?
- Isn't that how you do it?
- No.
- I see.
- Hit me here.
- Here?
- Don't hit my face.
- Do well.
- Let's get started. Get ready.
- Can I attack one side only?
- Yes.
- Set, go.
- Hey.
Don't make a fist.
- Don't do that.
- Go.
(He slaps Sae Ho's shin
with perfect accuracy.)
Come on.
Put it down.
(It's like a comedy skit.)
- Do it properly.
- I am doing it properly.
- He slapped 11 times.
- That was so funny.
- That was insane.
- Here I go.
What is he doing?
- You slapped 20 times.
- Okay.
(He succeeded in slapping 20 times.)
- You fool.
- He is an easy target.
Why did you make it so easy for him?
That was so funny.
- He will guide us to dessert.
- Sae Ho is an easy target.
- You made it so easy for him.
- Let me try it.
That was so funny.
Sae Ho, sit in the middle.
- He is an easy target.
- That was insane.
- For goodness' sake.
- He is an easy target.
- Jong Kook, go ahead.
- Me?
Why did you make it so easy for him?
- He is an easy target.
- I can't believe you.
For goodness' sake.
- I just need to do well, right?
- Yes.
Will we place last?
(Startled)
Look to the left.
For example...
- There you go.
- You got caught.
- Like this.
- Yes.
(Startled)
What?
My goodness.
Slap and move your hand.
- Like this.
- There you go.
- He is good too.
- I got you.
Okay.
Jong Kook's eyes are on his hand.
Get ready.
(Out of 20 times,
how many times will Sae Ho slap?)
Set, go.
All right. He got caught.
- Hey.
- Hold on.
- How are you so bad at this?
- Switch places with me.
- Switch places.
- I can't do it well.
- I will place second.
- Suk Jin, we need to place second.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Hit him.
Set, go.
He got caught.
I hit you, right?
(Ouch.)
(Screaming)
(He feels pain after a beat.)
I feel bad for him.
- It can't be helped.
- He is alone.
He must be lonely.
I hit you.
(Hitting)
He is getting hit so many times.
- How many times...
- This is the last chance.
It's over. He will place last.
Okay.
You slapped 12 times in total.
- Jae Suk.
- Should I go?
Go.
Here comes Jae Suk.
- The flippant man.
- Here comes Jae Suk.
- I need to do so many things.
- Who wants to go?
- Do you want to go?
- You should do it.
- Should I do it?
I want to see this match.
Seriously.
Get ready.
(It's a match
between the Grand Award winners.)
(Will this end their relationship?)
Jae Suk.
Set, go.
(Go.)
- I hit him.
- You hit him.
He hit him.
(Jae Suk is quite fast.)
For goodness' sake.
(The slipper flies off.)
Once you lose your rhythm...
That's right.
He is fast.
He missed Jae Suk.
- Hey.
- What?
Jae Suk, Sae Ho is an easy target.
Attack Sae Ho.
Don't attack Jong Kook.
(Sae Ho shows off his charms
as an easy target.)
Hit him properly.
Your 20 tries are up.
- What was that?
- He is done.
- Sae Ho. What was that?
- I couldn't do it.
- Okay.
- You were easy.
- He's easy.
You should hit.
- You should sit.
- Come here.
- Jong Kook.
- You're safe.
- What? It's your turn.
- Stay there.
- You're the only one.
- Here?
- Yes.
- It must be tough for Sae Ho.
You should switch your legs.
Doesn't it hurt?
- Can we switch?
- Sure.
- For my leg.
- That's even better.
He's right-handed.
- He can expand.
- Good.
- Okay.
- Can I use my right hand?
- Do I go?
- Yes.
(Turning)
- Let's watch.
- What?
Aren't you going to look
anywhere else?
- Sae Ho. You need to get a grip.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook only aims at one side.
What will be the result?)
Set, go.
He's a boxer.
- Look at Sae Ho.
- Poor Sae Ho.
- He's hurt.
- Wait.
Sae Ho.
(Sae Ho resumes
with tears in his eyes.)
His face turned red.
Bring the slipper close.
Come closer.
He's hitting his own leg.
(Sae Ho's hand is too slow.)
Poor Sae Ho.
(Angry)
Poor guy.
He won't run away.
That's crazy.
I feel bad for him.
Poor guy.
(Sae Ho's shin keeps
getting attacked.)
He looks unstable.
- You're too slow.
- No.
Oh, he blocked.
He blocked.
Sae Ho. Keep the slipper close.
You keep blocking.
Wait.
(Groaning)
It's over.
(Sae Ho is knocked out.)
- You got hit 19 times.
- It was a delayed...
- Seriously, Sae Ho.
- I made a delayed attack.
Like this.
(Sae Ho blocked only once
and got hit 19 times.)
You're so funny.
That was better.
- You're next.
- You were so terrible.
Anyone who wants to try
for the last time?
Why play again?
That's how you hit him.
- She's good.
- I blocked her.
He hit me here.
- You can't do that.
- Then where do I hit?
- "You can't do that."
- You can't hit the arm.
- Let's not do that.
- She said you can't do that.
Okay.
(Captain Cho with multiple roles
tries for the last time.)
It's over.
(Screaming)
One, two...
- It's over.
- Is it?
(It's over.)
They're so funny.
- We won.
- Comedians are so funny.
You succeeded 4 times out of 20.
You're last.
That was tough.
- I'm so proud of my comedians.
- Good job.
So, first place goes
to Team Jong Kook.
(1st place, Team Jong Kook)
- We take 2nd place.
- Team Ji Eun places 2nd.
- Okay.
- Team Sae Ho places third.
- Let's get some desserts.
- We placed second.
Director. Do we need this later?
There is a prize.
The decision is up to you.
I'll tell you
what the prize is later.
I'm eating.
- We need to eat.
- We need to eat first.
Is the prize nice?
If it's nice, I'm saving up.
Let's save up.
- I think the exchange rate is nice.
- It'll be nice this time.
Do I get 30?
Yes, you all get the same amount.
It's the same,
but the exchange rate is different.
Oh, I see.
The value is different.
- You learned that now?
- No.
(The boy in plastic finally
understands the rule.)
I knew it.
I just didn't understand it.
Sae Ho. You should wear these.
- They're better.
- I can wear them.
(He got slippers.)
- I got slippers.
- Let's check the exchange rate.
- Done.
- We need 50 bills.
Oh, 50 bills.
We need to eat.
It's 40 bills. Fine. I'm eating.
This is better. I need to eat.
I'm getting coffee at least.
- Thirty and... Are you eating?
- Two, three, four,
- One, two, three, four...
- five, six, seven, eight,
- five, six,
- nine, ten.
- seven, eight, nine, ten.
- One, two...
I can eat.
I'm getting coffee.
I'm finally here. Time has come.
I should've had the meal earlier
instead of the dessert.
I'm hungry.
Here are 50.
(Suk Jin's here to exchange.)
Two, three,
four.
I already handed them in.
I have 50.
- Why aren't you buying?
- I'm saving up.
You never know what it'll be next.
- It's better to use than to save.
- You should eat.
- Ji Eun. Eat.
- Hurry up and eat.
I want to take the prize.
Should I just take the prize?
I'm going for the prize.
- I can't eat anyway.
But the prize might not be worth it.
- It might not be worth it.
- I'm selling Jong Kook bills.
- Should I sell them for a dollar?
- It's worth a lot.
- I think that's better.
- For a dollar?
Two Jong Kook bills up for sale.
It's worth a lot.
What? I can't just give it to you.
Give me slippers.
I'm selling these shoes.
(Reselling designer brand shoes)
Right. Sell them for a dessert.
I think my feet are getting itchy.
You should get them back soon.
But I don't have enough to buy them.
- For a dollar.
- You can't return them.
(Exchanging Sae Ho's shoes
for a dollar)
I'll get a dessert with this.
What do you want for a drink?
- Yogurt.
- I got blueberry.
I'll have blueberry too.
- Ji Eun. Did you save up instead?
- Yes.
She said she'll give me a bite.
- Let's share mine.
- Thank you.
You can't share it.
I'll pay her.
- No. Ji Eun. I'm sorry, but...
- That's okay, right?
- I'll pay her.
- There are rules.
You gave me lobster.
We have rules.
So I had lobster earlier.
I'll take this,
but I don't need this money.
Is it Ji Eun?
But I still saved ten.
Because of Jong Kook.
Is that okay?
I'm not going to use it anyway.
Look.
- Why are you ripping it?
- She's not going to use it anyway.
Give it to me
if you aren't going to use it.
I'm going to decorate it.
- It's here.
- It's coming.
Who ordered blueberry?
- Enjoy it, Se Chan.
- It looks good.
Is that cake?
I suddenly want it.
Thank you.
- I'm finally eating.
- Se Chan's finally eating.
- Yes.
- Is that laver powder?
He finally gets to have rice.
It's ice cream cake.
Is it cheese?
It's got Sae Ho's face.
That looks like half of a rice ball.
- Is that cake?
- What is this?
Is that ice cream?
- Ice cream.
- It's cake.
- Cake?
It's too greasy to eat
in an empty stomach.
Is it too greasy?
(The Korean food lover is eating
greasy rice.)
It's oily.
He ate everything today
from the start.
- I ate everything.
- I know.
- He has no regrets.
- You must be happy.
Now, there's only one mission left.
For the last mission,
you'll cast dice.
If you want to change your team,
this is your last chance.
- No.
- This is totally random.
The sum of two people's dice
will determine the winner.
- Okay.
- Two people's dice.
If you're alone,
you may cast it twice.
I have to play twice again?
- If I'm alone?
- Yes.
- Someone might join your team.
- So Min.
- Yes?
- You should join me.
Sae Ho. I'll go.
- Really? Okay.
- Yes.
- That works for me.
- I'm moving to Sae Ho's team.
I'm moving to Jong Kook's team.
- Okay.
- Sounds good.
Good.
Ji Hyo secretly saved...
- Jong Kook bills.
- I have Jong Kook bills.
I have no place to go.
- I'll stay here.
- Ji Hyo. Great choice.
- Right. The dice.
- Let's go.
The last game is the dice.
Two people will cast the dice,
and the ranking will be determined
in the order of a higher sum.
- Good luck.
- Decide who'll cast it...
- Okay.
- before casting it.
I will reveal the prize.
- It's pine mushroom.
- What?
Wait. What?
Natural pine mushroom?
This natural pine mushroom is
worth 500 dollars.
- It's really tasty.
- It's my favorite.
- It's so good.
- I must take it home.
It's...
- It's so good.
- I want to play.
- Let's eat one here.
My goodness.
If you make rice with it,
it's really good.
It's worth 500 dollars?
That's crazy.
I really want it.
I'm sorry, but...
I usually give the prize to the guests,
but I'm taking it today.
Me too. I won't make
concessions today.
Ji Eun and Suk Jin will cast
from my team.
Who's casting?
- Do we go first?
- Cast it twice,
and I'll take the higher sum.
- Here we go.
- Go.
(He must get a high number.)
Okay. You just cast it.
- Two.
- No.
What do you mean no? It's two.
- It's two. Admit it.
- Fine.
We'll take turns.
- Next is Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
- One.
- Go, Suk Jin.
- That's one.
- Oh, my mistake.
- Why would you kiss one?
- Right. That's how you should cast.
It touched the ground.
You don't mind?
(And?)
It touched the ground.
You don't mind?
Two.
- I thought it was six.
- You almost scared me.
- Me.
- Do I go first?
I'll go first.
Good luck, So Min.
Spin it a lot.
- You got it.
- That's right.
Even now...
That's good enough.
- He thought it was six.
- That's good.
- Here.
- You need to spin it in the air.
- We're all about the same.
- Yes.
- This is your last turn.
- The last turn.
(This number will determine
their rankings.)
- One.
- Two or three.
(It's 6.)
That was crazy.
Ji Hyo. That was amazing.
What's gotten into her?
- What happened?
- Ji Eun.
- Let's go for six.
- Get six.
- How?
- Six.
(Captain Ji Eun saved up
for the prize until now.)
Six.
- Okay. We beat them.
- Two and three.
- They'll get over five for sure.
- Five.
- If they get five, it's a tie.
- You must get six.
- You need to get three.
- Get six.
- I'll show you.
- You need to spin it a lot.
- I can do it.
- You can do it.
Spin it. Okay. Good.
(If he gets 6, he wins 1st place.
If it's 3 or more, he's 2nd place.)
(Team Sae Ho wins 1st place.)
- Go!
- You win.
They win.
They were so lucky.
I think you two have good chemistry.
- I think so.
- Right.
First place, second place,
and third place.
- Let me cast it again.
- No, you can't do that.
They are lucky
when they are together.
Okay. So Min.
- We can't beat them.
- Okay. Do it.
- How much do I have?
- My gosh.
- I don't have Sae Ho bills.
- You'll get more money.
I have Ji Eun bills.
I can't get the pine mushroom.
- Oh, dear.
- I'm sorry.
It's all right, Ji Eun.
What matters is
the value of the money.
What's the current exchange rate?
(Sae Ho 90, Jong Kook 100,
Ji Eun 110)
- Is it 110?
- I told you.
Is it 110? Hang on.
Seok Sam, how many do you have?
I think I can make it.
Go ahead and count them.
- I have 40... I need 110.
- I can't make it.
This is 40. So this should be 60.
I think I can make it.
(Sae Ho 90, Jong Kook 100,
Ji Eun 110)
No, I need 70.
It might not be enough.
- Suk Jin, I'll give you 30.
- What? Really?
You can't exchange money now.
- We can't?
- We can't do that?
Then this is...
Then this will go to waste.
I have a lot.
Me too. I have 80.
But Team Ji Eun didn't...
You could've made it
if you didn't eat earlier.
- This is 50.
- If you didn't eat the dessert.
- Hang on. You're right.
- I know.
I shouldn't have had the dessert.
I'm so happy that I had the dessert.
It's all right.
You should go get the pine mushroom.
I have the money.
Ji Eun gets the prize.
- Good for you, Ji Eun.
- My gosh.
- You did it.
- I saved the money.
- Thank you.
- Ji Eun gets the pine mushroom.
(The captain finally got
what she wanted.)
This is ten.
This is 70.
Gosh. Does Ji Eun have 110 dollars?
My gosh, I have 100 dollars.
(Does he have 100 dollars?)
- You do?
- Yes.
- That's amazing.
- This is worth 10 dollars, right?
This is 50, 60,
seventy, eighty,
ninety, and a hundred.
(Jong Kook gets the pine mushroom.)
I have exactly 100 dollars.
- You don't have enough?
- I have 100.
You counted them.
I have...
I have 90 dollars here.
I want my shoes back.
(He gets his expensive shoes back.)
I'm glad you got your shoes back.
- I feel at ease now.
- I see.
Bring in his shoes. There...
- He got his shoes back anyway.
- So Min.
I sold them, Sae Ho.
He will need shoes
on his way back home.
(Captain Cho managed
to recoup his loss.)
He gave up the pine mushroom
to get his shoes back.
(And Captain Kim won the prize
on her first time on the show.)
We'd like to thank
the two guests again.
- Thank you.
(We thank Kim Ji Eun and Cho Sae Ho
for joining our show with smiles.)
- Thank you.
(He's No. 1 at playing soccer
with his mouth.)
We have the president of FIFA here.
(The carried-away president
of Running Man)
(The president kept insisting
on watching the World Cup together.)
(Do you have a camera?)
(Is this for "Jiseokjin World?")
(No. I'll watch it with my family.)
(I don't want to watch it with you.)
(Running Man is like family.)
(They will shout their heads off,)
(keep chatting...)
(until their ears burst,)
(and enjoy late-night snacks.)
(Enjoy the World Cup
with Running Man!)
(Will We Have
Our First Win in the World Cup?)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)