Before we start,
we'll give you...
- a mission fund as you want. - Really?
We'll give you what you wrote.
But if you wrote the most or the least amount, you won't get it.
You should think about what others would've written.
- This means something. April 7. - I wrote 375 dollars.
I wrote 205 dollars.
- I wrote 100 dollars. - I wrote 93 dollars.
I want 732 dollars.
This is a moderate amount. I think 80 dollars is enough.
- Okay. - You wrote the highest amount.
Jae Suk. You wrote the lowest amount.
So you get zero dollars.
- You will start with zero amount. - I knew it.
- It's Yi Kyung. - Woo Jae is coming.
Sorry! I pressed the wrong number!
If you don't choose us, we will get off now.
- I choose them. - Okay.
I just want to see Jong Kook's fall.
Do Kwon, will you finalize the team members now?
Yes.
- It's okay. - The weather is hot,
so you should eat at a cool place.
- Say it openly. - I will give you 200 dollars.
- Nonsense. - I'm leaving then.
Know that I offered 200 dollars.
I am leaving. Know that I offered 200 dollars.
I'm not kidding. It really is 200 dollars.
I'll announce
the amount So Min owns.
- How much is it?
- Zero dollars?"
It's 470 dollars.
(As much as 470 dollars)
(Her huge offer was true.)
You should've
offered more money then.
She has 470 dollars?
And Lee Yi Kyung was
offered 340 dollars.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- And he will receive...
- How much is it?
Zero dollars.
- It's these two.
- This is great.
- That was so close.
- This is amazing.
Hey, you should be happy.
- This is how things go here.
- It's all right.
- Gosh, they got me.
- It's just like that.
I got fooled.
You took him in.
She has the most money.
I offered you 150 dollars.
- So Min is the richest.
- Yes. She has the most money.
- So Min is the winner.
- But I...
- So Min, you're the winner.
- The weak link is the winner.
- So Min.
- The sole winner.
So Min is the winner.
Get lost.
She's the winner.
- Joo Woo Jae.
Do you have 270 dollars?
- Hey, you...
- She's the winner.
Why did you say that?
- She has 270 dollars?
- No.
You should thank me.
- I have zero dollars.
- Hang on.
No one on my team has money.
- We are...
- We can start saving money now.
All right. I will explain the rules.
Today, we're doing something
Se Chan loves.
- Me?
- What is it?
It's Race of Groups where you will
complete missions in groups.
- Race of Groups.
Se Chan went
to Jeju Island as a group.
(The truth behind the group activity
that Se Chan likes.)
(One month ago)
(I went there
with Jae Joon and Jin Ho.)
(And there were a few more
in the group.)
(The word "group"
flew out of his month.)
(Apparently, there were
three more people.)
(His trip to Jeju Island
remains unsolved like that.)
- In groups.
- I heard Se Chan is seeing someone.
- Who?
- No, I'm not.
- People say that.
Will you just let him see someone?
Why would you bring that up?
Just let him date.
So Min, let him see someone.
- Look at his face.
- She made things awkward.
I barely know the trot singer,
but things got awkward
between me and her.
Why?
Her stylist suddenly said...
(What about Mirani?)
- What about Mirani?
- No.
Mirani, I'm Se Chan.
Things are awkward
between Mirani and me too.
- Hey, today...
- Everyone I see...
"How is So Min?"
"What do you think of Mirani?"
"What do you think
of the trot singer?"
This is So Min's big picture.
This is driving me crazy.
She's trying to isolate you
in the show business.
They say you become pretty
when you're in love.
- This is a good thing.
- But his face is a mess.
- I can't date anyone.
- He's too ugly to date someone.
- To date someone...
- I can't date anyone.
All right.
So this is the Race of Groups.
The three members with the most
mission funds will get prizes.
And the two with the lowest money
will get penalties.
- There will be a penalty.
- Okay.
Just like the name,
the first half will be a race...
between the teams of 3, 3, 3, and 1.
And in the second half,
you'll be divided into two teams.
So it will be a 5-on-5 race.
When the first race is over,
the two teams with...
the least money will be absorbed...
into the other teams
in the second half.
Before we start,
I will exchange your money...
for R money.
The exchange rate is 10 to 1.
So you get 1 dollar of R money
with 10 dollars of cash.
Now you may get changed
before the first mission.
(Team So Min: 47 dollars,
Team Do Kwon: 12, 8, 27.5 dollars)
(Team Woo Jae: 5, 18, 6.8 dollars)
(Team Yi Kyung: 0 dollars)
All right. What should we do today?
Okay.
So Min looks so lonely.
- Why am I lonely when I'm with you?
- She has a lot of money.
- She's rich.
- She's the winner.
- I'm with you guys.
- So Min.
That's a fake smile.
Why? I'm feeling good.
(Only her eyes are smiling.)
- That's a lot better.
- I'm very happy now.
- You are?
- That's fake.
I'm in a good mood.
That's not true. You're not happy.
Jeon So Min's fake life.
Your life is just as fake as mine.
All right. I'll explain the rules.
This mission is
Storytelling Strawberry.
- Strawberry?
You know the strawberry game.
- It's four beats.
- This one?
- It's too hard for me.
- It's tricky.
This is Jae Suk's thing.
But this game isn't
about the rhythm.
I'm good at this game.
- Do you see the letters here?
- Yes.
- It says ji, go, sa, and so on.
The first player says something
that starts with "ji."
Like how?
Something like,
"Ji Suk Jin is the best."
And the second player says
something that starts with "go."
But you're supposed to say something
that fits a certain situation.
(They can only say things
that fit the suggested situation.)
- For example...
- We have to make something up.
- Let's say the keyword is diet.
- Diet.
And the letter you're given
is "un." Then...
you say, "I need to work out."
And you call
the next player like "Haha."
Then Haha should say something
about diet with the next letter.
- "I should eat sweet potatoes."
- Something like that.
- I call the next player.
- Something related to it.
Call the next player.
(They should make something up
with the given letter.)
Since this is a difficult game,
you are allowed
to attack in three turns.
- Okay.
Isn't this easier than numbers?
- This is easy.
- It sounds easier.
But you have to say something that's
appropriate for the situation.
Jae Suk, it's easy, isn't it?
This is so easy. I can do this.
- But your lips are parched already.
- Don't worry. I can do this.
Let's start.
- The first word.
- What is it?
- New employee.
- Okay.
You should say something
a new employee would say.
- Suk Jin, will you go first?
- Let's start with Seok Sam.
- Start with the letter "ji?"
- Yes. And you call the next player.
- Hang on.
- Okay. It starts with "ji."
- New employee?
- New employee.
Start.
- Start already?
- Sure.
- Just do it.
- Okay.
(Role: New employee)
It's not Ji Suk Jin, right?
- What does that mean?
- That's true.
It's not Ji Suk Jin, right?
- What does that mean?
- That's true.
I'm not a new employee.
- You can't do that.
- Ji Suk Jin isn't a new employee.
You should say something
that a new employee would say.
- If you were a new employee...
- What are you doing?
- Let's say you're a new employee.
- What was that?
- Say something as a new employee.
- Hey.
- I don't have any experience.
- "I just got here now."
- Something like this.
- "Make some coffee now."
- You're good at this.
- Sure.
- "I'm late."
- After I say something,
it goes this way?
No, you should call someone.
You should call someone.
I'm so sick of this.
- He still doesn't know the rules.
- We can't play this game.
What's wrong with him?
- Just give up.
- Okay.
Okay. I got it.
- We need to win money.
- Yes. Do it right.
Let's start again.
Start.
I'm going to work.
Haha.
Thank you, Assistant Manager.
Suk Jin.
(Role: New employee, Sa)
Fraud.
- What?
- My gosh.
(The new employee raises his voice
all of a sudden.)
- What was that?
- You sound like the boss.
You're a mean boss.
You should call someone else.
- Why did you come back to me?
- We're a team.
- But...
- This is funny.
- You don't understand the rules.
- It's not like that.
This isn't a word chain game.
- He can't do this.
- Hey.
What are you doing?
There should be rules.
Why did you come right back to me?
You should say something like
"Hello, boss."
You should try it.
- All right.
- Let's do this.
Woo Jae!
Let's win.
- Why are you so bad at this?
- You should do it right.
Let's do it right.
Jong Kook goes first this time.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Where?
- It's "ra."
- Ra.
(Role: New employee, Ra)
I have no time to eat ramyeon.
Woo Jae, Woo Jae. Like this?
(Woo Jae, Woo Jae. Like this?)
- "Woo Jae, Woo Jae?" What was that?
- "Woo Jae."
- "Woo Jae." Like this?
It feels like I'm playing...
- a game with old men.
- What are you doing?
- We can't move forward.
- What was that?
- I was just...
- Just say it once.
It's fine
as long as I call out a name.
- I just need to call out a name.
- Why are you so bad at this game?
- Say it gently.
- I said that to the beat.
"Woo Jae, Woo Jae." What was that?
Woo Jae, Woo Jae. What about it?
- Woo Jae, Woo Jae. It's fine.
- Woo Jae.
- What are you talking about?
- Doesn't it sound nice?
Woo Jae, Woo Jae. Can't I do that?
Say it just once?
- You can't do that.
- "Ha Do Kwon." You can say this.
You guys are so bad at this.
Do Kwon goes first. And it's "ra."
Start.
(Do Kwon goes first
with the letter "ra.")
Can I listen to the radio?
Suk Jin.
It's time for the meeting.
Woo Jae.
Oh, no. I'm late for the meeting.
Suk Jin.
Move your car.
(Laughing)
The new employee sounds rude.
(He yells all of a sudden.)
- I can understand though.
- Suk Jin.
- It was okay though.
- It's fine.
He has no idea
what a new employee is like.
Call Jae Suk instead.
- He's like a treasure house.
- Suk Jin.
- He's your teammate.
- We're on the same team.
You two are on the same team.
Do you have to see my shirt?
Okay.
- Let's do this.
- This is fun.
- It's not fun.
- So Min.
So Min is alone.
You should call her.
- This is very confusing.
- All right.
The keyword is mom.
- Mom?
- Mom.
Something your mom would say.
- Let's start with Yi Kyung.
- Yi Kyung goes first.
- What letter?
- Woo.
- Woo?
Start.
(Role: Mom, Woo)
I love my son.
(I love my son.)
Suk Jin.
- He's our team.
- Bring me a toothpick.
Suk Jin.
(Startled)
(Bring me a toothpick?)
- Seriously.
- I'm not doing this.
- Hey.
- Why me?
What are you three doing?
- I'm not doing this.
- This is not fun.
- I don't want to play this game.
- What's this?
Let's not do this. There must be
another game, right?
- What are you three doing?
- Why...
- Why did you call him?
- I just...
- Everyone called Suk Jin, so...
- This is ridiculous.
- We're on the same team.
- I mean, why...
Everyone calls Suk Jin,
and I just did the same.
I was so surprised.
Why did you attack our teammate?
You should look far ahead.
- He attacked his own team.
- Yi Kyung.
Don't attack your teammates.
Why did you attack your teammate?
I just said that because
everyone kept calling Suk Jin.
Why are they so bad at this?
- Jae Suk, you go first.
- Me?
Let's call Jae Suk no matter what.
- Something a mom would say.
- Mom.
- Who goes first?
- Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk goes first.
- Okay.
Start.
(Role: Mom, Cha)
Hey, Mr. Cha Seung Won.
- What?
- No, that's not right.
(Hey, Mr. Cha Seung Won.)
(Wrong)
What are you doing?
It should start with "cha."
- It was just an exclamation.
- Why do you use an exclamation?
- It's just an exclamation.
- You lose one point.
It's an exclamation.
Why would you say Cha Seung Won?
"Hey" is an exclamation.
- Are you a fool?
- What about Cha Seung Won?
- Seriously...
- I mean...
Why would a mom call Cha Seung Won?
"Hey" is an exclamation.
Why did you say "hey?"
It should start with "cha."
Is that a silent syllable?
This is like poetic license.
- Poetic license?
- Why would he say "hey?"
Gosh. Seriously...
We can't continue the game.
So Min goes first with "jeo."
- Me?
- My goodness.
- It's about mom, right?
- Yes.
Start.
Honey, come and eat.
Jae Suk.
I don't know what you are doing now.
I don't want to do this.
(A letter from Mom)
- What's this?
- What was that?
- Why is it so long?
- "I don't know..."
"I don't know..."
"I don't know
what you are doing now."
Why does it have to be so long?
You have to make it short.
- Is that what your wife says?
- Leave him be.
I mean...
- Why is it so hard?
- Why is he sending a message?
Hey. It can get long sometimes.
"Check your blood sugar level."
You just never stopped talking.
"I love you, honey."
- "Let's eat, honey."
- This is unbelievable.
- "What are you doing, honey?"
- Or...
"Go buy some glass noodles."
- Mind your own business.
Mind your own business.
- Stop sending out messages.
- This is a mess.
Why did you send a message?
- Can't I say things like that?
- No.
- Don't send a message.
- All right.
I'll wait and see how good you are.
- Bring it on.
- Let's see how good you are.
- Let me try.
- What's the letter?
- Is it mom again?
- Haha goes first.
- The keyword is announcer.
- All right.
It's about an announcer.
- Start with the given letter.
- Which one?
It's "dang."
Start.
(Role: Announcer, Dang)
This is it for the news
from Dangjin.
- What did you say?
- Suk Jin.
The intersection is clogged
with traffic now.
(The intersection is clogged
with traffic now.)
Woo Jae.
High school students are preparing
for the college entrance exam.
(High school students are preparing
for the college entrance exam.)
Jong Kook.
There was an accident.
Ji... What?
- What kind of announcer is that?
- What's wrong?
- "There was an accident."
- What kind of announcer...
- It's the North Korean news show.
- I mean...
An announcer...
- That's not an announcer.
- I said it like that on purpose.
Let's say you succeeded.
I'll resume right away.
I'll start right away.
(Role: Announcer, Ga)
So Min.
Waiting without moving.
- What?
- What was that?
- Woo Jae.
- What?
- What was that?
- What does that mean?
- "Waiting without moving?"
- What's that supposed to mean?
- That sounds strange.
That's just what announcers say.
What does that mean?
I'm just doing an impression.
- Like how?
- It's not just about the tone.
What is the news about?
- This?
- What accident?
The culprit is waiting
without moving...
- in front of the bank.
- What?
- A culprit?
- Hey.
- What culprit?
- What?
Why is the culprit waiting?
He should run away.
The culprit is waiting
without moving in front of the bank.
- Who is he waiting for?
- The police?
- That doesn't make sense.
- The police...
- This is just...
- This is ridiculous.
- That doesn't make sense.
- No.
"Waiting without moving."
- Shall we change?
- Yes. We will change.
Who goes first this time?
Something Kim Jong Kook would say.
(The new keyword, Kim Jong Kook)
- Me?
- My gosh. This is a problem.
- What Jong Kook would say?
- Yes. Jae Suk goes first.
Can I continue?
- I will just...
- With "ji?"
- Start with "sa."
- "Sa?"
Start.
I love you, Ji Hyo.
Jong Kook.
Go away, you punk!
Jae Suk.
Turn on the radio.
What?
(Kim Jong Kook and radio?)
- What was that?
- This is...
He keeps saying radio.
- That's all he says.
- Radio?
Is radio all you know?
Go as in Go Doo Shim.
Ra as in radio.
Cha as in Cha Seung Won.
You can say things like
"Don't eat ramyeon."
"I'll kill you if you eat ramyeon."
- "Who was it?" Something like that.
- Doesn't he say to his manager,
- "Turn on the radio?"
- I don't listen to the radio.
Let's eliminate one team.
- I've never been this upset here.
- Why is it so hard?
- Seriously.
- I'm so upset.
I'll go first. Let's begin.
Let's begin.
- Think of Jong Kook's personality.
- Why is it so hard?
- "Don't eat ramyeon!" Like this.
- Ramyeon.
- That's a good example.
- Why can't my answer count?
This time, we'll start with So Min.
- It's "woo," right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Ready, go.
Woo Jae, you jerk!
Woo Jae.
Do you want to lose all your teeth?
Suk Jin.
Go to your car, you punk!
Hold on. Do I have
a personality disorder or what?
- Do I have a personality disorder?
- Se Chan.
Why won't that jerk
come to play soccer with us?
(Role: Kim Jong Kook, jeo)
Jae Suk.
Get lost this instant, you jerk!
Se Chan.
How dare that jerk?
Suk Jin.
(Role: Kim Jong Kook, go)
(Taken aback)
- It's "go."
- What are you doing?
(The skit ended helplessly.)
- It was going well.
- What was that?
- We were doing well.
- It felt like it was never-ending.
This is how we should continue
the game.
- It was never-ending. Everyone...
- It was fun.
- Everyone...
- I apologize on his behalf.
- I just came up with an idea.
- It was fun.
- Right. It was really fun.
- Everyone is good at this game.
- It wasn't that bad, right?
- He's so bad at improvising.
- What's your problem?
- It's understandable, isn't it?
- Let's play another round.
- It was good.
- We just have to get upset.
- Let's do it again.
- All we have to do is get upset.
- How come you're all so good at it?
- We just have to say "you punk..."
- Or "you jerk."
or "you jerk"
at the end of the sentence.
That's true.
(Everyone except for Seok Sam is
good at acting like Jong Kook.)
- This is fun.
- Everyone except for him did well.
Let's keep playing the game
with the same role.
That was so funny.
- The next role is...
- A new role?
- So Min, do you want to go first?
- Let's start with So Min.
- It's a tour guide.
- A tour guide?
Where do you begin?
- Let's start at "ji."
- "Ji?"
- "Ji."
- A tour guide?
- A tour guide. It's easy.
- Ready, go.
Mediterranean food is good.
Jong Kook.
Tilt your head up and look at it.
Ji Hyo.
(He stuttered.)
- What?
- Gosh, you.
(It was a team kill.)
- Hey.
- Why did you do that?
- How did it happen?
- I meant to say his name.
- But I said Ji Hyo's name instead.
- "Ji Hyo."
- I guess...
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
- it came out wrong.
Why did you say my name?
- I hadn't thought of the target.
- "Ji Hyo."
(Team Do Kwon lost a point
because of Jong Kook's team kill.)
- "Ji Hyo."
- That was cute.
- You should've pulled it off.
- He sounded cute.
- I didn't expect to be called.
- It's easy.
We'll start with Se Chan this time.
- A comment for product placement?
- What should we start with?
- What is that?
- It's difficult.
Something you'd say...
- when you do product placement.
- Okay.
- To please the advertiser.
- Okay. Let's go.
Ready, go.
- It's very delicious.
- Good.
Ji Hyo.
What is that?
Se Chan.
It's so high in sugar.
Jae Suk.
At this moment, I'll eat this,
and I'll really...
(The letter to the advertiser)
- Listen. Let me explain.
- Hey!
- Assume the push-up position!
- Hold on.
- Why?
- Stop writing a letter!
- What's wrong with it?
- What's the problem?
- What's wrong with you?
- Why would you write a letter?
- It's for product placement,
- so we should be wholehearted.
- It's a game.
- You should follow the rules.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Please keep time.
- He's unbelievable.
- That's not fair.
- He keeps making a video message.
You guys won't let me express
my creativity.
I can't believe this.
We're not telling a folktale story.
- What was that?
- Gosh.
- That was...
- Woo Jae will go first this time.
Woo Jae will go first.
Say what a customer at a restaurant
would say.
- What?
- A customer at a restaurant?
- That's not bad.
- It's too easy.
- Let's do this.
- Ready, go. It's "woo."
(Role: a customer
at a restaurant, woo)
Please take out the burdock.
Jong Kook.
I almost broke my tooth.
Jae Suk.
Can we have two servings of brisket?
Se Chan.
Excuse me.
Can I get more radish kimchi?
Suk Jin.
You ordered this!
- Ji Hyo.
- What did you say?
"You ordered this?"
(A customer at a restaurant would
say, "You ordered this?")
- "You ordered this?"
- What did you say?
Why did you get upset?
What did you say?
- Why would you get upset?
- I'll explain the situation.
- Why did you talk in an angry tone?
- Let me explain.
- What did you say?
- It happened not long ago.
- Why did you get upset?
- My wife and I...
were eating together.
- And she didn't like the food.
- I'm so dumbfounded.
- She asked why I ordered the dish.
- That's irrelevant.
- I said, "You ordered this."
- That's not acceptable.
- It happened at a restaurant.
- "You ordered this."
Why? It's true.
- I was eating with my wife.
- No, that's weird.
- It didn't suit her palate.
- It's weird.
It's weird. Why would you get upset?
- That's just your story.
- It's weird.
That's not a usual situation.
- Why would you get upset?
- That happens.
- Haha, do you want to go first?
- Yes.
- Is the situation the same?
- Yes. It's "i." Ready, go.
This is good.
Jeon So Min.
Give us the tea first, please.
Jong Kook.
I won't eat this.
Jae Suk.
Who are you to refuse to eat it?
(Role: a customer
at a restaurant, dang)
(The conversation with "you")
- Gosh.
- Why?
Couldn't you think of any other word
but "you?"
Gosh!
Don't ruin the game.
- But... What's the problem?
- Don't ruin the game!
- We're enjoying playing the game.
- Hey...
- He's a fun spoiler.
- Don't ruin it again.
- "I don't like glass noodles."
- Don't ruin the game.
"I'd like to have
extra glass noodles."
- An owner can get upset sometimes.
- Jae Suk, that wasn't relevant.
You could've said,
"I have high blood sugar."
I mean, that's... Gosh.
Everybody seems to be upset
with "you."
Glass noodles.
- I didn't think of "glass noodles."
- Oh, right.
- Say what Jong Kook would say.
- Good.
- What Jong Kook would say?
- That's great.
- All we have to do is get upset.
- But it'll go on for too long.
- We'll start with Se Chan at "ji."
- We just have to get upset.
- "Ji?"
- Ready, go.
How dare he?
Jae Suk.
Keep going on like that
and see what happens.
Haha.
You're such a troublemaker,
you jerk.
Jae Suk.
Go, you jerk!
Se Chan.
Eat ramyeon, you jerk!
Suk Jin.
(Role: Kim Jong Kook, woo)
Do well while I'm spoiling you,
you punk.
Gosh. What was that?
What...
(Do well while I'm spoiling you,
you punk.)
(The skit is over.)
- What was that?
- What did you say?
- I said, "Do well..."
- We could've made it to the end.
- What are you doing?
- "Come to my gym."
- Something like that.
- I mean...
- "Do well while I'm spoiling you."
- What were you thinking?
That's just ridiculous.
- What's that?
- Take his team out of the game.
- What are you saying?
- Take Team Orange out of the game.
- We were doing great.
- You understand, right?
- Nonsense.
- It's understandable, right?
- I mean, why...
- It's the easiest role.
I'm sorry,
but exactly what did you say?
- Spoiling someone?
- Stop it while I'm spoiling you,
- you punk.
- "Do well while I'm spoiling you."
Why doesn't it count?
- It's what he would say.
- Why are you so bad at this game?
That's not what Jong Kook would say.
- Me? Okay.
- Jong Kook will go first.
Ready, go.
(Role: Kim Jong Kook, woo)
Come to my gym.
So Min.
I'll go play soccer now.
Woo Jae.
Come to play soccer with us.
Jong Kook.
Are you talking to me?
(He suddenly spoke cutely.)
(He failed.)
- "Are you talking to me?"
- He can't act like himself.
- That was cute.
- He failed to speak as he does.
- "Are you talking to me?"
- That was cute.
- Are you talking to us?
- "Are you talking to me?"
Hey, you called my name too late.
- That was cute.
- Don't you think so?
- "Are you talking to me?"
- I said what my friend would say...
- Jong Kook.
- What's wrong with that?
- in response to the question.
- But that was...
- Look.
- Jong Kook. This is...
- "Are you talking to me?"
- acceptable.
- Why can't you stay on the beat?
- "Are you talking to me?"
- What was that?
- Right?
- It's over.
- All right.
- The game is over.
- Yes.
The team in the first place is...
(Result of
the Storytelling Strawberry)
Team So Min.
- Really?
- It's good to be a one-person team.
She doesn't have to worry about...
- the other members.
- That's true.
- Right. She has no such worries.
- I only worry about myself.
- The team in second place is...
- I'm jealous.
- Team Woo Jae.
- Yes, Team Woo Jae.
Team Do Kwon placed third.
Team Yi Kyung placed fourth place
by a large margin.
- They'll likely be absorbed.
- It must be really nice.
- But they have no money.
- We have no money.
- You have your money, right?
- Yes.
Gosh, I have no money. How...
The maximum amount of money
you can receive varies...
depending on the team's ranking.
Write down the amount you want
within the limit.
The member who wrote the highest
amount won't receive any money.
- I see.
- My gosh. Really?
Only the one who wrote
the highest amount can't get money?
- The team in the first place...
- So Min will get all the money.
- gets 50 dollars. You get it all.
- I see.
- Thank you.
- The next team gets 40 dollars.
We'll begin right now.
Write the amount you want to receive
that's no more than 40 dollars.
The member with the highest amount
won't receive any money.
The member with the lowest amount
can receive it, right?
Yes, the other two members will
receive money.
We don't need to get
a lot of money now, right?
- Then...
- Haha is trying to trick them...
- as always.
- Haha is trying to trick them.
Haha, let's let him have it all.
We'll write 40 dollars.
You should write 39 dollars.
- You can get it all.
- Right.
- With an innocent look on his face.
- Okay.
- Write 39 dollars.
- Right?
- With an innocent look on his face.
What if the three members write
the same amount?
None of them would receive money.
Oh, my. You can't get any money
if you write the same amount.
All right. Show us your boards
on the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three.
He wrote 20 dollars,
and he wrote 8 dollars.
- Okay. I got 8 dollars.
- Right. He can't get 20 dollars.
Haha won't get any money. The others
will get 8 dollars and 18 dollars.
- I got at least eight dollars.
- Haha,
- why did you write 20 dollars?
- It's a shame though.
(All of them got timid
and wrote small amounts of money.)
My gosh. I thought hard. It was hard
for me to make the decision.
Gosh. They're so petty.
- I thought of writing 22 dollars.
- You have a lot of money.
- Right.
- The maximum amount is 30 dollars.
- Thirty dollars?
- Yes.
Okay. I shouldn't be greedy.
I won't be greedy.
You should write an amount
under ten dollars to get the money.
(Their current sums: Jong Kook, 8,
Ji Hyo, 27.50, Do Kwon, 12 dollars)
The minimum amount is one dollar.
- It's better to get one dollar...
- Exactly.
in this situation.
Okay. One, two, three. Show us.
I wrote ten dollars.
- Show us.
- I wrote ten dollars.
- Jong Kook got the money.
- Right?
- Great. I got it.
- He got the money.
- So did Do Kwon.
- Jong Kook and Do Kwon got it.
- They're quite gutsy.
- She was considerate of them.
Right. She has a lot of money.
The maximum amount for you is
20 dollars.
- It'll be intense.
- We won't be considerate...
- We all need money.
- But...
If Yi Kyung writes 20 dollars...
Is it 20 dollars and under?
Yes.
(Peeking)
It'd be funny
if they all wrote 20 dollars.
My gosh. Jae Suk.
I should write at least this much.
We don't go small.
Right. That's true.
- Are you all done?
- Yes.
One, two. Show us.
Show us.
Eighteen dollars?
You wrote a large amount.
I thought they'd write
a higher amount.
- As a result, Suk Jin...
- Okay!
- got the money.
- Well played.
- Right. That went well.
- Exactly.
As a result, the two teams
with the least money will be...
- merged with the other teams.
- Really?
The team in the last place is...
- Team Yi Kyung.
- Yes.
We all knew it.
The team in the third place is...
- Team Woo Jae.
- What?
(Team Woo Jae placed third.)
- They placed 3rd?
- We placed 3rd?
- Why?
- But they have a lot of money.
- It's good. If we join So Min...
- No, it's not.
The members of the two teams will
join the other teams.
We'll get hit during the game.
I wonder what game they'll play.
I bet
they're going to slap each other.
The last two teams should sit
on this side.
- On this side?
- He said we should sit here.
Jeonsobari
Four of them will join Team So Min.
- Okay!
- Wait for me.
- Who do you want on your team?
- I want no penniless members.
- I'm warning you.
- I'm penniless.
Don't join my team
if you're penniless.
- So Min, I'll join your team.
- Me too.
I've saved up enough money
to join your team.
- I'll join your team.
- Those leeches.
- I'll explain the rules now.
- Okay.
If you win first,
you get to choose your team first...
and lose less money.
You suffer less damage
if you win your match.
I see.
As you can see,
you'll play Cham, Cham, Cham.
You'll have one-on-one matches.
Two players stand on the beam.
When your attack succeeds,
you hit your opponent.
If your opponent falls off,
he's out.
Oh, dear. That sounds intense.
Also, you will draw a number...
to make the list of matches.
Three pairs will have matches
in the order of numbers from 1 to 6.
Got it.
- Numbers 1 and 2 have a match.
- Yes.
And the winner gets to choose
their team.
Right away.
Then numbers 3 and 4 have a match,
and the winner chooses his team.
And then numbers 5 and 6
have a match.
The losers have another match
to choose their teams.
Oh, that's how the losers move up.
- We'll be at a disadvantage...
- You'll be at an advantage...
if you pick a small number
and win your match.
- Okay!
- Okay.
Let's draw a number.
Pick one.
- I got number two!
- Come out.
- You picked number one?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- I'm number four.
- I'm number three.
- My gosh.
- Number 3.
- I picked number 5.
I should win this match...
You'll get to choose your team
and lose no money.
Okay. Good.
I want to see
how well Woo Jae can do.
- Woo Jae moves slowly.
- Woo Jae is so skinny.
- Woo Jae could be blown away.
- I won't. I have a strong core.
- Okay.
- He has a strong core?
He says he has a strong core.
The balance beam is
wider than I thought.
- Wait.
- It's a wide beam.
He's not just skinny.
(The anchovy with a strong core
has never played this game before.)
It won't be easy to hold out
on the beam.
Here we go.
(Jae Suk will go first.)
Ready. Cham, cham, cham.
- Okay. Now, he can attack.
- He defended successfully.
- Cham, cham, cham.
- Oh, gosh.
Cham, cham, cham.
- Cham, cham, cham.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk failed to defend.)
- I can hit him now, right?
- Here we go.
- Go ahead.
Here we go.
(This is a chance for him to end
the match between the anchovies.)
(He's determined to win.)
He's preparing to fall.
- What was that?
- Oh, great.
(His attack was too weak.)
- Gosh. Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae, that was too weak.
- He's so weak.
- My gosh.
- Let's move on.
- Why?
Let's go.
Gosh. Woo Jae.
Cham, cham, cham.
- Cham, cham, cham.
- Darn.
Since they jeered at me,
- Okay. Sure.
- please understand me.
- You've done enough to be funny.
- Right.
Finish him now.
There he goes.
(He got another chance
while everyone was laughing at him.)
(Will Anchovy Joo's attack succeed
this time?)
(Jae Suk stumbles.)
- I survived.
- Gosh.
(After an attack with no damage,)
(he fell off the beam.)
He's so weak.
- He's so weak.
- Jae Suk wins.
- Okay!
- What was that?
He's just useless.
Did you do that intentionally
to win him over?
Jae Suk, please choose your team.
But if I choose Team Do Kwon,
the others will join the other team.
If more people choose a team
than they can accept,
the team captain will pick
the members to accept.
- Okay.
- That's a good idea.
- That sounds great.
- We'd be in an awkward position.
- That'd be better.
- Good.
Then Captain Jeon, I'll join
your team if you give me 50 dollars.
- Fifty dollars?
- You have a lot of money.
- If you give me 50 dollars...
- They'll all demand money.
(Contemplating)
- So Min, do you have no pride?
- That's too much. Ten dollars.
- Okay. Give me just ten dollars.
- So Min.
- So Min, wait. We all might...
- join your team.
- Okay.
- Are you buying him?
- Just give me ten dollars.
Is Jae Suk worth the money?
- I bought him.
- I'm on Team So Min.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Next up are numbers 3 and 4.
- I need him.
I had to recruit a good member.
(Round 2, Se Chan versus Haha)
I'll join that team.
Ten dollars was reasonable.
- Or else, it would hurt.
- Like this.
How painful could it be?
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- It doesn't hurt.
- Right. It doesn't hurt.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Cham, cham, cham.
- They're having a match after all.
Cham, cham, cham.
Ouch.
(Ouch.)
- He hit my ear.
- It's okay.
- Hey, Se Chan. You can hit him too.
- Does it hurt?
I'm hearing buzzing in my ear.
Is this okay?
- Are you all right?
- Se Chan.
- Hit me with the tip, not the palm.
- It's okay.
- Okay.
- You should hit with the palm.
- Oh, okay.
- Are you okay? All right.
- It's bearable.
It's not so bad.
Cham, cham, cham.
- Okay.
(Haha got caught!)
(Se Chan fell off the beam.)
(While trying to hit Haha hard,
he fell on the wrong body part.)
Oh, no. It must hurt.
Hey. My gosh.
- Hey.
- It must hurt.
Hey, why... What just happened?
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
- Hey, Se Chan.
- It must be so painful.
- He fell on it between the legs.
- How did that happen?
- My gosh.
He hasn't gotten married yet.
I feel bad for him.
- Are you okay?
- My gosh.
- What was that?
- Check if you're okay.
- Does it seem okay?
- I'm fine.
- It's okay. He seems fine.
- Are you okay?
- My gosh.
- Check if it's intact.
- I tried to hit him hard.
- Is that allowed?
What a shame.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
Hey, Woo Jae, did you see it?
That's how you should've done it.
(He suddenly lectures Woo Jae
on being funny on a variety show.)
- You stood out too much earlier.
- I admit it.
- Right.
- I should choose my team.
Haha, you lost one dollar.
You can choose your team now.
- Give me just ten dollars...
- Sorry?
- Give me ten dollars, and I'll...
- No.
- Haha hasn't chosen his team yet.
- I won't accept you.
- Are you upset with me?
- No. I don't have enough money.
- If you give me three dollars...
- Haha is choosing his team?
Two dollars.
- Two dollars?
- Yes.
- I want to win and join her team...
- Can't you give me ten dollars?
so that I can get ten dollars.
- I chose Team So Min.
- You don't have to give me money.
- Okay. Haha is on Team So Min.
- Yes.
Come here.
Which side is better?
- I won't go easy on you.
- Hey.
Of course, you shouldn't.
- I won't go easy on you either.
- Do you mean that?
You know, right? The world of
variety shows is cold-blooded.
Is it okay for me not to
go easy on you as a senior man?
- You punk.
- Ouch.
(How dare you?)
Why is he hitting Yi Kyung?
When he was eating tteokbokki...
Show him the spicy taste
of tteokbokki.
It's spicy.
- Cham, cham, cham.
- He's good at it.
Cham, cham, cham. What's that?
Suk Jin, come on.
Yi Kyung, you won. Hit him.
- No.
- Come here.
- You can hit him.
- Hit him.
- Wait.
- Hold your nose, Suk Jin.
- You'll hear buzzing in your ear.
- Look at him. Yi Kyung.
- That's not fair.
- Why? What's wrong?
- Why did he hit Yi Kyung?
What's going on? Did he win?
- What's going on?
- Why did he hit Yi Kyung?
- He hit Yi Kyung...
- Take this!
- Why did he hit Yi Kyung?
He's falling off.
- He hit Yi Kyung...
- Take this!
(He lost at one blow.)
He said...
Good job.
Yi Kyung wins.
(Seok Sam got knocked down
by Yi Kyung in the end.)
Good job.
- You did well.
- That was good.
- Oh, gosh.
- Are you okay?
- I joined Team So Min.
- Give me just one dollar.
- Haha hit me like this earlier.
- Here we go.
- He hit me in the neck too.
- Oh, we met again.
- "Love Me Actually."
("Love Me Actually")
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors
Okay.
- Cham, cham, cham.
- It's too long.
- I fell because I moved like this.
- It's over.
Oh, no. It's over.
- Woo Jae will fall off. Oh, no.
- I fell because I moved like this.
- Se Chan, make him fall off.
- Go for it.
Hit him.
(He's wide awake.)
He's taken aback.
- That was loud.
- It's okay, Woo Jae.
- That was good.
- Woo Jae.
- It's good.
- Can you see?
- He just provoked Woo Jae.
- It was good.
- Are your eyes okay?
- He just provoked Woo Jae.
Woo Jae, you're okay, right?
- That's normal.
- I'm fine. My gosh.
- I'm ready.
- Cham, cham, cham.
- Okay. It's my turn.
- Finally.
Cham, cham, cham.
- Cham, cham, cham.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- He got a chance.
(Core Joo finally got a chance
to attack.)
- Hit him with the palm.
- Se Chan rarely falls off.
- Go ahead.
- Hit him with the palm.
- He won't fall if you use the tip.
- Hit him hard.
(Will he show
how strong his core is this time?)
- Okay. Good.
- He missed.
My goodness.
Okay. That's good.
Keep going.
That's a good strategy.
Okay.
- Keep going.
- You're doing great.
- That's his strategy.
- Hold out.
- Okay.
- That was funny.
- That's his strategy.
I will never fall down.
- Okay.
- It's my turn.
- They're so strong.
I see that "Love Me Actually"
made them like sworn enemies.
- Indeed.
- It's my turn to attack.
- Cham, cham, cham.
- My gosh.
- He's going to get hit again.
- Wait. Okay. I'm ready.
- Hit him right now!
- Shake it, Se Chan.
In the opposite direction.
Like this?
I should hit him like this.
- Where?
- A chop in the neck.
- I don't think that'll work.
- Go for it.
(Will Woo Jae be able
to ride it out again?)
You're getting smacked around today.
The one that is loved is me!
You won.
Se Chan won.
You lost three dollars.
I'll join Team Do Kwon.
(After losing 3 dollars,
Se Chan joins Team Do Kwon.)
My chances are better here.
You're being smacked around.
- For the final round...
- Yes?
It'll be a free-for-all match.
Knock him down with jabs.
His legs will easily give in.
The old man's legs
will easily give in.
(After non-threatening jabs)
(Suk Jin loses due to
his weaker core strength.)
- Woo Jae wins.
- This...
It's easier on that side.
I want a rematch.
- It's easier on your side.
- A rematch?
Woo Jae wins.
He will choose a team...
which will send Suk Jin
to the opposite team.
- Either one of them...
- I'm pretty sure...
that no one will offer me any money.
- Of course.
- Try placing a deal though.
- So Min might be willing to pay.
- Offer her a deal.
Woo Jae, she might
give you five dollars.
I'll offer you two dollars.
- Get lost.
- How about ten dollars?
- Here.
- What?
Okay!
- Two dollars?
- I'm glad you're here.
- Do you know how much I have?
- We're good.
Two dollars wasn't enough.
Two dollars after
all the beating I took?
Tell me about it.
You should at least get ten dollars.
This is spacious.
- I knew things would get physical.
- Nice.
Our team is well-balanced.
Things would've been bad
if Yi Kyung was on that team.
Come this way.
We would've had a hard time
even with Woo Jae on our team.
Woo Jae thinks
he's the strongest on our team.
- Who?
- Look at Woo Jae.
- He's shadowboxing.
- Let him have his fun.
Think of him as
a taller version of Hwang Kwang Hee.
- Hwang Kwang Hee?
- Right.
A paper doll.
This next game is called...
Arithmetic One-legged Fight Rumble.
We're supposed to do math?
- I'm bad at that though.
- All right.
You will decide an order
for the players.
The first players will face off
in a one-legged fight.
The next player...
will sit on both sides
and solve a simple math question...
- in their heads.
- In our heads?
How difficult are the equations?
- Yes, in your heads.
I'm really bad at that.
(None of them are good
at arithmetic.)
I'm bad at arithmetic.
But I didn't major in
math or science.
- Does it include factorial?
- I bet it's long.
- Just because you studied math.
- Don't get cheeky.
- He studied math and science.
- Please include factorial.
- Factorial?
- Try including some muscles...
in your buttocks instead.
They're flat.
- Don't leave your buttocks at home.
- Him...
Quickly solving the questions...
- is how we can enter the ring.
- That's the way to do it.
First of all, please decide on
an order for your players.
The first one in the ring
has to stay there.
- Yes.
- Right?
Isn't it better
for you to go last...
- and wipe everyone out?
- Yes, it is.
- Do Kwon will go first.
- Right.
- Se Chan and you will go last.
- He'll be third.
We won't be able to enter the ring.
We need to answer it correctly
to enter the ring.
What's our best option
if we are to win?
This...
We don't have a chance.
Guys, allow me
to lift up your spirits.
My gosh. Really?
(She gives them money.)
- Ms. So Min.
- Please do a good job.
Thank you.
- Please do your best.
- This is great.
Thank you.
I don't have any change,
so I'll get back to you.
- Ms. So Min...
- She...
Ms. So Min can be quite impulsive.
- I'll get back to you.
- She's a big spender.
- Don't forget me later on.
- I won't.
Let me ask you this. Multiplying...
Multiplying comes first, right?
He said arithmetic.
Let me tell you how it'll be.
- How will it be?
- Plus, minus, multiply, or divide.
That's all you need to do.
- Do you know what this is?
- Multiplying comes first.
Yes, multiplying.
Is this the number three?
- What is it?
- Fleming's Left Hand Rule.
- Fleming. Like this.
- Who?
Fleming's Left Hand Rule.
- But this...
- You should know this.
What does this mean?
Plus, minus, and multiply.
(Directions of force
in a magnetic field)
Se Chan, you might
be sitting there forever.
Plus, minus, and multiply.
Do you know the Plank's Rule?
(Do you know the Plank's Rule?)
- The Plank's Rule.
- That's not it.
- The plank is an exercise.
- Fleming's Left Hand Rule.
Yes, Fleming's Left Hand Rule.
It's Fleming, not Plank.
The Plank's Rule?
We should be glad
he knows anything at all.
- Fleming...
- You're right.
- Here is the list of matches.
- Sure thing.
First up...
are Do Kwon and Yi Kyung.
- Yi Kyung, can you do this?
- This is bad.
- He seems athletic.
- It's fine.
Just lay him out.
Yi Kyung, take your time
and let me join you.
- Yi Kyung, good luck.
- Got it.
I'll take my time.
The first players
will take their positions.
Ji Hyo and Jae Suk,
please take your seats.
Let's do this.
- So Min, you...
- Get ready.
(Go!)
I'm doomed.
All right. That's 52.
That's 52...
Let's ride it out
until the others join us.
- Shall we?
- Isn't that better?
Sure, let's do that.
Why bother, right?
(Her brain is at full power.)
That's 52. With 2, that is 4.
Multiplied, it's 1,000.
Can't I write it down somewhere?
It's hard to stand on one leg,
- so I'll approach you for now.
- Please don't.
(Charging forward)
I'll approach you for now.
I'm finding it hard
to keep my balance.
(Sprinting)
(Yi Kyung swiftly runs away.)
You're quite fast.
Do Kwon, don't chase after him.
- I can't catch him on my own.
- Right, you need help.
(The game won't end
if it's 1 against 1.)
Is it 1,072?
(Incorrect)
Is it 306?
- Is it 306?
- That is incorrect.
Is it 320?
- Is it 320?
- You can't lean on that!
(Incorrect)
Roar.
(Do Kwon tries to take him on.)
- Hop away from him.
- Don't chase him, Do Kwon.
Seriously?
- Hop away from him.
- Don't chase him, Do Kwon.
Seriously?
Are you kidding me?
- Hop away from him.
- Don't chase him, Do Kwon.
Seriously? Are you kidding me?
- What's with you?
- What did I tell you?
- What happened?
- I told you not to chase him.
Guys, hurry up.
(They trusted Do Kwon,
but he got eliminated.)
Someone has to get in here.
(The correct answer)
Is it 233?
(Incorrect)
- What now?
- Who knows?
- Hurry.
- Just a second.
- That's 52...
- Lean on that.
- I'm dying over here.
- Is it 1,092?
- That is correct.
Okay, get in here.
Come on, Jae Suk.
Let's stand in front of her.
Yi Kyung, over here.
- Suk Jin.
- Am I next?
(Seok Sam's next.)
So 23...
Is it 323?
- Is that right?
- Woo Jae, you're next.
- Hurry.
- What the...
- Get in here.
Hold on.
- Hurry.
- Okay, fine.
- Stand in the middle.
- At least be in the middle.
- Come on.
- Get them from the inside.
Target them from the inside.
(The science major
receives his math problem.)
- Go ahead.
- Hurry.
Jae Suk, be merciless.
- Be careful.
- Don't lose this match.
That's 78...
Jae Suk, be merciless.
- Be careful.
- Don't lose this match.
- Why you...
- Next!
Next! Bring it on.
(Ji Hyo is eliminated.)
(They are dominating
the playground.)
Lean on each other.
Let's take a break.
Let's wait.
So with 180 and 16...
Se Chan, don't help...
No, nevermind.
"Nevermind?"
What do you mean by that?
Is it 288?
- Okay, come on.
- Bring it on.
(The science major is in the ring.)
Lay him out flat.
(Meanwhile, the business major...)
No, that's not it. 700...
That's 780.
Lay him out flat.
(It's currently 2 against 1.)
Okay, I have 340.
And then 12...
(Se Chan needs to join them
to level out the playing field.)
(Jae Suk attacks,
but Woo Jae holds his ground.)
Woo Jae, nice!
(Jae Suk attacks,
but Woo Jae holds his ground.)
(The paper doll
is sturdier than expected.)
Is it 897?
(Correct)
Suk Jin, eliminate him.
(Suk Jin joins the fight!)
Keep going for now.
I'll join you soon.
- Come on.
- Bring it on!
- Don't pressure yourself.
- What's happening?
Se Chan, this is an easy one.
Keep going.
Don't pressure yourself.
Bring it on.
(It's as if Se Chan spotted
a major mathematical flaw.)
Se Chan, hurry!
Is it 740?
Is it 840?
(Wrong and wrong again)
(Whimpering)
(Will it help if he looks at it
from a distance?)
Can't I get a pen?
That's 8 and 64.
Bring it on.
(Woo Jae is now surrounded.)
Se Chan, this is an easy one.
We forced him off the ring.
See?
(Woo Jae has been eliminated.)
Okay.
What on earth is this?
- He stepped on this.
- What is this?
We've got this.
- Guys, huddle up.
- What on earth is this?
Huddle up and lean on each other.
Lean on each other.
Lean on one another.
(They come together
to save their energy.)
Unbelievable.
What's taking you so long?
(They're exhausting their energy.)
Is it 188?
- Hurry.
- Hurry up, darn it!
That's 2 and 7. And that's 3.
- So 40...
- That's 2.
- And 7.
- Then 4...
You're confusing me.
(This is confusing!)
Se Chan still hasn't been able
to solve his.
I know the answer.
Is it 407?
- Is it 408?
- Hurry out here.
- He's here.
- Is he?
- Okay, here we go.
- He's here.
He's coming at us, isn't he?
(Se Chan decides to take them on.)
- Is it my turn?
- Get him!
(Jong Kook's the last player
for Team Do Kwon.)
- You've got this.
- You can take your time.
This is an easy one.
Okay, I'll take it slow.
(They might turn things around
if Jong Kook manages to join them.)
But...
(It wasn't easy,
but he got his moment in the ring.)
Run him over, guys.
(They come at Se Chan all at once.)
Suk Jin lost his strength.
(Falling)
What's with him?
You need to hurry.
(Seok Sam's legs give out,
making him fall.)
(What's with him?)
Guys! We can take our time.
It's hard to stand on one leg
for a long time.
What's the answer? Hold on.
- Oh, gosh.
- What was that?
What was that?
We need to get rid of him fast.
You'll fall if you stay like that
for too long.
What was that?
(His foot got stuck
between the mats.)
- Goodness.
- What was that?
- Se Chan!
- My foot got stuck!
(Everyone
got eliminated in an instant.)
- We won.
- He beat everyone.
(They won without doing anything.)
- My foot got stuck.
- Someone pushed me!
Someone pushed me!
- What was that?
- Hey!
My foot got stuck!
Darn it!
We're done for!
(Lost all his will to fight)
- I'm sorry. My foot got stuck.
- We were so close!
- Is it 1,435?
- Good.
Is it correct? All right.
We got it. You can set off now.
- It's so annoying!
- We're doomed.
- We could've won.
- How could you...
Is it 432?
- Sorry?
- Is it 432?
All right. Come here, So Min.
(All right. Come here, So Min.)
It's okay. Haha can join her.
So Min has to face him.
- Help me.
- Okay.
- Because of this...
- The mat is the hard part.
- It is.
That's right.
- Hold on.
- Hold on. Gosh.
What do I do?
Hold on. Here we go.
All right.
Come on in, So Min.
- So it's 2 times 9... It's 218.
- It's 211.
It's 211.
Haha should solve it.
- It's hard.
- Go for 211.
- She's done for.
- You can just fall.
- So Min is done for.
- Just sit there, So Min.
- It's 2 times 9...
- So it's 240...
- Hurry up! I'm exhausted!
- Is it 198?
- Hurry up!
- It's 228.
- So Min is done for.
Darn it!
- It's 228.
- I'm exhausted.
So Min is done for.
(Falling)
- Hey!
- What am I supposed to do?
What was that?
So Bal!
(He has to face Jong Kook
and Ssaeb Ssaeb.)
Hey, just go for it. You can do it.
- Go for it.
- You're So Wool's father.
- I'll throw myself at them.
- They will get tired too.
I'll give you two dollars this time.
Crush them.
(Stepping on to the mat
with a weird shout)
- Bring it on.
- Gosh, that guy.
- Great. Don't go to them.
- Bring it on!
No, just go.
You need to make them fall.
(Screaming)
- Oh, gosh.
- Don't go to them!
(He steps back, all scared.)
- Make them come.
- Let's wait.
Can they stand with shoulders
around each other?
(It's a match between two hyenas
and Haha.)
- We lost.
- You'll fall at that rate.
The moment you go to them,
you'll get a taste of the fiery pit.
Gosh. Let me stand with you guys.
Hold me.
- Rest for now.
- Rest for now?
- Let's finish it at once.
- Go away first.
- Let me rest for a bit more.
- Let go of me.
- Leave him be.
Just for a while.
Go!
Come at me!
Darn it.
Please come at me!
- While smiling.
- We'll watch you fall alone.
Come at us!
What is he doing all by himself?
(Complaining about the pain
in his thigh)
What is he doing all by himself?
(The game ends
with Haha destroying himself.)
What was that?
- All right!
- Why did he fall by himself?
Why did you...
What were you doing?
- Help me.
- He's so weak.
- That was hilarious.
- How embarrassing!
I mean, what were you doing there
all alone?
Hey, you couldn't even put up...
- What was that?
- a good fight.
Give me back the dollar I gave you.
- Haha.
- Give back the dollar I gave you.
- My foot got stuck here.
- But it was so hard for me.
My foot got stuck here.
- So that's what happened.
- My foot got stuck.
I knew we wouldn't be a match,
but we couldn't even win once.
Gosh, the game was disadvantageous
for us.
Everyone, the winning team can win
as much as 50 dollars.
The losing team can win
as much as 30 dollars.
- Us?
- Since there are five people,
the top two
won't get the prize money.
The top two won't get it?
Let's reveal
the winning team's first. One, two,
- three, open!
- Let's see.
(50 dollars)
Open!
I told you to lower it.
- All right.
- I wrote 23 dollars.
(Woo Jae wrote 21 dollars.)
Those who wrote 50 and 48 dollars
are eliminated.
What about us?
(Do Kwon, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo
were all eliminated.)
Woo Jae won 21 dollars.
The "Love Me Actually" team.
- "Love Me Actually!"
- All right! Us?
- It's your turn.
In 1, 2, 3. Open!
I wrote 23 dollars.
- You wrote 19 dollars?
- Yes.
I wrote 12 dollars.
(So Min wrote 14 dollars.)
- You wrote 19 dollars?
- Yes.
Those who wrote 23 and 20 dollars
are eliminated.
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin get nothing.)
You failed!
- You wrote 12 dollars?
- Wait a minute.
- You wrote 14 dollars?
- So Min, how much did you write?
- I wrote 14 dollars.
- She's one funny woman.
- She's so bad.
- It's not that.
Give us the money first.
(Only So Min, Haha, and Yi Kyung
won the money.)
I wanted to give you a dollar each.
- Is that so?
- I meant to give you a dollar each.
You want to keep us
under your influence, don't you?
- That's right, Jae Suk.
- Right?
It seems like So Min wants to
keep us under her influence.
- Give me some money.
- How much do you have?
- You spent 30 dollars?
- I only have 2.5 dollars.
- You have 2.5 dollars?
- I wanted to increase it.
- You should've lowered the number.
- Please give me a dollar.
- Why?
- Aren't they counting it?
I earned two dollars
because they pitied me.
Is it okay to give it out?
- You should donate some to me too.
- You got an allowance?
- All right?
- I don't have much either, but...
You do have a lot.
- An allowance?
- I'm in the upper rank.
- No, still...
- You can take four dollars.
- How much do you have?
- I have only three dollars.
I should have won.
Use this for your taxi fare.
What? That's money too!
(Suk Jin, who is too proud,
refuses to take 10 cents.)
Ten cents are considered money too.
- How could he give me ten cents?
- Ten cents.
It's considered money too.
- You're the reason...
- I'll collect them one by one.
they look down on me.
Then you should give me some too.
Ji Hyo. Oh, you're not Ji Hyo.
- Jae Suk.
- Ji Hyo.
(Fluttering)
(The members of Running Man world
cry and laugh because of R money.)
Ten cents is too little.
You're too annoying.
It's nice to have ten cents,
at least.
- I wouldn't accept it.
- Tables could be turned...
because of ten cents.
The three of us never...
We didn't even win once.
- The three of us...
- Why am I so exhausted?
- We started with no money.
- We never won once.
I'm so exhausted too.
You guys did your best, though.
I'm seriously doing my best.
All right. The last mission
is foot volleyball.
It's Option Foot Volleyball
we're proud of.
Option Foot Volleyball?
It's our style of foot volleyball...
- with different options.
- We're aware of that.
It'll be a 4-on-4 game,
and the remaining players
will be a substitute.
You can substitute players
all you want.
The opponent team can decide
two players...
who'll constantly be playing.
- Really?
- Two members from each team...
will be fixed players.
- We'll choose for each other?
- And the three remaining players...
can be substituted among themselves.
So Min and I will be fixed players
for sure.
There will be different options
for each round.
If you don't follow the option,
the opponent wins a point.
Your point won't get deducted.
They'll win a point instead.
Here's the option for Round One.
Making the sound the opponent set
every time you touch the ball.
- What?
- Let's say this team decided...
on a certain sound.
Each time you touch the ball,
you need to make that sound.
That sounds fun. If they decided...
on this sound,
then we have to make the same sound?
- "Aya!"
- I still haven't gotten over...
the sound Bo Mi made.
(The sound Bo Mi made is
still ringing in Jae Suk's head.)
- Then we'll pick "Nah."
- "Nah."
The moaning sound.
- It's allowed.
- Is it? All right.
- The moaning sound.
- It could be worse too.
That's the option for Round One.
It'll be a game to win 36 points
in total.
While playing the game,
if one team earns 12 points first,
we'll move on to Round Two,
and the option will be changed.
If one team earns 24 points,
we'll move on to Round Three,
and the option will be changed.
The team that reaches
36 points first will win.
Got it.
The option for Round Two
is informal talk.
- Informal talk?
- If you talk formally,
- the opponent wins a point.
- All right. Sounds good.
The option for Round Two
is not getting upset.
- It's been a while.
- We're good at that.
- That's what we're good at.
- Staying positive.
No cursing or getting mad.
I've never gotten mad at someone
in my life.
- Of course.
- Suk Jin is at risk.
First, choose two fixed players
for this team.
And do the same for the other team.
- It'll be Ji Hyo and Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae.
It'll be So Min and Suk Jin.
- We knew it.
- We knew it too.
- They knew it themselves.
I knew it'd be you and me.
Please decide the sound
for Round One.
(They'll decide the sound
the opponent team will make.)
- What could it be?
- You can change it in the middle.
- We can?
How about this?
The one that Yeong Goo made.
"Hello."
Sounds good. "Hello."
- "Hello." We'll go with this.
- We'll go with this.
- "Hello."
- Every time you touch the ball,
say, "Hello."
- "Hello."
- It's easy.
- "Yeong Goo is not here."
- "Hello."
- What about this one?
The one Yeong Goo said.
We'll just go with the one
we came up with earlier.
- The moaning sound.
- "Nah."
- Try it.
"Nah." Like this?
- That's right.
- He's good at it.
You try saying "hello."
"Hello." Does it go like this?
(He has surpassed his teachers.)
- "Hello."
- How come you're so good at it?
- Ji Hyo, you try it.
- It suits him.
- "Hello." Of course I'm good.
- You're good.
Strangely, as you say it,
- you kick clumsily too.
- I know.
- "Hello."
- You try saying "Nah."
- "Nah."
- We don't need to do the gesture?
"Nah."
- That's it.
- No.
- That's exactly it.
- Right?
- Do Kwon, you try it.
- Say "Hello."
- "Hello."
He's good because he's an actor.
- He's good.
- My real name is Yong Gu.
- Oh, right. He's Yong Gu.
- I see.
Please stand in position
including the fixed players.
(It's time to play foot volleyball.)
There you go, Suk Jin.
Kick it higher.
(Jae Suk is only good
during practice.)
You need to keep making the sound.
"Nah." This one?
Nah.
(Knee kick)
(Suk Jin is in good condition.)
Aren't you supposed to say "Hello?"
Where did the ball go?
Are you all ready?
Serve the ball outside the court.
- Okay.
- Shall we begin?
Please say "Hello" with passion.
- Hello.
- Don't say it half-heartedly.
- Say "Nah."
- Hello.
- Serve the ball. Nice.
Hello. Here I go.
Hello.
- It's out.
- Okay.
(It's immediately out.)
- Let's go.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Okay.
- It's 1 to 0.
(Team So Min that scored first
will serve.)
- That's right.
- Hello.
- Good.
- Say nah.
- It's my ball.
- Nah.
- Come on.
Nah.
Come on.
(He showed the 1st slapstick
of the season.)
But we can't take him out.
- Serve the ball.
- We can't take Suk Jin out.
- I'm sorry.
- Just think you're not playing.
I'm sorry.
Give me just one more chance.
Just one more chance.
- Let Se Chan serve the ball.
- Give me one more chance.
- Try it. Okay.
- Okay.
When will I play volleyball
anywhere else?
All right.
Hello.
- Hello.
- I'll take it.
- Nah.
- Okay.
Kick it over the net.
- Nah. Oh, gosh. It was too strong.
- It's out.
- Okay.
It was too strong.
- Good.
- I'll kick it over the net...
- if you kick it high.
- I know.
- Woo Jae, that was nice.
- Jae Suk.
You should say nah.
- Did I not do it?
- You stopped...
- in the middle.
- Nah.
- We made a good choice.
- It's funny.
- Hello.
- Nah.
- What?
- It's out.
It's out.
- It's safe.
- Didn't it touch the line?
- It went out.
- It's out.
- Isn't it safe?
It touched the line a little.
- It totally went out.
- It touched a little.
- Misters.
Why did you slap my face?
- It touched a little.
- It completely went out.
What are you talking about?
It touched a little.
- It touched a little.
Did you just touch him?
(It touched the line a little.)
(They realized the situation
belatedly.)
- Is it allowed?
- Why?
- I'm sorry if I misunderstood.
I'm a little pissed off.
- Why did you touch his bang?
- I'll apologize. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry if I misunderstood.
- You wait.
- Okay.
I'm sorry if I misunderstood.
Did it go out?
- It went out.
Did it go out? They said yes.
- This is driving me crazy.
- I should pass it to Ji Hyo.
Hello.
- Okay.
- Head the ball.
- Nah.
- Will you do it right away?
That's it.
- Hello.
- So Min.
- Did you see it?
- Nah.
- Kick it over the net.
- Hello.
- That's nice.
(Woo Jae received the ball nicely.)
- Go.
- I'll kick it.
- Hello.
- That's right. Take it.
- Nah.
- I'll do it.
- You do it.
- Nah.
- Okay.
- Yes.
(Jae Suk scored a point.)
(Nah!)
- What was that "nah?"
- Good job.
- But...
- What was that "nah?"
All right.
He didn't follow the extra rule.
I'll give the other team a point.
That's right.
- Why? It's...
- You should say nah.
- You should've said "nah."
- You should say "nah."
But while I was doing the move...
- It doesn't go like that.
- It's fine.
Here I go.
So Min, get ready to take it.
So Min, don't do it.
- Hello.
- I'll take it.
Nah.
- That's right. Slow it down.
- Who will take it?
Nah.
- Just kick it over.
- Nah.
Hello.
Nah.
- Nah. Oh, my.
- Nah.
Nah.
(He made a mistake again.)
(Nah!)
Oh, my goodness.
- I'm sorry.
- Use your head.
- Nah.
Good job.
- He didn't do it.
- Now...
Jae Suk didn't follow the rule
again.
- They get one more point.
- No.
- Okay.
- Just kick it over.
(Nah!)
(Jae Suk is busy kicking the ball
over the net as he's nervous.)
He didn't do it. Okay.
- Hey, go back.
- Why didn't you do it?
- Get out.
- Come in.
- Haha.
- He can't say it.
- I can't do it.
- Say it properly.
- You should shout when you kick it.
Let's make it clear one more time.
This is how you should say it, guys.
"Nah." Like this.
Nah.
- You should emphasize the end.
- This is driving me nuts.
We'll change it too then.
- You can change it.
- "Oh, my."
Do this.
(What's that?)
Why would you change it?
- No, Suk Jin. Make them do this.
- What?
(Screaming)
- Do this.
- That's easy.
- Make it higher at the end.
- Make it higher.
- For three seconds.
- That's hard.
- It's not funny.
- How is it possible?
It's so hard to judge
whether it's done properly or not.
Then how about this?
(Jajakjakjak, ahjajakjajak.)
Like this. Jajakjakjak.
- No.
- Ahjajakjajak.
It can't be over 5 or 6 syllables.
- That's good.
- It's hard.
- Jajakjakjak, ahjajakjajak.
- It's too long.
- Make it shorter.
- Just do "ahjajakjakjak."
(Ahjajakjakjak.)
- Yes. You can do that.
- Ahjajakjakjak.
- Like this.
- Is it okay?
Ahjajakjakjak.
How about this?
"Jong Kook, you punk."
(The sound Team Do Kwon should make)
- That's...
- What?
I'm just asking.
- I'm just asking.
- No matter how much...
If it's not okay, forget it.
- Of course, you can't do it.
- I'm sorry. We won't do it.
- Okay. You shouldn't do it.
- Yes.
What should we say then?
- Screaming?
- Yes.
Make it real high.
Do you know the sound
water deers make?
You should make it high.
Like this?
- Some people can't do it.
- They should do "ahjajakjakjak."
- Ahjajakjakjak.
- Try it.
- You should scream like that.
- Ahjajakjakjak.
- You should do it like this.
Like this.
No.
No. It's this.
(Screaming)
- Hey.
- Why are you doing this?
- I'm sorry, but you should do it.
- Why are you doing this suddenly?
We have just decided.
- Do it.
- This is not right.
- You should do it.
- Just pick one.
- How can we do it?
- We can do it. In 1, 2.
(The sound Team Do Kwon should make)
You said
we should do "ahjajakjakjak."
- Go.
- But...
- Ahjajakjakjak.
Their voices will be gone.
- You can't do your concert.
- Wait.
So Min, Ji Hyo,
you can use your hands.
- Okay.
- We can use our hands?
- You must receive it.
- Okay.
And you come here.
- Ahjajakjakjak.
- Okay.
Good.
- Nice.
- Ahjajakjakjak.
- Oh, my.
- Okay.
- Don't try to...
- Ahjajakjakjak. Oh, my.
(Little One's header mistake)
- Don't try to do it by yourself.
- Okay.
- Doing "ahjajakjakjak" is...
- I'll do it.
- "Ahjajkjakjak" is too long.
He said he would receive everything.
- What should we do?
- Hey.
It's 10 to 7.
They got 2 points left.
- We should win now.
- Here I go.
I won't go easy now.
Here I go.
- Ahjajakjakjak.
- There you go.
- Nice.
- Let So Min do it.
- Ahjajakjakjak.
- Yes.
(A frog spike with her hand)
It was nice, So Min.
- Okay.
- Oh, right. "Ahjajakjakjak."
- They earned a point,
but So Min didn't say the chant.
We'll give both teams a point.
- He said she hadn't done it.
- Okay. Right. She didn't do it.
Ahjajakjakjak.
- Focus.
- Ji Hyo didn't do it either.
You didn't do it.
- I didn't do it?
- You didn't.
- She didn't have to do it.
- I didn't kick the ball.
- You didn't kick the ball?
- I...
- I didn't kick the ball.
- She didn't touch the ball.
Why do you see hallucinations?
I'm sorry,
but why are you not doing anything?
- I'm doing it.
- You should do something.
- Suk Jin, she needs a ball.
- The ball didn't come to me.
- Then...
- I mean...
Hey, you should follow the ball.
She didn't even touch the ball.
Why would you say that?
- I mean... Hey, you.
- She didn't have the ball.
- "Hey, you?"
- Hey, you.
- How dare you call me like that?
- Did you see hallucinations?
Who are you?
- We're on the same team.
- Are you her relative or something?
- He's her boyfriend.
- What did you say?
- Her boyfriend?
Let's do it.
Don't forget.
- Don't forget.
- Think...
- that you lost your mind.
- You should increase the energy.
Think that you lost your mind.
- Just put it in your head.
- Okay.
It should be this loud.
- Mine.
- Ahjajakjakjak.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- It's 12.
- I'll do it.
(Ahjajakjakjak.)
(Oh, my gosh.)
It's 12.
- It's 12 points.
- Okay.
They scored 12 points.
- What's wrong with him today?
- What's wrong?
Do we have a spy today?
It's 12 to 8.
Now, you should speak informally
to each other.
- Speaking informally. It's nice.
- Speaking informally.
Suk Jin. Listen up.
- They told us to speak informally.
- Suk Jin.
- Speak informally.
- It has started.
Don't speak formally.
- Of course.
- Drop the honorifics.
- Don't speak formally.
- It's the worst for Suk Jin.
- This is a disadvantage for me.
- Listen up, Jong Kook.
- Yes. I got it.
Do Kwon.
- You should look at my side too.
- I contributed...
about 70 percent to our scores.
- Hey.
- Suk Jin.
- He spoke formally.
Deduct one point.
- Yes.
- Come on.
He spoke formally. Deduct one point.
- Yes.
- Come on.
You can't speak formally
at a moment like this.
- Speak informally to them.
- You know it, right?
- Don't do that, Suk Jin.
- Okay.
Speak informally, okay?
- Jong Kook, kick it over.
- All right.
(Jong Kook, kick it over.)
(Glaring)
Why are you glaring at him?
I mean he didn't have to say that.
- Woo Jae.
- I should let you know.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook, laugh it off.
- Jong Kook, hurry up.
- Hurry up, Jong Kook.
Hey, Lump.
- Muscles, give us the ball quickly.
- I got it.
- Okay. It's our turn, right?
- Muscles.
- Yes, it's you.
- It's you, isn't it?
- Hurry up and give it to me.
- It's your turn.
Isn't it your turn?
- It's you.
- It's me?
- We lost a point.
- No, they're right.
- It's because of the extra rule.
- Does it not matter?
- You lost a point due to the rule.
We just gave them one extra point.
Why are you speaking formally to me?
Then try deducting my score.
(Shocked)
Why are you speaking formally to me?
(Then try deducting my score.)
(Very childish response)
- He's the scariest.
- He's...
(The producer fears nothing
since he is quitting next week.)
Thank you.
- Thank you. Seriously.
- Hey.
Give us a point
since you spoke formally.
- It was so nice.
- Right?
Give us a point.
Okay, let's go. Get ready.
- Throw it, you punk.
- All right.
You punk.
- He didn't make any sounds.
- What?
That's not what we are doing.
- That option is over.
- We are speaking casually now.
- What's wrong with him?
- What are you doing?
- Is that option over?
- He doesn't understand.
- Isn't that what we are doing?
- Hey.
- It's over.
- Is he a fool?
- What's wrong with you?
- I am sorry.
- Is he stupid?
- Hey.
- I am going to take a break.
Didn't you call Jeju Island
a metropolis last week?
- Didn't you do that?
- No!
- Welcome to Jeju Island!
- Was that him?
- Metropolis?
- He called it a metropolis.
- What's up with him?
- I am going to take a break.
- Metropolis.
- Suk Jin.
- He became a fool.
- Suk Jin, give me the ball.
- Let's go.
- What?
- Hey, Lump.
- Hurry up.
Lump, why do you keep playing?
- You can't even play soccer well.
- Give other people a chance.
- What?
- You can't even play soccer well.
- Why do you care if I serve?
- Hey.
Stop being cocky.
- Give other people a chance.
Instead of this ball,
I will use your head.
- Come here.
- Will you rip my head off?
Why won't you guys help me?
(Standing afar)
Why won't you help me?
Give me your head.
- That's scary.
- Hurry up.
- Do Kwon, you should go.
- Ha Lump.
- Do Kwon.
- Do it right.
- I like that look in your eyes.
Don't glare at me, you punk.
You lost a sense of it.
Here you go. It's yours.
- Is it mine?
- Mine.
Hurry up.
- Hey, Suk Jin!
- I was behind you.
(Suk Jin failed
to receive the ball.)
- Suk Jin!
- I was behind you.
It went out.
- Give me the ball again.
- It went out.
- Hey.
Sit here.
- Sit here.
- What are we going to do with him?
Stay here.
- You should have moved.
Let's go, Suk Jin. Get ready.
- Yi Kyung, we need to do this.
- We need to do this.
Suk Jin, are you going
to stand there?
- Okay.
- All right.
Jong Kook, move up a little.
- Okay.
- Is it me again?
Is it me again?
(Passing through)
- Okay.
- Is it me again?
(He received the ball
with the back of his neck.)
(Suk Jin messes up
even when he is at a corner.)
- Again.
- You are good.
- Do Kwon.
- Guys.
- You are good.
Let's go.
- Are you going to play like that?
- I gave you the ball.
- What?
- Hey.
- Are you going to play like that?
- Listen.
- Hey. For goodness' sake.
- You can't win a single point.
- Are you going to play like that?
- What's up with this toothpick?
- Hey.
- Who are you?
- Hey, who are you?
- What's wrong with you?
They are about to jump me.
What's up with that pose?
What are you going to do?
- What are you doing?
- What are you going to do?
- Just go.
- Suk Jin,
- I will move to the back.
- Okay.
- Receive it.
- He dodged.
- That's good.
- Send it over the net, Suk Jin.
- Okay. That's good.
- Kick.
Move out of the way!
Okay.
(He belatedly ran over to the net.)
(Team So Min scored thanks
to Yong Gu's slapstick comedy.)
- One at a time.
- What?
- Give us the ball.
- Do you want the ball?
- Webfoot octopus, bring it here.
- I will stay at the front.
- Flatfish, what did you say?
Hey, webfoot octopus.
Hey, gamjatang.
- Gamjatang?
- Hey, bag of bones.
Hey, dried cabbage.
- What are you doing?
- You little...
Get lost, paramecium.
- Hey.
- Paramecium.
- Get lost, paramecium.
- Mosquito larva.
What are you doing?
- Cocoon.
- Pouty Mouth, bring it here.
Hey, what's the score?
It's 19 to 15.
We are four points apart.
Let's win this set.
- You are cool.
- Let's win this set.
- Let's go.
- Wake up, Jong Kook.
Let's win this set.
All right.
- Good.
- Let's win this set.
- Kick it.
- Good job.
- Okay. Nice.
- All right.
- Good job.
- Kick it. Good job.
- Okay. Nice.
- All right.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook showed slapstick comedy.)
Good.
- He looked like a fool.
- Good.
- It's okay, Jong Kook.
- All right.
Muscular Pig looked like a fool.
- Muscular Pig.
- This isn't hard.
- Hey.
- This is good.
Aren't you going to play?
- Give us the ball.
- I am playing.
- Aren't you going to play?
- That isn't the issue here.
- Give them the ball.
- What are you doing?
- Give us the ball.
You can do that later.
- Hey, euglena.
- You can do that later.
Hey, Do Kwon,
do you want to have a go at me?
- Receive the ball.
- Here I go.
- You are doing well.
- Baldy, here I go.
- Come on.
- Are you ready?
Good.
There you go.
- Okay.
- Throw it.
There you go.
- Okay.
- Throw it.
- Nice catch.
- There you go.
- What was that?
- That was just wrong.
- Nice catch.
- Seriously.
- You can't grab the ball.
- That was just wrong.
- Nice catch.
You caught the ball well, Miss.
They are hopeless.
Suk Jin said,
"You caught the ball well, Miss."
- One point to the other team.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- You spoke formally.
- Really?
- Hold on.
I didn't speak formally.
I was being sarcastic.
- "You caught the ball well, Miss."
- Is that casual?
- It's formal.
Is it formal?
- He spoke formally.
- Let's go.
- Everyone is...
- nice.
- Let's go.
- Mine.
- Everyone is nice.
It's because everyone is nice.
- Like this?
- Se Chan.
- There you go.
- Don't touch it.
- All right.
- Why didn't you kick it?
- For goodness' sake.
- You should have kicked it.
You should have kicked it.
I gave you the ball.
Suk Jin should have received it.
Bang!
Good job.
- Suk Jin.
- It's 23 to 21.
- Two more points.
- It's our turn.
- Let's win two more points.
- We can come from behind.
- Two points.
- Let's win.
- We haven't turned the tables once.
That startled me.
- You got this.
- Okay.
- Head it.
- Knees.
- Jae Suk.
- All right.
- Good.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Do Kwon.
- Don't forget to speak casually.
- Good job.
- Good.
- All right.
- Yi Kyung.
- Good.
- There you go.
(It's an impressive rally.)
- Here it comes.
- Go slow.
- You are good.
- There you go.
(He tried to receive the ball
with the top of his head.)
Hey, Woo Jae is good at this.
- Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae is good at this.
- Who knew? Woo Jae.
You are good.
- You are good.
- All right.
Suk Jin.
You are good.
The rally was going well.
Now, the score is 24 to 21.
How are you so good at it?
You have to maintain a smile
and continue speaking casually.
(Maintain a smile
and continue speaking casually.)
(Laughing)
Smiling isn't hard.
Members of our team
have smiley faces.
- Continue speaking casually?
- Smile.
- Smile and keep speaking causally.
A blank face...
- will cost you a point.
- Of course.
- We can't get angry.
- Just smile...
no matter which team scores.
- Okay?
- You need to smile.
- Hey.
- I am smiling.
Smile even if you lose a point.
- You need to smile.
- All right. Let's go.
Let's go, guys.
(They begin with a cheerful serve.)
- Haha, receive it.
- Let's go.
Good.
- Come on.
- Yi Kyung.
We are doing great.
- Do Kwon.
- Smile.
Do Kwon.
- Hey.
- Out.
Hey.
Do Kwon.
- Out.
(He headed the ball
that was already out.)
(Laughing)
It was out.
- It was out.
- I am sorry.
Out.
Do Kwon, you did so well.
We don't need to be greedy.
It was out.
- Suk Jin.
- Why did you do that?
- You fool.
- It was out.
- Why did you do that?
- Really?
- Suk Jin, it was out.
- Why did you do that?
I got confused.
- Suk Jin, I don't understand you.
- It's not like that.
- It was out.
- I...
- You are really bad at this.
- Why did you head it?
- I had to think for a second.
- Really?
Still,
- it's nice that no one is angry.
- Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, give us the ball.
- We have to smile.
- Why did Suk Jin do that?
- Give us the ball.
- It was unbelievable.
- Let's smile.
- Here it comes. One, two, three.
- Here it comes.
- Se Chan, smile.
- Maintain a smile.
- Okay.
What a beautiful smile.
- So Min.
- He looks angry.
- Okay. Good job.
- Good job.
What a beautiful smile.
- Good.
- Go.
- Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
- Big sister...
could have received it
with her hands...
Big sister could have received it
Did you just say "Big sister?"
- He said "Big sister."
- Big sister.
One point to the other team.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Woo Jae.
There is no big sister.
I think Woo Jae gave us ten points.
- Let's speak less.
- Woo Jae.
- You are cool.
- Woo Jae,
- you are giving them many points.
- Let's speak less.
- Speak casually.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Hurry up.
- Here we go.
- Let's win.
- Let's go.
- I think we can win.
- Good job.
Good job.
I can't believe he succeeded.
- Okay.
- Send it over the net.
- It didn't go over the net.
- Yes, it did.
- Send it over the net.
- Okay.
- It didn't go over the net.
Yes, it did.
(Did it go over the net or not?)
- His foot went over the net.
- Sir, it went over the net.
- Is that a blank face?
- It went over the net.
- Look.
It went over the net.
- No, it didn't.
- My foot stopped right here.
It shouldn't have gone over the net.
It didn't go over the net.
Since Yi Kyung spoke formally,
the other team got two points.
My goodness.
(They got 2 points at once.)
- Did you speak formally?
- To the producer...
- To that punk producer...
- Don't speak to him formally.
Seriously.
We even speak casually
to the director.
- He is younger than you.
- Since when were you so polite?
But...
Here comes a serve.
All right.
Se Chan's face is too blank,
so they will receive a point.
- Okay.
Se Chan's face is too blank,
so they will receive a point.
- Okay.
- Se Chan, you need to smile.
- I...
- You need to smile.
- Here I go.
- Would you give me the score?
It's six to four.
- Okay, we have a chance.
- Just now,
- he spoke formally.
- Let's go.
Since Jae Suk spoke formally,
they will receive a point.
- A point.
- Why did you do that?
- All right.
It's hard to win a point, Jae Suk.
It's hard to win a point.
- Seriously.
- Why did you do that?
Why did you do that?
- Jae Suk, thank you.
- It's hard to win a point.
- Maintain a bright smile.
- Let's go.
- Go ahead.
- Here we go.
That was sharp.
It's over. Out.
- My goodness.
- Good job.
Thank you, sir.
You are a fool.
Yi Kyung said, "Thank you, sir."
The other team gets a point.
(Yi Kyung spoke formally.)
It's okay.
- It's okay.
- That's great.
Hey, get out.
- Get out.
Get out.
I spoke to the sky.
- What should we do?
- Get out.
What's the current score?
It's 29 to 27.
You are playing until 36.
- What's the current score?
- It's 29 to 27.
- Let's turn the tables.
- Okay.
Let's go.
- How many points do we have?
- You have 27 points.
- We have a long way to go.
- I said it so many times.
- You could tell me once more.
- Are your ears stuffed?
- No.
- I said it so many times.
Your pronunciation is lousy, okay?
Let's go.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- Let's turn the tables this time.
- Ji Hyo, you can use your hands.
- Let's go.
- I can use my hands.
- Smile.
- You need to smile.
- There you go. Good job, Woo Jae.
- Okay. There you go.
- Can you get it over the net?
- Okay.
- Mine.
- Yes.
(Paramecium made
a careless mistake.)
(Forced happiness)
Foot volleyball is so much fun.
- You fool.
- Woo Jae, what was that?
What was that?
Look at Ji Hyo.
Sir, Ji Hyo pulled his hair
with an angry look on her face.
- I felt so loved.
- I did it with a smile.
It wasn't like that.
You spoke formally.
- They get a point.
- That's right.
They get a point.
Hey.
- He fell for his own trick.
- Get lost if you want to be formal.
- That's right.
- Maintain a smile.
- Let's go.
- Why did you do that?
- We can turn the tables.
- I did it with a smile.
How about Ji Hyo?
- I didn't see it.
- I did it with a smile.
- You didn't see it?
- Give me the ball.
- Let's go.
- What will we do with Woo Jae?
- Let's smile. Here I go.
- Let's go.
- Move out of the way.
What are you doing?
This is fun.
- Out.
- Let's go.
(He slapped the ball angrily.)
He expressed anger.
- He expressed anger.
(He acted out in anger.)
- Let it slide.
Wouldn't you say
it was an expression of anger?
Wouldn't you say that?
All right. Se Chan spoke formally
and Suk Jin expressed anger,
so both teams will gain a point.
- What's wrong with you?
- Keep quiet.
Calm down.
Speak less.
Se Chan, keep quiet.
I am sorry.
- Speak less.
- Let's do this seriously.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
I am happy.
- Why?
- I am so happy.
- I am happy too.
- Stop speaking nonsense and begin.
Stop being an eyesore
and send the ball over.
- Here I go. Move out of the way.
- Okay.
Focus.
Smile.
- It must be mine.
- What a beautiful serve.
Good.
- Good.
- There you go.
Nice save.
Good.
- Good.
- There you go.
(Jong Kook received the smash well.)
- Good.
- That was cool.
- Nice save.
- I got this.
- You are doing well.
- Kick it.
- Mine.
- Send it over the net.
Okay.
(He smashes the ball
for the 2nd time.)
- Okay.
- Out.
- All right.
(He failed to return the ball.)
- Good.
- Okay.
(They scored a point
after a nice rally.)
- Good.
- It was great.
- Good job.
- You did so well.
You did so well.
(Disappointed)
It was an easy one.
It was so close.
- It was too deep.
- You did so well.
- It's okay. It was a great rally.
- It was so nice.
- All right.
- Smile.
- Smile. A few people didn't smile.
- Of course.
- We are happy.
- Let's make it a tie.
Let's make it a tie. Let's go.
- We are doing so well.
- Let's go.
One more point.
- One more point.
- Good job.
- Don't be polite.
- Okay.
Smile.
(Team So Min serves
on the verge of a tie.)
- Smile.
- Don't give them a point.
- There you go.
You are good, Woo Jae.
- Mine.
- Good.
- All right.
- Jae Suk, send it over the net.
- Let's go.
- Move out of the way. Good.
- All right.
- Go slow. Okay.
- Mine.
- Move out of the way.
- Okay. Good.
- Go slow.
(Se Chan sends the ball
to a corner.)
- Go slow.
- There you go.
There you go.
Suk Jin.
- Go slow.
- Suk Jin.
- Send it over the net.
Receive it.
- Good job.
- Let's smile.
- Let's send it up.
- Smile.
- We are happy.
- Send it over the net.
There you go.
Come on. Go slow.
- Yes. Move out of the way.
- Send it over the net.
- Okay.
- Good.
- This is a nice rally.
- Go slow.
- Jae Suk isn't smiling.
- Smile.
- All right.
- Jae Suk isn't smiling.
(Jae Suk's smash)
- Smile.
- Jae Suk isn't smiling.
(He received it.)
- All right.
- The net.
Go slow.
- Suk Jin, go slow.
- Hey.
Send it over the net.
Good.
(Gosh.)
- It was close.
- Good job.
Good job, Woo Jae.
(Woo Jae ended the longest rally
in the history of the show.)
(They succeeded to score after
a tight rally.)
- Good.
- We got this.
We can win.
Good.
- You guys are so cool.
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, smile.
- Smile.
Suk Jin.
- It's 34 to 34.
- It's 34 to 34. It's a tie.
- Two points remain.
- It's a tie.
- There won't be a deuce.
- Let's score two points.
- Two points.
- Smile.
- Okay.
Let's go, Woo Jae.
- Smile.
- Maintain a smile.
- Smile. Don't be polite.
- Let's score two points.
- Good.
- That was perfect.
Good job.
- All right.
- Woo Jae, go slow.
- There you go.
- Use your hands.
- Go slow.
- What should I do?
- Send it over the net.
- No way.
- Good job.
- Good job, Suk Jin.
- Good.
- There you go.
- There you go. Nice header.
- Use your hands.
- All right. I will pass the ball.
- Suk Jin.
All right. It's a bit difficult.
- But you got it.
- Good.
- It's a bit difficult.
- Go slow.
- But you got it.
- Good.
Nice. Send it over right away.
- Nice.
- There you go. Good job.
- Good.
- Nice.
- There you go. Good job.
(He cleverly tipped the ball
over the net.)
There you go. Good job.
- Nice.
- Good.
- There you go. Good job.
There you go. Good job.
(My goodness.)
- Nice.
- Good.
(He fell down.)
I am okay.
- I am okay.
- Are you in pain?
(They laugh more loudly.)
Are you okay?
(They come together
whenever Jong Kook makes a mistake.)
Are you in pain?
- It looks like you are hurt.
- I am okay.
Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- I am okay.
I am okay.
- What was that?
- I am okay.
- I feel dizzy.
I felt like I could save it.
What was that?
I fell to the floor.
- My stomach hurts.
- I fell to the floor.
I fell to the floor.
- One more point.
- That was so funny.
- One last point.
- I felt like I could save it.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- They will win...
if they score
two consecutive points.
- Okay. I could have saved it.
- Let's make it a tie.
- One more point.
- Yi Kyung, one point.
- One point.
- Smile.
- Speak casually.
One point.
- Smile.
- It was close.
- Focus.
- Okay. I am okay.
- One point.
- Speak casually.
- Smile.
- You did well.
- Good.
- Smile.
- Mine.
- Okay.
- You did well.
- Go slow.
- Smile.
- I could have saved it.
- Good.
- Go slow.
- You got this.
- Good.
- It's over.
- Out.
(The ball went out.)
- It went out.
- Out.
Look at Suk Jin's face.
- Why did you do that?
- Look at Suk Jin's face.
It was close.
- It was so close.
- All right.
This point will decide the winner.
We tried to be too serious.
- This point will decide the winner.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
One point.
- This is the last point.
- One point.
One point.
- This is fun.
- We can do it.
- Seriously.
- This is a neck-and-neck match.
- Smile.
- My cheekbones hurt.
- Be careful.
- This has never happened before.
- I am so happy.
- Be careful.
This is nerve-racking.
- Just don't speak.
- Right.
- Mine.
- Will you receive it?
- Go slow.
- Send it over the net.
(My goodness!)
(The whistle marks
the end of the game.)
- Yes!
- We won!
Let's turn.
We won!
(Team Do Kwon won.)
- Let's turn.
- We won.
We won.
I mean...
You were doing so well.
What was that?
Are you kidding me?
- You were doing so well.
- Seriously.
Why did you mess up
at a crucial time?
- I was under so much pressure.
- We haven't won once.
- Jae Suk.
- We need to win once.
- Jae Suk, what was that?
- We were so close.
- We need to win once.
- We can't let it slide like this.
- Why did you do that?
- Isn't the game over?
- What? We lost because of you.
- I am so angry.
- Why did you do that?
- We played so diligently.
Our effort went to waste
because of you.
Why didn't you focus?
What did you say?
- We were so close to winning.
- I don't know.
While you drink water,
we will distribute the prize money.
We were so close.
- We were so close.
- Woo Jae received the ball...
even when it was a difficult shot.
I see that I am good with balls.
- I want to play another game.
- Right? It was fun.
- It was fun.
- All right.
For the winning team,
the maximum amount is 70 dollars.
For the losing team,
the maximum amount is 40 dollars.
- We didn't win once.
- Not once.
- Suk Jin, Yi Kyung, and I...
- We didn't win once.
- Seriously.
Can you tell me how much money
the first place has?
The first place has a lot of money.
As for the rest, it's similar.
- Really?
- Yes.
I shouldn't be greedy.
I am a candidate for the penalty.
- It's about the three.
- I have to win the prize.
- Jae Suk is...
- I can't be sure yet.
The difference isn't so big.
- Let's just say it openly.
- One, two,
three. Open.
- It's 32 dollars.
- My gosh.
(32 dollars, 51 dollars, 51 dollars,
69 dollars, 20 dollars)
The 3 members with 51 dollars
and 69 dollars are out.
You get 32 dollars and 20 dollars.
What happened to you?
Hey, how could you...
- You're a pushover.
- You got it.
- We have the same amount.
- This is...
All right. You're up next.
- Okay.
- One.
(How much did they write
within 40 dollars?)
- Two. Three.
- Open.
(20 dollars, 40 dollars)
I got it.
- This is so tight.
- All right.
The members with 40 dollars
and 24 dollars are out.
- My gosh.
- You get 22 dollars.
- I wrote 20 dollars.
- You did well.
- It's not bad.
- Well done.
- We never know how it will end.
- Right.
We don't know it yet.
Count your money now.
Hang on. How much do I have?
Now you can't exchange money.
I have only 29 dollars.
That's a lot.
- It's not much.
- Do you have 29 dollars?
I should've won at least one.
I have 33.6 dollars.
- I have 49 dollars.
- You have 39 dollars?
No, it's 49 dollars. Yes.
Hey, there's not much
of a difference.
I wish I made more money
at the last moment.
All right. The results are in.
This is bad. It must be
either you or me.
All right. We will show you
the prize for the winners first.
- What's that? My gosh.
- My gosh.
- What's that?
- That's amazing.
I want it.
- Seriously?
- The first place prize is...
something useful in summer.
It's an electric fan of D company
and a watermelon.
- My gosh.
- It's good for a family with kids.
The second place gets beef,
and the third place gets pork.
(Beef for the 2nd place,
pork for the 3rd place)
- Who is the winner?
- All right.
I'll announce first place.
(Who is the winner
of the Race of Groups?)
It's Jeon So Min with 64 dollars.
(1st place: Jeon So Min
with 64 dollars)
She's our team.
(1st place: Jeon So Min
with 64 dollars)
(So Min is the sole winner.)
- You did it.
- It's her first time winning.
- No, it's her second time.
- It's been a long time.
- That was Jeon So Bal.
- I see.
This is my first time.
- Is she the winner?
- Thank you.
You're so lucky, So Min.
- This is great.
- My gosh.
Well done.
- Good.
- Congratulations.
- She takes it right away.
- Today...
- That looks great.
- I'll announce the second place.
It's Lee Yi Kyung with 49.1 dollars.
- I can't believe this.
- Is he second place?
(2nd place: Lee Yi Kyung
with 49.1 dollars)
(Me?)
I turned the game around!
- It's unbelievable.
- Hey.
You won second place with ten cents.
- Really?
- Is that true?
The ten cents. It's from you.
Third place is Kim Jong Kook
with 49 dollars.
- I told you before.
- My goodness.
I said you could win
with the ten cents.
Se Chan threw away the ten cents.
- I...
- Really?
The money you gave him earlier?
(Se Chan gave Suk Jin
ten cents for a taxi earlier.)
Why? It's still money.
(The ten cents was
dumped on the floor.)
(And Yi Kyung took it
with gratitude.)
(He won 2nd place
with the ten cents.)
- I...
- Really?
The money you gave him earlier?
I begged for money.
And I collected money
I found on the floor.
You get beef.
- Take this.
- It's all thanks to you.
- Congratulations.
- Kim Jong Kook gets pork.
- Thank you.
- Pork belly.
Now I will announce
the members who get the penalty.
This is driving me crazy.
- Here.
- We started with no money.
It was neck and neck.
First, the member
with the least money.
(The last is announced first.)
It's Ji Suk Jin with 27 dollars.
It's settled then. It must be me.
(It's settled then. It must be me.)
- And Ha Do Kwon.
- What?
(Ha Do Kwon with 27.1 dollars)
- Isn't it me?
- Why?
(Ha Do Kwon with 27.1 dollars)
(Ha Do Kwon?)
- He fooled us.
- Why?
(Did Jae Suk survive?)
- It's not me.
- You survived. What happened?
- How much do you have?
- I'm not right for Running Man.
- How much is the difference?
- I have 27.1 dollars.
- I have 29 dollars.
- It's about 1 dollar.
It's two dollars.
- That's a lot.
- At the last moment,
Ms. So Min gave us a dollar each.
Ms. So Min gave me a dollar.
I thought I was rich.
That's funny.
Let's start the penalty then.
- Do Kwon.
- This is the worst.
Today, Do Kwon is...
(Today's penalty:
Human Webfoot Octopus)
Do Kwon, are you ready?
- Yes, I'm ready.
- All right.
- Do Kwon will go first.
- Okay.
One, two...
Two...
(Swelling up)
- My gosh.
- That went well.
That was fun, Do Kwon.
Next up is Seok Sam.
Can you do this, Yi Kyung?
- Of course.
- Throw it hard like this.
- Can you do this with a smile?
- Sure.
I will do it as you sing.
- That sounds good.
- I’m looking and looking at you
- My goodness.
- What was that?
- Hey.
- Gosh.
Hey, come on.
(His aim is off.)
- It's not fun.
- Yi Kyung...
Yi Kyung doesn't know how to do it.
I'll do it.
- Why did you let him do it?
- He wanted to try.
- Let me try it again.
- I'll do it. My goodness.
- Do it again.
- He doesn't know how to do it.
Why are you doing it again?
- Did you get my consent?
- No.
Do it again.
- This is...
- We didn't see anything.
- I should throw it hard.
- Okay.
- As if it rains.
- I'm looking and looking at you
(That was neat.)
He's a pro.
That was perfect.
- He's professional.
- Thank you for today.
This is what you should do.
Good work today.
(We thank Lee Yi Kyung, Ha Do Kwon,
and Joo Woo Jae for joining us.)
(For real estate transactions)
(7 Commandments)
(1. Understand
topography and geography.)
I don't like this one.
- I should buy Dongdaemun-gu.
- There will be an apartment.
(2. Occupy the land
rich in resources.)
- This is so delicious.
- Isn't it spicy?
(3. Otherwise, you'll starve.)
(Did you buy all this?)
(4. Buy as much land as possible.)
Give me some salad.
(No way.)
"No way?"
(5. It's all about negotiations.)
What's this?
(6. Unfavorable factors
can happen anytime.)
I got a call.
(7. Believe only half
of what others say.)
- Exchange.
- Thank you.
- Are you a thug?
- What?
(And...)
(As always...)
- What was that?
- What?
- I bought the wrong one.
- My gosh.
(There's a twist.)
(Investment in Real Estate)