Let's go.
Over here.
All right. Hello.
- Hi.
- Hey.
So Min, you look good.
Let's work.
This is the concept.
Yes, sir.
- What are we doing today?
- Yes, sir.
- Am I a farmhand?
- Seriously,
I don't look good in this costume.
But it looks great on you.
- It suits you best.
- Isn't this what you wore...
when you were in elementary school?
- When you were little.
- Right.
- I wore this all the time.
- With a knapsack.
- Hello.
I'm a farmhand.
- We're wearing costumes today.
- I know.
- What are we doing?
- What do we do today?
- Why are we dressed like this?
- By the way,
- So Min called me yesterday.
- Why?
"Jae Seok, we will be wearing
a slave costume tomorrow."
(Did the concept leak?)
- How did she know?
- I heard that too.
- She even knows about ads.
- Who is that?
I said I was hungry,
and she said, "Haha, we will
get to eat some chicken today."
What?
(So Min always knows about
concepts and ads before the shoot.)
(Episode 599)
(So Min always knows
where we will be doing the shoot.)
- Who told you that?
- Really?
- She hears it from an insider.
- It's an insider job.
She's close to the production crew.
Do you...
- I mean...
- Who are you dating? Tell me.
- I was...
- Who is it?
- There's someone.
- Who told you?
- Who is it?
- You're surprised too, right?
- Is that true?
- Who on earth is that?
She told me not to eat.
- She said we'd eat some chicken.
- She knows everything.
We need to know this.
We should enjoy the food...
- to please the advertisers.
- So where did you hear that?
- Who's the insider?
- Who told you that?
- Bo Pil.
- We have to find it out.
- Who is it?
I'll offer a reward for that.
Seriously...
If you find it out, I'll give you
1,000 dollars in R money.
R money?
A thousand dollars in R money?
What would we use the money for?
- We can use it in Running Man.
- We will use it sometime.
- Give me the initials.
- I'm sure...
- it's her boyfriend.
- No.
- Listen to me.
- It's impossible...
- unless they're in love.
- Look at So Min.
She even braided her hair
for this costume.
- Isn't it good to know?
- Look at her hair.
- This is against the rules.
- I'm prepared for this.
- Just give me the initials.
- I wonder who it is.
- Why are you holding my hand?
- Who is it, So Min?
- It's hot.
- Who is it?
- It must be her boyfriend.
- Why are you doing this?
All right. Let me tell you
about today's race.
The name of today's race
is Running Chronicles.
- Running Chronicles?
I bet we will eat some jeon today.
You will be the characters of
many different fairy tales today...
- through the race.
- Fairy tales.
The rules of Running Chronicles.
The members will be characters from
many different fairy tales today...
for each mission.
But among the seven characters
they are going to pick,
there is a corrupt official,
which means a spy.
One of the characters will be...
a spy, which is called
a corrupt official.
- Really?
- Yes.
And this is what the spy is doing.
The member who picks a character
with the corrupt official stamp...
has to hide the identity of
the corrupt official in the story.
While the corrupt official
pretends to be a good person,
the prize money of 10 dollars
is accumulated every 5 minutes.
Meanwhile, the other
six members will get...
one penalty ball every 30 minutes.
The longer it takes them
to catch the corrupt official,
the more penalty balls they get.
The rest of the members can
reach an agreement...
to put the corrupt official to
the Bell of Truth and arrest him.
If the corrupt official is arrested,
he doesn't win the prize money...
and gets an extra 20 penalty balls.
If the corrupt official
is not arrested,
he wins the prize money,
and the rest of the members get
three penalty balls each.
Once the Bell of Truth rings,
they will pick one of the penalty
balls that have been accumulated.
And the member who's picked
will get a penalty.
Once the penalty is over,
the new fairy tale starts.
And the members will pick
new characters.
There can be a new corrupt official,
or the one from the previous story
can pick the corrupt official again.
- I don't want to be a spy.
- I know.
Once you arrest or fail to arrest
the corrupt official,
the next fairy tale begins.
(Whether the corrupt official is
arrested or not, the story changes.)
- And there will be a new spy.
- A new spy.
We don't know how many fairy tales
there will be until four o'clock.
We prepared many different stories.
Please remember that you can arrest
a corrupt official at any time.
Just put the corrupt official
on the straw mat...
and say, "Ring the Bell of Truth."
- The Bell of Truth.
- It's like "Truth Game".
It's been a long time.
I was the host of the show.
- Weren't you on the show?
- I was.
- Was he the first MC?
- No.
Seok Jin was after me.
I took over the show from him.
- You did?
- He took it over.
And it got canceled.
(He took it over,
and it got canceled.)
("Truth Game": A game show where
they found out what was real...)
(that aired from 1999 to 2008.)
(The last MC of "Truth Game")
(They will say the same thing
to arrest the corrupt official.)
- It got canceled?
- Yes.
- It was over after a year.
- Oh, dear.
- Were you the last MC?
- It was a great show.
I was the last MC.
- Let's begin the first fairy tale.
- What is it?
Chapter One of Running Chronicles,
"Heungboojeon".
Characters. Heungboo, Nolboo,
and Nolboo's wife.
All right. You will pick
the first characters then.
When you've gathered again,
- there will be a spy.
- Okay.
Does the spy have a special mission?
You seemed to understand
all the rules earlier.
When the corrupt official comes,
you should cook
the corrupt official.
- You should cook it...
- Like Beijing duck?
- With some water...
- Let me slap you.
I wonder what my character will be.
I want to be a spy.
(One of the scrolls has
the corrupt official seal on it.)
Does one of the scrolls
have the corrupt official seal?
I can play for money
if I become a spy.
- I can get the R money.
- Right.
You will get real money.
- Real money?
- Yes.
This is...
I want to be a spy.
- Does it say "corrupt official?"
- Yes.
(Jeerren Buffett wants to be a spy
and win the prize money.)
Ta-da.
(Did Seok Jin pick
the corrupt official as he wanted?)
So you picked Nolboo.
You punks.
We have 6 scrolls
with 3 different characters.
(It's Jae Seok's turn.)
I don't want to be a spy.
(I don't want to be a spy.)
(Jae Seok also picks Nolboo.)
What are you?
- Are you Nolboo?
- I'm Nolboo, you punk.
- What are you?
- I'm Nolboo.
You're a fake Nolboo.
- You can't be Nolboo.
- I'm Nolboo.
Don't be ridiculous. I'm Nolboo.
- Ridiculous?
- I picked it first.
I'm glad to hear that.
Move over, you punk!
How dare you...
- This is my seat.
- You punk.
You are a fake.
- Fake?
- I'm Nolboo.
This one looks tight.
We didn't mean anything like that.
(He picks one
after an unnecessary mind game.)
(What's Jong Kook's identity?)
The world is full of fake Nolboos.
Why do we have the same characters?
What? I bet you are
a corrupt official.
(Laughing out loud)
- That was sharp.
- You're being strange.
(You're being strange.)
This is really...
I'm sorry.
- I went overboard.
- You're being...
You're being strange.
Aren't you the corrupt official?
- If I were the corrupt official...
- The corrupt official?
- I'm not the corrupt official.
- You can't even look at me.
- Hey.
- It's Seok Jin.
- I just...
- You insolent brat!
- It's Seok Jin.
- I was going to say that.
- Welcome.
- It must be Seok Jin.
- Hey.
- He's being strange.
- He's really strange.
- He's weird.
- Don't sit down.
- He just sounded suspicious.
- You know that, right?
- That was unnatural.
Let me tell you something.
I was watching him from a distance.
- This is crazy.
- He had one hand here.
(Defective Kim is known
to have a good hunch.)
"You can't even look at me."
He was like this. He's strange.
It's Seok Jin.
- That's not true.
- What are you?
"That's not true, you punk."
- I'm Heungboo.
- Heungboo?
- You're Heungboo.
- Yes.
Hey, is he Heungboo?
We have the wrong person.
There might be...
- the corrupt official in there.
- Yes, that's possible.
- I pick this one.
- Okay.
(Haha is done
choosing his character.)
I'll pick this one.
I'm...
(Why is Ji Hyo smiling?)
- What are you?
- Your lips...
- Honey.
- Hey.
- You're Nolboo's wife.
- Who's Nolboo here?
- I'm Nolboo.
- These two.
He's a fake.
- I'm Nolboo.
- I'm Nolboo's wife.
He's the corrupt official.
- What are you?
- I didn't pick it.
- Are you Heungboo?
- She's Heungboo.
- Hello, Nolboo. I'm Heungboo.
- Hey, Heungboo.
- Hello, Heungboo.
- How are you, Nolboo?
Come here, honey.
"Honey?" What are you talking about?
I'm Nolboo.
- She's Heungboo.
- Hang on.
- Seok Jin.
- I'm your wife.
- What are you doing?
- I'm Nolboo's wife.
- What's with you?
- What are you talking about?
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry, Ji Hyo.
- He's strange.
- No, that's not it.
- She's Heungboo.
- She's your younger brother.
You said you were Heungboo.
- I'm Heungboo, and she's Heungboo.
- Right.
- Two Nolboos and two Heungboos.
- What's wrong with you?
Hey, Heungboo.
- He's the corrupt official.
- No.
It must be him.
As soon as the rest
of the members get here, let's...
Okay. Let's do that.
Put him on the straw mat.
I can't believe this.
We're still here,
but all the cameras are gone.
Hey, there's Jimmy Jib.
(Hello.)
Right.
The biggest one is still here.
- Heungboo is unbelievable
- One, two, three, four.
("Heungboo Is Unbelievable", 1995)
(It's a hit by Yukgaksu that swept
the country in the mid-1990s.)
(Those who are in their mid-30s
and over know this legendary song.)
- Heungboo is unbelievable
(Yukgaksu returns.)
Heungboo is unbelievable
- Oh, dear, Nolboo
- How could you kick me out
- Where am I supposed to go
- In this freezing winter
Do you expect me
to tell you where to go?
- Should I go to Mount Jiri?
- This is...
- Only we know the song.
- Kids these days don't know it.
- They don't know.
What are you?
- Heungboo is unbelievable
- What are you?
- What is he?
- I'm Heungboo.
Why do we have so many Heungboos?
I'm Nolboo.
- Are you Nolboo?
- I'm Nolboo.
- Aren't you the corrupt official?
- You're right.
I'm bossam.
- Bossam?
- You're bossam.
- That's right.
- Is he budaejjigae?
- He's budaejjigae.
- Budaejjigae?
I'm Grandma One.
- You're a woman.
- What are you?
That's right.
- I'm Nolboo's wife.
- Ma'am.
- Yes.
- She was pretty when she was young.
- Hey.
Will you put it on right?
- You're an aristocrat.
- What?
Just don't put it on your head.
You should wear it properly.
- Right. Wear it properly.
- You should.
- I'm wearing it properly.
- Pull it low.
- Wear it properly.
- My gosh.
Your hairstyle is not important.
- Because of his hair... Come on.
- Come on.
- He just cares about his hairstyle.
- Don't do that.
- It took me an hour to do my hair.
- Grab him.
Grab him.
- Play some music.
- Don't do that.
- You should...
- Don't do it!
- Let your fringe down.
- Come on.
- That looks good.
- Gosh, you ruined my hair.
- Now, you're wearing it properly.
- That's good.
- Great.
- Gosh, my hair.
- Let your fringe down.
- You look great.
(Play music.)
(After pulling a prank,
they start a village party.)
(The last member So Min
who picked Nolboo's wife enters.)
- Hey!
- She's my wife.
(There are 3 Heungboos, 2 Nolboos,
and 2 Nolboo's wives.)
(One of them is
the corrupt official.)
Who are you?
- She's my wife.
- Me?
I'm Nolboo's wife.
Nolboo's wife?
- That suits her.
- She's Nolboo's wife.
- I'm Nolboo's wife.
- He's...
- Nolboo's wife too.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Honey, come and sit here.
- Hold on. Guys.
Guys, So Min took a lot of time.
She must've had a lot
to think about.
- She didn't even have a choice.
- What took you so long?
I bet she needed time to take it in.
- I had makeup done...
- I agree.
I mean,
there was only one role left.
- What role did you pick?
- I'm Nolboo's wife.
- You...
- I had to have makeup done.
Why are you Nolboo's wife?
- Hey, who are you?
- You...
- Why don't you sit here?
- Gosh.
- You sit here.
- Switch your seats.
My sister-in-law, please sit here.
- Right.
- Hey.
- Oh, boy.
- Oh, my.
Are you Nolboo's wife?
(The two Nolboo's wives started
a war of nerves.)
When did you get married?
- I got married 30 years ago.
- My sister-in-law.
- They're fighting.
- My sisters-in-law are fighting.
- I got married 35 years ago.
- Go for it!
- Who are you? You're bald.
- Hey.
Honey, sit down.
- I mean... Honey.
- Which one of us?
- Mister, put on your hat properly.
- Why?
- Come on. Stop it already.
- Grab him.
- All right. Let's grab him.
- I'll play other roles too.
- Leave me alone!
- Let your fringe down.
Don't touch my hair.
- Stop it.
Let your fringe down.
- How dare you style your hair?
- Good.
- You're Nolboo. How dare you?
You should get into your character.
- You look cute with your fringe.
- You look cute.
- Do I look better with this style?
- My wife told me to pull it back.
- Press it down.
Everyone else says I look better
with my fringe down like this.
- When did I say that?
- You look cute.
- When did I tell you to do that?
- Gosh.
Pull it back.
- You wench.
- He looks...
- Hey, you wench!
- You wench.
I'm his wife, you wench!
(They keep fighting over
Jee Nolboo.)
"I'm his wife."
I'm flattered to see them
fighting over me.
So this is how it feels.
Shall we ring the bell?
- The corrupt official gets...
- Who do you think it is?
- ten dollars every five minutes,
- Haha.
- and the others get...
- I'm sure of it.
an extra penalty ball
every 30 minutes.
- I think...
- It must be 1 of the 2 of them.
that the Heungboo over there is
the corrupt official.
- Why?
- Oh, really?
- You mean, Kim Heungboo?
- He keeps squinting.
- Me?
- He's suspicious.
- I squint my eyes?
- As if he were trying to seduce me.
- My eyes look...
- You can't love each other.
- We're both Heungboo.
- He has eyes like a snake's.
- A snake's eyes?
- Look at him squinting.
- My husband isn't the one.
- I'm not.
- What makes you think so?
- He's just Nolboo.
- You don't know that.
Honey, what was that?
- What are you doing, honey?
- So Min.
- I can't...
- That'd make it look weird.
- They look weird...
I can't kiss you.
- But I can kiss him.
- Honey.
My goodness. Honey.
There are some people
who would criticize me.
I can't do that.
- But him...
- Please don't criticize him.
- Please don't.
- It's okay if I kiss him.
- He hates being criticized.
- Right.
- He'd be in big trouble.
- He hates being criticized.
- Seriously...
- I can't kiss you.
Please don't criticize Seok Jin.
- Please don't do that.
- That's okay.
- Please don't criticize him.
- That's okay. I don't mind.
- He cries all night long.
- No, I don't do that.
- We're just acting.
- I'm okay.
I can't make everyone like me.
Criticize me if you want to.
- He's lying.
- Yes.
My gosh. It went up to 20 dollars.
- The money is being accumulated.
- Oh, it's going up.
- That's right.
- We should hurry up.
- Let's catch the corrupt official.
- It goes up every five minutes.
We should hurry up.
The spy gets the prize money
if someone else is caught.
- If someone else is caught?
- Yes.
The spy should try to make us
believe that it's someone else.
But there's nothing we can do
to catch the spy.
- Should we just go with our hunch?
- Should we choose a random person?
- That's fine too. Or you can get...
- Right. There should be something.
a hint about the spy
by completing a mission.
That means that the spy will
try to fail the mission.
I'll explain
the first mission to you.
- What is it?
- It's the kind of game you like.
- It must be the drawing game.
- The drawing game?
- Is it the drawing game?
- Let's do that.
But it's not the drawing game.
- Gosh. Why?
- Oh, no.
You have to describe a proverb
using a single photo.
- It's One Photo Proverb.
- One Photo Proverb?
One of you guesses the answer.
The rest six of you...
- have 20 seconds...
- To take a photo?
to take a photo
that describes the given proverb.
It's similar to the game
where you explain with actions.
You win points if you guess
the right proverb from the photo.
Kind words...
Will come back...
- It sounds difficult.
- to you...
You have three attempts,
and if you succeed even once,
you get a hint
about the corrupt official.
It's difficult.
- I'll give you the proverb.
- Yes.
And 20 seconds after that,
we'll take a photo of you.
- All right.
- It's an order, I guess.
Twenty seconds will start...
Ready, go.
(To try to cook beans with lightning
and eat them)
Gosh, that's too difficult.
- We can pose like this.
- Make the shape.
(The members in the front describe
"lightning".)
- It's not easy.
- Lightning?
- How should we...
- Thor.
- We should describe...
- It's not easy.
Wait. Keep it there.
I'll describe "beans".
- You do that.
- "Beans".
Okay.
- Four, three...
- I'll join you guys.
Two, one.
- Click.
- This is too difficult.
It's too difficult.
(This is the photo
that's been taken.)
- Hold on.
- It's too difficult.
- It's difficult.
- What was Haha doing?
Look at the photo
and guess the answer.
- What were you doing?
- What was Haha doing?
What did you do?
- Now...
- Haha, what does that mean?
You're not allowed to
give him any hints.
- Okay. Let's be quiet.
- Haha didn't do a good job.
It starts here and ends here, right?
- Correct.
- It goes in this direction.
(Seok Sam tries to
figure it out calmly.)
Something is falling from the sky.
- What...
- It was so hard to describe.
- What is he trying to describe?
- My pose...
- Don't think about it.
- He ruined it.
Why didn't you do
what you said you'd do?
(Haha's pose makes it hard
for Seok Jin to deduce.)
He's the corrupt official.
Right. He must be.
- Three.
- What is this?
- Two. One.
- Gosh.
- I don't know. I really don't.
- It's too difficult.
It was so hard to describe
"lightning".
- To cook beans with lightning...
- Exactly. How...
One of us should've described
"beans".
- I did.
- One of us...
- I posed like I was cooking.
- I was eating them.
- I see.
- What did you do?
- Don't suspect me. I'm not the spy.
- Or maybe...
- Let's move on. I'll go next.
- Haha is suspicious.
- I think Haha was just confused.
- It's Jong Kook.
We should divide the words
to describe.
- Don't change the order.
- Right?
- I swear it's Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, we'll start with him.
- Let's give it a try.
- I'm 100 percent sure.
Let's do this.
Hey, So Min.
Put them on, please.
- Okay.
- Me?
- I'm serious. Trust me.
- He's framing Jong Kook.
- Let's see how he acts this time.
- You have to believe me. I'm sure.
Haha, why would you frame him?
- That's suspicious too.
- Right.
I swear.
Hey, So Min.
- Put them on, please.
- I think it's Se Chan.
- Me?
- I'm sure of it. It's Se Chan.
- I'm not lying.
- Let's begin. Come here.
Let's see
if he gets the correct answer.
- But Haha is suspicious...
- Just do a good job in the game.
- He's trying to frame Jong Kook.
- Seok Jin, it's him.
- Believe me.
- It's not me.
- Well... Let's go.
- Let's discuss it after this round.
We'll give you the question.
You have 20 seconds.
Show them the question.
- Okay.
- This one is easy.
- Slapping.
- We can do this.
- Slap me.
- This one is doable. Here.
- Right.
Like this.
Look. It says "Han River".
(To get slapped at Jongno
and glare at the Han River)
(So Min, Se Chan, and Ji Hyo will
describe the latter part.)
- I'll describe the river.
- I'll cry.
- I'll describe the water.
Hold on.
- I'll describe tears.
- It's "glare".
- It says "glare".
- What does it mean?
- My gosh.
- Five.
- Four.
- It's "glare", not "cry".
- Three. Two. One.
- Stair angrily.
Click.
Three. Two. One. Click.
- Good.
- Okay.
- I wasn't ready.
- You weren't supposed to cry.
- Okay. Take them off.
- He's taken aback.
- You should've glared...
- Jae Seok.
- Jong Kook.
- What's wrong with Seok Jin?
I was...
My gosh. What's with this pose?
I wasn't ready.
Why didn't you...
- What is that?
- I mean...
- But he can get the right answer.
- What were you guys doing?
- He can get it right.
- What's that?
- Oh, I know the answer.
- Right.
- I know the answer.
- You can get it right.
- It's an easy one.
- Yes.
- You can do it.
(Did he figure it out?)
To get slapped at the Han River...
- What?
- Five.
- Where do you get slapped? Wait.
- What did you say?
- To get slapped somewhere...
- Hey.
- Euljiro?
Right.
- Stop it. Gosh, you.
- It means...
you take your anger out on
someone who's not to blame.
- Just say the proverb.
- Give me a second.
- Why... What?
- Where do you get slapped?
Where do you get slapped?
- It's 100 percent certain.
- Wait.
Where do you get slapped?
Well, I never get slapped.
That's true.
- It's 100 percent certain.
- I don't get slapped.
- I mean, usually...
- Hold on a second.
- Apple trees.
"Hey, Doo Han."
- He keeps giving him hints.
- Wait.
- "Hey, Doo Han."
- Right.
Is it "To get slapped at Jongno"?
Yes, that's correct.
To get slapped at Jongno...
- Jong Kook, look at this photo.
- Look at the photo.
- Look at us.
- Five.
- Jongno... Come on. Wait.
- Four.
- Three.
- To get slapped at Jongno...
- Two.
- Han River.
- Gosh.
- One.
- To get slapped at Jongno...
- It's difficult.
- and run away to the river?
- Let's catch the spy.
- The answer is...
- To get slapped at Jongno...
- And glare at the Han River.
- Glare at the Han River.
(They failed to get a hint again.)
Hold on. What was Seok Jin doing?
It wasn't my intention.
I didn't hear him counting down.
- It's Se Chan.
- I'm not lying.
I told him that it's "glare",
not "cry", so many times.
- But he made a crying face.
- I was just pointing at my eyes.
To describe the word "glare",
you should've made this face.
Exactly. He's suspicious.
- I described the eyes.
- He's suspicious.
- Shall we go with Se Chan?
- Let's go with him.
- I'm not the spy. I meant the eyes.
- Let's do that.
- Shall we do it now?
- Yes.
- I knew it was Se Chan.
- I'm telling you, I'm not the spy.
- Is it Se Chan?
- Let's catch him for now.
You can catch him now.
If he's not the spy,
the spy gets the prize money,
and the others get
three penalty balls each.
- No.
- We must be cautious.
- Let's go with Se Chan.
- Right. Se Chan...
- Let's go.
- Se Chan?
- What if I'm not the spy?
- I'm sure you are.
- Isn't Haha acting suspiciously?
- He's suspicious.
- He's...
- I suspect Haha too.
I don't know why,
but he kept accusing you.
- He kept framing you.
- It's Se Chan.
I'm not the spy. I swear.
- Hey, come here.
- You suspected me before.
- It's Se Chan.
- I'm not the spy.
- Hey. I knew you were fake.
- Come here.
- Are you serious? Me?
- Go on.
- Me?
- He accused me?
- We'll pick Haha?
- Gosh.
- Okay.
- Wait.
I swear I'm not the spy.
- I'm not the spy either.
- Haha is definitely the spy.
I told you it was Jong Kook.
- See? He keeps...
- That's suspicious.
- Right. He can't be the spy.
- He thinks I'm the spy? That's odd.
- That's suspicious.
- How do we arrest the spy?
If all of you agree, ring the bell,
and let him sit under it.
- But if we complete the mission,
- Okay. Sit down.
- we get a hint, right?
- Yes, correct.
Then let's get a hint first.
- Why? Do we get a hint?
- Let's complete the mission.
But the prize money is going up.
- We can stop that.
- It's better to catch the spy.
- We can arrest the spy...
- after narrowing down the suspects.
- We already narrowed it down...
But we've made it this far!
(But we've made it this far!)
- Can you step aside for a second?
- We just have to ring the bell.
- Step back, please.
- The money is going up!
- Step back for a second.
- He's your older brother.
- Heungboo, he's your older brother.
- I'm Nolboo.
- He's your older brother.
- I learned a low kick last week.
- Jong Kook. I mean, Heungboo.
- What are you doing?
- What I'm saying is...
- You're his older brother.
- The money is going up.
- that we have...
no information right now.
It's 50 dollars...
It went up to 60 dollars.
- They won't give us a good hint.
- It just went up to 60 dollars.
- They won't.
- They'll give us a useless hint.
- I said I wasn't the spy.
- Let's check him first.
If you arrest the spy,
the spy gets 20 penalty balls.
- Okay. Let's do this.
- It's Se Chan.
- Let's just do this.
- I'm really not the spy.
Who picked me? You picked me, right?
And you too, right?
- I didn't pick you.
- And you suspected me.
- Let's check.
- Okay.
- Let's go ahead.
- Ring...
- the Bell of Truth!
- The Bell of Truth!
(The final suspect Haha is
in front of the Bell of Truth.)
- Haha...
- Haha.
- Is he the corrupt official?
- is...
Right?
(Haha was brought to trial
33 minutes after the beginning.)
(Could he be the corrupt official?)
- not the corrupt official.
- I told you so.
(They failed to arrest the spy.)
I told you I wasn't.
Why didn't you believe me?
Why did you accuse him suddenly?
What's wrong with you?
- She...
- She's not close to you.
- She always suspects me.
- Hey.
- Then it must be him.
- I'm not the spy.
The corrupt official will receive
60 dollars of prize money...
- right away.
- Gosh.
And the others will get
three penalty balls each.
- Now...
- But it's too hard to find the spy.
Here's 60 dollars.
The first corrupt official...
- It's not that hard.
- Se Chan.
Jae Seok, come and receive it.
(Jae Seok, come and receive it.)
(The real corrupt official is
Jae Seok.)
I said it was him...
- What?
- I knew it was him.
(Everyone is shocked
as no one suspected him.)
(Jae Seok receives 60 dollars.)
Why would you give it to me
right here?
Why would you give me this here?
You should've given me at the back.
- You corrupt official!
- Darn.
- How dare you?
- I can't believe this.
- See? I told you so.
- Why did you give me this here?
I said he was suspicious.
- I was going to do so.
- I mean, why would you...
- Why here?
- But he stopped me.
Why in front of everyone?
- Gosh.
- You evil man!
I'm sorry, everyone.
Gosh, that was embarrassing.
(When he picked his role...)
(Unlike his wish,
he picked the corrupt official.)
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
As soon as everyone is here...
(Jae Seok's strategy:
1. Framing Seok Jin)
(2. Telling on the members
who give hints)
(3. Following the majority opinion)
(4. Pushing forward with a trial
before completing the mission)
The six members got
three penalty balls each.
- Okay.
- We almost got him.
- Why did you act suspicious?
- There's nothing we can do now.
- I did my best.
- Now...
Why did he act suspiciously?
We'll pick the person
to get the first penalty now.
- Let's go.
- He distracted us.
- He rushed us to arrest the spy.
- That's right.
- Haha seemed suspicious.
- Let's dance to a fast song
- He did seem suspicious.
When I say I swear to the deity,
I'm telling you the truth.
- I don't believe you.
- But you lied many times before.
I had no idea.
- Just pick a ball already.
- Let's dance to a fast song
He's so excited.
Here it is. Let's see.
Who is it?
Well...
Yang Se Chan.
(Yang Heungboo will
get the penalty.)
Oh, no.
The first penalty is to reenact
the iconic scene of "Heungboojeon".
It's getting slapped
with a rice scoop.
Who should hit him?
- Let's let So Min hit him.
- That sounds good.
- Let's let her do that.
- Any one of you can do it.
- Right. She's Nolboo's wife.
- Yes.
- She's Nolboo's wife.
- You...
Did you come to my house
to borrow money?
My dear sister-in-law,
can you give me some food?
We have no food for you!
(We have no food for you!)
(Yu Jae Seok, the corrupt official,
won in Chapter One.)
- We have no food to give you!
- Okay.
We'll reveal the second story.
What is it?
Chapter Two of Running Chronicles,
"The Sun and the Moon".
The characters are
the big brother, the little sister,
and the tiger.
(Se Chan is the first member
to pick the role.)
I'll open it.
(What could be Se Chan's role?)
I thought it was her.
(He picked the little sister
in a red skirt.)
- Who are you?
- The little sister.
- I'm the younger sibling.
- The younger sibling?
- Yes.
- Oh, the younger one is a girl.
- Yes, a girl.
Since I've been suspected,
I want to be the corrupt official.
(Did he become the corrupt official
as he wished?)
- He must be the older sibling.
- I'm the big brother.
- Your sister is here.
- He's my brother.
- Yes, I'm your brother.
- You didn't do anything.
No, they said I could come out
without makeup or anything.
I'm the tiger.
- You must be the big brother.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Hey, get off the seat.
- Why?
(Hey, get off the seat!)
- I said, get off the seat!
- Why?
- Who are you?
- Don't you know I'm your brother?
- You're my younger sister. Leave!
- But...
- This is my seat.
- Leave.
That's how older brothers act
toward their younger sisters.
- An older brother in real life.
- Get off the seat.
- But... Brother.
- What's your problem?
- Get off the seat.
Get off the seat.
Then I'll tell you.
- That's so realistic.
- Get off the seat.
- But why...
- Can't you just...
- Get off the seat.
(I don't want to hear it.
Get off the seat.)
- Gosh.
- An older brother in real life.
- Why must you...
- Just leave.
- sit here?
- So this is how older brothers act.
- Gosh. I hate my brother.
- You're the tiger?
Why would he take the stress
from being singled out on me?
Their younger sisters would
get back at them.
- You mean, the older brothers?
- Yes.
Why would an older brother do that?
- Lifting up your skirt.
- An older brother...
Lifting up your skirt.
- Gosh, this is...
- Lifting up your skirt.
- What's wrong with you?
Lifting up your skirt.
(She's acting weird.)
I'm the tiger.
- So? What are you going to do?
- I roar.
I mean, you're not a real tiger.
Ji Hyo, why did you do that?
She lifted up his skirt.
- When little boys see a girl...
- Just be quiet.
wearing a skirt,
- they do that.
- You never act like that.
Ji Hyo, what...
- What happened to you?
- She's acting weird suddenly.
- Suddenly...
- She's acting weird.
- Did you see her roaring?
- No, she's not suspicious.
She usually becomes quiet
when she's chosen as a spy.
- No, she's acting differently.
- This is difficult.
In this mission,
- we'll give you a letter,
- Yes.
and you all have to write a word
that starts with that letter.
- A letter?
- But...
each object should be smaller
than the previous one.
You'll give us the first syllable?
The first syllable?
(They have to write an object
smaller than the previous one.)
(The first syllable: "han",
Korean Peninsula, Korea, Han River,)
(Korean beef, hanbok, hanji,
hallabong)
That sounds easy.
Of course, we can do it.
- In your position...
- Oh, we have to guess?
Yes, you have to guess.
You don't know what the person
in front of you will write.
Why don't we pick one person
and put him or her on trial?
Right.
Let's put Ji Hyo on trial now.
You're not the spy again, right?
- What?
- No, I'm not.
- Right now?
- Why suddenly?
- We should get a hint.
- Let's play it. It sounds fun.
- Right now?
- Are you the spy this time too?
- Why suddenly?
- To reduce the probability?
- Who do you think is the spy?
- Why would he...
- I don't know.
- He's suspicious.
It's possible that he became the spy
for the second time in a row.
- It's possible.
- Right.
But there's a low probability...
because there were only two roles
left for me to choose from.
Then why did you suggest that?
Let's get a hint first...
- this time.
- It'd make it easier.
Okay, then. Let's do that.
- He's really suspicious.
- Right? That's weird.
Please bring whiteboards
and partitions.
Since we failed last time,
let's get a hint first this time.
- Okay.
- This game requires good sense.
Since I'm the first person,
I should write something big.
Jae Seok,
why are you sitting in the middle?
(Jae Seok,
why are you sitting in the middle?)
- Why is Jae Seok...
- Then where should I sit?
- Sorry?
- Where do you want me to sit?
- Detective Kim, you seat us then.
- I mean...
You can sabotage the team easily
if you sit in the middle.
Then where do you want to sit?
(Glaring)
Where should I sit?
- Pardon?
- Where?
You should actively arrange
the order as I do.
You seem suspicious
because you're just sitting there.
- But actually...
- All right.
- You wouldn't be blamed...
- I mean...
- even if we fail.
- But that's not all.
He doesn't seem determined
to pull this off.
- Look at him.
- He's trying to...
- get away with it.
- He didn't analyze the game.
- Look at me standing here.
- He was just sitting there.
Do you even know the rules?
- Hold on.
- Do you know the rules?
- Do you want to pull this off?
- Why wouldn't I?
That's why I chose to sit
in the middle.
- But...
- Time is passing.
Then you should've arranged
the order.
Okay. Got it.
- Jae Seok must not be it, right?
- No.
It's possible that he became the spy
for the second time in a row.
- I don't think he's the spy.
- Jae Seok, sit at the end.
- I'll move to the end.
- The biggest thing...
should be something
we can think of right away.
- Write something huge.
- Okay.
Do not discuss or give one another
a hint. Here's the first question.
I'll write something predictable.
- Something predictable, okay?
- Yes, and something huge.
Also, I'm not the corrupt official.
Let's begin the first round.
Write a word that starts with "ji".
- "Ji"?
Write words that start with "ji"
from the biggest to the smallest.
- Write the biggest thing.
- "Ji"?
You're not allowed to discuss
or give one another a hint.
- Write the biggest thing.
- A word that starts with "ji".
- "Ji".
- "Ji"?
- Hey.
- What could there be such words?
- I'm done.
- The first word should be...
- that word.
- Of course.
- Right? You wrote it, right?
- You can think of nothing else.
There's nothing bigger than that.
- But that...
- It must be something huge.
How big is yours?
- You can't ask that.
- Come on.
- Use your brain!
- Five.
- Think of one.
- Four.
- Must I write one too?
- Yes, right now.
- I thought it was in order.
- Hurry up.
- Just a second. I didn't know.
- Five.
- Four.
- But...
- Three.
- Write down your name.
Two, one.
- Haha, say yours out loud.
- His is going to be short.
Haha, go ahead.
Earth.
- Good.
- Nice.
Jong Kook?
Mount Jiri.
- Okay.
- Nicely done.
- Nice, right?
- Ji Hyo, you're next.
- Jee Seok Jin.
- My gosh.
- What?
- Jee Seok Jin.
- My gosh.
(Jee Seok Jin after Mount Jiri?)
- Seriously?
- Jee Seok Jin?
- What?
- After Mount Jiri?
- How's that a good answer?
- Seok Jin wrote subway. Fail!
Subway?
Seok Jin wrote subway. Fail!
- You wrote subway?
- Ji Hyo, come on.
- Ji Hyo.
I can't help but question Ji Hyo.
- What the...
- Seriously?
Se Chan wrote worm,
so you had no chance anyway.
- Worm was supposed to be mine.
- Come on.
- Worm?
- It had to be smaller.
Ji Hyo, why on earth
did you write Jee Seok Jin?
- Mount Jiri and then...
- Before worm...
The subway is too big.
- The subway isn't so bad.
- Right?
- I went with Mount Jiri.
- Yes, Mount Jiri.
How can the subway
come out in the middle?
Just think about it.
After Mount Jiri...
- No way.
- Mine was good enough.
- Mount Jiri and then...
- The subway isn't so bad.
- Seok Jin.
- But Ji Hyo...
- Let's swap seats.
- Sure thing.
- But Seok Jin...
- For the third word?
That was odd, right?
Jae Seok,
would you like to go first?
Okay.
Okay, Jae Seok will go first.
- The first word is the easiest.
- The middle section is difficult.
- Ji Hyo, go to the end.
- Sure.
- Will Ji Hyo be at the far end?
- Yes.
No, swap seats with Se Chan.
- I don't think it should be Ji Hyo.
- Se Chan, go to the far end.
- Who are you suspicious of?
- The far end?
We won't know until
we play one more round.
It really isn't me though.
- I think it's Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin?
- He suddenly suspects Seok Jin.
- Out of the blue?
Why are you suddenly accusing me?
- It's not me.
- I think it's Seok Jin.
- Doesn't it seem like Seok Jin?
- Suddenly?
- Why are you suddenly accusing me?
- But subway seemed all right.
It seems reasonable.
Subway?
I think it's Seok Jin.
- He assumed it would be Earth.
- Yes, Earth.
I thought the first word
would be Earth.
I get that, but...
- We'll go into the next round.
- This is impossible, you know.
Let's give it a try.
- We might get lucky.
- Let's try and beat this game.
- Seok Jin.
- That sounded forced just now.
"Let's try and beat this game."
- You're right.
- Think about it.
He said,
"Let's try and beat this game."
That sounds unnatural.
- "Let's try and beat this game."
- Who said that?
Am I the target this time around?
- It has to be Seok Jin.
- I mean...
- It must be Seok Jin.
- "Let's try and beat this game."
- Why?
- How was that not weird?
- Trust me on this.
- "Let's try and beat this game."
- Let's give it another try.
- Right, just one more round.
- Let's give it another shot.
- Let's get ourselves that hint.
I'm sure of it.
- I know it's him.
- But...
- What he said got to me.
- Why?
"Let's try and beat this game."
Are you accusing me
because you're the spy?
I mean...
The spies are the ones
who fervently accuse others.
- Seok Jin...
- Keep that in mind.
- Next round.
- Sure thing.
The Korean word starting with "woo."
- Woo?
- Yes.
- I know what I'm going to write.
- Woo.
I'll write down something
that is of a similar size.
- I wrote down something huge.
- The first person has it easy.
The Korean word
must start with "woo."
- Just a second.
- The middle is not easy.
- The spy must be smart.
- My pen.
- Here you go.
- Just a second.
- Give me a second.
- The spy has 50 dollars already.
- This is of a similar size.
- The spy has 50 dollars.
Hey!
- I'm changing my answer.
- Seok Jin's the spy.
- Why?
- He's taking the longest...
to write down his answer.
- No way.
- Why would that be?
- Why are you accusing me?
- One and you're done.
Open!
- All right.
- Here.
- Space.
- Of course.
Jong Kook, you're next.
- Uruguay.
- Uruguay?
Darn, I wrote Uzbekistan.
- We'll see which one is bigger.
- Seriously?
(They will fail if Uzbekistan
is larger than Uruguay.)
Wait, we must check
which country is bigger.
You shouldn't have
written down a country...
when I'm second in line.
What could I have written?
You should've known that
I would be writing down a country.
- It's Seok Jin for sure.
- Seok Jin.
Uzbekistan. Fail!
- Why?
- Who wrote down Uzbekistan?
- Let's put Seok Jin on the stand.
- It's bigger than Uruguay.
Let's put Seok Jin on the stand.
- Yes, let's do that.
- Put him on the stand.
- Why?
- Get over here.
- Seconds ago...
- We can get him this time.
- Guys, it's not me.
- I'm sure of it.
- When we talked about the spy...
- It's not me.
You shouldn't have
written down a country.
It's hard to decide
what to write in my position.
Guys, don't let
Jae Seok persuade you.
- Let's put it to a vote.
- Hear me out.
- You should've seen him.
- What did I tell you?
He faced the camera earlier...
and smirked. I saw it.
That's true.
More than anything,
he said,
"Let's try and beat this game."
You know how that is, right?
- Let's put it to a vote.
- Guys!
- Jae Seok baited us all last time.
- It's Seok Jin.
- Him saying that is unnatural.
Trust me on this.
- Let's put this to a vote.
- Take your seat.
(They put Seok Jin on the stand.)
I'm sure of it.
- It's Seok Jin.
- I know it's him.
- Okay, let's do this.
- It's time.
- Ring the Bell of Truth.
- Uzbekistan was a weird answer.
- Exactly.
After space, of course,
I would write down a country.
- Seok Jin...
- It's him, isn't it?
Chapter Two, "The Sun and the Moon."
- The corrupt official...
- It's him, isn't it?
- I know it's him.
- It has to be.
(Is he the corrupt official?)
- The corrupt official...
- It's him, isn't it?
- It's Seok Jin.
- Yes!
(They were able
to capture the corrupt official.)
What did I tell you?
I saw him smirk.
"Let's try and beat this game."
- You're right.
- "Let's try and beat this game."
That's how I knew.
"Let's try and beat this game."
Let me be
a corrupt official for once.
One, two.
Darn it.
You will play the role
of the sister...
who is in fact a corrupt official.
(He took the seat in the middle...)
(which was a good position
to get the answer wrong.)
(When Ji Hyo was accused
of being the corrupt official...)
(He smirked proudly at the camera.)
(But Haha caught him.)
I think it's Seok Jin.
Out of the blue?
(He reacted awkwardly
completely flustered.)
Let's try and beat this game.
(Because he was flustered,
he said something out of character.)
(Jae Seok saw
right through his words.)
Just so you know,
you managed to catch him
in 27 minutes...
which means you didn't get...
- any additional penalty balls.
- What a relief.
Only Seok Jin has penalty balls,
so he'll be receiving the penalty.
- Okay!
- Nice!
- Got you!
- All right!
Here's the penalty.
- After "space..."
- I knew it.
- "Let us..."
- The penalty for chapter two.
The corrupt official
will receive a flogging.
And thus,
they managed to capture Seok Jin.
Nice!
How could you write down Uzbekistan?
- He will be flogged twice.
- All right!
Twice?
Do I get to choose?
No, the others will choose.
- Then...
- It should be one of the tigers.
Just don't let it be Jae Seok.
Don't let it be him.
How else would it be funny though?
- Don't let it be them.
- Okay, fine.
- I'll take one from each of them.
- Okay.
All right. Here comes the first one.
The first one!
My thighs!
Darn, my thighs!
- You hit the back of my thighs!
- Nicely done.
Seriously?
- Here's the second one.
- The second one!
- The second.
- Go for it.
It's all right.
You can aim for his thighs.
(Ji Hyo aimed for
where So Min hit him.)
- You only patted him.
- You didn't hit him hard.
Then Ji Hyo...
acted weirdly for no reason.
(She acted weirdly
for no particular reason.)
I was only messing with him earlier.
- That ends the second chapter.
- Okay.
And we'll now move onto the third.
Not being a corrupt official
might be better.
Chapter Three of
the Running Chronicles.
"Chunhyangjeon."
The characters are
Sung Chun Hyang, Lee Mong Ryong,
and Magistrate Byun.
("Chunhyangjeon")
So Min, you're up first.
I always went last,
so I never got to choose.
This is the one.
I don't want to be
the corrupt official.
It'll only stress me out.
(So Min didn't want to be
the corrupt official.)
I wouldn't mind
letting others go first.
Choosing a role
is just as nerve-wracking.
- Who are you playing?
- Chun Hyang.
Who is she supposed to be?
(In comes the fair lady in red.)
- Chun Hyang?
- Is this "Simcheongjeon"?
Is this "Simcheongjeon"?
Is it "Chunhyangjeon"
or "Simcheongjeon?"
And she's Chun Hyang?
(Modest and obedient)
You're more like a nun.
Serve me, woman!
What?
(What?)
(What Seok Sam said
was completely irrelevant.)
If I had...
If I had chosen a role,
they would've accused me
of being the spy.
You would've accused me, right?
- There comes Magistrate Byun.
- Darn scoundrels.
- He's Magistrate Byun.
- Get going.
You actually look the part.
- You look the part.
- Is he a nice guy?
- He's a villain.
- Is he?
So Min,
how does it feel
to be the corrupt official?
- It's not me.
- How does it feel?
I wasn't successful.
(She didn't even bat an eye
at his question.)
Are you the corrupt official?
I'm not.
- Are you the corrupt official?
- Over my dead body.
There's a good chance
that the role will get chosen early.
- Was that the case with you?
- Yes.
It really isn't me.
I saw So Min
when she came back out...
and her expression seemed off.
(Is So Min the corrupt official?)
So Min's expression, I mean.
- Really?
- Why are you accusing me?
Chun Hyang!
Are you going to serve me?
No, I will not serve you.
As I have promised myself
to someone else,
- I cannot...
- You silly girl.
How dare you speak so many words.
(In comes
the pretty Magistrate Song.)
- I will serve you, my lord!
- Magistrate Song.
(Chun Hyang falls in love
at first sight.)
- How dare you.
- Serve me, silly girl.
- You want it easy, don't you?
- I will serve you, my lord!
Magistrate Byun, will you serve me?
Why you...
You're the one who should serve me.
You're hindering my role-playing.
Serve me, darn it.
How dare you!
(While the two magistrates argue
about who serves who)
(In comes Chun Hyang
who is large in size.)
Chun Hyang, you silly girl!
The role suits you.
Darling.
- Are you kidding me?
- Darling.
Why do you even like me?
Why are you so obsessed with me?
- What are you talking about?
- What do you like about me?
Why do you like me?
- Why do you...
- Don't you dare give him service.
I'll kill you
if you give him service.
I'll slap you in the face
if you do that.
He won't let you live.
My goodness.
- Hey.
- Who are you?
- I'm Chun Hyang.
- Are you Chun Hyang?
- You're fake Chun Hyang.
When did you become Chun Hyang?
- "When"?
- When did you become Chun Hyang?
I'm the first.
- I'm the second.
- You're younger than me.
Hey.
So Min had this horrible look
when she came out.
It's because I'm tired.
I think it's So Min based
on how she looked when she came out.
She won't stay still if I ask her
when she became Chun Hyang.
- I said I'm the second.
- That's true.
She would make a fuss
if I say something like that.
- I said I'm the second.
- She said it timidly.
And So Min isn't making a fuss.
- Listen up.
- She isn't making a fuss.
Haha, can you just arrest her
as soon as she came out?
- So Min is really...
- So Min.
- Let's go with So Min once.
- She's been too quiet.
It's so strange.
- I'm really not.
- Come here
(Let me carry you on my back)
- Gosh.
- What is it?
(Young Master Yu entered the room.)
- He's Lee Mong Ryong.
- Gosh.
- Hey.
- I should run away.
No. Let's get married.
I'll go to your bedroom.
(She proposed to Magistrate Yang
to run away from Mong Ryong.)
- Wait.
- No.
I did wrong.
Honey, I'm here.
- Honey.
- No.
- I'm a nice woman.
- Magistrate Byun hit on me.
- No.
- I like neither of you.
- Honey.
- I've been waiting for 30 years.
- I like neither of you.
You're not my type either.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
- My boyfriend is here. I should go.
- And I... Hold on.
I should tell you guys this
in advance. I'm Mong Ryong,
but I'll be single for a while.
- What? Hey.
- Okay?
- You're...
- Without any burden.
- I've been waiting for a long time.
- It's okay.
I want to be by myself
without any burden.
It's Mong Ryong.
- Oh, my.
- Little colleagues.
- He looks like a crown prince.
- Hey.
As you said, let's go with So Min
as soon as Jong Kook comes out.
Yes. So Min is acting weird.
- Let's do it right away.
- Her look was so strange.
- Let's do it immediately.
So Min was too weird.
- I just...
- Do it right away.
Her voice got a little lower.
- I know.
- She can't talk back.
- She's awkward.
- It's not like that.
I said a joke,
and she can't take it or talk back.
- She can't.
- Let's do it right away.
- It's because I'm hungry.
- That's possible.
- No.
- Her voice...
Shall we check
before Jong Kook comes?
- I'm not.
- Let's do it right away.
- It's Jeon So Min.
- Yes.
I became confident about it.
The corrupt official must be
having fun. I don't know who it is.
- Okay. What's this...
- I really...
I choose So Min.
- So Min.
- Sit down.
Let's check So Min first
before moving on.
I'll do it when everyone agrees.
- I'm not though.
- The Bell of Truth.
I'm really not.
(Chun Hyang quietly
takes a seat by herself.)
- The Bell of Truth.
- So everyone agrees, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Do you agree as well, Jong Kook?
- Of course, I do.
- I'm not.
- Fold it and...
- You'll regret it.
I'll check each of you.
- Ring the Bell of Truth.
I'm not.
(Ring the Bell of Truth)
(Who is the corrupt official
in "Chunhyangjeon" Chapter 3?)
All right. The corrupt official
in "Chunhyangjeon" part two...
It's only ten dollars.
It'd be amazing if we arrest
the culprit as soon as it began.
I'm not.
So Min...
Is she not?
- Is the one.
So Min isn't the one.
I told you. Who is it?
(They failed to arrest
the corrupt official.)
You should've told us.
I did.
You should've kept telling us.
Why did you not say it firmly?
- I said it firmly.
- You were not into your role.
That's not true.
- She...
- All right.
The corrupt official
of part three...
Who was it?
(The real corrupt official
who had it easy behind So Min)
Congratulations.
- It's Jong Kook.
- I did nothing.
(Jong Kook, the corrupt official)
- I was in the back.
- It's Jong Kook.
I did nothing. I was in the back.
He didn't even try.
(Jong Kook who came last and agreed
with them is the corrupt official!)
- I didn't even try.
- Was it left until the end?
(I didn't even try.)
Yes.
There's one left.
(A while ago)
No way.
Oh, my.
Gosh.
(He thought it was unlikely, but he
picked the corrupt official scroll.)
(Gosh.)
Do I really have to do this?
(Young Master Kim went out
with worries.)
Gosh, what's this?
(As soon as he went out,
they insisted it was So Min.)
- Do you agree?
- Of course, I do.
(He sealed his victory even before
he finished wearing the headpiece.)
(The corrupt official in Chapter 3
did nothing.)
- Was it left until the end?
- I opened it, and it was the one.
- This is unbelievable.
- We couldn't suspect you.
Right?
Because everyone
was ganging up on her.
Jong Kook,
this is ten dollars for you.
- I did nothing.
- He did nothing.
I'm not.
- You had a weird look.
- All of a sudden,
he asked me if I agreed,
so I said, "Of course."
- As soon as you came out.
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- You...
- The penalty is the leg screw.
- Isn't it the leg screw?
This one.
- This would be painful.
- Okay.
Get the penalty balls.
There are three for each of you.
Don't act weird.
I didn't imagine
it would come out at the end.
"Ji Hyo".
(Ji Hyo was picked.)
Screw her legs.
(Painful)
Don't hold it in.
Why would you hold it in?
Say it quickly.
- Say it.
- But...
there's a way
to make it not painful.
How?
How do you do that?
Let me try it. Do it to me.
- Not painfully?
- So that Seok Jin would believe it.
- If it was a little less weird...
- Come here.
- Look.
- Why?
- This is...
- To make it not painful?
- You can avoid it.
- How?
- Try it.
- Okay.
- You can avoid it?
- How can you avoid it?
- Put them in.
- There's a way.
- Look. Over there.
- You should put it here?
- Try it.
- He said he would avoid it.
- You can put it anywhere.
- You're going to avoid it?
- Go.
- Try it.
(Shouting)
- Go.
- Try it.
(Painful)
- How can you avoid it?
- Give me a moment.
Get into a position you want.
- There's a way to avoid it.
- Who?
- The suspect?
- Okay.
Look. You should...
- put your legs like this.
- Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3.
Is he straining his legs?
I can't do it.
- It will break the wood.
- Did you see it?
I'll try it.
No.
(An unexpected scenario)
Stand aside.
- You're going to avoid it?
- No.
- You don't know the situation.
- Try it.
- Se Chan, did you tell him?
- I didn't talk with him yet.
- It seems it's not arranged yet.
- You said you would strain them.
- No. I mean...
- In 1, 2, 3.
(They proceed to twist his legs.)
- Tighten your muscles.
- You son of a gun.
You said there's a way to avoid it.
- It hurts.
- I did it because I was curious.
- I'm sorry.
- We didn't talk about it yet.
It hurts so much.
Did you not talk about it?
- No, I didn't.
- I'm sorry.
- I got it.
I know what you were up to.
If he had acted like it didn't hurt,
you would've made me do it...
- and suffer the pain, right?
- Did you not talk with him?
- I just heard about it too.
- It's funny.
- I see.
- Yes.
(The plan to twist Seok Sam's legs
failed.)
It hurts.
- Goodness gracious.
- Okay.
The secret inspector is here.
- Myung Jae.
(The secret inspector is here!)
(A secret inspector appeared
in "Running Chronicles".)
(The assistant director appeared
shyly in an expensive outfit.)
- What are you doing?
- Myung Jae.
What's the matter?
Is it a mission?
This is for sinner Jong Kook
and Haha.
What?
You don't deserve
to have product placement...
as you're promoting other products.
You shall be arrested for the damage
of product placement in our show.
- Okay.
- Go.
(You shall be arrested!)
Get out of here.
- Get out of here.
- Do I have to get this?
Do we really have to get this?
Why are you not cooperating
for the show?
(They became criminals at once.)
- How dare you promote other stuff?
- This is...
I'll wait
until you have product placement.
- They're in danger too.
- I don't have one.
- I don't.
Why do they not let us
do product placement?
- I want to do that and leave too.
- Me too.
- It's cool.
- To where?
I want to leave with them.
It means
he wants to film a commercial.
- Enjoy your food.
- Okay.
- Go.
- See you later.
- Say what the whole family enjoys.
- Don't worry.
- I'll say the line.
You must say
that my son would like it.
I'll eat it with rice.
You guys eat this bibimbap here.
- Thank you.
- Why are you speaking informally?
You can't say that.
That young man.
(The role-play doesn't work
in the small room.)
You don't even come out
to play soccer these days.
I'm fine
with not being able to see it.
(The two criminals
are imprisoned in the small room.)
What's today's product placement?
Okay.
I'm having homemade food
after a long time.
Really?
- Because it's a "Mom."
- "Food from a mother."
- Homemade food after a long time.
- It's coming.
Mom.
- The fried chicken looks amazing.
- It's fried chicken today.
- It's a party.
- It looks delicious.
It smells so good.
Why are the burgers so big?
She's not my real mom, but...
(The hungry people will enjoy
their mom's food.)
Mom.
I haven't had homemade food
for a long time.
This fits my taste.
This fits my taste. It's thick.
That's my line.
- Why?
- "This fits my taste."
- You...
- They will edit it nicely.
Can you see what they're holding up?
You'll take a bite and leave
as if you forgot something.
(Jee Seok Jin is to leave
as if he has an urgent business.)
You'll take a bite and leave.
This is really to my liking.
The combo that has
both burgers and chicken.
(They try western food
without minding the conditions.)
- The sauce is really nice.
- It suits my palate.
- The chicken is quite spicy.
- It's good.
It's really good.
(They enjoy their lunch
while showing a natural reaction.)
By the way, we look classy
without those two.
We can have a talk at peace.
With Haha, it'd look too tacky.
- Haha is...
- Poor him.
- He...
- He just says random things.
He makes it look so cheap.
There's a certain degree
you must keep for product placement.
There's this standard we must keep.
But he lowers the standard a lot.
And we haven't mentioned
the world "family" the whole time.
- Right.
- Seok Jin! I...
- I didn't know you were so classy.
- Did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes.
All right. Here's Chapter Four.
Chapter Four.
Running Chronicles Chapter Four.
"The Story of Terrapin".
Characters.
Rabbit, Terrapin, and Dragon King.
It's "The Story of Terrapin".
I hope I won't be
the corrupt official this time.
Please, I ask of you.
I'll choose the one in the middle.
(All 7 of them chose
their characters...)
(for "The Story of Terrapin".)
- So you're Terrapin.
- I am Terrapin.
- It's Terrapin.
- Look at the way he's walking.
I wish I could be Terrapin too.
- I got one that suits me so well.
- What did you get?
- You're Rabbit?
How come a rabbit is so threatening?
- He's one scary rabbit.
- He's here.
- He's so threatening.
- Jong Kook.
- It's like he's shooting lasers.
- He's not cute.
It feels like he'll shoot laters
from his eyes.
He looks like...
a GMO rabbit.
A genetically modified one.
He looks like a GMO rabbit.
A rabbit whose genetics went wrong.
The result of a research
that went wrong.
- What's Seok Sam's character?
- Dragon King.
Oh, he's Dragon King.
- It suits him.
- Get on your knees.
It suits him. Right, Ji Hyo?
It feels like...
I'm going into a Chinese restaurant.
One jjajangmyeon, please!
It feels like I'm standing in front
of a Chinese restaurant.
- That's so funny.
- Like this.
- That's hilarious.
- I feel like I have to go in.
You should lower your hat.
- I have to keep wearing a hat.
- That's it.
Two servings
of jjajangmyeon, please.
It's hitting your nose.
- It keeps hitting my eyes.
- It keeps hitting his nose.
I'm supposed to be Dragon King.
I'm not happy with it.
It keeps hitting his nose.
A table for three, please.
(A table for three, please.)
Gosh, it's like I'm in
a Chinese restaurant all day.
- You're Rabbit.
- I'm Rabbit.
You're Rabbit. It suits you.
We have only one Dragon King.
- There's only one Dragon King.
- How come there's only one?
And we have three Terrapins.
- Everyone, this mission...
- Yes.
Yes.
requires your teamwork.
It's really important.
We have the best teamwork.
It's called Team Play Running.
- All right.
- Great.
The rule is really simple.
We'll hand these out.
- It measures your distance.
- Our distance?
Carry one of these.
(Carry a smart tag
that measures your distance.)
(Go as far as you can from
the starting point for 20 seconds.)
For 20 seconds,
go as far as you can
from the starting point.
The total distance between
the 7 of you must be more than 500m.
More than 500m?
(They'll succeed if the 7 of them
traveled more than 500m in total.)
(Travel more than 500m in total
within 20 seconds.)
The total distance?
You must all scatter.
You can't end up in the same spot.
We need to travel 500m in total?
The distance... Listen.
If we come back to
the starting point by mistake,
the total distance
could be shortened.
- So we need to go as far as we can.
- Let's do this, then.
Those on this side, run to the left.
Those on this side,
run to the right.
It's 500m starting from here, right?
That's right. Since we need to
run too, let us get ready.
Those who can run fast
should run the furthest.
It needs to be
more than 500m, right?
- Yes.
- It needs to be more than 500m.
Let's say it takes 15 seconds
to run 100m.
- Maybe 16 seconds?
- How many seconds will we get?
You'll get 20 seconds.
It's been a while
since we ran on the show.
But it's...
It's difficult for me to run.
All right. Get ready!
- Let's go!
- Get ready.
- We're all running together?
- Yes.
Ready, go.
You're all running together.
- Hurry.
- Ready, go.
(They're given 20 seconds.)
- Hurry up!
- We can't be in the same spot.
- Hurry!
- Run, So Min!
- This is impossible.
- This won't do.
- This won't work.
- Hurry up, Seok Jin!
- You need to run more!
- This won't do!
(They run as fast as they can
in different directions.)
Darn it!
You need to run more!
I need to go as far as I can.
I should go that far.
(Jae Seok runs
to the farthest building.)
(Jong Kook)
I should go that far.
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo
head in the same direction.)
Hurry up, Seok Jin!
(So Min went elsewhere
all by herself.)
What do I do?
Should I climb up here?
(Jumping)
(Se Chan went to the back
of the building from the start.)
You shouldn't come this way.
(Haha went to a secluded place,
following Se Chan.)
(Grunting)
Gosh, these hit my face so much.
(Gosh, these hit my face so much.)
- Stop!
- Gosh.
(Time's up.)
(The members who ran as fast as
they could come to a halt.)
- Stop!
- I couldn't go that far.
- Do we have to stop?
- Please stop where you are.
Darn it!
(Will the total distance
be over 500m?)
Why didn't So Min run
in the beginning?
How come you only went that far?
- Let's do it one more time.
- They didn't run so fast.
- This spot...
- Right, I had to turn the corner.
How come you only went that far?
This won't do.
Why did you run so slowly?
You should try running
with this hat!
Then you should've gone last.
They hit my face so much!
I think I ran over 100m for sure.
(They all ran pretty far.)
- Gosh, these beads...
- You'll put on a blindfold now.
Why?
(The staff members are putting
blindfolds on them.)
- Will you put this on?
- The blindfold?
(The staff members are putting
blindfolds on them.)
- You want me to put this on?
- Yes, hang it on your ears.
- Why?
- Please put it on.
I'll take your glasses.
(They put on the blindfold for now.)
Why are we putting a blindfold on
all of a sudden?
Why are we putting it on?
All right.
We'll tell you the actual rule.
What is it?
(We'll tell you the actual rule.)
(There's an actual rule
set aside for this mission?)
Really?
With your blindfold on,
you'll find the other members
within two minutes.
If all seven of you hold
each other's hands,
- you'll succeed in this mission.
- Darn it.
You'll find the other members
within two minutes.
If all seven of you hold
each other's hands,
- you'll succeed in this mission.
- With a blindfold on?
(They must find the other members
and hold their hands in 2 minutes.)
Gosh.
Guys!
- Se Chan, you should come here.
- Get ready.
Set, go.
- Se Chan!
- Ji Hyo!
You know how it goes, right?
- You should come.
- Come this way!
Get ready.
(The 2 minutes start.)
- You know how it goes, right?
- I'll go to you, Seok Jin.
- Come this way!
- Ji Hyo!
- Hold on. I'm on my way.
- Hey.
- Okay.
- Come this way!
- I'm coming.
- Let's gather at the center.
- You need to go up here.
- I'm coming.
- Ji Hyo.
- Come this way.
- Ji Hyo!
Seok Jin, don't leave.
Hey!
- Jae Seok!
- You know how it goes, right?
You know it, right?
- Hey.
- Jae Seok.
- Yes.
- You saw me. I'm right here.
Hold on. I need to go up there.
- I'm coming.
- Come this way.
(Walking carefully)
- Hold on.
- Where are you?
- I'm right here, Ji Hyo.
- Right here.
- I'm right here.
- Ji Hyo, I'm here.
- Seok Jin!
- I grabbed your hand.
- I grabbed Ji Hyo's hand.
- Ji Hyo!
- Where are you?
- I'm right here. My left hand.
(Ji Hyo and Seok Jin managed to hold
each other's hands in 25 seconds.)
- I got Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin!
- Come over here.
- So Min!
- Seok Jin!
- Jae Seok!
- So Min, over here!
(So Min, over here!)
- So Min!
- Seok Jin, I'm right here.
- Come over here.
- I'm right here.
- Come here.
- Jae Seok.
- So Min!
- We're right here.
- I'm here.
- We're here.
- Jae Seok, we're here.
- We're gathered here.
I got So Min!
- I'm here.
- Jae Seok.
- We're here.
- Jae Seok!
- Ji Hyo, we're here.
- We're close.
- Let's succeed in this mission.
- It's here.
- We're close.
We're close. Reach out your hand.
Don't you mess this up,
corrupt official!
Reach out your hand!
- It's here.
- Over here, Jong Kook!
- I got you.
- We got you.
Over here, Jong Kook!
- We're here.
- The four of us are gathered.
Jong Kook!
- Jong Kook!
- Hey, corrupt official!
- Be careful.
- Don't ruin this.
Jong Kook!
Over here, Jong Kook!
I'm right here.
(I'm right here.)
- I'm over here.
- Jong Kook.
- I'm with Seok Jin. Come here.
- I'm with Ji Hyo here.
I'm over here. This is...
Shouldn't you guys guide us?
(Shouldn't you guys guide us?)
- Jong Kook!
- Corrupt official!
I can hear you.
Let's make this work!
- Over here, Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook!
Jong Kook!
(Calling for them)
- I'm here.
- Jong Kook.
You should tell me
if there's something in front of me.
- Jong Kook!
- Yang Ssaebssaeb!
- Over here, Jong Kook!
I can easily make it.
- Come over here.
- Jong Kook!
- I can easily make it.
- Come over here!
Forget about Jong Kook.
Hurry up! Come this way!
- Is this So Min?
- Yes, it is.
- Hurry up!
- Yang Ssaebssaeb!
Se Chan, you should come here.
(Haha and Se Chan
ran to the opposite corner earlier.)
- Se Chan!
- Coming!
- Haha!
- Yes, come over here.
You should come first.
(They come in contact first.)
I'm scared.
We need to join hands first.
(We need to join hands first.)
- Se Chan.
- Haha!
Come over here.
Tell me if it's not safe.
(Haha is suddenly going
in the opposite direction.)
- Haha!
- Come over here!
Haha! Talk to me!
(Silence)
Haha!
Why is he running away?
(Why is he running away?)
Haha! Talk to me!
(Haha is going the opposite
direction without talking.)
You have 30 seconds left!
- We have only 30 seconds!
- Guys!
- Haha!
I want to succeed in this mission!
We've been doing this for 12 years!
- What's gotten into you?
- What?
- That was so random.
What does that
have anything to do...
- with this?
- What's wrong with him?
Let's make a touching moment!
Why would we do that
with this mission?
Let's make this work, you brats!
Hey, Haha!
Corrupt official,
don't you make your move.
- Haha!
- We need to make this work!
Hey!
- Haha.
- Over here.
- Oh, gosh.
- Gosh.
I got you.
Jae Seok!
(They're getting closer
to each other.)
- Haha!
- We're here.
- Se Chan!
- Where are you?
Ten!
- Nine!
- Se Chan!
- Eight!
- Over here!
- Seven!
- Let's make this work!
- Six!
- Try clapping your hands.
- Five!
- Let's make a touching moment!
- Try clapping!
- Hey!
- Hurry up!
- Try clapping.
- Hey!
- Two.
- Are they coming?
- Hey.
- One.
- Over here. Hey!
- Two,
- Are you there?
- one.
- Here.
Time's up.
- For goodness' sake.
- Where are they?
(Time's up.)
- Gosh.
That corrupt official.
- Hey.
- One of them is a corrupt official.
- All of us gathered around.
- I was at the back.
You failed the mission.
I wanted to succeed.
- We were so close.
- Seok Jin, what was that earlier?
"Let's make our chests go hot."
Don't bet 12 years
on something like this.
- Twelve years of Running Man.
- Don't do that.
I really wanted to succeed.
It was hard to meet him.
I was at the back.
- As for us...
- Don't do that.
- I really wanted to succeed.
- All right.
- It's Haha.
- It's one of them.
- I have something to say.
- It's Haha.
I called for him,
but he neither answered nor came.
- It's Haha.
- Haha.
- Let's go with Haha.
- It's Haha.
I swear to the higher power.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- No.
- It's him.
- Hurry up.
It has to be him.
- He is strange.
- Let's take him to the bell.
- It's one of them.
- It's Haha.
- It's Se Chan.
- Let's talk as we move.
- We called for you.
- Why didn't you answer?
- Seriously.
- I didn't hear their voices.
- I was looking for Haha.
- You know,
- It's him.
- Haha didn't answer.
- It's Haha.
The corrupt official
shouldn't have done anything.
- It's Haha.
- Twelve years of Running Man...
- was on the line.
- Stop it, Seok Jin.
- It isn't that serious.
- A chance to make our chests hot...
- Why is he being so serious?
- It's so strange.
- Twelve years of Running Man?
- We were so close.
Running Man has been around...
for 12 years,
but you went astray
for 3 to 4 years.
- Think about the game.
- Why would you do that?
- All of us were blindfolded.
- Seriously.
- It isn't that serious.
- "Ji Hyo!"
We grabbed her.
"So Min!" We grabbed her.
"Jae Seok came."
"Jong Kook is right there!
Grab him! Let's succeed!"
- It made my chest swell.
- Why did your chest swell?
Why did your chest swell?
We were so close.
Are you going to pick me?
It's either you or Se Chan.
It isn't me.
You think it's either me or Se Chan.
- Yes.
- It isn't me.
- Then it's Se Chan.
- Why?
- It isn't me.
- Why didn't you make any sounds?
Seriously. You kept quiet.
- I was at the back. I was here.
- It's Se Chan.
- Whenever we do this...
- Hey.
(Hold on.)
Hey.
- It's Se Chan.
- Why were you there?
We definitely told you
not to stay...
- near this place.
- Ji Hyo, you look angry.
Why are you so serious?
- Listen.
- Hey.
We couldn't be at the same spot.
We couldn't be at the same spot,
but Jong Kook definitely said...
that staying near this place
will shorten the distance.
- That's right.
- So I went to the back.
If you stayed here, it's you.
It's Se Chan.
It's you.
- Trust me.
- Jong Kook's first hunch is right.
- How did the two of you meet?
- It's Se Chan.
Let's go with Se Chan.
- It isn't me.
- For goodness' sake.
- You know...
You can arrest him
after the mission.
Would you like to go right away?
- Is there a mission?
- Let's find out.
We prepared the next mission.
- Go ahead.
- You can do what you want.
- Give us the mission.
I will show that
I am not a corrupt official.
- Let's have a mission.
- Okay.
The next mission is...
Your Scent in an Unfamiliar Word.
- What is it?
- Your Scent in an Unfamiliar Word.
When we give you a person...
and an object,
write down what they have in common.
(Write down
what they have in common.)
You will receive points
if your answers match.
Let's begin.
So Min and cup noodles.
- So Min and cup noodles.
- They get incensed.
- Incensed.
- Hot.
- I was going to write that.
- My answer is similar.
They are hot-tempered.
Jae Seok.
After a breakup, she cried
while eating cup noodles.
Why are you spouting nonsense?
- No.
- Yukgaejang.
Why Yukgaejang?
That's the only brand So Min eats.
She just gave the brand name.
- What's up with her?
- Come on.
You can't give the brand name.
None of the answers matched.
Hot-tempered.
- Jong Kook...
- Jong Kook.
and doenjang.
- Doenjang?
- Jong Kook and doenjang.
- This is too easy.
- A penchant for aging things.
- Homely.
- Poop.
Poop.
Why is Jong Kook poop?
- That came to my mind.
- Why did you write "Poop"?
- None of the answers matched.
- Why is Jong Kook poop?
You should have answered seriously.
Jae Seok and a vacuum cleaner.
A vacuum cleaner?
Ugly.
(Ugly)
- Loud.
- I also wrote "Loud".
- There you go.
Two answers matched.
I wrote "Fitting pants".
- Fitting pants?
- That's ridiculous.
- Ji Hyo.
- I couldn't think of anything.
- She is strange today.
- Jae Seok, what's your answer?
- Neat.
Come on.
- Come on.
- For goodness' sake.
- What's wrong with him?
- Neat.
- That's absurd.
- You are loud.
Don't glamorize yourself.
- Se Chan and hotteok.
- What?
- Hotteok?
- Okay.
- Pressed.
- Come on.
(Pressed)
- Ugly.
- My answer is "Ugly" too.
- Three points.
You succeeded to win three points.
(They finish the mission
after acquiring 15 points in total!)
- Let's go with Jae Seok.
- Here comes a hint.
Let me tell you
what the hint will be.
It will be something
the corrupt official did...
- after picking a character.
- Okay.
(Something the corrupt official did
will be provided as a hint.)
It would be incredible
if it's crossing the arms.
The corrupt official touched...
- the Dragon King's hat.
- The Dragon King's hat?
(It's one of the people
who touched the hat!)
- I didn't touch it.
- My hat?
You mean the hat.
- Se Chan touched it.
- No, I didn't touch it.
- I didn't touch it.
- All of us touched it.
Jae Seok touched it.
- Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo touched it.
- I touched it.
- Ji Hyo.
- So Min touched it.
- All of us touched it.
- Did you touch it?
- No.
Okay. I didn't touch it either.
So it's someone
who touched this hat.
Ji Hyo stood behind me and said...
- "Two servings of jjajangmyeon."
- Jae Seok touched it.
- I touched it. I moved the beads.
- She touched it.
- So Min touched it.
- You didn't touch it.
- I think it's Jae Seok.
- It really isn't me.
It's suspicious that his answer
for hotteok was "Pressed".
He kept insisting on
picking the answer...
- that entered his mind first.
- Didn't he touch it?
I didn't touch it. Think about it.
- I didn't touch it.
- I didn't touch it either.
(The two suspects insist
that they didn't touch the hat.)
- It's Ji Hyo.
- No.
- It isn't me.
- It's Ji Hyo.
- If you pick me...
- It really isn't me.
- If you pick me, it means...
- It isn't me.
- you are being played by a spy.
- Jae Seok touched it the most.
- That's right.
- I touched it too.
- It isn't me.
- Jae Seok.
- Ji Hyo touched it from behind.
- Yes. I admit...
- that I touched it.
- I touched it from the front.
- But it isn't me.
- It's Ji Hyo or So Min.
- No, it really isn't me.
- To be honest...
- It really isn't me.
- Really?
- Jae Seok is telling the truth.
- It really isn't me.
You think it's So Min or Ji Hyo.
- It's So Min or Ji Hyo.
- I touched it.
- So Min touched it first.
- It's So Min or Ji Hyo.
- It's So Min.
- It isn't me.
- The chance...
- It really isn't me.
- It's you.
- It isn't me.
- Haha, didn't you touch it?
- I didn't touch it.
- Maybe it's Seok Jin.
- He didn't touch it.
- It might be Seok Jin.
- Right.
- Maybe it's Seok Jin.
- You touched it too.
- I touched it continuously.
- That's right. You touched it too.
The corrupt official has
100 dollars now.
- We need to make an arrest.
- Let's go with Seok Jin.
(Let's go with Seok Jin!)
- Me?
- Hey.
Do you want to fall
to the fiery pit?
- That came out of nowhere.
- It's Seok Jin.
- He suddenly talked about the pit.
- Seok Jin.
He suddenly talked about the pit.
It's Seok Jin. I am certain of it.
- It's him.
- Ring the Bell of Truth.
- It's Seok Jin. Seriously.
The prize money is 100 dollars now.
Hurry up. It's Seok Jin.
I am serious. It isn't me.
- It isn't me.
- I will give you my money.
- It really isn't me.
- It's Seok Jin. Go with Seok Jin.
- It's Seok Jin.
- You could misunderstand, but...
You did make strange comments
during the game.
- Like what?
- You did that.
I thought it was strange...
- that he brought up 12 years.
- It was strange.
(Seok Jin suddenly shouted out
a comment about 12 years.)
- He says such things...
- Would he have done it again?
- to cover something up.
- That's not true.
- But he got caught because of that.
- It came out due to nerves.
That's right.
- It's a habit.
- "I am working hard."
- You know what he does.
- Guys.
- Didn't you feel that passion?
- Listen.
- You had no reason to say that.
- Didn't you feel that passion?
- No.
While wearing blindfolds,
we held hands.
- Let's go.
- Ji Hyo! We shouted for each other.
- One, two, three. Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin gets picked.)
(Seok Jin will take
the Judgment Stand.)
- Ring the Bell of Truth.
Please sit down.
You will fall to the fiery pit.
I told you that I am not it.
All right. The fourth fairy tale was
"The Story of Terrapin".
- I hope we got it right.
- Who is the corrupt official?
The corrupt official
of "The Story of Terrapin..."
is...
(The corrupt official
of "The Story of Terrapin" is...)
It's him.
- Not Seok Jin.
- It isn't him.
I told you so.
(They failed to apprehend
the corrupt official.)
- I think it's Jae Seok.
- It's Jae Seok.
- It isn't me.
- It isn't me either.
- All right.
- He is serious.
Who will receive 100 dollars
and avoid the penalty?
Congratulations.
The corrupt official is...
- So Min.
- I knew it.
It was So Min.
(The corrupt official, So Min)
- So Min.
- I knew it.
It was So Min.
(Was it So Min?)
She kept quiet.
I told you
that she was overly quiet.
- So Min.
- I told you that it was So Min.
(So Min was the first person
to touch the Dragon King's hat.)
(During the outdoor team mission,)
(she hesitated
even though she heard the voices.)
(She went in the opposite direction
on purpose.)
(So Min killed time
by pretending to be lost.)
(When Seok Jin emerged
as a suspect,)
(she began to corner him.)
- It was So Min.
- She stayed in the back.
I should have known
that it was So Min.
You should have denied it strongly.
What more could I have done?
I even said that
you will fall to the fiery pit.
You should have denied it strongly.
- I did.
- You should have denied it...
- strongly.
- This is so hard.
- I don't know anymore.
Let's pick the penalty ball.
(1 out of 24 penalty balls
will be chosen.)
We could have done better.
I will pick a ball.
All right.
- Come on, So Min.
- It's okay.
Let's go. Drum roll.
(Who will receive the penalty?)
Oh, no.
(Who is it?)
- I didn't do it on purpose.
- Who is it?
Jee.
(Seok Jin got chosen.)
- I really didn't.
- Fall to the fiery pit.
Jee.
Fall to the fiery pit.
It's the penalty that suits
the Dragon King, water slap.
That's good. Water slap is good.
- Okay.
- That was weak.
(Throwing)
That was weak.
It must be cool.
All right.
This is hard.
You had 2 successes and 2 failures.
This is your last chance.
(It's time for the last fairy tale.)
The last fairy tale is
"Altair and Vega".
Chapter Five
of the Running Chronicles.
"Altair and Vega".
The characters are
Altair, Vega, and magpie.
It can't be this one.
I hope I don't get chosen.
Vega!
Altair!
Fall to the fiery pit.
- Fall to the fiery pit.
What's up with him?
Why does Vega look like that?
I am so annoyed.
- I don't want to meet this Vega.
- Vega.
This Vega is too ugly.
Why does Vega look like that?
- The fake Vega.
- How is Vega so ugly?
I think she got punched in the face.
- Her face is puffy.
- Hey, crows.
I will pull out your feathers
if you don't quiet down.
Seriously.
(This Vega has
rough looks and words.)
- Altair.
- All right.
The fifth corrupt official
is among you.
Who could it be?
Se Chan and Haha haven't gone once.
- That doesn't matter.
- It isn't me.
- Ji Hyo hasn't gone once either.
- That doesn't matter.
Altair, close your mouth.
- Hey.
- Vega.
- My goodness.
- Fall to the fiery pit.
- They don't get along.
Close your mouth.
- Are you Bbaengdeok?
- What?
Are you Bbaengdeok?
- Don't you know who Vega is?
- You can't be Vega.
- The two of you are a couple.
- What?
- Give me a break.
- A couple, my foot.
- What's up with your skirt?
- Excuse me?
- Why? It's sexy.
Who do you think you are?
The two of you are lovers.
- What?
- The two of you are lovers.
The next mission is
Speak with Your Actions.
We are good at that.
Express an idiom with your actions.
- Idiom?
- We got this.
One person will give the question...
- and two people will answer.
- Okay.
Once the correct answer is given,
the person who gave the question
will answer the next one.
One of the two people who answered
will join the waiting area.
- Okay.
- Okay. I got it.
The corrupt official
will show strange actions.
- Okay.
- The corrupt official.
Go.
Are you nervous?
You tied the skirt...
very tightly.
- What?
- Seriously.
Hold on.
It doesn't even look like a skirt.
- You tied it too tightly.
- There goes the detective.
- You guys are lovers.
- That little...
- "That little"?
That little...
- That little...
- Help them get along.
Should we describe one word each?
It's up to you.
I think I will need to describe
one word each.
I mean...
Se Chan is too suspicious.
- Why?
- Right?
- I heard it too.
- Why am I suspicious?
- You heard it, right?
Se Chan is asking
too many questions.
He is too forward.
I might not understand the idiom.
- For example...
- When it's an idiom...
It isn't me.
Seriously.
- He is nervous.
- I was just wondering...
if I should describe one word each.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Get ready. Set, go.
(Heart in your mouth)
(The first syllable
is pronounced as "Jeon".)
Turn a misfortune into a blessing.
- What?
- Sending...
(Her last name)
Heart in your mouth.
(Jee Altair is correct.)
- Good.
- You are suspicious.
- Seriously.
- It's strange. Why didn't you know?
(Detective Kim chose his target.)
- Okay.
- Why didn't you know?
(Ji Hyo has to describe the idiom.)
(Studying at night)
What's that?
- A pot.
What? Studying at night.
Studying at night.
You shouldn't speak.
- Why did you speak?
- You shouldn't speak.
- I had to prove my innocence.
- It doesn't count.
- Then let me go again.
- Let her go again.
- It doesn't count.
- Haha, why did you do that?
For goodness' sake, Haha.
- For goodness' sake.
- Haha.
- Muscle?
- Egg?
- Arm.
Muscle?
- Muscle?
- Arm.
- Why are you answering?
New Year's greeting?
- Rock.
- Paper.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Work without plans.
Rock.
- Hold on. The pronunciation...
- What you befriend will affect you.
- That's right.
- That's right. Good job.
- I am good at this.
You should stay there.
- So Min answered it.
- Good job.
Good job.
- What's that?
- A gourd bottle.
- Curves?
- A mountain.
- Lightning?
A well in the mountain.
- A tree.
- A mountain.
- You can't help them.
A creek.
Jeju Island.
- Jeju Island.
- You can't speak.
- It's "Dainty hands".
- Jeju Island.
- Yes.
Island.
Jeju.
Ju. Je?
Island. A homophone for "Dainty".
- Dainty...
- Dainty corn.
What was "Dainty corn"?
- Dainty...
- Dainty corn.
("Dainty corn"?)
(They can't figure out
"Dainty hands".)
- Dainty...
- Dainty hands.
"Dainty corn"?
(Ms. Dainty Corn got it right.)
- "Dainty corn"?
- You shouldn't make it so easy.
- Go ahead.
- Use actions.
All right.
(Apple of the eye)
It's a baby.
A baby.
Coddling.
- What's the 1st word?
He is acting strange.
- What?
- He is acting strange, right?
- Wealth.
- He is nervous.
- Muscle.
Muscle. Head.
- Hair.
- Head.
- Hot?
- This.
- What's that?
- Gold.
- He is acting strange.
- Return home in glory.
Return home in glory.
- Gold.
- Gold and silver.
Come on, you punks!
Gold.
Four characters.
- Of course it has four characters.
- Yes.
What's the second one?
Hurry up.
Apple.
- Apple?
- Apple.
Apple of the eye.
- That's right.
- Okay.
- Why...
- Hey.
All right.
- I got this.
- Go ahead.
Jae Seok is suspicious.
- All right.
- Ji Hyo.
The first character.
Very difficult.
Why are you speaking?
Don't speak.
You can pass.
Okay.
- What?
- A sword.
- A knife.
- A fight.
- A war.
A fight.
He is suspicious.
Why is he so bad at this?
What's up with him?
Fall to the fiery pit.
A knife.
- No.
- A sword.
What's that?
- Describe the idiom.
- A watermelon?
It's him.
It's him. I am sure of it.
A cabbage?
A radish.
- A radish.
- My goodness.
- My goodness. No way.
This is ridiculous.
- My goodness.
- My goodness. No way.
- Why...
- Paradise.
Correct.
- Why...
- Paradise.
Correct.
- Paradise?
- What?
Why did you describe it
with such difficulty?
I started with a homophone,
"Radish".
- You should have done this.
- Paradise.
- What would you have done?
- Park Joon Hyung's comedy skit.
- Radish.
- That's right.
- Park Joon Hyung.
- You could have done that.
I couldn't think of that.
I showed the shape of a radish.
When you cut it,
it becomes kkakdugi.
- It was hard.
- Why did you do that?
- A swordsman is a homophone too.
- My goodness.
- A swordsman.
- That's...
- He is so suspicious.
- Was that why you did that?
- Yes.
- I didn't want to suspect him.
- That was...
- Radish.
- That was too suspicious.
I didn't want to suspect him,
but he is too suspicious.
It's him. He moved around too much.
He moved back and forth like this.
- Let's go.
- It will be the third time for him.
Are you suspecting me again?
Who is grinning the most?
- It isn't me.
- It isn't me either.
- Jae Seok is suspicious.
- Jae Seok, you are suspicious.
You are a suspect.
- It isn't me.
- Dainty hands.
It isn't me.
- It isn't me.
- Haha blurted out the answer.
It isn't me.
He did it to sabotage the game.
- How about you?
- He threw out a question.
- That's right.
- How about you?
- It isn't me.
- Are you sure?
This is driving me crazy.
Didn't you see me
play the game diligently?
Remember the first question?
I pointed to So Min.
- Okay.
- Seok Jin was suspicious,
but Jong Kook answered
with seriousnesss.
The moment Jong Kook said,
"It isn't me..."
(He understood right away.)
I described it so well.
I answered that question quickly.
You did. Jae Seok is suspicious.
- He didn't get that question.
- Come on.
- You have a point.
- I got it right.
- He didn't get that question.
It's suspicious
that he didn't get it right.
- He didn't get that question.
- That's why he is suspicious.
He is suspicious.
- Let's go with Jae Seok.
- It really isn't me.
You did go through
the set number of questions.
- Really?
- A hint.
- You will receive a hint.
- Give it to us.
A hint.
- You will receive a hint.
- Give it to us.
Throughout...
the mission,
(Throughout the mission...)
the corrupt official
suspected other people the most.
Who is it? Hold on.
(The corrupt official
suspected other people the most.)
(Someone who suspected
other people the most?)
Throughout the mission,
someone made such comments.
- But...
- Haha and Jae Seok.
That's exactly right.
Right? This person made
such comments.
- "He is suspicious."
- Jong Kook did that a lot.
I did that a lot.
- Yes.
- Did you do that during the game?
Yes, I did that during the game.
I think it's Jong Kook or Haha.
- It isn't me.
- I suspected people from the start.
- Sit down.
- Let's go with Jong Kook.
- I admit that I did it.
But it isn't me.
- If I am the corrupt official...
- Hey.
- I figured it out.
- Listen.
- He is trying to get more money.
- No.
(It's already 50 dollars.)
If I were the corrupt official,
- Hey!
- I would've overpowered him.
Let me tell you the truth.
It's you!
(Let me tell you the truth.
It's you!)
- It's you.
- Right.
My gut feelings say it's you.
- One, two, three.
- Hang on.
Just hang on a second.
Seriously, I'm telling you...
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Wait.
- You can't let him get his own way.
- It's not me.
I think it's Haha.
- It must be Haha.
- Haha?
Haha is pretending to suspect me.
I'm sure he's hiding something.
- Come here.
- I swear it's not me.
- I swear it's you.
- Do you swear to the Almighty?
- It's him.
- I mean...
- Is it you?
- I said it wasn't me.
- Because he was...
- It's not him.
- It's not Haha. It's you!
- I tried really hard.
You should listen to me.
Just listen.
- Seok Jin.
- He just wants to be on screen.
Let's just go with Jong Kook.
- It's not me.
- Listen to me.
- I swear.
- Hang on.
- At this moment...
- I tried really hard.
I'll go then.
Okay. You go.
- You'll be embarrassed.
- It's Jong Kook.
It's So Min who pointed me out last.
All right. Ring the bell.
- Look at him.
- Oh, gosh.
- She's really...
- It's not Jong Kook.
- Let's go with Jae Seok.
- It must be Haha.
- It's so confusing.
- Let's...
No, just pick me.
Let's just say it's me.
Hang on. We need
some time to discuss it.
- Then...
- Will you hurry?
- Just say if it's Jong Kook or not.
- Hang on.
- I don't think it's him.
- Is it Jong Kook or not?
(Jae Seok suddenly says
it's not Jong Kook.)
- Is it Haha?
- It's not Jong Kook.
- It must be Jae Seok.
- Because...
he's really trying to kill me.
No, it's not like that.
(The investigation has gone
back to where it started.)
I'm just telling you the truth.
- Hang on.
- I don't mind being here.
- Why are you ruling me out?
- Hang on.
- What?
Wait. I just saw...
- I said it's Haha.
- Hang on.
- It's Haha.
- Hey.
- I just saw something.
- No.
- Hang on.
- I caught the spy.
- No, it's not Seok Jin. Wait.
- Here.
- I saw the eyes.
- What eyes?
What eyes?
- Who?
- Did you get goosebumps?
- Who is it?
- When I was about to stop you...
(When he was about to say
it wasn't Jong Kook...)
- Did someone smile?
- I saw Yang Se Chan.
- What did I do?
- Why?
(Yang Se Chan caught
Jae Seok's eyes.)
- Your eyes...
- What? Are you saying it's me?
What did he do?
It looked as if...
"It's almost over, but why..."
- He looked like this.
- Me?
- Your face was...
- Seriously, it's not me.
- Do you think it's me?
- The expression on your face...
- No, it's not me.
- You are blushing now.
Jae Seok, it's just that he's ugly.
This might put you in trouble.
It's not me.
- Yang Se Chan.
- It's just that he's ugly.
Seriously, it's not me.
- Se Chan, it's you.
- Why at the last moment?
Hang on a second.
- It might be him.
- No.
It's him, right? It might be him.
- I don't think it's Jae Seok.
- He keeps...
I don't think it's Jae Seok.
- I saw it. I saw Se Chan.
- It's not Jae Seok.
Just put me on the mat.
Seriously, it's not me.
- Hang on.
- I saw Se Chan's face.
He's standing by
with his arms folded.
No, it's Se Chan.
- With his folded arms...
- Yang Se Chan.
(They all keep insisting
without listening to each other.)
- Hey.
- Yang Se Chan.
Is this what we do after
spending 12 years together?
I'm not me.
- It's you.
- No, it's not.
- I saw you.
- What is all this?
- What's this mess?
- What are we doing?
- Aren't you ashamed?
- What's going on?
We just suspect each other.
- I'm not doing this.
- We don't trust each other.
- We just suspect each other.
- It's Yang Se Chan.
Is this all we have
after spending 12 years together?
It's Yang Se Chan.
You punks.
- Put me up then.
- It's Se Chan.
- Do you want to deceive us?
- Yang Se Chan.
- You go.
- Okay. I'll go.
- It's Se Chan.
- No, it's not you.
- It's Jae Seok.
- He's just ugly.
If it's not me, it's Jae Seok.
It must be Jae Seok.
He's just ugly.
- I saw it.
- He just has an ugly face.
- Jae Seok says he saw it. Go.
- It's Yang Se Chan.
- Se Chan was like...
- Just go.
Se Chan was standing here.
And when I saw his face,
he suddenly blushed.
But it's not me. That's not enough.
- I was suspicious of Haha.
- It's not him.
If it's him, it goes left.
If it's not him, it goes right.
Is it Se Chan or not? It's you.
- Let's go with him.
- Let's go.
Seok Jin, you leaned it a little.
- No.
- He leaned it.
- You threw it like this.
- Is it Se Chan or not?
See? It's him.
Is it Jong Kook or not?
It's not him. This works.
- I'm here.
- Is it Jae Seok...
- or not?
- You're moving it with your hand.
It might be Jae Seok.
Is it Seok Jin or not?
- Your hand was like...
- It could be me.
This is strange.
- Darn it.
- Let's just go with me.
Let's give it a try.
It's really hot in here.
(Actually, I'm not sure about this.)
- Actually, I'm not sure about this.
- Hang on.
Why are you doing this
when you're not sure?
- When you're not so sure...
- What?
(Now they use witchcraft
and superhuman strength.)
- When you're not so sure...
- What? It's not you.
- It's not you.
- Why not?
If you were the corrupt official,
you would've...
I would've rang the bell right away.
- We don't have time. Let's just go.
- I would've rung it right away.
- And you...
- Right. We're not spies.
- These two aren't spies.
- Jae Seok, you're not a spy.
- They aren't spies.
- And I'm not a spy.
- Gosh.
- We're not spies.
Right. Why are you sitting there?
- He's strange.
- Stand up, you punk.
You...
- Come here.
- He's weird.
It reveals itself...
- You can tell, right?
- over time.
- We know it's not us.
- Right.
- I'll go. Move over.
- You suspected him, right?
- Because...
- Move over.
(Haha suddenly wants to go
on the straw mat.)
- Seriously, it's not me.
- Move over.
(Watching them carefully)
- Me?
- Seriously, it's not me.
- It's you.
- No, I'm not the spy.
- I told you.
- It's Yang Se Chan.
- He is...
- I just saw it.
- I'll just sit.
- He's really...
- Did you see that?
- He seemed excited.
- I saw it. He smiled.
- When he got up from here...
- He got up right away.
- You sit.
(Se Chan smiled
when Haha was going to sit?)
- Se Chan was...
- Let's just do it. It's me.
- All right. Sit.
- What if it's not me?
- How could you...
- I clearly saw it this time.
Is it Se Chan or not?
- It's him.
- I...
If you're not the corrupt official,
- you're just ugly.
- Hey.
Let's just go with him.
- Okay.
- All right. Let's go.
- It's him.
- It's Se Chan, right?
- Okay. Let's do it.
- All right.
(Is Se Chan the corrupt official?)
Ring the Bell...
- Of Truth.
(Ring the Bell of Truth.)
All right. Chapter Five,
"Altair and Vega".
The corrupt official is...
(Who is the corrupt official
of "Altair and Vega"?)
Is it Yang Se Chan?
- Is it?
- It is.
(Yang Se Chan is...)
It's not me.
- It's Yang Se Chan.
- You...
(They successfully arrested
the corrupt official.)
- My gosh.
- That was amazing.
- Gosh, Jae Seok...
- I knew it.
(Jae Seok caught Se Chan
from the look on his face.)
- I knew it.
- My gosh.
(Impressed)
- You did a great job.
- That was impressive.
- I said it wasn't me.
- Sure.
Well played.
It was so close.
I saw your face at that very moment.
He kept staring at me like this.
(When Haha was being cornered
instead of him...)
(Jae Seok caught the movement
of Se Chan's lips.)
(The corrupt official couldn't
hide his joy for the moment.)
That was impressive.
- I saw it.
- Is that right?
- This is amazing.
- All right then.
- I saw it.
- Now Se Chan gets...
20 penalty balls.
And you guys have
one penalty ball each.
- It serves you right.
- Se Chan was flustered.
Good job.
- Well done.
- Okay.
Put in the penalty balls.
- It was so close.
- Well played.
I will show you
what the penalty is then.
- What is it?
- I wonder what it is.
This feels really nice.
Is it gourd-breaking?
- It's gourd-breaking.
- Is that it?
I don't think this will break.
- My gosh.
- This is easy.
I don't think this will break.
I hope I won't pick my own name.
You all have 1 ball each,
and Se Chan has 20 balls.
- Really?
- Yes.
Then it will be Se Chan for sure.
I know, right?
Please.
(It is highly likely that
Se Chan will get the penalty.)
(But there can be a surprise.)
- What if he picks the one ball?
- I picked one.
- Please. Lucky.
- What if he picks the one ball?
(Whose side will Lady Luck be on?)
Let's go.
- If I get picked here, I'm cursed.
- Exactly.
You are only three times
more likely to get picked.
- Okay.
- No way.
(Who will do the gourd-breaking?)
- Yang.
- Yes!
I knew it.
(Yang Se Chan gets the penalty.)
It has to be Yang.
- Be careful.
- It hurts.
- That's no big deal.
(A snapping sound)
(The gourd makes a snapping sound
through his skull.)
(It hurts even more
when the gourd doesn't break.)
(Shuddering)
- I should break it at once.
- That looks hard.
- You should break it at once.
- Oh, no.
- Die!
- It doesn't hurt anymore.
- Now I'm scared.
- You have to do it right away.
(He kisses the gourd goodbye.)
I have to break it at once.
(He successfully breaks
the last gourd.)
- Well done.
- Ta-da.
So this is the end of Chapter Five
of Running Chronicles.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- Thank you all for your hard work.
The last mind game
was really thrilling.
- It really was.
- This is so neat.
(The Running Chronicles
has come to a happy ending.)
(July 2022, Sangam-dong)
Excuse me.
(The members are making
shady deals.)
(Why are they wandering
around Sangam-dong?)
(Hide your name!)
(They can go anywhere they want.)
(It's an unlimited
name tag hide-and-seek.)
(They have to betray others
to keep their name tags safe.)
(Your name can become your weapon.)
Someone's in there.
Did you see So Min?
(But sometimes it can
become your weakness.)
(Passerby, producer, cafe staff)
(Or anyone...)
(Anyone can become your accomplice.)
(The Running Tag of Tails)