(The second mission is
Yang Se Chan Game.)
That game.
Donald Trump.
(Thanks to the paper doll,
Team Average gets 3 points.)
(Quick-witted Irene gets
her team 3 points.)
(McDonald's Grandpa?)
(Team Tall played well...)
(against Yang Se Chan
who's bad at Yang Se Chan Game.)
(How much does
this person make a year?)
(I guess over 100,000 dollars.)
(What does he wear?)
(Suk Jin, V)
(It's a man.)
(And he makes 10,000 dollars
a month wearing jeogori?)
(With all the indigestible clues,)
(Ji Hyo finds out
the answer is Pengsoo.)
(Ji Hyo becomes a genius
by answering Pengsoo.)
(Team Tall wins
the second mission again.)
(The members of Team Tall
get 3 coins each.)
(The members of Team Short
get 2 coins each.)
You should definitely buy
a block with your coins this time.
That's what I've done.
Sure. He's very tall.
You will take turns
to enter the voting booth...
and purchase either
a block or a shoe lift.
- Okay.
- My gosh.
It's a given.
He's right.
I'll go first.
All right. Go. I'll go too.
There's no need to hesitate.
(He said he didn't
even have to think about it.)
(Yoo Jae Suk of Team Tall, 2 blocks)
(1 shoe lift)
Well...
(Jong Kook who was bluffing
buys one more shoe lift.)
(Kim Jong Kook of Team Tall,
2 blocks, 1 shoe lift)
I'll be right back.
Remember that our team should win.
(Mr. Ji expects the paper doll
to be loyal to his team.)
(With his one precious coin,)
(he buys a shoe lift.)
I think we're going to lose.
I'm sure we'll be the last.
What's there to think about?
- There's no need to hesitate.
- I don't even have to choose.
There will be another chance for us.
- What is this?
- What's that?
- What's all this?
- There are cannons.
What is this for?
- Gosh, what is this?
- In the middle of the race?
- Is this for cream?
- It must be cream.
We don't usually do this
in the middle of a race.
- Isn't this for cream?
- Right.
- What did you say?
- I'm scared.
What does it spurt?
All right. This mission is...
a game where the team's life
depends on a member's hand.
It's called Thrilling Random Game,
Frightening Quiz.
Frightening Quiz?
Why would we have a quiz
contest with members like them?
- Haha, Hae Na is smart.
- We don't know that.
You still have hope.
Two teams will make
one team in each round.
- Two teams?
- The rest...
will sit in front of the canons.
(The rest will sit
in front of the cannons.)
So it will be a team
of 7 or 8 members.
You will take turns to say
one syllable of the answer.
(Each member will take turns
to give one syllable of the answer.)
That sounds difficult.
But for those who don't
know the answer,
we will give you
two chances to pass.
The next member will
continue giving the answer.
If you give the correct answer,
both teams will get one point each.
And this is what the other team does
when you give the correct answer.
One member presses buttons, and
the others sit in front of cannons.
They will pick a card
from number 1 to 6.
Let's say they pick a card
with number 1, 2, and 3.
The member standing here
will press a button.
The member with the chosen number
will get floured.
(They press a button every time
the opponents get a correct answer.)
So it's random.
I guess we all will get floured.
The team that gets floured
loses one point.
- Okay.
- These two teams go first.
- These two?
- Let's do that.
Then you should...
choose a member
to press the buttons.
I'll do it.
- I'll do it.
- Let me do it.
Haha is quite experienced.
You young punks, sit down.
You should be nice to the guests.
- I said I'd do it.
- Right.
- Haha is seasoned.
- He's an old fossil.
- He is an old fossil.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's do that.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Win)
(Embarrassed)
Hae Na survived.
- Is it all right?
- Hae Na.
- Are you going to be okay?
- Sure.
All right. You will start
giving your answers from here.
- So are we a team?
- We're a team now.
- Us?
- Mix them up.
This team is perfect.
Right. You should mix us.
I want to see how good they are.
It's not perfect.
She's from abroad, and she graduated
from Ewha Womans University.
And his wife went
to Yonsei University.
- Hey.
- His wife?
My wife has nothing
to do with this game.
- I'm curious about her.
- Then Suk Jin and...
- What was your name?
- Se Chan.
- "What was your name?"
- Switch places.
- Okay.
All right. You two should
pick cards now.
And show your numbers
only to your opponents.
The number you pick is yours.
- We're not supposed to see it.
- Right.
Show your cards.
All right. That's Ji Hyo's number.
- Okay.
They will never give
a correct answer.
How would they get it right?
We will give five quizzes.
- All right.
- Okay.
The category of the first question
is common knowledge.
Listen to the question
and give one syllable of the answer.
- Okay.
- Sure.
- Common knowledge?
- It's like common sense.
- Common sense? I see.
- Let's go.
It's to congratulate
a woman who's about to marry.
It's a party that a bride has
with her friends. What is it?
(It's a party that a bride has
with her friends. What is it?)
(The answer is a bridal shower.)
(It's a party that a bride has
with her friends. What is it?)
- Three, two, one.
- Pass.
Bae.
- What?
(Bae?)
Bae.
- Bae?
- No.
- It's a baby shower.
- No, it's a brother shower.
- That's not it.
(It's a baby shower.
No, it's a brother shower.)
(It's wrong again.)
No. That's not it.
What is that?
- No.
- Is it a party?
- What's that?
- It's a brother shower.
- A brother shower.
- A brother shower?
- Bridal.
- Brother.
What is a brother shower?
You mean a bride.
- A bridal shower?
- Anyways.
- It's not brother.
- It starts with the same letter.
- It's bridal. Hey.
- Bridal.
- So Min, you should go home.
- Come on, So Min.
- You should know that.
This is nice.
So Min, I love this game.
- This is really nice.
- You should know this.
- We should get this right.
- Do you want to switch seats?
All right. This time, you are
supposed to spell a word I say.
- Yes. Okay. It's good.
- Spell a word?
Spell the word I say in turn.
- Okay.
- The spellings.
- I'm nervous.
- All right.
- You can do this.
- Give the word.
Rainbow.
R.
(Spell rainbow.)
(R)
- Pass. I'm nervous.
- A.
- I'm so nervous.
- Pass.
- I.
N.
- B.
- O.
- W.
- Okay!
No.
(Haha makes a protest.)
It should go back to him.
- Of course, I know it's a W.
- It's Suk Jin's turn again.
- Do you not know it's a W?
- Should it go this way?
- Hang on.
- It was an A.
(Hang on.)
Let's talk about the pass.
Why would you pass?
- Don't do this to your friend.
- Rainbow?
We know how to spell rainbow.
- Is he serious?
- I know rainbow.
Don't make a joke now.
- It spells...
- We lost two times.
- Hey.
- They didn't know.
- We lost two times.
- It's not like that.
- We knew it.
I know rainbow. Just sit.
I just made use of the pass.
Woo Jae, you don't seem to know
much about your friends.
- You don't know.
- We knew it.
- It's not like that.
- We lost two games.
I was nervous,
so I didn't want to make a mistake.
- All right. Well done.
- I was afraid I might be wrong.
Since they got the second question right,
Hae Na will press a button.
Pick a number and press the button.
Okay. I'll pick...
(Will Hae Na be able
to avoid the penalty numbers?)
(Shutting their eyes tight)
- It's okay. It doesn't hurt.
- My goodness.
It will be all right.
- I'll press a button.
- Go ahead.
Press a button.
(She picks number 5.)
(They survived from the flour.)
(Fortunately, Hae Na managed
to avoid the penalty numbers.)
- They survived.
- Let's move on.
- Okay.
- Good.
I believe in Hae Na.
The next question is
about common knowledge.
(The next question is
about common knowledge.)
This is an industrial complex
in the northern part of the US...
where computer and software
products are developed. What is it?
(An industrial complex where computer
and software products are developed)
- It's impossible not to know this.
- What is it?
Three, two, one.
- You should know this.
- Mi...
- What?
(Mi...)
- It's Silicon Valley.
- Silicon Valley.
- I knew it.
- You should've passed.
What were you talking about?
- I thought it was Microsoft.
- Microsoft.
- That's what I thought.
- Silicon Valley.
I understand. You said software,
so I thought it was Microsoft.
You can just pass.
- Techno?
- You're unbelievable.
- Song Ji Hyo...
- What?
She said Techno Valley.
(Song Ji Hyo said Techno Valley.)
(When the answer,
"Silicon Valley" was announced...)
- Did you not know that?
- I didn't know.
I thought it was Techno Valley.
(I thought it was Techno Valley.)
(Ji Hyo loves Korea's IT industry.)
- She's a patriot.
- I'm glad it's not Techno Mart.
Techno?
Is this what you meant?
I'm glad she didn't say Techno Mart.
That's funny.
You meant Techno Valley in Korea.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
- I like the questions.
- I don't know.
- I'll just go for it.
- We can do this.
- I'm not afraid.
- I like the questions.
The next question is
about common knowledge.
In 1894...
It's 1894.
What's the antitradition
and antiforeign movement...
started by Jeon Bong Jun,
a follower of Donghak?
You know it, right?
What's the antitradition
and antiforeign movement...
started by Jeon Bong Jun,
a follower of Donghak?
- You know it, right?
- Pass.
Pass. In case I give a wrong answer.
- Three, two, one.
- Dong.
Hak.
(Donghak)
- What?
- That's not it.
- Isn't it Farmers' Rebellion?
- That's...
- Is it Farmers' Rebellion?
- Donghak Peasant Movement.
- Is it Donghak?
- It's right.
- So it was Donghak.
- Why did you not say anything?
- How can you not know Donghak?
- Seriously.
It's Donghak Peasant...
We said "Donghak."
- It's Donghak Peasant Movement.
- Why did you not say anything?
- Why didn't you say the answer.
- You should know this.
I was really...
I thought I was wrong.
- It's not like that.
- I just said "Hak."
- I didn't hear what he said.
- He said "Dong."
- So...
- I only heard you.
- I said "Hak.
- I said "Dong." Loud and clear.
So Round One is over.
(Round 1 ends
with the wrong answer.)
We didn't get floured.
This is great.
- They got only one question right.
- Okay.
All right.
They look just fine.
- Who will go next?
- I'll do this.
You know I'm good
at picking numbers. I'll do it.
- No, I'll press buttons.
- No.
- I'm really good at this.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- No one is better than me.
- I have a good hunch.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
No. I'll do it.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let me do this.
- No, play rock-paper-scissors.
- You should sit.
- You...
- I received eye surgery.
- So you should sit.
- But...
- You can wear goggles.
- He can do that.
Wait. Woo Jae...
Woo Jae just got eye surgery,
and they want him to sit here.
Okay. I'll wear goggles.
- He should.
- Wear goggles.
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay.
I'm the only one who lost.
- What's...
- Rock-paper-scissors
Okay.
Donghak Peasants' Movement.
- It's Donghak Peasant Movement.
- What's that?
I just added an apostrophe.
All right.
- She's smart.
- Let's go.
So Min and Woo Jae, pick a card.
We're better than them.
Show your cards.
- This is it.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Don't show it to your team.
I already made up my mind.
It's our turn.
- Good luck.
- Let's do this.
- We can do this.
- I'll appreciate your help.
- We should get it right.
I'll appreciate your help.
You should think
that she's number one.
Why?
No, Dong Hoon. You can do this.
Okay. I'll give it a try.
- He's improved a lot.
- All right.
The first category is person.
(The first category is person.)
I'm good at this.
Haha, you look cool.
I'll show you a picture,
and you'll answer who it is.
Okay.
Here's the question.
- An.
- Gel.
- Ii.
- Na.
- Jol.
- Ie.
- Okay.
- Yes!
(The answer is Angelina Jolie.)
- That's too easy.
- That was an easy one.
It's too easy.
Angelina Jolie is too easy.
- This is going well.
- Nice.
- Good.
- Well done.
We're good.
Nice.
All right.
Se Chan, pick a number
and press the button.
I already made up my mind.
- I picked a number.
- Hey.
Be good.
You...
It's not about good or bad.
I just pick a number.
- I mean...
- Should I try hard to press it?
I should try hard.
Is this what you want?
What am I supposed to do?
(He responds
to Suk Jin's request playfully.)
That's not what I meant.
Is this what you want?
- What am I supposed to do?
- Okay.
- Good.
- Come here.
Are you getting smart with me?
No, it's not like that.
(An old fossil shows up.)
- What's with you?
- What are you doing?
- What are you talking about?
- Why would I get smart with you?
It's not like that.
I just told him to be good.
- It's not about being good or bad.
- Seok Sam.
- You're being mean.
- Are you messing with me?
I'm not messing with you.
- I'm trying to be good.
- You're messing with me.
I'm just messing with you.
I'm trying to be good.
My goodness.
I'm warning you now.
If you don't do it right...
Why would you warn him?
Do you have
yellow cards or something?
- Do you?
- Why would you warn him?
- I thought we all have them.
- What?
- What's with him?
- Why are you upset?
- Why are you mad?
- We can give yellow cards.
- Hey, be good.
- I'll be good.
Pick a number and press the button.
I'll pick...
(Will he be able to avoid
the 3 penalty numbers out of 6?)
Number three.
(Number 3!)
(Ji Seok Sam is chosen.)
Number three.
(The disciplinarian who gives
warnings gets floured.)
(It's a perfect didactic story
where the evil gets punished.)
It's perfect.
This is amazing.
(Surprised)
It was perfect, right?
It's perfect.
- It's perfect.
- This is amazing.
How could it be so perfect?
Can you believe this?
He's punished.
You're being punished.
Was I good?
Yes. You were perfect.
I was good, right?
- You just did as you were told.
- I did a good job.
Suk Jin, they say I did a good job.
Suk Jin, I did as you said.
It's the best.
- Gosh. He's the Honorary Employee.
- This is nice.
- That's unbelievable.
- Hey.
- Did you know my number?
- No, I didn't.
You told me to be good.
It's unbelievable
that you picked Suk Jin's number.
That was amazing.
Well done. Nice, Seok Sam.
The next question is
about common knowledge.
- Se Chan.
- Gosh.
(The next question is
about common knowledge.)
Due to an increase
in the amount of money,
- currency loses its value...
- You know it, right?
and the price of goods continually
increases. What is it called?
(Empty Head seems to know
the answer too.)
- All right.
- This is an easy one.
- You know it, right?
- If you don't, just say pass.
- Bu.
- What?
You should pass!
- You know it, right?
- If you don't, just say pass.
- Bu.
- What?
You should pass!
- Just say pass!
- It's...
- It's inflation.
- You should pass!
- He said I'd know it.
He doesn't know inflation.
- What did he say?
- He said, "You know it, right?"
He was going to say bubble.
He said "Bu."
- Bubble.
- Economic bubble?
- My goodness.
- Inflation.
(Their chance to win a point
is gone like bubbles.)
Seriously, let's do this.
- We just need one more point.
- We should get one question right.
The next question is
about common knowledge.
- Okay. Good.
- That's a tough one.
It was a gift from France
to the US back in 1886.
What's the statue located on
Liberty Island in New York Harbor?
- Three...
- The.
- Statue.
- Of.
- Lib.
- Erty.
Okay!
Great.
- Pick a number.
- We have good teamwork.
- Can I pick number three again?
- No.
(Can I pick number three again?)
(He's the number 3.)
- Suk Jin, I can't.
- Hey.
Can they switch seats?
- I just asked.
- Good.
It can't be numbers 2, 3, and 4.
And it can't be numbers 3, 4, and 5.
(Se Chan is
thinking carefully again.)
Now I feel at ease.
They must be really nervous.
I'll pick a number.
(What's Se Chan's choice?)
I pick number four.
(Number 4?)
(Joo Woo Jae is chosen.)
I can't believe this.
It's unbelievable.
(The Variety Show Deity is here!)
Hey.
How...
- Did you really not know that?
- Seriously?
I'm doing my best.
- It's like...
- This is amazing.
The flour...
I can't believe this.
That's unbelievable.
- I can't believe this.
- He's really good.
- You...
- He's at a ski resort.
- It's a ski resort.
White snow is coming down
- She's right.
- It's like he is at a ski resort.
- He's at a ski resort.
- For sure.
How did he pick number four?
- This is crazy.
- That's unbelievable.
- Seriously, you're the best.
- How is it possible?
- You're the best.
- You really are.
- I didn't know.
- By the way,
they never won.
Is that because of me?
- We lost a point?
- We lost three games in a row?
- What will you do?
- All right.
- The last one.
- It's our turn.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- We won't do it anyway.
- Okay. Let's do this.
- Okay.
This is hilarious.
Jae Suk, where should we sit?
Do you want me...
to finish it early?
It's up to you.
Jae Suk.
- It doesn't matter.
- Let me be number two.
- Which one?
- It doesn't matter where I sit.
- Number two?
So Min, you're number two.
- Thank you.
- I'll go first then.
- Okay. You're number one.
- Thank you.
Let's be strategic.
Ji Hyo is number three.
- Please, Jae Suk. Se Chan...
- She's the first one to answer.
Can I switch seats with Se Chan?
I'm relieved. I can say pass.
- Can I switch seats with Se Chan?
- Pass!
Pass!
- Pass.
(They rehearse saying pass.)
Pass. This isn't right.
Pass. Okay.
- Pass.
- All right then.
(The first two players have
no intention to give an answer.)
Let me switch seats
with Se Chan, Jae Suk.
(She begs Jae Suk
to switch her seat with Se Chan's.)
- Okay.
- Save her life.
All right then.
- Se Chan.
- Se Chan and Woo Jae are switched.
Why? I want to say pass.
Se Chan and Woo Jae are switched.
Do you switch these two?
I'll let you switch seats...
after each question.
- Thank you.
- All right.
We can do this.
- Don't give up.
- I'll give it a try.
- Of course.
- I'll do my very best.
- Now...
- We've got this.
- This is a team game.
- You should dust it off.
- Okay. Where?
- I'll do it for you.
- All right.
- Ouch.
(Ouch.)
(Se Chan hit his glasses.)
- I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
- He practically hit Suk Jin.
- I bet it was intentional.
- I was trying to dust it off.
- You just wanted to hit me.
- You got the wrong idea.
- Don't get him wrong.
- Okay. You're good to go.
- He was trying to help you.
- Yes, he was.
I didn't mean to hit your glasses.
- He's a good guy.
- Show your cards to the camera.
(Team Tall revealed their numbers.)
- Don't let him see it.
- That's interesting.
- I couldn't see the numbers.
- Right.
- It's amazing they picked those.
- Exactly.
- I couldn't see the numbers.
- You can put them down now.
- Put them down so he can't see.
- That's neat.
The category of the first question
is common knowledge.
- Okay. Good.
- I'd prefer common knowledge.
- I want you to call it differently.
- I hope it won't be difficult.
It's an advanced knowledge quiz.
- "Advanced?" Okay.
- Good. Let's call it that way.
I feel offended when you call it...
- common knowledge.
- Right.
- It's an advanced knowledge quiz.
- "Advanced knowledge."
What is the Chinese idiom
that means a man must keep...
his promises no matter what?
Nam.
Three, two, one.
Pass.
(Both So Min and Ji Hyo
called pass.)
- Pass.
- A.
- Wait. Suk Jin...
- Il.
- Suk Jin told him the answer.
(Suk Jin got caught cheating.)
- He knew the answer anyway.
- Why would you do that?
- You shouldn't tell the answer.
Don't think we can't see you.
- Suk Jin, move to the end.
- Namaileon...
- It's unacceptable.
- I was supposed to say "Eon."
- Suk Jin, get up now.
- Never do that.
- I had no choice.
- Move to the end.
- Didn't you know the answer?
- Yes, I knew.
- You're not allowed to do so.
- Of course.
- What if...
(I apologize.)
- Trust me. I'll go first.
- He said, "I apologize."
- Suk Jin just said,
- Hey.
- "I apologize."
- You should know that idiom.
- Of course, I know that.
- I mean...
He wouldn't have apologized
if it hadn't been Bo Pil.
He said, "I apologize."
- Well, you know...
- He bowed deeply.
- Honestly, it was wrong of me.
- Yes, that's right.
- You two were right about that.
- Right. Never do that again.
- You ruined the fun.
- Let's move on.
The category is also
common knowledge.
- You mean, advanced knowledge.
- Right. It's advanced knowledge.
Let's get this one right.
What is the fruit that's a type
of green grape and that's popular...
- as it tastes similar to mangoes?
- They must know this one.
(It's easy.)
Three, two, one.
- Mus...
- Just call pass.
- It's shine muscat!
(It's shine muscat!)
- What's wrong with you?
- It's shine muscat.
- Don't you know shine muscat?
- Shine... seriously.
- Shine muscat.
- What's the point of being smart?
- Why were you so confident?
- Shine muscat!
- Isn't the answer "shine muscat?"
- I'm so disappointed.
- Shine muscat!
- "How about shine muscat?"
(How about shine muscat?)
Didn't you know it started with S?
- Even those idiots knew that.
- Let's change your seats now.
- Let's change your seats.
- I'm sorry, but let me say a word.
We're all shocked because of
what he said on this show before.
- None of you knew the idiom.
- Hey!
- Only I knew the answer.
- Shine muscat...
- It was an easy one.
- After I said the first syllable,
- Hey.
none of the next five of them knew
the second syllable of the idiom.
- None of them knew the idiom.
- Woo Jae, move to the end.
- Woo Jae.
(The empty heads beat
the smart guy.)
Hae Na, you go first.
- I remembered "mus."
- Yes, you did.
- I forgot "shine."
- He went blank suddenly.
- I'm not lying.
- Hey, listen.
We would've gotten it right
if you had called pass.
- Right. You should've called pass.
- That was funny.
- We all knew the answer.
- Sit down, everyone.
Woo Jae, move to the end.
- Gosh. Is he really smart?
- They didn't even know the idiom.
- Just sit down.
- I mean...
- Move already.
- Did he go to Hongik University?
That was unexpected.
Okay. Let's continue.
- This is so much fun.
- Let's go.
- Hae Na, let's do this.
- I'll call pass if it's English.
The next category is person.
- I'm not confident in it.
- It'll be easy.
- Let's go.
- Suk Jin, don't tell the answer.
- I won't. I promise.
- Never do that again.
Here's your question.
Pass.
- El.
- V.
- Is.
- P.
- Re.
- S.
- Ley.
- Good.
(Correct)
- I'm relieved.
- Great.
(Everyone is doing
Elvis Presley's dance.)
Suk Jin, that was good.
- We did well.
- We were amazing.
- Let's keep it up.
- Great.
- This is our team's true ability.
- That was good.
- Okay. Let's go. I'll pull it off.
- It's okay.
- Don't worry.
- Let's trust him.
- You can do it, right?
- He can do it.
- You can do it.
- Okay. I'll start right away.
I pick number one.
(He chose number 1.)
One, two, three.
(And the number he picked is...)
It's party time!
- One, two, three.
- It's party time!
(Jong Kook is chosen.)
I'm sorry.
- He apologized to Jong Kook.
- Oh, no.
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
- That was good enough for me.
- I didn't know it was your number.
- I feel bad for him.
Hey, are you crying?
- I'm okay.
- Why did you pick number one?
How come you picked number one?
- How come you pressed that number?
- We were amazing.
Can you please give me a chance
to redeem myself?
Woo Jae, you go first.
We'll be okay
as long as we're not in the last.
- Right.
- We can do this.
The category is person.
- I like this category.
- Good luck.
- Here's your question.
- It's difficult for me.
- It must be easy.
- Show the picture.
Go.
- Pass.
- Ke.
(Ke)
- Pass.
- Oh, my.
- V... I mean, S.
- My gosh.
- It's Keanu Reeves.
- Oh, right.
- You don't know Keanu Reeves?
- Hey.
(The correct answer is
Keanu Reeves.)
- It's Keanu Reeves.
- Oh, right.
- You don't know Keanu Reeves?
- Hey, it's Keanu Reeves.
- I don't know...
- why I said it.
- He said, "Ke."
- Hey, Hae Na.
- I knew his name, but...
- Oh, Keanu Reeves.
- Hey, Hae Na...
- I didn't know Hae Na would do it.
- Hae Na helped us.
- Why did you call pass?
- I got flustered.
- So I just called pass.
- Hey, Woo Jae.
- You don't know Keanu Reeves?
- "The Matrix."
I went blank again as I did before,
so I just called pass.
If you hadn't called pass,
we would likely have made it...
- because Haha knew the answer.
- Yes, I knew the answer.
I know shine muscat
and Keanu Reeves.
- Yes? Okay.
- Suk Jin, you go first this time.
- I'll do that.
- I know Elvis Presley too.
- Seriously.
- Go on. Cheer yourselves up.
- We've got this.
- Let's do this.
- We can do this.
- I almost remembered it.
Why don't you do the wave
starting with Suk Jin?
- Okay. Here we go.
- Don't give up.
- If we just start off well...
- Let's go.
(The wave begins.)
- You guys got up at the same time.
- You should do it consecutively.
Start over again.
But why must we do this?
I'm running out of energy.
To boost your morale.
- To improve teamwork.
- Okay.
- Great.
- We've got this.
(They're all obedient.)
- That's good. Right.
- You should sit down right away.
- Right after you stand up. Okay.
- Honestly, we're not in the mood.
Think about our situation.
- Still, you should do this.
- We feel hopeless right now.
- Why?
- You gathered these three idiots.
- This isn't fair.
- How are we supposed to do this?
- What are you talking about?
- Haha.
- I knew shine muscat.
- We all knew shine muscat.
- Who doesn't know shine muscat?
- Exactly.
- It's just...
- Who doesn't?
- We all know that much.
- We knew Keanu Reeves too.
What kind of idiot doesn't know
Keanu Reeves?
- Hey, sit down.
- Nobody can be that stupid.
(Tired)
Haha, we all knew shine muscat.
Let's continue.
This time, you have to spell
an English word.
- We can do this.
- This is your last question.
Here's your question.
- Spell the word "earth."
- What is it?
- This is...
- Pass.
E! It's "earth!"
(The 3 of them called pass
in the row.)
- My gosh.
- E, A, R, T, H.
I was taken aback. That's why.
- I was taken aback.
- Come on.
- Sir, please.
- We were taken aback.
- The 1st 3 of us were...
- The earth is getting warmer.
- Why "earth?"
- It's "earth."
- Hey! E, A, R, T, H.
- Come on.
Which is worse? Not knowing how
to spell "earth" or "shine muscat?"
I thought you knew.
- Which is worse?
- We were all taken aback.
I was so surprised.
- One of you should've known.
- Which is worse? Shine muscat?
- Or earth?
- Get lost.
- Hey.
- I was just taken aback.
- Is "earth" a difficult word?
I was taken aback. That's all.
- "Us?" "Earl?"
- "Earth."
- "Earth?"
- Yes.
- E, A, R, T, H.
- I was taken aback.
- I'll memorize it.
- I was flustered.
- I'll memorize the word.
- Okay.
- You were just taken aback, right?
- Yes, that's why.
- I was taken aback.
- That was shocking.
- I was really taken aback.
- I know.
- I thought you were playing soccer.
- "Pass."
They should be
as great as a Brazilian team.
- No one would shoot the ball.
- We'd keep passing it around.
- We'd never shoot the ball.
- We'd just pass it around.
I'll announce the winning team.
- Oh, boy.
- That was funny.
This team had a good chance to win
as they didn't lose many points.
- This team got four points.
- I guess it's not our team.
I bet it's Haha's team.
It's Team Short.
(Team Short will receive 3 coins
as the winning team.)
- Hae Na.
- We won?
- We won.
- Really?
- That team didn't do well.
- Oh, right.
- Team Tall came in second place.
- Okay.
- Team Average came in last...
with minus one point.
- It doesn't matter right now.
- You got one question right.
Now, go into your team's booth.
Yes.
- I'll go right away.
- Me too.
- I'll put in all my coins.
- We've never put in...
more than one coin until now.
Yes. I'll go right away.
(Starting with Haha
who ran into the booth...)
- Okay.
- Three coins, okay?
(Everyone has made a purchase.)
I'll explain about the last mission.
Please sit down.
We have the last mission.
- You never know how it might end.
- Right. It's not over yet.
As the saying goes,
you've been competing...
as if you were comparing
the size of acorns.
The last mission is Acorn War.
You have only 30 minutes.
You'll play Name Tag Elimination.
The first team to get eliminated
will come in last.
- Oh, boy.
- The last team to survive will win.
- I see.
- That's great.
However, you can't just tear off
others' name tags.
We hid a lot of acorns
in different places...
- in this building.
- Acorns?
- More than 100 acorns?
- Yes.
Collect five acorns and hand them in
to the staff in charge...
to get an elimination ticket
and reveal your target.
- I see.
- Really?
- Then you can eliminate the person.
- Okay.
Can't I tear off a name tag
without an elimination ticket?
Correct. You can't tear it off
without an elimination ticket.
But once that person starts
attacking you, you can defend.
Of course.
if you tear off his or her name tag,
the ticket becomes invalid.
Got it.
It won't be easy.
You need 5 acorns
to get 1 elimination ticket.
And you can get an open ticket
with 15 acorns.
Anyone can tear off
your target's name tag.
If you hand in 15 acorns.
I suppose you'll let us know.
Yes. If you hand in 15 acorns
and say your target is Jong Kook,
- everyone can eliminate him.
- "Kim Jong Kook."
- Everyone can attack that person?
- Yes.
- If you hand in 15 acorns.
- You'd become everyone's target.
Also, you can revive
your team member with 15 acorns.
- I can revive one person?
- Yes, one that's been eliminated.
- It's over when two teams are out.
- Got it.
- Now, please take your positions.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- It's difficult.
- This is where we start?
- What should we do to win?
If we collect enough acorns,
- who should we eliminate first?
- Exactly.
Suk Jin.
- Why?
- I don't know.
- We don't have to eliminate him.
- He's not a threat.
Which team is in second place?
Shouldn't we attack that team?
- It's Team Short.
- Right, it's Team Short.
- We should eliminate that team.
- Then we should eliminate...
- Team Short.
- Okay.
- Do you think we'll be a target?
- Our team?
Yes. We have only three on our team.
They must think they can beat us.
- We should aim to win.
- Okay.
Since I'm not good at attacking,
I'll collect acorns.
- That's a good plan.
- I like the idea.
- Who would be good at it?
- Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae and I will do it.
- Woo Jae isn't so strong.
- But I have long arms and legs.
- That's right.
- Se Chan, are you confident?
- Let's win this...
Let's win this round
and turn the game around.
- Let's use all three coins.
- That'll be awesome.
- Let's win a dramatic victory.
- Let's just not be in the last.
- One, two, three. Let's go.
- Two, three. Let's go.
- Then we'll begin the race now.
- Okay.
- The race begins now.
We should find acorns.
Are they hidden in random places?
- We should eliminate Team Short.
- We should eliminate them quickly.
- Let's go.
- I'll go find acorns.
Let's split up and look for acorns.
Let's gather again later.
- Should we split up for now?
- Yes, let's split up.
- Let's find some acorns first.
- But I'm scared.
But it can be dangerous for her.
Wait. There must be some here.
I wonder what it looks like.
Hold on.
I'm pretty sure that some are hidden
in a place like this.
Are those acorns big or small?
Or average? Are they small?
(Acorns will play a big part
as Team Short is outnumbered.)
Are they in a box?
I don't see any in the lockers.
Let's collect five acorns
no matter what.
Okay.
Is this it? Oh, I found one.
- Really?
- Yes.
Can we find acorns
in a place like that?
(Se Chan found his 1st acorn.)
So Min, this is what it looks like.
- Did you find one? Is this it?
- Yes.
Let me take a look.
Give it to me.
I'll have to keep acorns anyway.
I've become good at finding
hidden items.
(The observant Ssaebssaeb keeps
the momentum.)
There it is.
Acorn
I'll find them before others do
(While Team Average found acorns
one after another...)
(Haha found an acorn too.)
Okay.
There's none here.
- Haha.
- Yes?
- It must be easier for you.
- Why?
You are like an acorn.
- My gosh.
- You're small like an acorn.
(He's looking for acorns as if
he were looking for his friends.)
How many acorns did you find?
- What about you?
- I found two.
I found one.
Did you find any?
- No.
- Se Chan.
- We have five acorns now.
- Do we have five acorns?
- Se Chan.
- I found 2.
- That's 4.
- How many?
- Four.
We have five. Woo Jae,
get a ticket to eliminate Haha.
(Woo Jae, get a ticket to eliminate Haha.)
- Eliminate Haha.
- I don't think I can eliminate him.
- You can do it. Don't worry.
- Why don't you do it yourself?
- Hurry up.
- Go on. How many do you have?
- I have one.
- Give it to me.
Haha.
(Woo Jae purchased a ticket
to eliminate Haha.)
- Let's go.
- Let's tear off his name tag.
Let's go.
(Haha noticed
that something was going on.)
Gosh.
- Act natural. Don't let him know.
- Okay.
- I'll do it well.
- Good.
I'll lure Haha.
We should eliminate
the strong one first.
Okay. Great.
We're like Hansel and Gretel.
Look to your right. Where is Haha?
- Quiet down.
- He went that way.
- Come with me.
We should be careful. He's tactful.
- He'll figure it out.
- Haha went that way. Come with me.
(So Haha barely lost Team Average.)
You must have found a lot of acorns.
I haven't found any yet.
Did you find any acorns?
Gosh, no. I didn't see any.
This is too difficult.
Why is it so hard to find acorns?
- Indeed. I couldn't find any.
- Exactly.
- Gosh. You startled me.
- What's going on?
- You're not trying to do it, right?
- I couldn't find any.
(As famous scaredy-cats,
they both got scared.)
(You're not trying to do it, right?)
(He got startled and is chuckling.)
Jae Suk, we haven't found...
- I'm still looking too.
- enough acorns yet. Hey.
- We...
- They all must be here.
What are you guys doing here?
(The tigers who are after Haha
are here.)
It begins already?
- Hey.
- How many acorns did you find?
We couldn't find any acorns.
I haven't found enough acorns yet.
- What does an acorn look like?
- I found only two.
(Se Chan and Woo Jae go in
right away.)
Have I been in this room before?
They all look the same.
What's going on?
Do you have enough acorns?
(Haha figured it out.)
Let's run away.
Gosh. That scared me.
Why did they suddenly come up here?
I have no idea.
- They're acting weird.
- What are they doing?
- Jae Suk, give me just one acorn.
- I don't have any.
- Woo Jae is trying to eliminate me.
- I don't have any either.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- What's going on?
- He's trying to eliminate me.
What's going on?
Woo Jae, wait.
- No. It's not what you're thinking.
- What?
- Woo Jae.
- No. I'm not trying to do anything.
- Don't get me wrong.
- Why are you approaching me?
Why are you here? Are you after me?
- No.
- Then what...
I was just wondering
what you guys were doing.
(But...)
(Jae Suk attacks him!)
- I'm not attacking you.
- Hey.
(Jae Suk attacks him!)
Five.
(Jae Suk collected 5 acorns
3 minutes before he met Haha.)
I'll eliminate Haha.
(He chose Haha from Team Short.)
Here you go.
(Jae Suk's sudden attack)
- I'm not attacking you.
- Hey.
(Jae Suk is holding Haha down.)
(And here comes Woo Jae
who's also after Haha.)
(Haha is everyone's target.)
Is it me again? Wait.
Gosh. Me? Is it me again? Wait.
He's out.
(Woo Jae successfully eliminated
1 person.)
- He's out.
- He's out?
- Okay. Great job.
- I did it.
- Gosh.
- Are you okay?
(The elimination ticket
Jae Suk bought is invalid now.)
What a shame.
Haha is out.
Both of them were after me.
Gosh, that fool.
- We got one.
- We have to collect acorns again.
- Who should we eliminate this time?
- That's easy.
- Who...
- We'd better eliminate a weak one.
- Who should we eliminate?
- Then let's eliminate Irene first.
- Wait.
- I'll just check where she went.
Okay. The more we eliminate,
the better our chances are.
Where is Suk Jin?
(Meanwhile, Suk Jin...)
I just need one more acorn.
We should eliminate Jong Kook first.
(Surprisingly, Suk Jin is
targeting Jong Kook.)
There must be one in this room.
Here's one. Okay. Good.
I have enough acorns now.
Two, four, and five.
Who should I eliminate?
Would you like to purchase
an elimination ticket?
Of course, I'll get one.
- I'll eliminate Irene.
- Irene?
Irene... Hold on.
Who else is on her team?
Irene, Hyun Yi, Jae Suk,
and Jong Kook.
I'll eliminate Irene.
I've made up my mind.
- Okay. You chose Irene.
- Yes.
I wanted to choose
Jong Kook or Jae Suk.
Where is she?
- I don't see any acorns.
- Gosh.
We should keep looking.
Don't go too far.
What? Oh, hey, Irene.
(Se Chan found Irene
who was hiding in the room.)
What are you doing here?
How many acorns do you have?
I'll let you go if you give me three.
I have two.
Give me just one of them,
and I won't say your name.
- Just 1?
- Yes, give me just 1.
If you don't,
I'll find five acorns quickly,
and tear off your name tag.
(Thug Woo Jae is running around.)
I found another one.
- In 3, 2...
- Give me 1, and I won't attack you.
I give you one?
- I won't attack you.
- Okay. Deal.
- Will you give me one?
- No, you should give me yours.
No. Give me one of your acorns.
Why would I give it to you?
It's because...
I said I would eliminate you.
Why would you do that?
You're on another team.
I'll eliminate you.
- But I won't if you give me one.
- You don't have to attack me.
We'll just leave if you give me one.
- Do you promise me?
- Yes, I promise you.
- Or else, I'll tell on you.
- Okay. I promise.
- You'd better keep your promise.
- I promise.
- If you... Pinky promise. Sign it.
- I signed it.
- Make copies.
- Done.
- It's a promise.
- Okay.
- Now, give me one acorn.
- Look at this.
- It's a promise.
- Okay. I got one of your acorns.
You promised me, okay?
- Woo Jae, how many do you have?
- Four.
I'll give you one.
You tear off her name tag.
- Okay.
- Hey, you can't do that.
(Woo Jae bought a ticket
to eliminate Irene.)
(Hey, you can't do that.)
You crook!
- Irene.
No!
(I'll guard the back door.)
- Hurry up and take care of her.
- She's not even fighting.
- Hurry up and finish it up.
- It's done.
He tore it off.
(The naive Irene is out.)
- Irene.
- I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
I'm really sorry.
You guys are so mean.
- I'm sorry.
- This is Running Man.
- Gosh. Seriously.
(I'm sorry.)
Woo Jae, how many do you have left?
Irene is out.
This is quite scary.
It happened so quietly.
I didn't even hear her scream.
Darn it. Irene is out.
I should join Jong Kook
to get things done. Where is he?
(Meanwhile, the person who was
determined to eliminate Irene...)
Then what happens?
- Your ticket is invalid now.
- Can I choose another person...
I can choose another person.
Your elimination ticket is
invalid now. That's the rule.
(Chuckling)
I can't believe this. Darn.
It was so hard for me to find these.
I should find five more acorns?
(He lost his elimination ticket
as he targeted the weak one.)
This is driving me nuts.
Ji Hyo is out.
(Song Ji Hyo is out.)
- We'll team up.
- Song Ji Hyo is out.
(Ji Hyo is out?)
Oh, no. This is bad!
(Ji Hyo was alone
searching for acorns.)
Who could it be?
(The 86ers came together
to annihilate Team Short.)
It's me! Hold on.
- Is it really you?
- No, it's not.
What on earth?
(Woo Jae took her out
while Se Chan distracted her.)
It was Woo Jae.
(Ji Hyo was attacked
out of nowhere.)
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
But I had to do
at least something today.
(He already eliminated 3.)
Get lost, you jerk.
(Thug Ji Hyo wasn't enough
to save her own life.)
Oh, no. This is bad!
Hae Na's in trouble.
Hae Na's...
the only one left on the team.
I only need to find one more.
Just one more.
(She secretly searches
for more acorns.)
I found it.
I found one more.
Here. Who do I give these to?
(She has 5 and is looking
to buy an elimination ticket.)
Me?
Should I collect more or hide?
Maybe I should
just take someone out.
Hyun Yi.
I'll take Hyun Yi out.
(Hae Na buys an elimination ticket
that targets Hyun Yi.)
I need to find Hyun Yi.
(She targets Hyun Yi in secret.)
Where are the acorns?
Oh, there's one.
(Stealthily)
I need to eliminate Woo Jae.
- Hey, Hae Na.
- My gosh.
Are you alone?
Who are you trying to eliminate?
Are you all right?
(Her target Hyun Yi
appears in front of her.)
Are you all right?
Did you find any acorns?
(Hyun Yi goes after
Hae Na first though.)
I'll hold her for you.
(Hyun Yi goes after
Hae Na first though.)
(A sneak attack)
Rip her name tag off.
(The tall ladies battle it out
while screaming.)
Here.
(The tall ladies battle it out
while screaming.)
(Ripping off)
My gosh!
(She tore off the name tag!)
(Not long ago,)
(Jong Kook and Hyun Yi
saw Haha get eliminated.)
- They're...
- Let them be.
We should get to safety for a while.
Suk Jin.
That's five.
I found five.
Hae Na.
(She bought an elimination ticket
that could take Hae Na out.)
Here are five.
(They wanted to annihilate
Team Short first.)
(The last hope of Team Short
is eliminated.)
- Sorry, Hae Na.
- Hae Na is out.
- I almost got your name tag.
I would've lost if I were alone.
- I can't see anyone.
- Ji Hyo's been eliminated.
- Here.
- Look.
Here. I have more.
Why are you so good
at finding these?
We only need one more.
(The trio boldly targets Jong Kook.)
- We'll target Jong Kook.
- Is there one?
- Here.
- I knew it.
- Good. We have five.
- Let's do it.
- Suk Jin...
- Here we go.
- Did you eliminate them all?
- They must all be here.
Anyone could still win.
Jong Kook,
we should stick together.
Get up here, guys.
(Get up here, guys.)
I want to rip off
someone's name tag.
Why didn't I think of Se Chan?
Hold on.
- Why didn't I think of Se Chan?
- Hey. Woo Jae.
Jong Kook, look.
I'm going to buy
an elimination ticket.
Who should it be? Jae Suk?
- Should I target Jong Kook?
- We'll come for you.
(Only Jae Suk
can take Woo Jae out.)
Just know
you only have one chance with me.
I can fight back
once you lay a hand on me.
Me too.
I'll come after you too.
I have enough.
Who should we go after first?
Spare me two.
He wants two more
which means he's ready to fight.
(Jae Suk's trying to buy a ticket
with the acorns from Hyun Yi.)
- All right.
- You can...
I'll buy a ticket for Se Chan.
- Do it.
- Good one.
- Okay, Se Chan.
- Hold on.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Go after him too.
- I'll target Jae Suk too.
We're not allowed to intervene.
We can pin down their targets.
- Can we do that?
- Of course.
- I know.
- Go after Jae Suk.
We are almost done.
- Take the other side.
- What about our team?
- I'm going after Jae Suk.
Just Jae Suk.
How about a 1 on 1?
- You're dead today.
- I'll come straight for you.
- Be careful though.
- We should grab Se Chan.
Grab him.
I must be their target!
- Jong Kook's after me.
- No, wait.
Jong Kook's after me.
He's out.
(Ji Suk Jin is out.)
I was their target.
You!
- Ji Suk Jin is out.
- It was me all along.
Ji Suk Jin is out.
I was their target.
- Over here!
- Grab him.
Get him.
Let go of me.
Jae Suk.
Hurry!
Go after Jae Suk.
(The 86ers are desperate.)
Hyun Yi's so strong.
Go after Jae Suk.
(While Hyun Yi blocks Se Chan...)
Hyun Yi, grab him for a second.
No!
(But Jae Suk shows his back.)
I got it.
Watch out!
I got Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk is out.
- He's been eliminated.
- He got me.
Were you eliminated?
I'm out of the game.
Yoo Jae Suk is out.
(Se Chan went after him
when he showed his back.)
I should've been a part
of that dynamic takedown.
He got me from behind.
For now, we should fall back.
Jae Suk, gosh.
(They fall back for now.)
- Did you see me just now?
- I...
- Hyun Yi...
- Did you see it?
Did you film me
holding Jong Kook by the collar?
- I held him like this.
- I bet it wasn't intimidating.
No, I held him like so.
- Really?
- Like that.
- Do you have that on camera?
- Are you good?
I want it aired
as one of the best scenes.
Make sure music is played
in the background...
and play it in slow motion.
Se Chan was there.
We should stick together.
(Team Tall stick together.)
We should eliminate Se Chan.
Let's keep searching.
Se Chan...
Woo Jae and Se Chan.
There are two guys left.
I know.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
How many do you have?
- I have 2 or 3.
- I have 3.
- Really?
- We should eliminate Se Chan.
Se Chan?
- Woo Jae...
- Take one of the guys out.
- One of them needs to go.
- Okay.
Yang Se Chan.
(Jong Kook buys an elimination ticket
that targets Suk Jin.)
We'll then go after Woo Jae.
(He buys an elimination ticket
that targets Se Chan.)
This one is for Woo Jae.
Joo Woo Jae.
Then... Let's see.
Only So Min remains. Right?
(They can go after everyone
if they get another ticket.)
One for So Min.
Jong Kook is now an open target.
(Jong Kook is an open target?)
They're coming.
I'm an open target now.
- Let's run.
- Oh, no.
(Team Tall makes a run for it.)
- Let's go upstairs.
- We need...
- to find Jong Kook fast.
- Hurry.
(Team Average searches for him.)
I have three.
- How can we take Jong Kook out?
- We can't.
With 15 acorns,
we can buy an open ticket.
So anyone can eliminate him?
We'll have to collect 15
and make Jong Kook an open target.
One-on-one isn't an option.
Let's collect 15 fast.
Collect 15...
- and make Jong Kook an open target.
- Okay.
Okay.
Here's one.
We'll name our target.
An open target.
An open ticket.
- Jong Kook as an open target.
- Here are 15 acorns.
(They purchase an open ticket
that targets Jong Kook.)
- And then...
- This is for Hyun Yi.
Are they all targets now?
- Who can we target?
- Both of them.
- I'll go after Hyun Yi.
- Hyun Yi and Jong Kook.
I'll go after Hyun Yi.
Let's do this.
I bet they're sticking together.
- Here!
- Nice one.
So Min.
- Jeon So Min.
- We're all set.
(Hyun Yi buys an elimination ticket
that targets So Min.)
We can eliminate anyone now.
Only Hyun Yi and Jong Kook remain,
right?
Yes.
He's an open target,
but only our team remains.
- We can all go after him.
- It won't be easy though.
- Right.
- It won't be easy.
(Outnumbering him
doesn't always guarantee a win.)
There's another one over there.
- Let's bring Suk Jin back.
- How many do we need?
- Fifteen.
- Right.
- Let's do that.
- Let's bring him back.
- Yes, let's bring him back.
- We'll resurrect him.
Okay, let's collect 15 acorns.
(They make an odd decision
to resurrect Suk Jin instead.)
Four against two is better.
- They can do the same though.
- And resurrect Jae Suk.
- We need 15 acorns.
- Right.
(They're hoping to use Suk Jin
as a shield.)
I found one.
(Project Old Man Resurrection)
Here's one. I have five.
We have 15.
Okay, let's bring him back.
We'll bring Suk Jin back.
- A resurrection.
- Suk Jin.
- We'll bring Suk Jin back.
- That's 15.
- Right.
- You're bringing Suk Jin back.
- Yes.
- Where is he though?
- Maybe...
- We'll bring Suk Jin back.
- Bring him back.
Suk Jin has been
brought back into the game.
He's back?
Suk Jin's back.
We should eliminate him again.
- We need a ticket though.
- If we hurry...
- You're right.
- We need one first.
(They need an elimination ticket
for Suk Jin though.)
- They find acorns so well.
- Darn acorns.
They brought Suk Jin back.
Once the four of us
eliminate Jong Kook,
we can...
win the entire race with all 12.
How's that for a dramatic ending?
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin!
Thanks, guys.
- Aren't we loyal?
- You're the best.
Suk Jin, here's the deal.
- You guys are the best.
- Suk Jin,
we need to join forces
and eliminate Jong Kook.
- Okay, got it.
- Can I give this to you?
Sure thing.
- Later...
- I saw Jong Kook just now...
- on the seventh floor.
- Let's go then.
They were moving away
on the seventh floor.
- Away?
- We should head up this way.
Sure thing.
Suk Jin. You go ahead.
Suk Jin.
Then we're all set.
Hold on.
- How many do we need to resurrect?
- Fifteen.
- We should collect more.
- If only we had collected them.
- We'll bring Jae Suk back.
- That sounds good.
Sure. It sounds better.
- We can do this.
- It's a better plan.
We can bring him back.
(Team Tall aims
to bring Jae Suk back.)
- That's one.
- Se Chan...
We need to bring him back.
We need to.
Hurry. We have to find more acorns.
Suk Jin, do whatever you can...
- to stop Jong Kook.
- Got it.
Muster up all your strength.
I hear something.
I can hear something.
(I hear something from upstairs.)
- I hear something.
- Hey.
Let's go.
(Commence attack.)
Are they heading upstairs?
(Team Tall must avoid them
until they bring Jae Suk back.)
They're here.
We have a total of ten.
- We only need five more.
- Yes, five more.
- Don't we have ten?
- Yes.
Jae Suk,
hold on tight.
It won't be long.
We'll bring you back.
(Hold on. We'll bring you back.)
There they are. Let's go.
- Go.
- So Min.
We need to withstand him.
So Min, this way.
- Do we go downstairs?
- Go.
Hurry.
(Team Tall frantically runs away
while Team Average gives chase.)
They're going back up again.
Wait a minute.
- No way. Woo Jae.
- They're here!
Guys!
- They're good.
- Guys!
Suk Jin! Se Chan!
Jong Kook is here!
They're here! They headed upstairs.
Se Chan, they're here!
- They're here. They went upstairs.
- Where?
I can't catch up with them.
Hold on.
Let me catch my breath.
(Jong Kook and Hyun Yi
gave Team Average the slip.)
That was close.
We could've gotten So Min.
We just walked past So Min,
didn't we?
- That was really close.
- I was...
I was afraid we'd be surrounded.
(Jong Kook finds it regrettable that
they couldn't get rid of So Min.)
I should've gotten rid of her.
I couldn't decide what to do
in the heat of the moment.
- Me neither.
- Hold on.
We need two more.
Two more.
We just need one more.
(Jong Kook found an acorn.)
We just need one more acorn.
Just one more.
- They're here.
- One, two, three, four...
- I got it.
Hold on.
- We...
- I got it.
(Right then, Team Average appears.)
(The 4 members of Team Average
finally found the 2 of them.)
- There they are.
- They're here.
We can't get them.
(They run after Jong Kook
and Hyun Yi in a weird way.)
Go! Chase them until the end!
(We can't lose them again!)
Go!
(A chase in the middle of the day
begins abruptly.)
I almost got all the acorns
I needed.
Here they are!
- I almost gathered enough acorns.
- Join me!
Chase them until the end!
(They managed to capture Jong Kook.)
- Join me!
- Grab Jong Kook.
We must seize Jong Kook.
(A face-to-face confrontation
between the two teams)
(They work together to attack
Jong Kook who is an open target.)
Hey, this won't do.
Hold on.
Gosh, this is really frustrating.
- This won't work.
- Be careful.
Let go of him.
(Right then, the tall striker
subdued Se Chan.)
I got him.
- I got him.
- Grab it. That's great.
- Hold on.
- I got him. It's all right.
Se Chan, get Hyun Yi.
- Get Hyun Yi, Se Chan.
- Se Chan!
Se Chan!
Jong Kook! My eyes!
My gosh.
(The fiery fist is in danger.)
Hey. Woo Jae is out.
Woo Jae is out.
- Woo Jae...
- Great.
Woo Jae is out. Watch out.
(Joo Woo Jae is out.)
Joo Woo Jae, out.
I think Jong Kook's next target is me.
(Jong Kook's next target is Se Chan,
his strongest rival.)
- Jong Kook is after you.
- Hyun Yi, we can't...
- We can't eliminate Suk Jin.
- Over here.
- Here it is.
- We can't eliminate him anyway.
Suk Jin, hold her.
- Let me eliminate Jong Kook.
- You can't.
You will?
Suk Jin, go for it now.
Go for it.
Suk Jin, rip off his name tag.
(Jong Kook never shows his back.)
Hey, hurry.
(While the two of them
are struggling to get Jong Kook...)
Hurry!
I almost got her!
Se Chan!
- Hey!
- Hurry!
Hurry!
We need to hurry up!
- What are you waiting for?
- So Min!
Wait. Hyun Yi got me.
(Tearing)
- I got it.
- What was that?
(In the meanwhile,
Se Chan's name tag was removed.)
Yang Se Chan is out.
Wait!
(Meanwhile, So Min...)
Hold on.
(Hyena-like Hyun Yi
is only after So Min's name tag.)
Wait.
- Jeon So Min, out.
- So Min!
- I can't rip his name tag off.
- You can!
(Suk Jin didn't know
Jong Kook was an open target.)
- How come?
- You can rip his name tag off.
- Wait.
- No, he can't.
You can
rip his name tag off, Suk Jin.
- How come?
- Jong Kook is everyone's target.
He's everyone's target?
I didn't know.
Hey, stop!
(It's a 1-on-1 match
between Jong Kook and Suk Jin.)
- I got it!
- Jong Kook, you're out.
But he...
It's okay.
(Suk Jin ripped off
Jong Kook's name tag.)
But he... I couldn't remove
his name tag because of the strap.
Wait a minute.
(When Jong Kook lost his strength
and was fighting for his name tag,)
(Suk Jin removed his name tag
as an experienced player.)
(A big twist)
(Suk Jin, who got revived, did it.)
All right.
- So Min.
- She ripped mine off.
- What happened?
- Jeon So Min, Kim Jong Kook, out.
Is that all right?
(The open target,
Kim Jong Kook is out.)
- Jong Kook is out?
(The shocking news of Jong Kook's
elimination hits the prison.)
- Hyun Yi survived?
- Suk Jin eliminated him?
- Hyun Yi...
- That means...
- only Hyun Yi and Suk Jin remain.
- It's a one-on-one match.
For real?
(Suk Jin has become the last hope
for Team Average.)
- So Min is out?
- Only Hyun Yi and Suk Jin remain.
They said Jong Kook was out, right?
They did.
(It's a 1-on-1 match
between Hyun Yi and Suk Jin now.)
All right. I'll see you later.
- Let's see.
- It's just me and Hyun Yi now?
(Both Hyun Yi and Suk Jin
need to get an elimination ticket.)
(Hyun Yi starts collecting acorns
right away.)
My gosh.
(Now it's a matter
of who finds more acorns faster.)
I'm in trouble. I'm sure
Hyun Yi has some acorns.
(Suk Jin doesn't have acorns
as he just got revived.)
I have no acorns.
(He needs to find more acorns
to become the star of the game.)
I need to find them fast.
(He needs to find more acorns
to become the star of the game.)
(Right then)
Suk Jin, let's face it head-on.
Face me head-on.
(Hyun Yi provokes Suk Jin now that
she got an elimination ticket.)
Bring it on.
(Hyun Yi provokes Suk Jin now that
she got an elimination ticket.)
Wait. I haven't collected
enough acorns. Give me some time.
- I haven't found the acorns.
- I picked you out.
Really? But I haven't found
the acorns.
Give me a few more minutes.
We need to play it fair.
- You need more time?
- Please.
Okay. I'll give you some time
to run off.
Go.
(But Hyun Yi
isn't ready to let Suk Jin go.)
This won't be any good though.
What do you mean? Once I rip off
your name tag, you're done for.
No, I meant for me.
I'm only going to defend myself.
If I rip off her name tag...
You can't rip mine off first.
I can run away, right?
- No, you can't.
- Yes, I can.
How come?
Although it may not be effective,
I'll earn some time.
Why are you so strong?
(Grabbing tightly)
Shall we give it a go?
(Startled)
She's way too strong.
(Hyun Yi tries the thigh pull move.)
You're so strong.
(Suk Jin hopelessly
flutters about.)
You're way too strong.
(Hyun Yi tries
the thigh pull again.)
You're so strong.
(Glimmering again)
Goodness, you're amazing.
It must be because you play soccer.
(Hyun Yi's name tag was ripped off?)
(Suk Jin ripped off her name tag
before she could attack him.)
Oh, no!
(Suk Jin claimed that he had
no elimination ticket on Hyun Yi.)
(What exactly happened?)
I'm sorry.
(5 minutes ago)
I already have three.
(He barely managed to
gather 5 acorns.)
- I'll buy one on Hyun Yi.
- Bring it on.
(He bought an elimination ticket
right before a head-on match.)
(Then he fooled her, saying
he has no elimination ticket.)
(Suk Jin's blow on Hyun Yi
when she was off her guard)
(That's how Suk Jin ripped off
Hyun Yi's name tag.)
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Lee Hyun Yi is out.
(We haven't used this caption
for a while.)
(Ji Suk Jin wins.)
- I'm sorry. Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Lee Hyun Yi is out.
- We won.
- My gosh, we won, So Min.
- That was close though.
- What shall we do?
- That was close.
- We need to buy blocks.
- Everyone should buy blocks.
- Woo Jae, you must join us.
- Race over.
Gosh, what is this?
(The moment of destiny
has finally come.)
What is that?
I don't think we can win.
Are you kidding me?
I must increase my height.
Or I could stretch my arms.
We're so done for.
(Who will be the winner
of this race?)
- My gosh, this is...
- All right!
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- Yes?
You were indeed a hero
whom we brought back alive.
- Exactly.
- You were our hero.
- I can't believe it.
- Everyone is talking about...
- how fast and strong you are.
- She's incredibly strong.
I thought Hyun Yi had a chance
of beating him.
- We almost won.
- You almost did.
- But I got fooled by Suk Jin.
- Is that so?
I'll announce the results
of the final mission.
Team Average won first place.
- Nice!
- We can just buy those.
- Team Tall is in second place.
- Yes, we can.
- We'll win for sure.
- For sure.
And Team Short is in last place.
- We're in second place.
- We'll give you coins in order.
You're earning as many coins
as you eliminated others.
- Wow, that's incredible.
- Really?
- That's incredible.
- What did he say?
- That's five.
- I eliminated three.
As many players as you eliminated.
Then you eliminated six players.
Then we don't know who will win.
- I eliminated...
- Even still,
- we need to buy blocks.
- For real?
These are for Team Short.
As many players I eliminated?
You must buy blocks no matter what.
Let's use up all our money for that.
- I'm getting five coins, right?
- Let's seriously invest in it.
- We must.
- You have six coins now, right?
We have no other choice now.
We don't, but we could win
if we invest in blocks.
- Then actually...
- How many do you have?
- Even if I do nothing...
- He got five.
- It's meaningless for him.
- But I won't do that.
- Okay.
- Woo Jae.
It's meaningless.
There's no point fighting
among ourselves.
We must invest in blocks.
It's not a matter of why.
We must invest in them.
- It's a promise.
- Got it.
You must invest in blocks
until the end.
- Here I go.
- I'll go next.
- They have this much.
- Even so.
- This is my last chip.
- I didn't earn it for free.
(The team members of Team Short
got a coin each.)
(All of them bought blocks.)
Gosh, we never know
what will happen, do we?
Of course, we should buy blocks.
(Even Team Tall buys blocks
even though they were leading.)
Our can is full.
We must beat them.
- So Min, add all of them in.
- So Min is gone.
Did she go home?
(Team Average didn't buy
that many blocks.)
(She chooses to buy blocks.)
I'm the one who is in least danger.
I couldn't help but put it all in.
- You did?
- Since I'm short...
- What did you buy?
- The blocks.
Since we're in first place,
we can't help it.
(Woo Jae invests all 6 coins
in blocks.)
- I'm done.
- I'll put my trust in Team Average.
- What? Why?
- Okay.
- You revived me, that's why.
- We did.
(Suk Jin buys blocks
since he was revived.)
I added them all.
I really added them all.
They have great teamwork.
That's not good.
Do you think it'll work?
- Se Chan!
- This is strange.
You're the tiger!
Se Chan, everyone on our team
is bound to betray one another.
But we can pull it off though.
All right, everyone.
I'll announce the results now.
That was quite quick.
It looks like there's a big gap
between good and bad players.
I'll announce
the results of Team Tall.
I bet it's overpowering.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
You used ten coins in total.
Wait a minute. You're sharing
everything with us, right?
Why would you reveal that?
You'll get to see it anyway.
- Jae Suk bought...
- Among ten coins...
seven blocks and three shoe lifts.
- Okay.
- He got three shoe lifts.
That's a lot. At first...
You bought seven blocks?
Jong Kook.
At first...
- Out of 12,
- You bought a lot.
you bought 10 blocks
and 2 shoe lifts.
You bought shoe lifts too.
- You shouldn't have blamed me.
- There's no difference.
- My gosh. I only got two.
- They're all the same.
- I didn't lie.
- Irene,
you got 7 blocks and 3 shoe lifts.
- Wow.
- Goodness.
They all got shoe lifts.
- We still got a chance.
- We still have a chance.
- We really do have a chance.
- We have a chance.
- We're taller than them, at least.
- That's right.
Hyun Yi got 9 blocks
and 3 shoe lifts.
We're no different.
- I know.
- You got a lot of blocks.
- I only got three shoe lifts.
That's what I'm saying.
- I got nine blocks.
- You got a lot more than others.
She bought a block
every time she got three shoe lifts.
- That's enough.
- I piled up nine blocks.
- "That's enough?"
- They all had situations.
- Let's see.
- We all did well amicably.
Right, we did well.
- Of course.
- They all bought equally.
Did you buy shoe lifts
in the beginning? You did?
It was heartwarming for us at the end.
And for Suk Jin,
- he got 5 blocks and 3 shoe lifts.
- Yes.
- What?
- He did well.
Why are you suddenly so loyal?
- We were...
- Toward the end,
- it got heartwarming.
- heartwarming toward the end.
Woo Jae, you got 7 blocks
and 2 shoe lifts.
- Wow.
- Woo Jae bought a lot of blocks.
What is that?
Then this is disadvantageous for us.
We might be in last place.
- We're in last place.
- Next is Se Chan.
He got 5 blocks and 5 shoe lifts.
- What?
- He got five blocks...
(He got 5 shoe lifts.)
- Are you kidding me?
- Why didn't you contribute?
- I got five of each!
- Hey!
- Gosh, you punk.
- I got five of each!
- You're total garbage.
- They got seven blocks on average.
But it's...
- We lost.
- My gosh.
- So Min.
You got 3 blocks and 3 shoe lifts.
- My gosh.
- Darn you.
(So Min also invested
half of her coins in shoe lifts.)
- We're no different.
- Pass.
We could be in last place.
- We could be.
- All right.
Haha, you got 7 blocks
and 4 shoe lifts.
- What?
- I did well.
- I got 3 and 1 toward the end.
Look how brazen he is.
- You got four shoe lifts?
- Hae Na.
You got 7 blocks and 1 shoe lift.
- Wow, you're so loyal.
- How loyal of you.
- Ji Hyo.
- Let's listen to what she got.
- You got 5 blocks and 4 shoe lifts.
- What?
- Ji Hyo!
- Can you repeat that?
What does this mean?
She got a lot of shoe lifts too.
- Ji Hyo!
- She got many shoe lifts too.
- It's because I'm the shortest.
- Right.
We'll give you the shoe lifts now.
- All right.
- It's only a shoe lift difference.
- Only by that much?
It's only one shoe lift difference.
It doesn't look that different
from the others.
We'll start with Team Tall
who is obviously ahead.
- Then I'll go first.
- All right.
- It's all about the average anyway.
- Right.
If you can,
- hit as high as possible.
- I'll do my best.
- It's quite high.
- You should go as high as you can.
- Hold on.
- You should see from up there.
- It'll be better to hit sideways.
- It's quite high.
- You're right.
- It's really high.
- It's a bit scary though.
- Why?
- It looks scary to me too.
- It's really high.
You shouldn't be scared of this.
Can't you go first?
I'm a bit scared.
- But...
- We'll catch you.
- We'll catch you. Don't worry.
- Will you?
We will catch you like this.
- It's scary though.
- We'll catch you.
If you slap the wall and fall down,
- Just throw yourself at the wall.
- you won't get hurt.
- I should jump like this, right?
- Yes, you should.
If you hit too high,
you might fall backward.
No, you won't. I got you.
- I got you.
- We'll catch you.
- You got me.
- Okay.
- Jump like Freddie Mercury.
- Don't you trust me?
- I'll go first.
- All right.
The grasshopper is jumping.
- I'm so envious.
- The grasshopper?
(Will he be able
to overcome his fear?)
- The grasshopper!
(Will he be able
to overcome his fear?)
No way!
(He only jumped about 20cm.)
- What was that?
- What did you just do?
(What was that?)
- I'm sorry.
- You should've jumped more.
- I was scared.
- Gosh, seriously.
- He only jumped that high?
- You can jump that high...
without blocks.
- Are you serious?
- I was really scared.
- What was that?
- It was really scary.
- I mean...
- I suddenly got...
- really scared.
- Jong Kook, you're up next.
- He's being weird.
- You get me though, right?
You should've jumped higher!
You get me, right?
What do you expect?
How can I get you?
- Hey.
- But I get him.
- I think it'll be scary up there.
- I get him.
- You shouldn't have done that.
What was I supposed to do?
I was scared!
When I was about to jump,
I imagined my shoulders dislocating.
But still...
- He's deflating our blocks.
- I imagined my shoulders dislocating.
- Jae Suk, you're deflating ours.
- Our blocks are deflating.
Come down.
- Their blocks are deflating?
- Our blocks are deflating.
I should've jumped higher.
- Yes!
- I should've jumped that high.
- Darn it.
- That's really high.
You should jump sideways.
(Hyun Yi of Team Tall
jumps high as well.)
- Hey.
- What's with her?
- We got this.
- Good job.
- Well done.
- You did well.
- It's okay.
It's okay. You did a good job.
- She jumped diagonally.
- What is that?
- It's okay. You did a good job.
- It's a relief though.
- How can she hit his mark?
- What was that?
- Jae Suk is happy.
- It's okay.
Jae Suk, it's a relief.
- Hey! What was that?
- He's glad.
It's okay.
She hit Jae Suk's mark.
For the rest of the teams,
take turns in hitting the wall.
You should take turns.
- So Min, let's go.
- It was a mistake.
Goodness, Jae Suk made a bad start.
If you give me one more chance...
He will never give you
another chance!
Then stay quiet!
Why should I stay quiet?
Gosh, seriously.
(The Grand Award duo
is having a quarrel.)
- Go for it!
- So Min is going to jump.
(So Min of Team Average goes first.)
- That's pretty high.
- It's quite high.
- Well done, So Min.
It's 3.15m. Ji Hyo, it's your turn.
- Go!
- Please make it high.
- Nice.
- That's high too.
It's exactly 3m.
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, you're up next.
- Let's go.
- Suk Jin.
- I should've jumped higher.
- What's with your arm?
- What?
(Extended)
- Goodness.
- What is that?
Is he Lee Byung Hun in "Inside Men?"
- That's...
- What's wrong with your arm?
- Please hurry.
- Remove that.
- It's my arm.
- You can't do this.
- What on earth...
- It's my arm. What are you doing?
Mister, that's enough.
- Gosh, this man.
- Seriously.
What are you, a character
in "Inside Men?"
I want to try again though.
- Right? I'd jump higher.
- I know.
You can jump higher
if you're given another chance.
Gosh, he almost touched that.
He's pretty good.
- Suk Jin is pretty good.
- Didn't he just reach 3.6m?
Gosh, Suk Jin is really good.
(Suk Jin is showing
his reliable sides today.)
He can't do it because of Woo Jae.
- What was that?
(It was too short.)
It's 3.15m.
Gosh, Suk Jin!
- Hey.
- What was that?
- Hey. It was...
- What did he just do?
- It wasn't fun at all.
- Let me tell you a tip.
- Next is Hae Na.
- I jumped from afar.
He said he'd share a tip.
- What's with that man?
- I know.
- Hae Na.
- All right.
- It's 3.05m.
Next is Haha.
- He's intimidated.
- It's scary up there.
(The little kid can jump
quite high although he's short.)
- It's because he played basketball.
- Right.
Watch your knees!
(The little kid can jump high
because he used to play basketball.)
- Haha.
- He can't jump that high.
The highest he can reach is 3.2m.
- Didn't he jump up to 3.4m before?
- Before...
Haha, the highest you can reach
is 3.2m.
I knew it.
Haha, the highest you can reach
is 3.2m.
(It's exactly 3.2m.)
The highest you can reach is 3.2m.
(As expected)
- Mister 3.2m!
- It's as high as mine.
- It's 3.2m.
- Woo Jae seems relaxed.
- Darn it.
Let's see.
(Se Chan and Woo Jae
on Team Average jump comfortably.)
- That was cool.
- Well done.
So that puts...
Team Tall in first place,
and they win prizes.
- Yes!
- It's good for us.
- We got this.
- We're not in last place?
And the shortest member...
of Team Average
will receive the penalty.
Two members from this team
We'll give you shoe lifts.
Please put them on.
Shall we put the shoe lifts on?
- It's too small.
- I only have one.
- I'm...
- I should've got more shoe lifts.
I should've betrayed them.
This is the fun part.
We are all by ourselves now!
- I guess this is how it feels.
- So this is what shoe lifts are.
The shoe lifts...
- I'll go for it first.
- Sure.
- Could you step back?
- Gosh, this is...
- You're so tall.
- But you're wearing a cap.
- Let me see.
- Okay, I'll take it off.
We're similar in height now.
You're still shorter than me.
You can never be as tall as me.
- All right. First place...
- You can't be taller than me.
- goes to Haha.
- Yes!
Hae Na and Ji Hyo
will receive the penalty.
- All right!
- They'll receive the penalty.
(All right!)
He's ecstatic.
- He's so happy about it.
- He's so weird.
The two of them
are getting the penalty.
He's the worst.
- All right.
- For this team,
it's obvious...
- that Woo Jae is in first place.
- Okay.
- Do we have one more person to go?
- Yes.
- Is it me?
- You should come and stand here.
So Min's head is taller than others.
Please turn around.
Se Chan is definitely taller.
- First...
- Please take off your cap.
First, Se Chan...
(It looks like Se Chan lost.)
- Se Chan...
- It looks like Se Chan lost.
- Se Chan won.
- His shoulders are much higher.
- Of course.
All right.
- Look at him.
- Why are you adjusting your hair?
Push it down. Stop it. Push it down.
- Why would you adjust your hair?
- The grandpa is still young.
Suk Jin, are you ready?
- All right. Hold on, Suk Jin.
- Look how tall his hair is.
- That's so brutal of him.
- Look at his hair.
- They're similar in height.
- They are.
(They're similar in height.)
- They're similar in height.
- They are.
So Min wins!
What a load of nonsense.
(Jae Suk supports So Min.)
(What a load of nonsense.)
(Putting on a straight face)
- How could you say that?
- It doesn't make any sense.
You can check if you want.
- She won!
- This is too much.
How is that possible?
I'm looking down at her.
- Let's check again then.
- Do I look like a fool?
Then measure it yourself.
- Go ahead and measure it.
- Let's do that.
Measure it. You see?
Look where your hip is.
This is...
Come on, So Min.
I'm sorry, So Min.
This is how life is.
- All right.
- We're in second place.
Hae Na, Ji Hyo, and So Min
will receive the penalty.
(Hae Na, So Min, and Ji Hyo
will receive the penalty.)
Bring in the prize.
What is it?
It's Korean beef. You can grill it
or make rice cake soup with it.
It's so fresh.
- No way.
- And...
the penalty is a whipped cream bomb.
One of you
will be spared from it randomly.
One of us will be spared?
(Who will be the lucky survivor?)
Two,
three!
Okay.
Hae Na survived.
The nice one survived.
- Unbelievable.
- The nice one survived.
- My goodness.
- That was incredible.
- The nice one survived.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
Hello.
It's time to film
my favorite show, Running Man.
I will hurry up and sit down.
I can't wait.
What will happen today?
Ever since Haha began
to star in "How Do You Play?"
he doesn't look happy
on Running Man.
(Ever since he heard those words,
he shows happiness on Running Man.)
- My goodness.
- Hello.
Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, you are too much.
- What?
- Suk Jin.
- So Min.
- Why are you picking on me?
- You have no interest in me.
- So Min.
Of course, I have interest in you.
I worry about you.
- Hello.
- I prepared a special chair.
You didn't prepare it.
You have a point.
I can't believe
you tried to hit me with a crutch.
(She expressed herself
with a crutch.)
I feel sorry for you
that you injured your leg,
but you can be the judge today.
Are you okay?
You are slow.
So Min,
you can't get us water, right?
Seriously.
You still need to clap the slate.
- You are the youngest.
- Should I do it now?
- Do it later.
- You can do it from the spot.
Today, you should do the work
as a substitute.
- Do you want water?
- Yes, I need water.
I am sorry.
Don't be sorry.
How did it happen?
When you go down the stairs...
- like this,
- Yes.
women often twist their ankles.
- That happens.
- That happens to me often.
It's the same with men.
Then my foot became swollen,
so I got an X-ray.
I have a fracture.
- A fracture.
- Did your bone break?
- It's a fracture.
- I got a fracture in my foot.
Her toenails got bruised.
That's not true. It's a pedicure.
Her toenails got bruised blue.
She got a pedicure since she knew
that a guest was coming today.
- It's a pedicure.
- Did she get a pedicure...
- to look cute to a guest?
- It's a pedicure.
So we won't need a referee
for four weeks.
That's not true.
- You should wear a yellow uniform.
- That's right.
No.
In any case,
I hope So Min recovers quickly.
- I feel bad.
- She will recover soon.
- Time will pass quickly.
- Thank you.
Today, we will welcome 2022,
the Year of the Tiger.
Se Chan and So Min were born
in the Year of the Tiger.
Roar. Tiger is
my Chinese zodiac sign.
We invited guests
who were born in 1986 like them.
- Really?
- Did you say 1986?
Are there celebrities
who were born in 1986?
Not many celebrities were born then.
Guests who were born in 1986,
the Year of the Tiger, come on out.
This is "Tiger Is Coming."
- Who are the guests?
- "Tiger Is Coming."
- Hey.
(Three guests who were born
in the Year of the Tiger)
- My goodness.
- Hey.
My goodness.
Welcome.
Hello.
Bae Seul Ki.
- It has been a while.
- Seul Ki.
- Hey.
- Welcome.
It's Eunhyuk.
- Hey.
- I thought it was an idol singer.
I thought it was an idol singer.
(People who are the same age
greet each other warmly.)
You look much better.
- Eunhyuk.
- You haven't changed at all.
This is insane.
I haven't seen her in a long while.
- It has been so long.
- I thought you didn't recognize me.
That's not true. I was fascinated.
- She worked with me upon debuting.
- Hello.
Please come to the middle.
I can't believe
Soo Ah and Seul Ki are here.
I am close to tears.
- Come here.
- This brings back memories.
- It has been a while.
- I haven't met Seul Ki before.
- Hello.
- It's our first time meeting.
- Yes, it is.
- Are we the same age?
- So Min, sit down.
- We are the same age.
- The Year of the Tiger?
- Hey.
- We are...
- Sit down, So Min.
I broke my foot.
- It's nice to meet you.
- What is up with you?
Sit still.
- This isn't a reunion. Sit still.
- For goodness' sake.
- Was everyone born...
- Sit down.
- in the Year of the Tiger?
My goodness.
This is incredible.
She is here
with her boyfriend today.
(He is a good man
who looks after his girlfriend.)
That's right.
Are you taking a walk?
- Yes, we are. Hello.
- My goodness.
You have a good boyfriend.
I can't believe it.
It has been a while.
- Eunhyuk, it has been a while.
- Yes, it has.
It has been four years
since I visited Running Man.
- That's right.
- Really?
- You visited after your discharge.
- Eunhyuk doesn't get old.
Eunhyuk, you don't get old.
I didn't recognize him.
He looks younger.
- When he entered,
- He looks the same.
- I didn't recognize him.
- Eunhyuk, you look younger.
I am taking good care of myself.
- I see.
- You look after yourself.
Please tell me what you do.
- I go to a dermatologist often.
- Is it necessary?
- I use a sheet mask every day.
- I see.
When Eunhyuk first debuted
as Super Junior,
I thought,
"He must be an excellent singer."
- I thought that.
- Jong Kook.
You know what I mean, right?
"He must be an excellent singer."
I thought that.
- His looks improved a lot.
- Thankfully.
They improved a lot
compared to the past.
- Yes.
- I am taking good care of myself.
He looks exactly the same.
- Seriously.
- I saw him ten years ago.
- He looks exactly the same.
- You look better now.
- Your face is plumper now.
- Suk Jin should do the same.
- That's right.
- It wasn't like that before.
(Jong Kook won't stop talking
about how his looks improved.)
You keep talking
about how my looks improved.
I must have looked terrible
in the past.
You must have looked terrible
- "You look good now."
- How bad were my looks?
Other members
of Super Junior were...
- too handsome.
- Trainer Kook.
- Stop it already.
- Everything is relative.
- Today...
When he said it at first,
it sounded like a compliment.
But he kept going.
- Other members were too handsome.
- Trainer Kook.
Stop it already.
- Are you going to a ski resort?
- Stop it already.
For your information,
Eunhyuk went...
to the same elementary school
as So Min.
- That's right.
- Middle school too.
Elementary school and middle school.
That's nine years.
I heard Eunhyuk was very popular.
- He was very popular.
- Eunhyuk...
could dance well,
so he was very popular.
- His real name is Hyuk Jae.
- What?
- Hyuk Jae.
- Lee Hyuk Jae.
- Sit down, So Min.
- So Min.
- All right.
- We keep telling you that.
- We understand how you feel,
but you need to recover quickly.
Stay seated.
- He was so popular.
- Don't move.
What was So Min like
in elementary school?
So Min was the same even then.
- Really?
- She was innocent.
She was a bit obsessed with love.
- Really?
- Eunhyuk.
- In elementary school?
In elementary school?
When was I like that
in elementary school?
In elementary school, we had...
- a cute popularity vote.
- Right.
- Then...
- That's fascinating.
we voted for the top three girls.
- I see.
- Every time,
So Min placed 2nd or 3rd.
That's not true.
I remember it exactly.
Then she always asked the kids
who chose her as 2nd or 3rd place,
- "Why am I second place?"
- She is the same.
She is the same.
(Why am I second place?)
- She is still like that.
- I remember it exactly.
- I got goosebumps.
- Hyuk Jae wrote down...
the names
for 1st, 2nd, and 3rd places.
I think I was in seventh place.
(She remembers it exactly.)
Seriously.
- She is still like that.
- She pestered kids for days.
It's scary that you remember it.
She is still like that.
She pestered kids for days.
She hasn't changed
since elementary school.
She is the same.
Let's move on to the next guest.
It has been so long. Hong Soo Ah.
- Hello.
- She rarely visits variety shows.
I have seen her
ever since she was little.
Suk Jin, I helped her debut.
- That's right.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- I practically raised her...
- "Music Bank K-Chart."
on "Six Heroines."
- Do you remember "Six Heroines?"
- That's right.
- Hey.
- Suk Jin.
- I gave her screen time.
On "Six Heroines," you were...
I was the only one
who didn't make it big.
- Everyone else made it big.
- You weren't in that position.
- That's right.
- Seriously.
Everyone,
we are moving to the center
as if there is a bonfire.
- Please move back.
- So Min isn't the center.
So Min was sitting down.
So Min, stop moving closer.
- Okay.
- Stop moving closer.
Here is the thing about Seul Ki.
When there were...
a lot of dating variety shows
such as "Love Letter,"
she captivated the nation
with her retro dance.
It has been two years...
since you got married, right?
- What?
- Yes.
- Did she get married?
- Didn't you know?
- Seul Ki, did you get married?
- Yes.
- Seul Ki.
- You got married?
- You didn't tell us.
Why didn't you invite us?
- Why didn't you tell us?
- Well...
Hold on.
- Because I lost...
- Seul Ki.
my phone a few times,
my number changed,
and I couldn't reach many people.
- Seul Ki got married.
- I had no idea.
I wasn't invited
to Jae Suk's wedding,
but I went anyway.
I am sorry.
(Seul Ki went
even though she wasn't invited.)
(The vending machine of good deeds
encounters an error.)
- Hold on.
- Jae Suk.
- Come on.
Bring an envelope, Jae Suk.
Bring an envelope.
- You should talk.
- Your face is turning red.
Your face is turning red.
- Let me step outside for a second.
- Jae Suk.
You shouldn't have said anything.
He went to withdraw some money
for the wedding gift.
- Jae Suk.
- Seul Ki!
Seul Ki!
We met for the first time
in a long while.
You shouldn't be like that.
Jae Suk, it has been a while
since I saw your ears turn red.
- You shouldn't have said anything.
- You know...
Jae Suk feels bad
about such things.
- It's okay, Jae Suk.
- You didn't know.
There is someone who didn't come
despite receiving an invitation.
- Me? Did I receive an invitation?
- Hey.
- You are less than human.
- I sent it to you.
- You are so mean.
- You are less than human.
Just a moment ago, he was like,
"Did she get married?"
I am sorry.
- He is so mean.
- I will bring an envelope.
- Hey.
- Se Chan...
Did you like Seul Ki?
No!
That came out of nowhere.
- No.
- My goodness.
So Min. Today,
- your comments are impactful.
- Please slow down.
Please slow down.
I think your foot injury
made you better at talking.
- That's so funny.
- It made you better at talking.
- I don't want to look lazy.
- I understand.
- Sit down.
- That energy went to her mouth.
So Min's comments are clean-cut.
She gets to the point.
All right.
It has been a while,
so we should see Seul Ki's...
- Let's see her retro dance.
- The retro dance.
- Let's see it.
- Her retro dance is a must-see.
It's fascinating.
It's a must-see.
It's my first time seeing it.
Please play some music.
It will be fun.
Let's see it.
(She is shy for a second.)
She is moving to the rhythm.
- The music is perfect.
- It's old-fashioned.
(The old-fashioned beat...)
(makes her transform
in 180 degrees!)
(This is the retro dance!)
Her facial expression is perfect.
(Retro dance)
Yes!
Seul Ki.
- Seul Ki.
- She is good.
- Let's go.
- Seul Ki.
- Here it comes.
Here it comes.
- Seul Ki.
- She hasn't changed at all.
Here it comes.
- One, two, three.
- Here it comes.
(Here comes the retro woman.)
Seul Ki.
- That's how the dance goes.
- It's nice.
(The retro queen's hands and feet
move in a fancy way.)
She still has it.
(The legendary retro dancer
still has it.)
Seul Ki still has it.
- That was incredible.
- She hasn't changed at all.
Seul Ki still has it.
- I liked her facial expression.
- Seul Ki.
That brought back memories.
- That was great.
- You are so cool.
- I am going insane, Seul Ki.
- It's a little hot in here.
- Did it relieve your stress?
It really did.
There isn't a place
you can dance without worry.
I know.
I felt like I was watching
an old clip.
- Seriously.
- Yes.
You don't look like your old self.
Eunhyuk.
Eunhyuk, hang in there.
Eunhyuk, it means he likes you.
- Hang in there.
- Eunhyuk.
- Now, you are...
- Hold on.
- Suppress your anger.
- Your face improved a lot.
Show us what you can do.
You are the dancing machine.
- Just how bad did I look before?
- Dance as you did in the past.
Eunhyuk, please dance
to "Sorry, Sorry."
- "Sorry, Sorry?"
- Yes.
Yes. Eunhyuk, please dance
to "Sorry, Sorry."
That song came out
when I was 24 years old.
He is still at the age
to work actively.
(The politest dance in the world)
Let's go.
(Sorry, sorry)
Look at her.
(She dances with her injured body.)
- Don't do that.
- Don't move your legs.
(His elementary school alumna
dances in the corner.)
There you go.
- He looks cool.
- There you go.
(This is the secret
of winning the popularity vote.)
- He is different.
- There you go.
He rubbed his hands well.
- It has been a while.
- You did well.
- He did well.
- Eunhyuk is cool.
(Oh.)
- What is it?
I am curious, that's all.
He looks so much better now.
(He attacks with compliments.)
Isn't that right?
- Eunhyuk, it's a compliment.
- Yes?
- I know it's a compliment,
- That's right.
but he said it too many times.
- He is looking after you.
- That's right.
- Don't misunderstand.
- All right.
- So Min loved it too.
- She loved it too.
So Min, you...
No. Suppress yourself.
- Don't dance.
- Suppress yourself.
- That was insane.
- It's so good to see them.
(The 3 guests brought back
memories of the past.)
All of them are our age.
With the five members who were born
in the year of the tiger,
We will have The Myth of Dangun
in the Year of the Black Tiger Race.
The three guests who were born
in the year of the tiger...
as well as Se Chan and So Min
will be tigers...
and the rest of the members
will be bears for the race.
We are bears.
It's an individual event
between ten members,
so make sure to collect
as many garlic cloves as possible.
The top 3 will get a present
and the bottom 3 will get a penalty.
But each mission will be a match
between the couples.
A tiger and a bear
will be partners for the mission.
Your ranking will determine
how many garlic cloves you receive.
But among 5 tigers and 5 bears...
are two poachers in disguise.
Poachers?
(Among 5 tigers and 5 bears
are 2 poachers in disguise.)
(Poachers?)
- Is there one among bears too?
- Yes.
There is 1 among bears
and 1 among tigers.
Come on.
When did they notify the poachers?
If a poacher and an animal
are partners,
half of the garlic cloves
the animal earns...
will automatically go
to the poacher.
So the poacher will take
half of the partner's garlic cloves.
So it will be bad for you
if your partner is a poacher.
(Staring)
Those who place 1st and 2nd
in a mission...
can check someone's identity
and switch their partners.
Gosh, this is annoying.
What is it?
- Is it Haha?
- Did you get caught?
Did you get caught?
- Is it me?
- What?
- For goodness' sake.
- I was just looking.
- Jong Kook will tell us soon,
- Do we know who the poachers are?
so we just need to wait.
Jong Kook, who do you think
are the poachers?
I was just looking.
- This must be Kim Jong Kook Game.
- I was just looking.
We haven't picked the poachers yet.
- Really?
- You haven't picked them yet?
- I felt so victimized.
- Come on.
I was just looking.
Did you see the way he looked at me?
It was almost game over for you.
- Seriously.
- He behaved naturally.
- The poachers weren't decided.
- I didn't say anything.
I didn't say anything.
Nothing was out of the ordinary.
I thought the poachers were decided.
Once the race ends,
you will arrest the poachers.
I see. Okay.
If you figure out who they are,
you shouldn't tell the others
to give yourself an upper hand.
All right.
It's time to decide on your partner.
One at a time, the tigers will sit.
- Then all five bears will go up.
- Really?
If it's your favorite tiger's turn,
lower the rope and the basket.
- The tiger...
- I see.
will cut the ropes
he or she doesn't like...
and put a plushie in the basket
of his or her choice.
So it's random.
The rotten rope.
- So you don't know who it will be.
- The rotten rope.
You shouldn't look up
when you are sitting down.
Okay. Let's go.
Bears will go up.
Let's go.
All right.
The first tiger is So Min.
Eunhyuk and Se Chan's faces
shine differently.
- What?
- Your face looks like cement.
For goodness' sake.
Eunhyuk's face glows.
- I went to the salon too.
- It glows. Look at Eunhyuk.
He takes care of himself.
Eunhyuk, this is a treatment
you haven't received before, right?
- Eunhyuk, hang in there.
- What is up with him?
- This is only the beginning.
- He is messing with my mind.
- Hang in there.
Brace yourself.
Eunhyuk looks different today.
He looks cool since he came alone.
You are driving me crazy.
I can't believe you.
- So Min.
- You are driving me crazy.
You should focus on getting better.
All right. If you like the tiger,
lower the basket
without making a sound.
No one is making preparations.
- So Min.
- No one is holding the basket.
No one is turning around.
Why is one toe so long?
- Her toe is like that.
- It's really long.
It looks like a finger.
If any bears in the back...
want to partner up with So Min,
lower the basket.
You can't look up.
I will put the plushie inside...
- right away.
- Still...
My goodness.
Isn't it too early to do that?
- I...
- What?
Are you serious?
I will put the plushie inside
right away.
Please lower the baskets quietly.
They changed spots too.
I will put the plushie inside
right away.
- The baskets are coming down.
- Someone is looking...
- without doing anything.
- All the baskets are coming down.
(Pulling)
Who is it?
Did the baskets come down?
They are mischievous.
(They pull up the baskets
so that she can't catch one.)
All right.
It will be bad if you get caught.
- Be careful.
- It will be bad if you get caught.
- I will give you ten seconds.
- Be careful.
(Putting)
She put it inside.
- What?
- It will be bad if you get caught.
- I will give you ten seconds.
- Be careful.
She put it inside.
(What?)
I told you that
it will be bad if you get caught.
Jae Suk and So Min are partners.
Come on.
It's set.
- That's incredible.
- Good job.
I didn't mean to do that.
- Congratulations.
- She is so fast.
She is fast.
- So Min.
- She has quick hands.
How are you so fast?
(The tiger with a fracture is happy
that she caught a bear.)
It's set.
- Thank goodness.
- That was fast.
- Hey.
It was my first time
pulling a prank.
(Eunhyuk is the next one
to choose a partner.)
- He is happy.
- Eunhyuk, look up.
Look up.
Congratulations.
(Eunhyuk and Jong Kook
become partners.)
Is this for real?
It's for real.
(Suk Jin and Seul Ki)
(Ji Hyo and Soo Ah)
(Haha and Se Chan)
Now, you will have a random draw
to choose your identity.
Please don't let me be a poacher.
- You never know.
- Please don't let me be a poacher.
It's like the Mafia Game.
- That's right.
- The Mafia Game.
You look for the mafia members.
All right.
Choose one of the tiger cards
to decide on your identity.
- Will it last all day long?
- That's right.
Please.
(Once a poacher, always a poacher.)
(They check their identities.)
(Eunhyuk is relaxed.)
Out of these three?
(He gets a poacher card!)
Hang on. Wait a second.
Eunhyuk.
Wait a second.
My heart is beating fast already.
(He takes a big breath
and walks toward the door.)
Wait a second.
(He turns back.)
(Eunhyuk partnered up
with Jong Kook too.)
I won't be able to keep it a secret.
(The tiger poacher
has his work cut out for him.)
What?
(Will he be able to overcome
the difficult situation?)
Hang on. Wait a second.
(Poacher wearing
Tiger's mask, Eunhyuk)
(With 18 years of experience
on TV shows,)
(he needs to fool
the members of Running Man.)
(No, I'm not!)
(He pretends to be a tiger
and starts hunting.)
(However,)
(there's one more poacher
hiding in here.)
(It's me.)
(I know who it is.)
(Take off the mask of an animal...)
(and stimulate
the instinct of the poacher.)
(Protect the garlic...)
(with human intelligence
and patience.)
- Don't open it.
- It's Jong Kook.
(Who's the protagonist
of the Myth of Dangun?)
(The Myth of Dangun
in the Year of the Black Tiger 2)