Oh, there you were.
- My goodness.
That's ridiculous.
Jun Hwan. Ji Hee. How do you feel?
Is it less awkward now
compared to the opening?
- Yes.
- We switched our numbers.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Who asked first?
- I did.
Oh, you did?
I promised to treat him.
Right.
We've been filming all day today.
Who do you feel most comfortable with?
- Stop it.
- Seriously.
Jun Hwan. Was there anything
that surprised you?
- Well...
- You can be honest.
- What surprised me?
- Yes.
(Glancing)
If you felt closer or anything.
What about Suk Jin?
- It's not me, is it?
- You can say it.
I love you.
In the end.
- You think I wouldn't love you?
- They have a strong bond.
(You think I wouldn't love you?)
They have a strong bond.
(Suk Jin's pretentious statement
gives them goosebumps.)
- You think I wouldn't...
- That's so pretentious.
"You think I wouldn't love you?"
- Wouldn't you?
- My goodness.
- Why did you run away?
- That was so pretentious.
That was his best.
- Do you want to switch?
- No thanks.
- Hey.
- That's your seat.
I said it on behalf of the whole nation.
On behalf of who? Why did you
say that on behalf of the nation?
I said it on behalf of men my age.
- He's pretentious.
- Do your best.
Ji Hee. Compared to your first time
on Running Man,
which is better?
- Do you feel better?
- The second time is way better.
- Right?
- Yes.
We became very close today.
Yes. He was the most reliable person.
- Haha?
- Yes.
- He'll betray you. Be careful.
- Why Haha?
- I'd never do that.
- He always betrays.
- Never.
- His eyes look so earnest.
- I mean it.
- That's all fake.
- Really?
He's the best liar
among all Christians I know.
Don't say that.
He's the best liar.
- I can't tell from...
- Sit down.
Wait a minute. Jin Hee. Are you...
- It's Ji Hee.
- Ji Hee.
- Are you an only child?
- Yes.
She's an only child.
- What about you, Jun Hwan?
- I have a brother.
Does your brother figure skate too?
- Does he...
- No.
- Does he skate too?
- He's in a different field.
What does he do?
He just studies.
- He studies?
- He's a student.
How's your relationship with your brother?
We're close.
- Really?
Do you say you love him? Do you give hugs?
You tell your brother you love him?
No.
We never do that.
Between brothers?
- But...
- Say you love him?
Some brothers do that.
Jae Jung does that to his brother.
Jae Jung tells his brother he loves him.
Do you say that to Se Hyeong?
- Do you?
- Do you say that to Se Hyeong?
Are you crazy?
Even if someone pays me to do that,
I can never do it.
- Because he's shy.
- You don't say you love him?
Holding his hand? That's crazy.
That's totally crazy. No way.
Jae Suk. Do you tell your sister
you love her?
Are you crazy?
- You don't?
- Never.
- You should try.
Do you tell your brother you love him?
No. That's crazy.
Never.
- Do you say that to your sister?
- I say it often.
- You tell her that you love her?
- I tell her I love her.
- What's wrong with him?
- Even just now.
- What about you, So Min?
- To your brother.
Are you crazy? Never.
- Really?
- I heard her...
cursing at her brother.
Do you say it?
I do.
- I've heard it.
- You do?
- I do.
- What about your brother?
He's like, "Are you crazy?"
Really?
Parents have to tell their children
they love them often.
- To make their children say it.
- Really?
- But how come you don't say it?
- What?
(How come you don't say it to your son?)
I will. I will start saying it soon.
(I will. I will start saying it soon.)
(He's annoyed by the truth.)
We still have lots of time together.
- What's wrong with you?
- Why are you upset?
We still have lots of time left.
What's wrong with you?
Why do you tell others to do it
when you don't?
Because...
- Suk Jin.
- What?
You also have a brother.
- I do.
- Do you?
- Do you call your brother brother?
- Do you say you love him?
(Do you call your brother brother?)
Of course I call him brother.
What else should he call him?
- I can't call him mister.
- He should call him brother.
- I mean, if you love him.
- Why do you get confused?
I mean, do you tell him you love him?
I never had a chance to.
- See?
- I can never do that.
I can't even say it to my younger brother.
I never knew he had a brother.
- I had no idea.
- You too?
Yes. He never talks about himself.
You never asked.
Otherwise, why would I talk about him?
All I know about you is...
that you like Yang Jung A.
He still remembers it.
And that he'll graduate his marriage
at 60.
- Should I give you your mission?
- Yes.
From the 20s to the 50s,
the last mission will bring
all generations together.
It's Who Rang the Bell.
That sounds fun.
Each team will take turns.
This is the headquarters for Team Offense.
Team Defense will wait outside.
Team Defense has a minute...
to hide anywhere outside.
After the minute,
someone from Team Defense...
will ring the doorbell and hide.
After ten seconds,
the tagger from Team Offense will
go out to find them.
At that moment,
the rest of Team Offense...
will put on the eyepatches
and stay in here like zombies.
And Team Defense outside will
put on a bell.
Oh, my.
That's right.
The rule is simple.
If you touch the doll before the tagger,
you win the point.
- We played it before.
- Yes.
On the other hand, the tagger...
Let's say the tagger saw
Ji Hee over there.
He should say Jin Ji Hee
and touch the doll.
Then Ji Hee is out.
Right. We played it before.
- It's advantageous for the tagger.
- Yes.
If you hide to the end, you get a point.
If you touch the doll first,
you get three points.
- Touching the doll is better.
- Yes.
- Yes. Touching it is better.
- Though it's dangerous.
But if you don't feel confident,
you can stay hidden.
Either touch the doll
before you get caught...
or hurry up and touch the doll
if you get caught.
- Can we fight?
- Yes, of course.
- Can we go hide?
- We have to hide.
I have bells for those who are hiding.
And I'll give you a radio each.
That's very loud.
- Yes.
- You can talk to each other.
Hey. Se Chan. Do you hear me?
- Do we go out?
- Yes.
I'm not good at hiding.
Do you think it's better to get
a point each by hiding...
or get three points
by touching it like a thug?
We should touch it like a thug.
Let's go for three points.
- Three points?
- Yes, let's go for three points.
- Jun Hwan. Let's go.
- Yes.
Jun Hwan. You should press the bell
since you're fast.
We need to hide. Where should we hide?
I'll go hide.
Where should I go?
I'll go to the other side.
Suk Jin. This is our chance.
That Ji Hee is the tagger.
- Listen to Ji Hee's plan.
- You have a plan?
First, there are many doors.
So you should watch each door.
- This opens too.
- Two doors open.
So you should all stand by the door.
Jong Kook can watch the doll.
I should watch the doll
instead of the door?
What's better?
I think this is most important.
That's true, but if I guard the door,
they pretty much can't use that door.
Then you should guard the biggest door.
That's better.
You should take the big door over there.
Ji Hyo and I will take this door.
- So Min will watch the doll?
- So Min will watch the doll.
Right, So Min is... Wait, So Min?
(Wait, So Min?)
- So Min?
- What's wrong?
(So Min is Team Ji Hee's anxiety factor.)
- So Min will watch this?
- Yes.
So Min should...
Then Ji Hyo should watch here,
and So Min and I'll guard the door.
- Sure.
- Okay.
So Min. You should block it.
- Block it with the chair?
- Block it.
You should lie down here.
Lie down.
So Min. You can sit there. That's nice.
- Yes.
- You have the coolest role.
Then who watches this? Ji Hyo?
- I'm watching this.
- Then...
- you guard the door.
- Yes.
Okay.
I'll hide behind the water tank.
(Se Chan hides behind the water tank.)
This is perfect.
(Se Chan, Jun Hwan, Jae Suk, Suk Jin)
Se Chan. Are you hiding?
I'm behind the water tank.
Okay.
(Jun Hwan has to press the doorbell.)
(He spots a strong gatekeeper.)
I might run into this door.
(Sighing)
Where should I hide?
Help me.
I can hear everything.
(Jun Hwan has to press the doorbell
and hide in 10 seconds.)
I can hear it.
Okay. Got it.
You have to run really fast.
Are you sure your eyes are covered?
Somewhere close.
Jun Hwan. Did you press it?
(He rang the bell!)
(Jun Hwan starts running.)
He's running.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two. One.
Go.
- Do I go?
- He ran that way.
Are you outside?
Yes, I'm outside.
(Se Chan is standing guard.)
She's outside.
(Sharing Ji Hee's location through radio)
Is she outside?
If you see them, say their names out loud.
Okay.
Is everything okay over there?
Everything's okay.
(Referee Jeon is obviously spaced out.)
You can hear the bell.
They can't just sneak in.
(Se Chan)
She's leaving.
Why is this intimidating?
(But Jun Hwan couldn't hide himself.)
I don't think they're around here.
I see Ji Hee over there.
(He spots Ji Hee outside the window.)
I saw Ji Hee. She's coming this way.
(Team Defense noticed Ji Hee
coming toward them.)
Jae Suk. Where are you?
(Team Defense noticed Ji Hee
coming toward them.)
She's coming here.
(The scaredy-cats are getting nervous.)
She's going over there.
(Rushing)
(She heard a bell ringing.)
(Jae Suk who rushed out...)
(and Ji Hee who missed him by a whisker)
She's in.
(He dashes to the main building
after giving Ji Hee the slip.)
Someone's running here.
Someone's here.
Someone's here!
(Ji Hee doesn't hear
Jong Kook's signal...)
(and heads to the 2nd floor
of the next building.)
Where?
- He went to the right.
- He's here.
Ji Hee. He's here.
He went to the right.
Ji Hee. He's here. By the backdoor.
He's here!
He's here.
(Ji Hee senses something.)
(She spots Jae Suk.)
(She has to touch the doll
before Jae Suk does.)
I'm sorry. I run pretty fast.
He's right in front of me.
(Jae Suk gives up on the backdoor
and takes a detour.)
I can hear it by the backdoor.
Ji Hee isn't here.
(Meanwhile, Ji Hee came running to him.)
It's Jae Suk.
- I can hear the bell.
- It's Jae Suk.
He's running. Come and touch the bell.
- Who is it?
- The doll.
It's Jae Suk.
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk makes it in
through the side door.)
Guard the doll.
It's me, Ji Hyo.
- I can hear it.
- Touch the doll. Who is it?
- Who is it?
- The doll.
(Who will touch the doll first?)
(Running past So Min nonchalantly)
(All he has to overcome
is Ji Hyo's defense.)
- Guard the doll.
- Who is it?
Here.
- Hurry up.
- Here.
- I can hear it.
- Who is it?
(He manages to get through
tight security and earns 3 points.)
Jae Suk did it.
I did it.
- Who's that here?
- I did it.
Who is it?
- Jae Suk.
- I told you to guard the doll.
When did you get here?
What were you doing, So Min?
So Min!
- Jong Kook.
- What were you doing!
So Min!
I don't know. He sneaked in.
- What do you mean you don't know!
- Hey.
- I said I heard it.
- You have to tell us!
So Min! Pull yourself together!
How can you be a referee with that!
So Min! Seriously!
Do you think it's easy to be a referee?
- You can hear the bell!
- Focus!
Seriously!
I said...
- he was here.
- No more excuses.
(A defenseless gatekeeper
is only getting better...)
(at taking their nagging.)
They wouldn't go up there.
Suk Jin. Ji Hee.
She's going over there.
What just happened?
(Big Nose who's hiding
behind the curtain...)
Where do I go?
(and Jun Hwan who is still
wandering around)
I saw Jun Hwan running away.
(Ji Hee's camera)
(She spots someone hovering around.)
- If you see anyone, say the name.
- I can hear the bell.
I see Jun Hwan.
Do I say his name and touch the doll
while looking at him?
(Flustered Jun Hwan starts running
back to where he came from)
Not here? Where is she?
- Hurry up. Where?
- Cha Jun Hwan.
(Meanwhile,
Ji Hee easily touches the doll.)
(Cha Jun Hwan is out.)
Cha Jun Hwan is out.
Okay!
Good job.
What?
(Jun Hwan finally figured out
what happened.)
I can't believe it.
(Despondent)
(Proud)
Gosh. I'm tired.
I'm sure they're around here.
Who do we have left?
Suk Jin. I'll just hide here.
We need to get at least one point.
(The two of them
are scared of Ji Hee who is fast.)
Jun Hwan. Did you get caught?
Come toward So Min.
Come toward So Min and touch the doll.
Come where So Min is.
The door So Min is standing.
It's the window.
Even if the zombies touch you,
it means nothing.
Come where So Min is.
Someone's telling them
to come to where I am.
Someone's telling them...
to come where I'm standing.
Someone's telling them
to come to where I'm standing.
- She's upstairs.
- Everyone.
So Min. Pull yourself together.
Come through So Min's door quickly.
(He gives out his command
without faltering.)
He's telling them
to come through this door.
(The target is here.)
(Se Chan got Jae Suk's message.)
Come through So Min's door.
(Launching the operation)
(Meanwhile, at the main gate,
where it's guarded securely)
Team Pink.
(Meanwhile, at the main gate,
where it's guarded securely)
- This is bad.
- Who is it?
- Ji Hee.
- Oh, come in.
Where are they?
- I can't see.
- You shouldn't get too far.
Exactly.
(He infiltrates the building
after turning the corner.)
- You shouldn't get too far.
- Exactly.
You should look around.
- Wait.
- You shouldn't get too far.
(Ji Hee is suddenly running again?)
(She spots Se Chan.)
(She runs toward the doll
without a break.)
Wait. It's me, Ji Hee.
Se Chan!
He's in front of me.
(Se Chan takes a detour
and heads to So Min's door.)
(Will the operation be successful?)
What happened?
- Se Chan.
- He's in front of me.
- Yang Se Chan is out.
Se Chan. My gosh.
- Someone's coming.
- What happened?
Someone's coming.
- Ji Hee saw you.
- Suk Jin.
- We have Suk Jin left.
You have a minute left.
Did she see me?
If you came through So Min's door,
you would've been safe.
Let me tell you again.
It has to be So Min's door.
Is So Min an open door or what?
You must.
It's fun to run around.
(Youngblood who finds running fun)
Jae Suk. Did you get caught?
(On the other hand, there's old blood...)
Who got caught?
(who hasn't even taken a step
out of his post.)
(Suk Jin unexpectedly
became the last survivor.)
You have a minute left.
- What?
- You have a minute left.
Only a minute left?
Then I need to win a point.
I should go out.
I need to go.
(He's finally ready to face off.)
(Charging forward)
It's fun to run around.
(Ji Hee was just
running around innocently.)
(She runs into Suk Jin
as soon as she gets out.)
Suk Jin!
- Suk Jin!
- I hear the bell! It's the bell!
(Suk Jin's nowhere close to Ji Hee
who is a fast runner.)
- It's the bell.
- You can't go through that door.
Suk Jin!
You can't go through that door.
(Suk Jin is out.)
(The mid-aged man
arrived a little too late.)
It's over.
- It's over.
- This door doesn't count.
You could've used this door.
- I won.
- Okay.
You're very good.
You're good.
You'll switch now.
If we hide well, we might win.
- We don't have to touch it.
- Exactly.
- Go.
- I hear the bell.
Jun Hwan. You have to watch for Jong Kook.
- Kim Jong Kook!
- Okay. Come and touch it.
(Jong Kook was hiding
right in front of the door.)
(He gets eliminated right away.)
(Jun Hwan eliminates the tiger
as soon as the game starts.)
- Kim Jong Kook is out.
- Okay.
- We did it.
It's a deal.
Take this. I can't run anyway.
- So Min.
- So Min is out.
He's over there.
- Jin Ji Hee.
- Run.
Ji Hee. Run.
- Song Ji Hyo!
- No.
- Hurry up.
- Jin Ji Hee.
(He manages to eliminate everyone.)
- Everyone.
- Yes.
So...
Team Jun Hwan wins
by eliminating everyone.
Okay. We finally won.
- Well done.
- Here's 300 dollars, Captain Cha.
(Captain Cha gets 300 dollars.
Captain Jin gets 150 dollars.)
- Good job.
- And 150 dollars for Captain Jin.
Distribute it, please.
- We wouldn't place last.
- No.
We'd never place last.
Here are the revolt cards
for the rest of you.
We don't even need it.
What should I write?
This is the hardest time for the captains.
Ji Hee.
Just give me ten dollars. I mean it.
- I know.
- You know?
- You know me.
- Yes.
How many people get a penalty?
- Only one person gets the penalty.
- Okay.
But everyone aside the winner is
the candidate,
and we'll spin the roulette.
- Really?
- Right.
One space for 2nd place,
two spaces for 3rd place, and so on.
(They get spaces on the roulette
according to their ranking.)
They'll spin the roulette to pick one.
For your information, it's neck and neck.
- Really?
- We're all alike.
- I'm done.
- The members should...
hold only the envelope.
- Captain Jin will reveal it first.
- Okay.
Ta-da.
- How much do I get?
- One hundred dollars for Ji Hee.
Fifty dollars, four dollars,
twenty dollars.
Twenty dollars and twenty-one dollars.
Four dollars?
- Four dollars for Jong Kook.
- Four dollars?
Wait. How much does So Min get?
So Min didn't get the minimum amount.
I made a prediction.
(So Min rebelled against Ji Hee
when she wasn't in last place.)
You did a great job.
So Min chose to revolt
in that situation? I'm impressed.
So Min, you have ten dollars now.
Be honest with me.
Were any of you on my side?
I have too many enemies.
So Min, I was so excited
to have you on my team.
How many enemies do I have?
Captain Cha, please show us
your board now.
- One, two, three.
- Let's find out.
- How much?
- Captain Cha.
(This time, Captain Cha's decision
will be revealed.)
(Jun Hwan: 90 dollars, Jae Suk: 1 cent)
- Ninety dollars. One cent?
- Ninety dollars, one cent...
- Okay.
- One cent?
That's nice. He got one cent.
He gave me 110 dollars?
- Jun Hwan. Just one cent?
- One cent?
He gave Suk Jin 110 dollars?
It must be his strategy.
He thought Suk Jin might revolt.
Now, open your cards.
- Gosh, I didn't choose to revolt.
- I chose...
You just got one cent.
Me neither. I love you, Captain Cha.
(Se Chan got 99.99 dollars.)
(Big Nose who received 110 dollars
chose to revolt.)
I should've picked the revolt card. Gosh.
I'm impressed.
- That's impressive.
- Jun Hwan, you did a great job.
- Jun Hwan, you're so smart.
- Oh, he did it intentionally.
- We both succeeded.
- Yes.
- We caught the rebels.
- We pulled it off.
- I'll announce the final result.
- Okay.
The person in the first place
will be exempt from the penalty.
Starting with the 2nd place,
1 slot is added.
So the 9th place gets 8 slots.
- Eight slots for the ninth place?
- Yes.
That person will get the penalty.
- Please.
- I hope I'm in the top three.
- The winner is...
- The winner.
Is it Haha?
No way.
(Who could be the winner?)
- Se Chan.
- Yes!
- What?
- Jun Hwan, thank you so much.
- Really?
- Yes.
Thank you, Jun Hwan.
I thought it was Haha.
Jun Hwan, thank you so much.
- You got 272 dollars and 99 cents.
- That's amazing.
I don't think
I've ever placed first before.
The person who placed second is...
Ji Hee. And Jun Hwan placed third.
- Suk Jin placed fourth.
- Yes!
- Who is in last place?
- So Min.
It could've been me.
- So Min is so hilarious.
- While we're putting the letters...
- Suk Jin chose the penalty.
- Yes.
We've gone soft.
- Let's pick something harsh.
- Harsh?
Let's go with a harsh penalty.
- How about something stinging?
- Stinging?
Yes.
We can't make the guests do it.
You're right.
Then let's prepare
two different penalties.
One for the members
and the other for the guests.
It took us a long time to decide.
- Is it a bomb? Cream?
- Will you shoot something?
The penalty is to put wax strips
on your arms and take them off.
- What?
- Wax strips on both of your arms.
- That's good.
(It's stinging and harsh
just as Captain Ji requested.)
- On the arms?
- That's too harsh.
We can do it on the legs too, right?
- If you want, yes.
- Okay. Good.
If you wax your legs,
you'll have to wax your thighs too.
Exactly.
- The captains won't have to do it.
- I didn't get many slots.
- Pardon?
- You'll get a different penalty.
Oh, I see.
My name is on only a few slots.
- Two. And three.
- You see...
- It'd be nice if Ji Hee was picked.
- I got too many slots.
- Okay.
- Who will spin it?
- I'll do it.
- Ready.
(Ji Hee: 1, Jun Hwan: 2,
Suk Jin: 3, Haha: 4)
- Please save me.
- Now, spin the wheel.
Let's go!
(Jun Hwan spun it!)
(Who will get the penalty?)
- Here we go.
- Oh, my.
- It's slowing down.
It's okay. I'll just do it.
- Please.
- Oh, no.
(Ji Hyo: 5, Jong Kook: 6,
Jae Suk: 7, So Min: 8)
(The roulette slows down sharply
near Jae Suk, Haha, and So Min.)
- Please.
- Oh, no.
(Who will get the penalty?)
- No.
- Haha.
(Haha will get the penalty.)
(Disappointed)
But he...
Look at him.
(Haha with only 4 slots
beat So Min with 8 slots.)
- Monk Ha.
- I'm saved.
- Is it really Haha?
- It's hard to believe.
- So Min, congratulations.
- Thank you.
Wasn't Haha ranked high?
- I had a bad feeling about this.
- What are the odds?
We'll give the top two prizes.
- Ji Hee and Se Chan.
- Yes.
(The prize for the top 2 is
high-quality Korean beef.)
Okay.
Thank you.
- Shall I give you some?
- No, that's okay.
Haha will get the penalty now.
- Where do you want to do it?
- Okay.
(Haha will get the harsh, stinging
penalty recommended by Captain Ji.)
- Before that, Ji Hee and Jun Hwan,
- Right.
- please say a few words.
- Okay.
First of all, it was so nice
to see Jun Hwan after a long time.
I had so much fun today.
And I'll be back on the show later.
(Ji Hee, a leader like a big sister,
fell more deeply in Running Man.)
I, too, was excited to see Ji Hee
after a long time.
And I had so much fun
with Jae Suk, Suk Jin,
Se Chan, and So Min on my team.
- Thank you.
- Jun Hwan,
- we hope you get a good result...
- We're rooting for you.
- at the world championship.
- You can do it, Jun Hwan.
(The cast members received
good energy from Figure Prince too.)
- You can do it.
- It must be painful.
- I'm ready.
- You can do it.
- He looks like Krillin.
- Here we go.
Krillin?
(Child Monk Ha is ready to get waxed.)
Peel it off slowly. That'd hurt more.
(He screams and swears.)
- It must have hurt.
- It looked painful.
- Good job, everyone.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(We thank Ji Hee and Jun Hwan
for sharing their reunion with us.)
- Ji Hee, you did a great job.
- Thank you.
- We'll begin the shoot now.
- Yes.
Play the music. Go.
(Unlike the usual opening,)
(we begin on a stage
with dazzling lights.)
("Only One for Me" by BTOB)
(Ah, yeah)
(Shouting)
(You are the only one for me)
(Old man, please come this way.)
(They haven't sung this song
in a long time.)
- BTOB was supposed to come out.
- That's right.
- What a shame.
- Exactly.
- It's a shame.
- Please tell us how they're doing.
First of all, when we held
a fan event overseas...
to meet our fans in foreign countries,
- we always sang BTOB's song...
- True.
- as we began the event.
- "Only One for Me".
- We sang "Only One for Me"...
- Yes.
- at the beginning of the event.
- That's right.
(Despite the poor singing abilities
of some members...)
("Only One for Me" made them all
look like great singers.)
- We sang the song as we began.
- That's right.
- We planned to perform the song...
- Yes.
- with BTOB on our show.
- We were supposed to sing together.
- I was excited about it.
- For the past few weeks,
- I heard what BTOB said...
- Right.
- from some idols who knew BTOB.
- Yes.
"Why haven't they invited us
to their show..."
- "when they sang our song?"
- That's right.
- What a shame.
- Since BTOB made its comeback,
we decided to do a special episode
about BTOB.
- So we put on the same outfits...
- Exactly.
- that we wore in our concerts.
- That's right.
- And we rented this concert hall.
- But...
Unfortunately, this morning,
- one of the members of BTOB...
- That's right.
- tested positive for COVID-19.
- Right.
- I'm so sad.
- We're very disappointed too.
- Exactly.
- I'm so disappointed.
- They came to the entrance.
- Exactly.
- But they had to go back.
- What a shame.
- Look how sad So Min is.
- Right.
- She's all dressed up.
- I'm wearing a headband too.
- Exactly. I'm wearing earrings too.
- I thought she was crying.
Exactly. I can't
(I can't live without you)
(They sing the song again
as they're disappointed.)
- We're supposed to sing with them.
- What a shame.
We began the show with BTOB's song.
- Go, BTOB!
- Go, BTOB! "Only One for Me".
- We hope to see you guys soon.
- It's okay.
- Right. It's such a shame.
But the problem is...
Eat a lot of garlic.
- What should we do today?
- Eat a lot of garlic.
We're the ones who are in trouble.
What should we do today?
- What are we going to do?
- We planned something...
- to do with BTOB.
- What will we do today?
It was supposed to be a match
between Running Man and BTOB.
- A match?
- We prepared all sorts of games.
- I could've taught them a lesson.
- That's a shame.
- It would've been so fun.
- So...
We wanted to see the seven of you
working together to beat them.
But they wouldn't have been
able to beat us.
When we join our forces,
no one can beat us.
- No one can beat us.
- Of course.
- So you'll have to be divided.
- Let's do that.
- Then...
- Since it's the BTOB special...
- Yes.
- Many of us have blood type B.
- Oh, right.
- Me.
- Who else?
- I'm a type B too.
- Me too. You're a type B too?
- Right.
- All three of you are type B?
- Yes, we're all type B.
- Oh, really?
- You see...
- You're a type B?
Men with blood type B...
- are not popular with women.
- Men with blood type B...
- You're wrong.
- Men with blood type B are...
- popular with women.
- No, they're not popular.
- Women in their 20s like them.
- Oh, really?
- Because they're attractive.
- But it changes as they age.
- But you know, right?
- What?
It's pointless to talk about it.
- The blood type doesn't matter.
- True.
- If a man looks good...
- Men looking like us...
- Women would fall for him.
- They...
- They only care about the looks.
- Exactly.
- Your blood type doesn't matter.
- True.
- They don't care about it.
- They don't.
- They care about your looks.
- Why do both of them...
- have blood type B? How annoying.
- Just your looks.
Why? You look ugly too
because of your hair.
- I look ugly too?
- It doesn't matter.
Although the blood type personality
theory...
- is not absolutely accurate,
- Right.
there are a few traits I agree about
as a man with blood type B.
- I agree with Jae Suk.
- Is that so?
- Yes, there are a few things.
- All three of them are funny.
- There are some similarities.
- They say...
that people with blood type B
tend to be self-centered.
- That's not true.
- No, we're not.
- People with blood type A are...
- I heard...
- known to sulk easily.
- Come on.
- That's not true.
- His blood type is A.
- You're wrong about that.
- People with blood type A...
- They do sulk easily.
- Right?
But that's why types A and B are
compatible with each other.
- That's right.
- Type A...
- You mean, as a married couple?
- My wife is a type A.
- Is she?
- Kyung Eun is a type A too.
- Yes, she's a type A.
Jae Suk, Go Eun is a type A too.
- Really?
- Unbelievable.
- I got goosebumps. Unbelievable.
- Really? My goodness.
- I got goosebumps.
- Isn't your younger girlfriend...
who's in your house a type A?
(Isn't your younger girlfriend
who's in your house a type A?)
- Is she?
- You don't know?
- No.
- Ask her.
Anyway, we're type B, and...
What's your blood type?
- Ji Hyo, what's your blood type?
- What's Ji Hyo's blood type?
- I'm a type A.
- She's a type A.
- Oh, you're a type A?
- So Min, you're a type A too?
- No, I'm a type AB.
- Jong Kook is a type AB too.
- I'm a type AB.
- You're a type AB, Jong Kook?
(He used to think that he was a type A.)
- I turned out to be a type AB.
- Oh, I see. You're a type AB.
- Hold on. What was that?
- I think that's right.
- Are you belittling type AB?
- Why?
- My mom is a type AB. How dare you?
- My dad is a type AB too.
Are you speaking badly of my mom?
- My brother is a type AB too.
- Na Eun is a type AB too.
- You said she was a type A.
Oh, you're talking about Na Eun?
- Na Eun is a type AB too.
- You see...
- Jong Kook doesn't look like one.
- Those with blood type AB are nice.
Jong Kook looks like a type B.
- No. He's definitely a type AB.
- I thought I was a type A.
- No wonder...
- I found out that I was...
- a type AB 3 or 4 years ago.
- I found it weird...
that you didn't have a type A
personality. You're a type AB.
I knew it.
- I'm surprised that she's a type A.
- I'm a type A.
I thought you were a type O.
- I thought you were a type AB.
- You've known me for a long time.
- I thought she was a type O too.
- Right.
- She sulks easily, you know.
- She gets mad over what happened...
- She's a type A.
three years before all of a sudden.
- Who?
- Ji Hyo.
- When did I do that?
- That's...
- That's what a type AB does.
- That's you. You should know that.
- When did I do that?
Hold on a second.
- I said I was a type AB.
- Stop.
- Oh, gosh. He's scary.
- He really is.
- You three punks with blood type B.
- Okay.
- What's with those sleeves?
- He's a type AB.
- Are you going to do a mask dance?
- What do you mean?
- Anyway...
- Okay.
- BTOB couldn't make it here today.
- Right.
- Since many of us are type B...
- That's a good idea.
- How should we be divided?
- Into 3 teams of 2, 2, and 3?
- We'll be divided into three teams.
- I have a better idea.
The 3 of you team up together,
and the 4 of us will team up.
- That sounds good.
- One should play on both teams.
- Right.
- Then one of the female members...
- It should be a type AB.
- Yes, playing on both teams.
So Min often participates in games
as a referee anyway.
- You can move between the teams.
- Right.
- Exactly.
- So Min can be the referee.
- You can be the referee.
- She can move between the teams.
So Min, since you're a type AB,
- move between the two teams.
- Great.
- Between type A and type B.
- You should do that.
- But he's a type AB too.
- He should stay on that team.
- Be the referee at the same time.
- You have both type A and B traits.
- Listen.
- You know a lot about this.
Hey, you're playing a huge role today.
But... I used to like
being in a position like this.
- This is So Min's special.
- But now...
You're amazing.
It makes me look like I have
a weak presence. Pardon?
- Weren't you a weak link last week?
- Exactly.
- Suk Jin was a weak link too.
- But I...
Be a kkakdugi as in "weak link", and
sell kkakdugi as in "radish kimchi".
- It's not like that.
- So Min's kkadugi. Sounds good.
- I want a sense of belonging.
- You know, So Min might...
- A few months later,
- Yes.
she might actually sell kkakdugi
on a home shopping network.
- That would suit her.
- Wouldn't that be great?
(The premium quality kkakdugi
made by the human kkakdugi)
(It sounds like a good career plan.)
- It sounds great, right?
- Jeon So Min's kkakdugi.
- Jeon So Min's...
- Referee Kkakdugi.
- It's all about your image.
- Absolutely.
- That's right.
- So Min is also a great dancer.
- Indeed.
- Show us your dance.
- Kkakdugi
- Jae Suk, you should say,
- That's great.
- "Check out Locust too."
- Locust.
(Buy So Min's kkakdugi,
and get free Locust.)
We're going hunting for kkakdugi
- She plays along with every joke.
- Here we go
(So she became the only
kkakdugi artisan in showbiz.)
- Did you see her face?
- Exactly. She's so hilarious.
Then it will be a match
between type B and the rest.
- Okay.
- We'll begin the race now.
- "Type B and the rest"?
- Yes.
- What's that?
- "Type B and the rest"?
- That's not cool.
- Hold on.
- The BTOB special...
- It was supposed to be...
- BTOB must be upset.
- It's just...
- Just let it go.
- We're the stars of the show today.
It was going to be a 7-on-7 match,
so we had to change...
- the rules of the games.
- Yes.
- It's type B versus the rest.
- Got it.
You'll play games that are suitable...
- for the teams of 3 and 4 members.
- Type B versus the rest.
According to the game results,
- you'll receive penalty balls.
- Yes.
The team that's chosen at the end
will get a penalty.
- Understood.
- The whole team?
- What about me? I'm a weak link.
- Right. What about So Min?
- You'll choose one team at the end.
- The team you want to stay on.
If your team is picked after that,
you'll get a penalty.
- Oh, I see.
- You can choose. It's a good thing.
But what if no one wants me on their team?
- It's up to you.
- You'll be the one to choose.
- That wouldn't happen.
- You'll get to choose any team.
- We can't reject you.
- Exactly.
So Min, please choose the first team
before changing your clothes.
- For the first mission.
- You won't tell me about the game?
- Can't I decide after that?
- She won't get the information?
- No, she won't.
- So Min.
- We'll do it without you this time.
- For now...
- Right. We'll see how it goes.
- Hey.
- We're all type B.
- I knew it.
- I knew they'd say that.
- That's enough.
- In this round...
- You can join them if you want.
- Start with that team.
- So Min.
- You don't want to get a penalty.
- Right.
- So Min, for now...
- Try to change them.
- Blood type B...
- This is the BTOB special.
Only my mom is a type B in my family.
My dad and my little brother are
both type AB.
Therefore, I'm more like a type B.
- Good.
- I choose this team.
- Okay.
(So Min chose Team Type B.)
- In the first mission,
- you'll be divided like this.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Please change your clothes now.
- Okay. Let's go.
(Which of the 2 teams will win?)
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
What's this? I see something huge.
What could that be for?
- Oh, my. What's this?
- The streetlight is so pretty.
- It's really pretty.
- Indeed.
What's that image at the back?
Like some sort of background.
(The crazy So Min starts dancing
on the streetlight.)
What is this?
What are we going to do with this?
- I guess this is a wooden bench.
- What's this?
- Is this for hitting someone?
- I think...
- Isn't this place too big for us?
- I don't think...
- we need a place this big.
- It's too big.
- Right?
- Indeed.
Gather around, my team members.
- Right, she was on our team.
- Come.
People with blood type B don't
act up like that.
- You can take off your mask now.
- People with blood type B...
- don't act up.
- Oh, I forgot.
Let's do this.
Hey, don't be mean to her.
She has a different blood type.
What are your parents' blood types?
- You can move between the teams.
- Your parents.
But don't stay on this team...
- I'm the only one you can rely on.
- That's true.
Ji Hyo is the only one I can rely on
from that team.
Exactly. Ji Hyo is the only one
you can rely on.
- You can rely on me too.
- We care so much about you.
- That's right.
- Then why are you getting upset?
I'm just telling you
that you're wrong about that.
Hey, even Suk Jin doesn't say
anything either.
- He doesn't even care.
- I'll be nice to you. You'll see.
Isn't Suk Jin the captain?
- Exactly.
- You'll see.
- Suk Jin, aren't you the captain?
- Aren't you the captain?
- Exactly. He's the captain.
That doesn't matter to me.
- Of course, it matters.
- That's an outdated perspective.
- You see, Suk Jin...
- A good title can change a person.
- knows it instinctively.
- What do you mean?
He knows his position in the food
chain and how to survive.
He knows how to survive in a group.
He knows how to behave to survive.
- He sure does.
- The captain is at the end.
- He knows it.
- I just feel sorry for him.
Why does it matter...
- Only he's wearing a jacket.
- It doesn't matter to me.
- I didn't realize that.
- He's wearing a jacket.
- We'll begin the first mission.
- Yes.
Since all the members of BTOB are
very athletic...
- True. They must've worked out...
- Yes.
- very hard. They looked muscular.
- Lee Min Hyuk...
And they were so eager to beat you
as well.
- Exactly. I don't know why...
- So we...
- our guests are eager to beat us?
- But...
None of them were able to beat us.
- In fact, there's no one...
- They were no match for us.
- who would aim to beat Suk Jin.
- Exactly.
Suk Jin always acts so determined
and confident.
- No one can beat us.
- He speaks louder than any of us.
- He has so much to say.
- We'll accept anyone's challenge.
- Tell them to form a team of seven.
- The average...
Okay. Anyway, the first mission...
requires physical strength and agility.
It's Agonizing and Painful.
- I guess it'll be painful.
- We'll have to endure pain.
- The games we'll play today...
- I don't feel pain.
So Min, you're good at it, right?
The winning team will get
only three penalty balls.
- Yes.
- The losing team will get ten.
- Got it.
- I see.
Ten penalty balls.
In the first round, we'll give you
a sponge stick and flour.
You'll have a 1-on-1 match,
playing the rice barley game.
- You have to hit the opponent...
- Rice. Barley.
while saying "Rice" to get a point.
- You fail if he or she stops you.
- Okay.
Gosh, I would've had a chance
to smash the BTOB members' heads.
What a shame. He would've...
- smashed them to a pulp.
- You can say "Rice" five times.
The more you succeed in attacking,
the more points your team gets.
I understand.
Who will be the first player?
- Well... From our team...
- I'll go first.
- Okay.
- Then So Min will go first.
Suk Jin will be our first player.
Suk Jin should go first.
If it's Suk Jin...
How about So Min goes first
since it's Suk Jin?
Hey. My gosh. I can't believe her.
Hey, why would you...
It's just ridiculous...
how So Min thinks that she can beat me.
What makes you think that you can beat me?
You think you have a chance to win?
You think you can beat me, right?
It won't hurt.
Everyone on our team wanted to
compete with Suk Jin.
I wish I was out there.
- I wanted to compete with him.
- He's funny.
- Go ahead.
- Can we start now? A practice game?
- No. We should start right away.
- Start without a practice game.
There's no practice run in life.
I think you should take off your glasses.
- Ready.
- Don't hit the side.
- Say "Barley" or "Rice".
- "Barley."
- Is this the right position?
- Yes. Get set.
Go.
(Rice!)
- Rice.
- Gosh.
(What?)
- What's with you lately?
- Oh, man.
Seriously?
- Hey.
- Can you believe this?
- Hey, why...
- What's gotten into you?
- Why would she...
- Hey, So Min.
- I mean... Hey.
- That's not how you play this game.
- My gosh.
- You should've pretended first.
- It's not that.
- I'm sorry.
- I saw the madness in her eyes.
- It wasn't like that.
- She must have lost her mind.
- Exactly.
- You have madness inside you.
- I'm sorry.
- She drives me crazy.
- Watch me, So Min.
- Okay.
- Barley.
- Barley. Rice.
- Like this.
- I attacked him right away.
- You shouldn't just beat him up.
- You should pull it back.
- You were like this. "Rice!"
- I shouldn't skip that part?
- This is what you did.
- I'm sorry.
- Just wait and see.
- You shouldn't do it like that.
- I didn't hit you like that.
- Just wait and see.
- Suk Jin will get back at you.
- Right.
So Min, you can put less flour
on the stick.
- Oh, I see. Okay.
- That's too much.
The stick turned black
after a single blow.
- Here we go. Barley.
- Just do as you want.
- Like this?
- Yes, that's good.
- Barley.
- Good.
- Okay. Gosh.
(Flour falls off.)
- Barley.
- Oh, no.
- Good. That's how you should do it.
(Hitting repeatedly)
- She said, "Barley."
- Barley.
- Darn.
- He's upset.
- Right.
- Calm down.
- Why, Suk Jin?
- He's annoyed.
- His face is covered in flour.
- He got annoyed.
- Sit down now.
- It's just a game. What's wrong?
- He got upset.
- I'm so annoyed.
- It's just a game, Suk Jin.
- Why did you hit me so hard?
- Barley.
Barley.
(But Suk Jin keeps getting floured.)
Suk Jin, you should let it go
right after you grab it.
- Let it go right away.
- You should spread your arms.
- Barley.
- Good.
So Min, you shouldn't hit him like that.
- Barley.
- Hey, stop it.
You shouldn't hit him like that.
Barley!
- Wait.
- What's with you today?
- So Min.
- What's up with you?
- What's wrong with you today?
- Okay, I get it.
- There is madness in her eyes.
- Without a warning...
Rice!
- There is madness in her eyes.
- Without a warning...
Rice!
I won, right?
- I won.
- What are you doing?
- He has to be seated.
- Right.
You know what? Just consider I lost.
You did it five times, so take a seat.
Why?
Suk Jin...
- Can't you do it with a smile?
- At least put on a smile.
Suk Jin, come on.
(Laughing)
How is she supposed
to take this as a game?
- You did great though.
- Okay.
Suk Jin is on the offense next.
How many times must one take it?
- She's good at this.
- Seok Sam's with us today.
- He's Seok Sam today.
- Okay.
You know I respect you, right?
- Well...
- It doesn't mean anything.
It's only a game.
- This won't be a controversy.
- Can't the weak link...
change who she's up against?
- No.
- Don't I get that advantage?
- Here.
- Your hands shouldn't touch.
- Not like that.
- Keep your arms wide.
- Like this.
- At least this far apart.
- About this wide.
- Like this.
- Rice!
- What?
- She caught it.
(His blitz attack didn't work.)
- How slow of you.
- How did she grab it?
- How?
- That was very slow.
- That was slow.
- You...
- So Min, focus.
- So Min...
Barley. She's good at grabbing it.
So Min, you're doing great.
You look so cool right now.
Rice!
(His second attempt was a success.)
- Okay.
- Keep going.
- I can't see a thing.
- Right?
Bar...
Barley.
You can't block with your hands like that.
Keep your arms apart.
- That's right.
- Your arms should be that wide.
- There you go.
- Barley.
- Rice!
- Yes!
- It was right in the middle.
- Must you hit that hard?
- You smacked her on the head.
- That wasn't nice.
- I got invested in the game.
- You did it twice.
Are you all right?
Of course. The two weakest links
shouldn't be this way.
Exactly.
You're both the weak links among us.
They make quite the rivals, don't they?
You have one more attempt left.
Barley.
Nicely done. That was great.
- Barley.
- That gaze is perfect.
Barley.
(He keeps baiting her with barley.)
Rice.
(She's humiliated.)
Are you all right? I'm sorry about that.
That was mean of you.
(So Min was played by
the annoying Seok Sam again.)
- But...
- That was hilarious.
- That was mean of you.
- Wasn't it fun?
- You scored four points.
- Four points?
- Nice!
- All right.
- Suk Jin's loving it.
- Next up...
is Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook?
- Then...
I'll handle him.
Jae Suk...
- Then I'll...
- Okay.
He knows it should be him.
- I'll show you.
- Sure.
- If you think about it...
- Go, Jae Suk.
- Will you go first?
- No, you can go first.
- No, go first.
- You can go first.
- No, you go first.
- Gosh.
- He's being considerate.
- Sure, go first.
- Okay.
Bring it on!
So Min.
What are you doing?
- This isn't a sticky rice cake.
- So Min.
- Seriously?
- What are you up to?
This isn't a rice cake.
- I'm trying to do my best.
- Who made you the master?
What are you doing?
It's all in the hands, Jong Kook.
Don't be ridiculous.
"Su" means hands and "ta" means to hit.
- Here we go.
- Sure.
- Grab the blue part.
- Here we go.
(They bicker over
the placement of his hands.)
We're both men, aren't we?
- Don't cheat.
- It will hurt.
- If I hold it here...
- It won't hurt.
- What?
- Come on.
Where on the bat I hold
is not your concern.
Can I grab it anywhere I want as well?
What?
- Not his collar though.
- I see.
- All right.
- Our blood type is B.
- Let's do this.
- All right!
Show how unique our personalities can be.
(The two enemies go head to head.)
Go, Team Type B.
Go, Team Type B. You are the best.
Go, Team Type A.
Rice!
Show how unique you are.
- All right!
- Show how unique you are.
- What...
- Nice!
- Jae Suk.
- Don't be intimidated.
- Are you kidding me?
- Trick him with barley first.
- Got it.
- Barley.
- Good.
- Yes, have fun with him.
- Barley.
You're dominating this game.
Go, Team Type B.
He's trembling.
- Barley.
- He's trembling.
You can tell that he's nervous.
- Barley.
- Nice!
He's obviously nervous.
(He tricks Jong Kook.)
You're playing him nicely.
- He hasn't been able to attack you.
- Barley.
Nice.
- Rice!
- Yes!
(He lands his first attack!)
- Rice.
- No, don't.
- You got 1 out of 3.
- Only 1 out of 3.
- The second one didn't count.
- It did.
What are you talking about?
- You said rice.
- When?
- We heard you.
- Did I?
- You said it.
- Of course.
That didn't count though.
Barley.
- Rice!
- Jong Kook grabs it every time.
Why are you...
Don't say "rice" first.
Don't say "rice" first before hitting him.
There's no need to be nice.
- Keep it short.
- Is that how I did it?
- This is your last chance.
- Why are you afraid of the bat?
- How many did I get?
- Only one.
- You got one out of four.
- One out of four?
You need at least one more.
- Barley.
- You need this point.
Barley.
- You can tell when he'll say rice.
- Rice!
See what I mean?
(Jong Kook grabbed it again.)
- Seriously?
- Why are you so bad at this?
- Three barley, and one rice.
- You say barley twice...
or three times before going for the rice.
- Why are you so bad at this?
- Exactly.
You're terrible at this.
- Can I try it one more time?
- Jae Suk.
- Just let him smash you.
- Oh, no.
Why are you so bad at this?
Jae Suk's an idiot.
- Rice!
- An idiot.
Rice!
(The muscular warrior viciously warms up.)
Nice!
I love it. I love your gritty attitude.
- I won't cover it in flour.
- Let's do this.
No flour?
- Why won't you dip it in flour?
- You're scaring us.
I won't cover it in flour.
I'll keep it clean.
Where's the flour?
Why won't you dip it in the flour?
Jae Suk, he's more focused
on smacking you.
He wants to smack you around, that's all.
- You just need to grab it though.
- Of course.
All right.
Barley.
- Jae Suk's already scared.
- Barley.
- Open your eyes.
Watch out for the edge.
You might get injured
if you get hit by it.
- You get what I mean, right?
- Yes.
Look where it'll hit you.
- I'll scratch your face.
- He's nervous.
- Are you sure about this?
- What can I do?
Move a little forward.
You can tell that he's nervous.
- Get in a little closer. Good.
- He's intimidated.
Rice!
(Grunting)
- That...
- What?
- Is this allowed?
- Come in closer.
- Are you sure?
The bat has been ripped.
- Oh, no.
- What on earth?
Let's keep on playing. Bring it in closer.
Keep your hands lifted
and your eyes on the bat.
- You can grab it.
- Just don't close your eyes.
- He...
- He's about to cry.
- I feel bad for Jae Suk.
- He might cry.
Barley. Your swing shouldn't be big.
He's like a puppy.
No big swings.
He might cry.
Barley.
- Rice!
- He blocked it.
(One hit)
- Did he?
- Yes.
(Two hits)
Rice!
- There's static electricity.
- Are you okay?
(His hair is floating.)
There's static electricity.
- Are you okay?
- His hair.
- Look at his hair.
- Let's dip it in some flour.
It looks like it hurts.
- Please get him some flour.
- Why isn't there any flour?
- Right.
- Exactly.
- Why isn't there any flour?
- Dip it in some flour.
- Wait.
- Put some on your hair.
What's wrong with you?
Because there's none on here.
- I can't believe it.
- You got 3 out of 3.
- My gosh.
- What do you mean?
He missed one.
- I blocked one.
- No, I got it.
- You didn't.
- He blocked one.
- I blocked one.
- I really did.
- We'll say that he did.
- Sure. Let's say that.
"We'll say that he did?"
- I blocked it for sure.
- All right.
- Smile, will you?
- I feel bad for him.
- Poor Jae Suk.
- Barley.
It shakes too much.
Barley.
(Ah...)
- Barley.
- Jae Suk might cry.
- He's about to cry.
- Barley.
(You can tell that a defeat is imminent.)
Barley.
Rice!
(The game ends with him
getting a beating.)
(Mr. Static Electricity
couldn't even fight back.)
- Just sit down.
- Don't cry, Jae Suk.
- All right.
- Hold on.
- What did you think?
- I...
- How is this allowed?
- What do you mean?
- What?
Why do you look like you've been wronged?
You won four points.
- Sure.
- Nice.
- You did great.
- I know.
- It's all right.
- It's only a game.
That was only the preliminary game.
- It's time for the main event.
- Sure.
- Come on in.
- This is Round Two.
I see you came prepared
to entertain BTOB today.
You were going to milk
everything out of them.
I can't live without you
What's this?
- What's that?
- What's this?
- This looks like fun.
- I don't know what it is though.
- Those must burst open.
Gosh, look at that.
The 3.5m stick behind you
will be incorporated in this game.
When the stick is dropped,
you will try and burst the balloons.
You will stay on the ground
and reach up at the same time.
That's simple. It's not easy at all.
- It's not difficult.
- Sounds easy enough.
- We need to burst the balloons.
- Over here?
- It just needs to be dropped.
- That's right.
- Can you drop it for us?
- Let's see.
- Like this?
- Move forward, Haha.
Should I move forward?
Just look at where you need to be.
Sit below your designated balloons.
Here's the thing.
If you grab onto the stick too early,
the people behind you
could be out of range.
- Gosh.
- Exactly.
- Burst them at the same time.
- Sure.
(Their individual agility
and teamwork are crucial.)
- All right.
- Let's hold up our arms.
Please get ready.
- Wait.
- This is how it'll be.
- Gosh.
- That's terrifying.
- Do it once more.
Let me show you once more.
It'll be like this.
It'll fall exactly like this.
- Looks good.
- You can't...
- slow down the stick like that.
- I wasn't doing anything.
- Let me do it.
- We'll be watching.
No, we'll drop it for you.
You already put on your gear.
- I'll take it off then.
- What?
- Why...
- Are you speaking casually to me?
What do you mean?
You're younger than me, so I'm allowed to.
- Move.
- No, move.
Move!
Let me do it instead.
- Jong Kook allowed it.
- Go ahead.
Jae Suk, show us once more.
We'll try and get into position.
- Oh, no!
- It'll be like this.
- You're done practicing.
- This is doable.
- But...
- It's like an amusement park ride.
Don't worry.
It's like being at an amusement park.
Let me try that again.
- All right.
- You only get one chance.
- Got it.
So Min, if you grab it too early,
the stick won't reach them.
- You get that, right?
- Sure.
What principle is this?
- The principle of the lever.
- That is correct.
Why didn't the two of you answer?
Are you their teacher?
They are my students.
The principle of the lever?
- Your students?
- Yes, the principle of the lever.
I see they are on the same academic level.
- They are.
- Right.
You are pretty much on the same level.
You must have empty heads
as your students.
- All three of them?
- Yes.
- You want to have a quiz with us?
- Do you really want to?
Bring it on.
I can win against the three of you.
- Okay.
- All right. Here we go.
Let's go. Let's go for it.
- Let's start.
- Start.
- You only have one chance.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
In 1, 2, 3.
Three.
(How will the three empty heads'
challenge turn out?)
- All right! They got 2.
- They got 2.
(They got 2.)
- They got two.
- It's all right.
You missed that.
- It's okay. Let's get out of here.
- I slapped it right away.
You got two points.
- We're pretty good.
- We're good.
Type B is surely good.
- We should've burst all three.
- We can do it.
It was close though.
- Take a seat.
- All right.
Can you lower it a little?
- Okay, I will.
- Okay.
- Does it hurt?
- No.
- He can't feel the pain.
- Is it okay?
- It doesn't hurt.
- I bet it does.
I bet it hurts!
Are you sure you're okay?
It doesn't hurt.
(The man with a bamboo stick
is goofing around.)
I'm glad.
I'm glad it doesn't hurt.
I'm glad...
I'm glad you're okay.
- I am okay, but...
- Okay.
- He is annoyed.
- But you should know your limit.
Okay. You're okay, right?
I'm okay.
I tried it out for the sake of safety.
You only gave it a go.
- Yes, I did.
- Well done. You did well.
Try lowering it.
Watch. Try adjusting your position.
- Lower it.
- There you go.
- It's right here.
- Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3. Boom!
- Boom!
- Okay, I got it.
- Let's go for it.
You should lower it as is.
Of course. How else would I lower it?
Don't mess with it midways.
- So when I lower it...
- How far are you going back?
(Lowering backward)
- Hey.
- Sir.
Hey.
Are you shooting an arrow?
- What?
- Are you shooting an arrow?
An arrow?
What do you mean?
Your pose is extreme.
Are you going to cut us in half or what?
- It's because he doesn't get it.
- I'm sorry.
Type Bs can do only one thing at a time.
Gosh, seriously.
Every blood type
has its own characteristic.
Respect that.
Do you want to check
what your blood type is now?
What did you say?
What did he say?
- What did you say?
- What?
- I'll stop here.
- Stop. That's it.
- I'll start now.
- Okay.
- We got it. You can start.
- I'll start.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's start.
- Let's start. Grab it.
- I got it.
- Grab it.
- Grab it!
- I got it.
(What will be the result
of Team Type A and Type AB?)
- Okay!
- All right! We got it.
- Okay! They all burst.
- We got it, right?
- Three points!
- All right!
- Yes!
(They got 3 points
for bursting all 3 balloons.)
- You see?
- You practiced for too long.
They practiced for too long.
You let them.
- They rehearsed for an hour!
- You let them.
You enjoyed watching it.
Didn't they practice for too long?
- You let us!
- You let us practice!
- You let us practice...
- You let us!
because it was fun.
I was hit by the bamboo
several times because of you.
You still got another round.
- Let's start the next round.
- We still have more?
No, don't take off your helmets.
- We shouldn't?
- We're playing something else?
- What's that?
- It's long!
(Here comes a gigantic bamboo stick.)
Oh, my gosh.
- What's this?
- It's a longer stick.
- That's why they let us try it.
- It's longer.
So this is...
They wanted to make it longer.
It's scary though.
- It's thrilling though.
- It looks fun.
I'm actually scared.
Let's get to it right away.
This time, it'll be a 6m stick.
Originally, we were going to have
all six members try it,
but we'll have only three members.
- All 3 of us?
Since you're wearing the helmets,
let's start with you guys.
This isn't anything hard!
Why don't we give them
no time to practice?
We won't have practice this time.
They practiced too much.
Exactly.
(Exclaiming)
- They practiced too much.
- I know.
(Lifting)
- This is...
- There will be no practice.
- All right.
- Wait. Sir!
- You should figure it out yourself.
- We need to know where it drops.
You should figure it out yourself.
- Lower it for us. That's not fair.
- That can't happen.
- We'll do it just once.
- Yes, let's try it.
- Let's lower it.
- We need to get in our position.
We must get in our position.
It's about here.
- You should lower it more.
- Wait.
That's it. It's around here.
- That's it. It's around here.
- You should try it now.
- Let's start.
- Here we go.
- Okay.
You must say "start"
on the count of three.
- Start!
- In 1, 2, 3. Start!
- Wait, it's so scary.
- Start.
(Team Type A and Type AB burst
all 3 balloons in the previous round.)
(Will they be able
to burst all the balloons this time?)
(Screaming)
(Smashing with a bamboo stick)
Yes! Well done!
- Was it you?
- Were you hit? You burst them.
You popped two balloons.
- Suk Jin, well done.
- All right.
Actually, it doesn't hurt.
It doesn't hurt.
(It's Team Type B's turn.)
- Who's going to skip the turn?
- I will.
- Gosh, you.
- I'll skip my turn.
- You should let So Min sit out.
- Have So Min sit out.
- But So Min found it fun.
- So Min.
So Min. Thank you.
You should sit out since it hurts.
It hurts.
- What?
- You should sit out...
- because it hurts. No.
- But she likes it.
- You should sit out.
- What's with you?
- It's better if she sits out.
- Why are you worried about me?
So Min, you should do it.
- You should do it for her.
- Don't let her sit here.
Se Chan told me to sit out
because it'll hurt.
It'll hurt.
(Se Chan told me to sit out
because it'll hurt.)
(Smiling from ear to ear)
(Laughing)
My gosh.
(Team Type B's old guys are
enjoying their fresh love story.)
- To be honest...
- All right, then.
That must've been heart-fluttering
for you, So Min.
- Sir, don't meddle in.
- Why not?
I should put this on, right?
Then I'll sit in front.
I'll sit in front.
You should sit at the back.
(The little scaredy-cats volunteer
to sit in the front.)
I think the last seat is really scary.
It is. Let's have Jae Suk sit there.
That's the scariest seat.
Let's have them check their positions.
- We'll give you only one chance.
- Guys, don't worry.
- Give us a chance.
- We'll give you a chance.
Jae Suk, sit closely.
- Sit closely.
- Don't tell us what to do.
- Okay.
Here it goes. Watch carefully.
You should get one, at least.
- It's long.
- It's right here.
- You got it, right?
- Hey!
That's it.
(Grunting)
Hey!
- Jae Suk.
- That was a delay of game.
- Come on!
- Hey, Mr. Delay!
We're running out of time!
(Scared)
It's so scary.
- I guess it's impossible.
- That little...
This is it.
It doesn't hurt!
You can do it!
- Are you ready?
- You got this!
- We popped two.
- Wait.
- We'll start now.
- No! We need to practice.
No, you're done with it.
- We haven't checked our positions.
- Let Jae Suk get the feel of it...
since it's his first time.
- That's right?
- What?
Did you just drop honorifics?
- No!
- Okay.
Lower it.
- Here we go.
- You must watch it until the end.
Keep your eye on it.
(Swinging)
(Gosh, darn it.)
This is how it'll be like.
I even grabbed on it.
Hey, it's much faster in the real game.
Okay. Let's go for it!
- Brace yourselves.
- I have no fear!
- Type B has no fear!
- You can do it!
- You got this!
- Type B!
- Jae Suk, you shouldn't dodge.
- Let's go, Type AB!
- Come on! What are you on about?
- Don't dodge.
I'll lower it once you say, "start."
- In 1, 2, 3. Start!
Here we go!
- Here it goes.
- It'll fall on your heads.
It's going to hurt a lot.
(It's Team Type B's last chance.)
(Will they be able
to burst all the balloons?)
Don't avoid it.
- Okay!
- Okay! We got this.
What was that?
(Doing a big bow all of a sudden)
- What was that?
- Jae Suk!
- Why did you dodge?
- What was that, Jae Suk?
Gosh, you scaredy-cat.
- They got two as well.
- Seriously.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Gosh, you scaredy-cat.
He told us this earlier
because he was scared to get hit.
"I think it'd be fun
to control the bamboo stick."
"So Min, you should do it."
- He kept telling me to do it.
- It's so scary.
All right!
Team Type A and Type AB
wins with a score of 25 to 21.
(Team Type A and Type AB
wins with a score of 25 to 21.)
- You did well.
- Really?
Team Type A and Type AB
gets only three penalty balls.
And Team Type B gets ten penalty balls.
- All right.
- It doesn't sound bad.
You'll get ten penalty balls.
I won't be leaving.
I think it's only right
for you to join the other team.
- But I won't.
- All right.
- It's time to have lunch.
- Okay.
Today's lunch menu was prepared
by someone more important...
than Captain Ji.
You'll have delicious tteokbokki
and crunchy fried chicken...
that our client prepared for us.
- It sounds good.
- I love crunchy fried chicken.
I'd like to change my name
to Yoo Crunchy Fried.
It suits you.
- I'll change it to Habokki.
- I'll change mine to Jeon Chicken.
- Call me Yoo Crunchy Fried.
- I'm Yang Tteok.
You can call me Crunchy Fried.
Those who sit with Haha
can't have crunchy fried chicken.
- Why not?
- He's a model for another brand.
You should stay out during lunch.
- You should pack your meals.
- Why did you have to choose it?
Haha can choose two members
to have tteokbokki with.
It's Jae Suk for sure.
But I'm Yoo Crunchy Fried.
It'll be Jae Suk and Jong Kook.
Who? Me?
- You can't pick me.
- But I'm Yoo Crunchy Fried.
- Then...
- Jae Suk and Suk Jin...
But I'm Yoo Crunchy Fried.
- Let him have tteokbokki.
- It's because...
he went through a lot as a captain.
- I didn't do much though.
- I'll pick So Min and Se Chan then.
What? Why me?
I just wanted to have tteokbokki with you.
That's ridiculous!
- No, I don't want to.
- That's right.
They should get some quality time
while having tteokbokki.
- No, I don't want to.
- Let's have tteokbokki together.
- You should.
- Why should we?
- Why are you so conscious of them?
- This is great!
- He's so conscious of them.
- This is great.
- I...
- So Min...
Haha is indeed good with variety shows.
- With variety shows?
- You're great with variety shows!
- My gosh, it looks good.
- It's rose tteokbokki.
It's Fen Haozi noodles.
It's a type of glass noodle.
It looks good.
- It looks good.
- Enjoy your meal.
I haven't seen you for a while,
crunchy fried chicken.
Crunchy fried chicken!
Let's see how their
crunchy fried chicken tastes.
(Opening the box)
- It looks really good.
- It's seriously...
- Here.
- There are no bones.
- I love that there are no bones
- Thank you.
Gosh, it looks so good.
I love that there are no bones
The sauce is...
(They have a feast of crunchy
fried chicken and tteokbokki.)
The sauce is really good.
It tastes different.
It's so crunchy.
I really wish you two could start dating.
- What did you say?
- I wish they start dating.
- You can't just say that.
- It's not that.
- They look good together.
- Don't do that.
Why don't you try feeding a piece
to Ji Hyo?
Don't make them do something like that.
- Why would you make them do that?
- I just wanted to see them do it.
Should I punch you in the face?
Don't they look good together?
I think they look great!
Didn't you two send signals to him?
But I want to try
the crunchy fried chicken.
(But I want to eat crunchy fried chicken.)
Why don't you say something?
Describe the taste, will you?
It's their turn.
- What's this?
- Won't our part be aired?
No, we won't because
we're only having tteokbokki.
If I were to steal their attention,
you'll have to kiss each other.
(If I were to steal their attention,
you'll have to kiss each other.)
I would if this was a drama.
I would too,
- but I can't just do it.
- Let's say this is a drama.
I can't do it with him.
- Why not?
- Why don't you just turn his head?
No, I can't.
Just turn his head.
- We're friends, that's why.
- For the preview.
- I'm serious.
- Just turning his head.
Many of them told me that I kiss well.
(Grabbing)
What are you doing?
- He just told me to turn your head.
- Right. Just turn his head.
- I'm going this way?
- Yes.
You're kissing all of a sudden
while having tteokbokki.
- That guy...
- What?
You're so annoying.
Why do you want us to do it?
- What? Because...
- To steal the attention.
they're stealing the limelight.
Is this tteokbokki or udon?
Of course it's tteokbokki.
How many times do I have to tell you?
The crunchy fried chicken is really good.
It is.
- Crunchy fried chicken.
- I met Yi Kyung the other day,
Only the strong.
- Second syllable.
- Jeong Il Nam.
What was that?
It was an acrostic poem.
Who is Jeong Il Nam?
What? I have no idea.
- Gosh, it's spicy.
- Why did you say his name then?
That's how you do acrostic poems.
Doesn't he sound strong?
Right! Jeong Il Nam sounds strong.
It sounds like a name a bully would have.
(They all got on the bus
after their meal.)
Put your seatbelt on.
- You see our soccer team...
- The soccer team?
We moved the stadium to Yangjae-dong.
- Really?
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- There's only one member...
of your soccer team here.
I haven't been to the games lately though.
Why would you tell us...
- I'm just sharing...
- where the new stadium is?
Aren't we supposed to share
what's going on in our lives?
The director of our show
went to one of your games.
- I heard he was good.
- He's pretty good.
But what did Myung Jae say?
Did he mention about Jong Kook?
- Did Myung Jae...
- This is exactly...
what Myung Jae said about Jong Kook.
- What did he say?
Tell him to say it to my face.
Why would you speak on his behalf?
He didn't like to see Jong Kook
acting out, right?
- He mentioned two characteristics.
- What are they?
The first one is...
that the teammates are boisterous
when one of them makes mistakes,
but when Jong Kook does,
they suddenly grow quiet.
(They suddenly grow quiet
if Jong Kook makes a mistake.)
It's supposed to be a secret!
- That's for sure.
- It's a secret?
Yes, it is. It must be kept a secret.
A witty guy like him didn't know that.
- He's like a textbook.
- What else?
The second one...
is that...
when he runs out of energy
in the second half,
they suddenly have fights
against each other.
(They have a fight
when the second half begins.)
I like to have tussles,
so I tell them not to take it easy.
I tell them to have tussles...
and to focus on having tussles.
Does every ball go to Jong Kook?
- No, that's not the case.
- It's not?
Jong Kook is in a position
that doesn't score.
- He's a supporter?
- He's a striker who doesn't score.
- That's right.
- Is that so?
Maybe he can't score.
- I don't score on purpose.
- He doesn't score on purpose.
I pass the ball to the other player
at a critical moment.
He really does.
- That's what I do.
- There are...
many players who are in their early 20s.
They can't catch up with Jong Kook
in terms of stamina.
We went to play a game in the new stadium.
I saw someone with big ears
playing soccer.
It was CODE KUNST.
- CODE KUNST?
- Yes.
- What did you call him?
- I heard he's good.
It's CODE KUNST.
- It's CODE KUNST?
- Yes.
CODE KUNST is good at soccer.
No, he plays like an old man.
Like an old man?
He just slanders everyone else.
I compliment those who play well.
Then who is one player
that you approve of?
Patrice Evra.
- Patrice Evra?
- Park Ji Sung.
- Ji Sung.
- Patrice Evra and Park Ji Sung.
- Or Son Heung Min.
- Heung Min and Ji Sung...
are pretty good.
(He only approves
of world-class soccer players.)
They're approved
by people all around the world.
- Young Jae will come to play often.
- I know this place.
- It's the ophthalmic clinic...
- Which one?
- I often go to.
Me too.
No one asked you.
(No one asked you.)
(Suddenly spewing out an acronym)
- That's so childish.
- Right.
- No one asked him.
- No one wants to know.
No one wants to know
where your ophthalmic clinic is.
- No one wants to know.
- We don't care...
Do you even know what that means?
That no one asked you
and no one wants to know.
- That's not it.
- That's not what it means.
"No one wants to know."
Isn't that what it means?
- "No one wants to know."
- No, that's not what it means.
No one asked you and no one wants to know.
Then tell me what it means
in three seconds.
- One, two, three.
- Mul naengmyeon.
(Mul naengmyeon)
- They don't want to know.
- I don't want "mul naengmyeon."
It means I don't want "mul naengmyeon?"
Don't sit your butt down.
(I don't want mul naengmyeon
Don't sit your butt down.)
You guys have perfect teamwork.
It really means that.
What do you want as a gift
when you two get married?
Stop talking about that!
Can't I even talk about it?
- We already talked about this.
- Why do you keep mentioning it?
Do you want an 85in TV?
Don't promise things carelessly.
I can afford a TV myself.
- If you get married...
- What's wrong with you?
- A 99in TV is a bit expensive.
- Forget it.
I'm sorry but even if we do get married,
you shouldn't come.
- Why not?
- You don't want him to come?
- You're...
- Why not?
- That means you actually...
- Whatever!
(Whatever!)
- Whatever?
- Whatever. No one cares.
- Whatever!
I can't believe he's saying that.
- Gosh, this is...
- No one asked.
It's weird to hear him say such things.
- Whatever.
- It doesn't suit you at all.
It doesn't suit him.
- They say that a lot.
- Whatever.
Now that I'm older,
I realized that's what everyone feels.
- Whatever!
- "Whatever?"
- You can't say that.
- Whatever.
- Whatever. He's right.
- You can say that to everything.
- Whatever.
- But...
- I don't care what you say.
- You can say that to everything?
- Whatever.
- Whatever. Get your face away.
- That's not right, Suk Jin.
- Why not?
- You have to use the right words.
- Whatever, you punk.
- Hey.
- That's not right.
- He told me...
- So Min, that's not right.
- to get my face away.
- Still. It's not right.
- You must filter what you say.
- When you're in your 50's,
- What's wrong with you?
you'll be flustered by it.
Because you find it cute?
Who came up with that?
You don't know how it came to be, right?
- Whatever...
- I do.
It means, "Whatever, go watch TV."
- That's what it means.
- You didn't know?
- "Whatever, go watch TV."
- Whatever...
They're telling you to go watch TV.
It's like,
"Whatever, go watch Running Man."
Oh, "Whatever, go watch Running Man?"
- Yes.
- That's right.
- You didn't know the meaning?
- You know what NANC is?
- Of course.
- What does it mean?
- "I don't want mul naengmyeon."
("I don't want mul naengmyeon.")
"Don't sit your butt down."
You're right. You're pretty good.
"I don't want mul naengmyeon,
but you'll be curious about it."
You can make use of it.
- NANC.
- Please...
I hope someone uses this on another show.
- NANC.
- Of course I know what it is.
- "I don't want mul naengmyeon."
- I can learn whatever you tell me.
- Of course.
- I've been memorizing it.
- That's so cute.
- By the way,
- It's what young kids use.
- this thought occurred to me.
- What is it?
I wish Eun Hye...
was here with us.
Why you...
- Wouldn't it have been fun?
- That was so random.
It'd have been fun.
That's how thoughts occur.
You just throw your ideas.
On our YouTube channel...
- You just throw your ideas.
- Did you see it?
Eun Hye Special lasted for almost an hour.
- What do you mean?
- There's a collection of it.
- There's a collection on it.
- A collection of it?
- There's a special collection.
- And why would they do that?
I didn't do it. They did!
They made a collection of it.
Guys, you should check it out.
- Stop it. Why would they?
- There's a collection of it.
- By the way...
- Eun Hye, I'll call you!
Have you ever met Eun Hye, though?
Of course! We used to work together.
- Really? I bet you didn't.
- On which show?
It was a show called "Fort Boyard."
It's one that Nam Hee Suk
and Hyo Lee hosted.
- "Fort Boyard?"
- Eun Hye was on it?
- You were the host?
- You were the host of the show?
He was the grandpa
who was stuck in the castle.
- I see.
- No wonder.
- Hey!
- You were an extra?
(Suk Jin played a man living
in a steeple who gave quizzes.)
Actually, Hee Suk and Hyo Lee
were the main hosts.
- They were the main hosts.
- They were the two main hosts.
- Right.
- I was a man who gave out quizzes.
- A man who gave out quizzes.
- Like an extra?
How can you say that? Come on.
- Hey. He was Extra Ji.
- Hey!
Extra Ji?
- He was Extra Ji.
- Extra Ji?
It was such an important role.
Because they had to give you a role.
I was so happy with that role then.
- Back then.
- Right.
We shot the show on an island.
So I talked with Eun Hye...
Okay, that's enough.
What do you mean? It's only the beginning.
- Whatever!
- You can stop it now.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Whatever!
Eun Hye said that she liked Jae Suk.
When she said that, you said this.
- What?
- "I like Yang Jung A."
- Hey.
- Am I right?
- Aren't I right?
Yang Jung A might be shocked
when she hears this.
Jung A, I'm rooting for you!
He's such an oldie.
He made a heart like this.
- He made a heart like this.
- I can't live without you
(Shyly confessing his feelings as a fan)
Stop it. I'm always rooting for you.
He made a heart like this.
- She still looks the same.
- I'm your fan.
- By the way,
- Yes?
when can I switch my team?
You can switch your team now.
Which team would you like to join?
Why did you bring it up?
- Then she can...
- She can switch.
She should join the other team too.
- Right.
- Right. That way, it'll be fun.
Aren't you too lazy to get changed?
- Switch your team.
- I pick Team Type A and Type AB.
- Team Type A and Type AB?
- Yes.
- I want to give it a try.
- Go ahead.
- But her clothes...
- You didn't get a taste of Type B.
You should try out the other team too.
For your information,
So Min will be playing
a very important role.
- Okay.
- Really?
She switched to Team Type A and Type AB.
Are we playing a quiz?
Could it be a quiz?
- It must be a quiz.
- They won't let us...
- play foot volleyball, will they?
- Then she can be a referee.
We must be playing foot volleyball.
- We are playing foot volleyball.
- We are?
- We're playing foot volleyball.
- Nice!
- Someone pooped here.
- It's mud.
The ball won't bounce from here.
- I'll tell you the rules now.
- Okay.
The next mission...
is called Longing to Score.
You came up with a good name.
You'll be playing foot volleyball.
It's impossible for So Min to play...
- because she injured her leg.
- That's right.
Here's the role she'll play.
She will play a referee.
But...
- Why do I get to play a referee?
- She'll be a referee.
But it's not just an ordinary referee.
When your team scores,
(When your team scores)
you can raise two points by lying.
Come on.
(She can raise 2 points by lying.)
- However,
- You are the best.
if the other team catches her lying,
her team won't receive any points.
They can catch her lying.
If you make a mistake,
you will lose one point.
Okay.
We can catch her lying.
- So Min lies often.
- You might fail to score a point.
So they can catch her lying.
Do it when things are uncertain.
I won't raise the points
unless it's necessary.
- Okay.
- I won't do it if you are winning.
- Try not to do it.
- We planned to have a 4-on-4 match.
- Okay.
So each team must recruit...
one female staff member.
- What?
- But...
each team must recruit
one female staff member.
- What?
- But...
Seon Myung is really bad at it.
All the female staff members...
- are hopeless.
- Just don't give the ball to her.
Pick a staff member each.
Seon Myung, come here.
- Seon Myung, come here.
- Let's recruit Ji Yeon.
Seon Myung is hopeless.
- Seon Myung is hopeless.
- Ji Yeon is better. Ji Yeon.
- Join our team.
- Ji Yeon, have you done this?
- Ji Yeon.
- Seon Myung, come here.
- Look at Seon Myung.
It's better to recruit someone
who has done this before.
- Seon Myung, come here.
- Ji Yeon is better.
- She is better than Seon Myung.
- I think she is pretty good.
- Both are hopeless, but...
- Seon Myung, join our team.
Seon Myung, you are better.
- We will recruit Ji Yeon.
- Now,
you will change into uniform
and play foot volleyball.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Okay.
Come over here.
- My goodness.
- Weaklings.
- Hey.
- Stand over there.
I couldn't shorten the straps.
- They are adjustable.
- I couldn't shorten them.
Se Chan is good at it.
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
- I heard that you are good at it.
- He can't do it. He is on my team.
He is on my team.
Se Chan is really good at it.
You are a junior comedienne.
Shorten my straps.
"Comedienne?"
What did you say?
Forget it.
- Here.
- How do you shorten them?
I left them as they were
because they were too much work.
Here.
(Impressed)
Hey.
This is incredible.
Are you stupid? I mean...
It's easy.
None of us could do it.
Go ahead.
Suk Jin, this strap is a bit short.
This strap is a bit short.
It got caught.
Hey.
- It got caught.
- You should help Suk Jin properly.
- Pull it up like this.
- It's good enough.
Stop.
Stop. It's good enough.
- Let's shorten them more.
- Hey.
- Stop.
- So Min.
All right. Let's begin.
She came into power.
- She came into power.
- You can scatter the mud...
- on the opposing team's court.
- Okay.
You can scatter it to hinder their moves.
- Yes.
- Okay.
The mud will be effective
at the right spots.
- Here.
- We need to cheat.
Put some mud in the middle.
This spot is dry.
- There you go. That's good.
- That's good.
Let's put all of it in one spot.
Nice.
- All right.
- More.
Spread it out.
- It's neat.
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
- Why don't you poop here?
What are you talking about?
I was just joking.
- For goodness' sake.
- We wouldn't do it for real.
- I am serious.
- Stop pooping with your mouth.
Just give me three minutes. I can do it.
Don't be so stinky.
You can't poop on the court.
- I was just joking.
- Just give me three minutes.
Go to your position.
Let's begin.
Okay.
You will play a single round
for 15 points.
Okay. Give me the ball.
Let's begin. Let's attack.
Let's begin.
- Let's go.
Send the ball toward Seon Myung.
Seon Myung and Suk Jin
are the weak members.
- I need to cover for Seon Myung.
- Send it to Seon Myung.
All right. Let's begin.
(The game starts.)
- I need to cover for Seon Myung.
- Send it to Seon Myung.
- Do your best.
- Seon Myung.
- Okay.
That's it.
(She shows
her 1st slapstick comedy of 2022.)
Good job.
Good job, Seon Myung.
That was funny.
- That was sweet.
- Go ahead.
That was as sweet as honey.
- Give them a point.
- Seon Myung.
Give them a point.
- Go. Let's begin.
- Go.
Seon Myung.
- Okay.
- It's for Seon Myung.
Score a point.
- Mine.
- Kick it right away.
- Okay.
- Why did you send it so high?
I don't want to touch the ball
with my face.
- Send it over the net.
- Get ready.
- No, Suk Jin. Leave it be.
- Suk Jin.
(He hits a home run.)
I am sorry.
I am sorry. I thought I could do it.
About six people went,
- "Gosh."
- I am sorry.
- It won't matter if we win.
If they score a point,
So Min will give them two points.
- It's 2 to 0, right?
- Yes.
- It's out.
- Out.
- Raise the number.
- It's out.
So Min, we scored.
- Good job, So Min.
- Okay.
Good job.
(So Min can secretly raise
2 points as a referee.)
Jae Suk, wait.
- Will you object?
- We need to be careful.
- She won't do it from the start.
- Object if you want to.
(What will be Team Type B's choice?)
- We object.
- What?
- All right.
- Did she do it from the start?
- Referee Jeon...
- She would do it from the start.
I told So Min not to do it
if she can help it.
Referee Jeon...
changed the number honestly.
So this team will lose a point.
(Referee Jeon only raised 1 point!)
(Team Type B loses 1 point.)
- They don't know me.
- Good job, So Min.
They don't know me.
- Why did you object?
- You should have asked us.
- Ji Yeon, make sure you watch her.
- Good job.
He suddenly nags at Ji Yeon,
- "Make sure you watch her."
- Let's begin.
All right.
Hold on.
- You need to kick hard.
- Are your feet okay?
- Good.
- It's mine.
- Okay.
- Get it over the net.
- Come on.
- Good.
- I will kick it.
I will get it over the net.
Get it over the net.
- Okay.
- There you go.
(A dead ball shot)
- That's how you do it.
- Okay.
- Good job.
- Raise the score.
- So Min, there is no need.
- Did you raise the score?
- Raise the score.
- The score.
Seon Myung, you stood there well.
- Shall we object?
- No.
- Will you object?
- Let's give it a pass.
- Let's do that.
All right.
This time, Referee Jeon raised two points.
(Team Type B: 1 point,
Team Type A and Type AB: 3 points)
(She succeeded in coning them.)
All right.
- So Min.
- Good job, So Min.
That was terrific.
So Min, nice timing.
(Referee Jeon's poker face
is pretty good.)
We have an advantage.
(Haha serves.)
- A sky-high serve.
- Okay.
Okay.
(A mud shot)
You hit the spot perfectly.
It's a mud festival.
How did it land on the spot?
- I didn't think of that.
- It was the perfect shot.
There is no way around it.
Let's not lose a single point from now on.
- Seon Myung, go.
- Don't touch the ball.
- Leave it be.
- Seon Myung.
- Kick it.
- Okay.
- Seon Myung.
- Kick it.
- Okay.
- Seon Myung.
(Backheading)
(She attacked her own team with her head.)
You did well.
- Why won't you let her play?
- You did well.
- Seon Myung is so funny.
- Why won't you let her play?
Good job, Seon Myung.
Ji Yeon, you should serve.
- It's okay.
- Give it a try.
- Ji Yeon, serve.
Are you lowering yourself
to Seon Myung's level?
Ji Yeon, serve.
- Stand behind the line.
- Ji Yeon, serve.
(Her foot volleyball skills are
still a mystery.)
I am sure Ji Yeon is better.
What?
(A fiery shot)
What was that?
(Shaolin foot volleyball)
- What was that?
- That was incredible.
- Hold on.
- How did you do that?
- I don't know.
- Hey.
- How did you do that?
- What was that?
- How many times did she touch it?
There were two touches.
- Was it a fiery shot?
- Did I succeed?
- That was awesome.
- Really?
- Ji Yeon, do it again.
- Do it again.
- How did you do that?
- Teach us.
- You are so cool.
- Move to the back.
How did you do that?
- Hold on.
- You can kick gently.
You shouldn't go over the line.
It's in.
(A no-spin drop shot)
- That was cool.
- For real. How did you do that?
How did you do that?
(She plays the Shaolin foot volleyball.)
For real. How did you do that?
How did you do that?
- This is unfair.
- Do it again.
- What was that?
- Is she a secret weapon?
- Hey.
- Ji Yeon is good.
- It's okay. Try it again.
- Let's go.
- Try it again.
- Send it that way.
- Let's receive the ball.
Hold on.
- Send it that way.
- Let's receive the ball.
(She suddenly showed a knee kick.)
- Out.
- Okay. Give us the ball.
- Ji Yeon.
- You did well.
Raise the score.
- Let's go. What's the score?
- Will you object?
- Okay. Let's go.
- Hold on. Will you object?
- This time...
- Catch her.
- Let's catch her.
I don't think she did it this time.
We need to catch her.
- Catch her!
- We object.
Catch her!
We object.
She got caught.
Okay.
(Referee Jeon got caught
raising 2 points!)
- Zero points.
Team Type A and Type AB
won't receive any points.
So it's...
We should object every single time.
It only costs us one point.
- Let's go.
- Ji Yeon did so well.
- She did a superb job.
- It's okay.
- Ji Yeon.
- We can't head the ball.
- Here we go.
- You can do it.
- I will receive it.
- Ji Yeon, receive the ball.
- Mine.
- Ji Yeon, it's yours.
- Let Ji Yeon receive it.
- Ji Yeon.
- Ji Yeon, it's yours.
- There you go.
- Receive it.
- Seon Myung.
(You can go.)
- Gosh.
- We got this. Good job.
- Good job.
- Good job, Seon Myung.
Good job. You did well.
- It won't matter if we win.
- Suk Jin,
pick up the ball.
Why are you making her do it alone?
- Why is no one picking up the ball?
- Seriously.
She is the one who missed it.
Seon Myung, why did you go?
- You need to do better.
- Here I go, Ji Hyo.
Come on.
- That's good. Suk Jin.
- Jong Kook.
- Go.
- Give it to Ji Yeon.
Let Ji Yeon kick the ball.
(A heel kick)
- Come on. Kick it.
- Head it.
Okay.
- Come on. Kick it.
- Head it.
(She twitched on the spot.)
What are the two of you doing?
They fell in love when their eyes met.
Did time suddenly stop?
Did you fall in love suddenly?
Time must have stopped.
- You raise me
- Did your heart beat fast?
Seon Myung, stop going after the ball.
Suk Jin, you should go.
Why aren't you moving?
- Go.
- Here I go, Jong Kook.
- Okay. That's good.
- I got it.
- That's good.
- Seon Myung, kick it.
- I got it.
- Let's score a point.
- There you go.
- Get it over the net.
- Let Ji Yeon kick it.
- Okay.
- Ji Yeon, it will be hard.
- Move out of the way.
- Do well.
Ji Yeon.
(She hit the mark.)
(Nice slapstick comedy)
Se Chan, that was great.
(Se Chan got into an accident.)
- Se Chan.
- It's okay.
I can't believe
you received the ball with that.
That startled me.
I couldn't receive the ball.
I should have done it confidently.
Will you catch her or not?
- Jae Suk, let's catch her.
- What?
I haven't changed the score yet.
You haven't changed the score yet?
Did she change the score?
- I bet she has a headache.
- You raised two points, right?
Jae Suk, let's catch her.
Look at her eyes.
All right.
- Maybe not.
- Please decide.
- One, two, three.
- We won't catch her.
(They decide not to catch her.)
- Correct.
- I knew it.
(Referee Jeon had only raised 1 point.)
- She probably didn't have a choice.
- That's right.
Shall we begin?
You need to do better.
- Move out of the way.
- Ji Yeon.
- All right.
- Move out of the way.
It's okay. We saved the ball.
One more time?
- There you go.
- Seon Myung.
- Get it over the net.
(My goodness.)
Get it over the net.
He is really bad.
- Did you do that on purpose?
- No.
- Are you a spy?
- I really didn't.
This is driving me crazy. We might lose.
- My goodness.
- It's okay. You did well.
What are you doing?
Ji Hyo is bad at foot volleyball.
- Okay. You will kick it, right?
- Will you kick it?
- Okay. I got it.
- Send it over the net.
- Okay.
- Why did you send it so high?
Will you kick it?
(The rally keeps going.)
Mine.
Okay.
- All right.
- Okay.
(Se Chan makes a mistake.)
- All right.
- The court is too slippery.
Good job.
- What will it be?
- One, two, three.
Let's catch her.
- Let's catch her.
(They decide to catch her!)
(Team Type B: 12 points)
- She got caught.
- Why does this keep happening?
(Team Type A and Type AB
fails to score a point.)
- I mean...
- I told you not to do it.
- They keep catching me.
- You don't need to do it.
- So Min has that face.
- We caught her.
- You keep twitching your lips.
- It was a hard-earned point.
Why do you keep twitching your lips?
Okay. Let's resume. It's okay.
- How did they know?
- Hey, just turn around.
Let's begin.
(Jong Kook serves.)
- Go.
- Nice.
That's good. Ji Yeon.
No.
All right.
(Oh.)
- Why did you run toward the ball?
- She is cute.
- You should have done this.
- The ball was coming nicely.
- Okay.
Why did you block it?
(Team Type A and Type AB
is a complete mess.)
- The last point.
- Matchpoint.
Ji Hyo, here I go.
Come on.
Nice serve. Suk Jin.
Jong Kook.
Okay. Send it up in the air.
- Good.
- All right. Two touches.
- This is hard.
- Ji Yeon, get it.
- Ji Yeon.
- Move out of the way.
- Okay.
- Good.
Ji Yeon, can we play
a slow-motion video...
- of your face?
- Ji Yeon.
Ji Yeon, you did this.
Seriously.
It will be funny with the right music.
Will you catch her or not?
They couldn't receive the short shot.
Did you raise the score?
- Yes.
- She raised the score.
(Referee Jeon changed the score
after much deliberation.)
- What?
- Catch her.
- Let's catch her.
- One, two, three.
- Let's not catch her.
- We won't catch her.
Correct.
(They are correct again.)
So Min has that facial expression.
- Why are you so easy to read?
- We...
Even I can read her.
If she has raised the score correctly,
she looks at them.
If she did it incorrectly,
she looks at us.
She can't look at them.
(When she raised the score correctly)
(Confident)
(When she conned them)
(Avoided eye contact)
How do they know? It's so fascinating.
I told you not to be greedy.
For goodness' sake.
This is driving me crazy.
It's okay.
Good luck.
- Matchpoint.
- I will serve.
- Serve well.
- Let's have a rally.
(The game will end if Team Type B scores.)
Good.
Let's go.
- Okay. I got it.
- Suk Jin.
- Mind your manners.
- Head it.
- I told you to head the ball.
- Nice.
- Okay. I will save it.
- Okay.
- You saved it.
- Head it.
- What are you doing?
- Kick it.
(A grand finale)
Hey.
Suk Jin.
(Captain Ji laughs
even though it was his mistake.)
- It wasn't you. It was him.
- Seon Myung.
I know that it was me.
Your fighting spirit made me laugh.
- It was a spike.
- We just needed to get it over.
- Game over.
- I knew they would lose.
- Ji Yeon, good job.
- Team Type B won.
- Okay.
That hurts my pride.
- You did well, Seon Myung.
- You did well.
Team Type B will get
three penalty balls...
and Team Type A and Type AB
will get ten penalty balls.
Seon Myung and Ji Yeon were funny.
- You did well.
- They are good.
It was nice to have So Min as the referee.
- She did well.
- So Min, it was funny.
So Min finally found something
she is good at.
- It was twice as interesting.
- I really want to play the game.
- You need to think about your leg.
For the last game,
both teams need to use their teamwork.
It's the Chalk Is a Must.
- What is it?
- Chalk?
It's a race that is a mix...
of the Name Tag Elimination
and Save the Chalk.
Okay.
Among the chalk pieces you have saved,
you will combine the length
of the longest five.
The team with the longer length will win.
- Five?
- Yes.
We have more members.
(Now,)
(we have sad news for the viewers.)
(To enjoy the proper
Name Tag Elimination,)
(we rented a spacious and dynamic place.)
(But the race ended in 11 minutes.)
(1. The members were distracted
when they hid the chalk pieces.)
I can't believe it.
What?
It's blocked.
(They were hopeless
from the hiding stage.)
This is bad. It's blocked.
I am sorry, but...
Okay. I will hide it here.
There is no time.
(2. They were one-dimensional
in selecting the hiding places.)
- What?
- What is it?
(The chalk got found in 2 minutes.)
- It's here.
- Where?
Let's see it.
(They destroyed it right away.)
Maybe it's Suk Jin's.
(He found another one.)
Where is it?
(Suk Jin didn't exceed expectations.)
Suk Jin is out.
Suk Jin doesn't travel far.
Gosh.
(3. 4 minutes into the race,)
Reflection Skill.
(Jong Kook got eliminated
due to the Reflection Skill.)
(Reflection Skill)
Jong Kook is out.
(The ace member went to the jail
in less than 5 minutes.)
- Out.
- How did this happen?
- I need to get it wrong, right?
- Suk Jin is out.
I will give you the question.
Who is the man behind the saying,
"The die is cast?"
Number 1, Julius Caesar.
Number 2, Abraham Lincoln.
- I need to get it wrong.
- You need to get it wrong.
I think the answer is number two.
- Number one.
- No.
It's correct.
- It's correct.
- Hey.
- So Min.
- It's correct.
- You got it right.
You lost 30cm.
- It's correct.
- Is it correct?
- Why is it correct?
- She keeps getting it right.
- You should go to Seoul University.
- Is it correct?
Take off their name tags.
Jong Kook is out.
- Come here.
- Jae Suk.
- Take Jae Suk out.
- We are men.
- We are Type B.
- We are Type B men.
- What happened?
- Team Type B won.
- Yes!
(Team Type B won.)
Okay.
It will be funny
if they receive the penalty.
Team Type B
versus Team Type A and Type AB.
The number of Team Type B's
penalty balls...
- is 16.
- I did my best.
For Team Type A and Type AB,
the number is 23.
- It's okay.
- The difference isn't great.
The difference isn't great.
- Seven.
- That's right. We can still win.
This is the real deal.
It will be satisfying
to win in this state.
I will first tell you what the penalty is.
What is it?
The penalty of the day is...
the water bucket.
- It's cold today.
- It's a big one.
The water bucket.
(They prepared a water bucket
on a cold day.)
- It's a big one.
- It really is.
Producer Lee Myung Jae will draw a ball.
- This is...
- My goodness.
This is scary.
- Let's huddle close.
- Put the penalty balls inside.
The team loses
if its penalty ball gets picked.
Then a bucket of water
will be poured on them right away.
Okay.
I have a bad feeling about this.
- No.
- I am mistaken, right?
- Don't say that.
- Please don't let it be us.
So you get the water
if your penalty ball comes out.
- That's right.
- That team loses.
- Yes.
We should take off the audio equipment.
Now comes the final result of the race.
- Okay.
- Mix up the balls more.
- Stop looking.
- Okay.
- Se Chan, stop looking.
- Shall I stop looking?
- All right.
In terms of probability,
Team Type B has an advantage.
(In terms of probability,
Team Type B has an advantage.)
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Which team will it be? Please pick a ball.
Are you going to tell us the result
before pouring the water?
- Team Type B has an advantage.
- Please.
The water will be poured
right after the announcement.
Please announce the result.
(Team Type B: 16 balls
Team Type A and Type AB: 23 balls)
(Which team will get the penalty?)
- It's Team Type B.
- Team Type B loses.
(Team Type B loses.)
- It's Team Type B.
- Team Type B loses.
(Pouring water)
Team Type B loses.
(Presenting a bucket of icy cold water)
Oh, cold.
Okay! We won.
- We won.
- See?
I told you.
(Team Type A and Type AB won in the end.)
- So cold.
- I told you I had a bad feeling.
I told you I had a bad feeling about it.
- So cold.
- Good work.
Because I never fail.
- We won!
- Yes. We can do it.
Okay.
(Ten men and women are wandering
to find their love.)
(Park Ah In, Kim Hee Jung,
Roh Jeong Eui, Yoo Jenny)
- Go.
- Ah In.
(Love is about seducing.)
I love only one girl.
I love you.
(Love is about getting swayed.)
He reminds me of the boy
I had a crush on in university.
(Love is about winning.)
They're all very pretty.
(War of love is sometimes sweet...)
(and sometimes brutal.)
(What's the 1st need
of Maslow's hierarchy of needs?)
(Something phenomenon?)
(It starts with S?)
(However)
You have been...
(There are people interrupting
their love.)
(Not Spring, Candy or Penalty)