(The stockholders of E Biotechnology
are devastated.)
(Lee Kwang Soo's account balance)
(The tall investor's rate of return
is minus 36 percent.)
(He heads to the Information
Exchange again.)
(He bought Level 1 Information
about I Chemical.)
(The government announces plans
to fight fine dust.)
(How is this related to I Chemical?)
(He asks Jae Suk
when he doesn't know.)
(Still hurting from E Bio)
- It's real.
- What is it?
(He forgot
about the bad memories...)
(and hears the information.)
(Let's go with it.)
(He keeps repeating himself.)
I will invest everything
in I Chemical.
(With Kwang Soo's information,
he invests in I Chemical.)
(Yoo Jae Suk's account balance)
(He followed Jae Suk
and invested in I Chemical.)
(If I remember correctly,
biotechnology rose in 2017.)
(Based on his experience, Suk Jin
kept his eye on biotechnology.)
F Biotechnology.
(Then he invested
in F Biotechnology.)
(Other investors invested
in F Biotechnology too.)
(Jong Kook invested
all his money in G Foods.)
(The novice investor Ji Hyo...)
(heard the word "shipbuilding"
and invested all her money in it.)
(I changed at the last moment.
I went all-in.)
(The investors start to feel nervous
with only a few years left.)
That's dangerous, but investors
like him end up making it big.
It's true...
that biotechnology
will rise in 2017.
But this is risky. Biotechnology...
Jong Kook, what about chemical?
It's good, isn't it?
(Will it be chemical
or biotechnology?)
(Or will it be foods?)
- It's closed.
- Please.
- Please. Just one year.
(Ji Hyo kept going back and forth
until the end, but finally decided.)
(Anxious)
Once I earn the principal amount,
- I'll keep the cash.
- Please.
I just want to earn back
the principal.
Hey, you should buy land...
- with the money.
- I should do that.
- That would be better.
- You should buy an estate.
Jeju Island.
- Aewol in Jeju Island.
- It's almost time.
If you invest in real estate
in Aewol, Jeju Island,
- you will go from rags to riches.
- Hey.
- Buy land in Jeju Island.
- Go to Aewol.
Once I get the principal back,
- I'll go to Jeju Island.
- I'm really nervous now.
(What will be the investors' fates
as they all hope for a big break?)
I have no confidence.
Happy New Year!
(Kwang Soo and Jae Suk
invested in I Chemical.)
(And many others invested
in F Biotechnology.)
(The stock prices of 2017
are revealed.)
- Biotechnology!
- G Foods.
Please. Biotechnology.
- Yes!
- Biotechnology!
(The 2017 Stock Market)
(F Biotechnology,
G Foods, I Chemical)
(The stock prices of F Biotechnology
and G Foods rose sharply.)
(Ji Suk Jin's account balance)
With no information...
What did I tell you
about biotechnology?
You were right about that.
Biotechnology.
I bought the G Foods' stocks, right?
(Jae Suk also succeeded
in making a profit.)
Biotechnology!
I went all-in on F Biotechnology
at the last minute!
(Se Chan is a super-wealthy investor
who will soon have 100,000 dollars.)
I made profits too.
(So Min's stock price rose
by 233 percent too!)
I knew biotechnology stock prices
would rise.
I made the right call.
G Foods.
I invested all of my money
in G Foods.
- Biotechnology!
- G Foods.
I succeeded without any information.
How did the stock price
for biotechnology rise so much?
(How did the stock price
for biotechnology rise so much?)
Gosh, G Foods...
Gosh, really...
The G Foods stock price rose
by 220 percent.
Did you invest in G Foods, Se Chan?
I had profits,
but it doesn't feel good...
because other stock prices rose
so much.
F Biotechnology is no joke.
(Everyone had a jackpot this year
except for Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.)
- It feels real!
- I will cash out now.
- Let's go for a drink today.
- It's on me.
- This is a great day.
It's on me.
It's on me!
Congratulations.
I invested in foods
and biotechnology.
- You guys are small-time investors.
- I told you...
- that biotechnology will rise.
- Se Chan.
It's on me.
Let's check out
the current asset ranking.
Okay.
I bet I moved up a lot.
(He was at the very bottom
the last time.)
I am in second place.
Gosh, the ranking changed a lot
this time.
- I am still in third place.
- Okay! I beat Ji Hyo!
Okay! I beat Ji Hyo!
(It's most likely
that Ji Hyo will get the penalty.)
- I am still in third place.
- Let's move up.
- Am I in 5th place?
- I am in 2nd place.
I am going up.
Jae Suk is one place above me.
Gosh, this is...
Not many years are left.
We have three years to go.
(With 3 years remaining,
the 2nd investment ends.)
Se Chan is incredible.
Let's move on to the last mission.
Se Chan started with 500 dollars
and nearly reached 100,000 dollars.
- Se Chan has 100,000 dollars.
- That makes no sense.
It all depends on luck.
- Hey.
- I am bragging.
It all depends on luck.
- We have three more chances.
- When will I get more money?
I need to get good information now.
You need to play the game well.
Information is key.
Now,
it's time for the last mission
to win information points.
For those of you who are thirsty
for information points,
we will play the game
that we played as the first mission.
We will have another round
of Debate Battle as a bonus game.
- Let's begin the last mission.
- Okay.
(This is what Debate Battle is.)
(The production crew will give
a topic for debate.)
(Will Jong Kook be able to
get married within 3 years?)
(A: He can, B: He can't)
(The members will have a draw
for A or B.)
(They must come up
with plausible reasons...)
(and persuade the staff members.)
(The team that persuaded
more staff members wins.)
If you win, you will receive
three information points.
- The topic.
- What is it?
Is face reading science or not?
- That's the topic.
- Face reading is science.
Let's have a draw.
I hope I get A.
(A: It's science,
B: It isn't science)
- Okay.
- What?
I got B.
If you have B, sit over here.
If you have A, sit over there.
- I have B.
- I have A.
Face reading is science.
It isn't science.
You can't judge someone by his face.
Face reading is science.
I say that...
because I took an elective course
in university.
- There is a course.
- Then it's undeniable.
There is an official curriculum...
because it's science.
Give us...
something important you learned
from the course.
Something that
would convince people.
For example, this part shows
marital compatibility.
- What?
- Marital compatibility.
- If there is a mole...
- She is a face reader.
(She is a face reader.)
- For example...
- She is a face reader.
- "Am I destined to be a king?"
- "Tell me, face reader."
People who have
a mole or a scar here...
get treatments to have it removed.
Doing so will increase
your marital compatibility.
It might also help you
to marry well...
- or meet someone nice.
- But such information...
comes from accumulated data.
I like these big words.
It shows the probability
that comes...
- from many people's appearance.
- Data?
- Data or probability is science.
- That's science.
Probability isn't
necessarily science.
It's chemistry.
Isn't he picking a fight?
No!
(His oppressive tone creates
a controversy.)
- Please don't misunderstand.
- Excuse me?
He isn't picking a fight.
- That's his usual tone!
- Excuse me?
- I am not picking a fight!
- That's his usual tone!
That's his usual tone.
- Isn't he picking a fight?
- Jae Suk.
That's his usual tone.
- While there is that approach...
- I mean...
- Listen.
- Are you pointing a spoon at me?
- You punk!
- All right.
- Are you pointing a spoon at me?
- "You punk"?
Listen.
- Didn't they say you look unlucky?
- They did.
But he isn't unlucky, is he?
- Seriously.
- He is the luckiest man.
- Look at him.
- Suk Jin.
- Let me tell you this.
- Tell them.
- Tell them my story.
- This is important.
There are old sayings...
about how big ears are associated...
- with a long and successful life...
- Long life.
and how a big nose is associated
with good fortune.
There are such sayings.
But my ears aren't that big,
Suk Jin's ears are big.
- My goodness.
- Hold on.
- Suk Jin.
- Don't be like that.
- I mean...
- Aren't we on the same side?
What are you trying to say?
Give us a concise summary
of your words.
- I do have bigger ears.
- I mean...
- What about it?
- So you have good fortune...
- and Suk Jin doesn't?
- I didn't say that.
- Earlier,
you said
that face reading is based...
- on probability and data.
- Yes.
Most scientific fields
draw conclusions...
- from probability and data.
- That's right.
- Listen.
- I have...
- one complaint about the way...
- Okay.
you participate in the debate.
Your tone is aggravating.
Come on.
(Jae Suk takes an issue
with his attitude.)
- Your tone is aggravating.
- Listen.
I am talking in a reasonable
and persuasive manner.
Reasonable? You punk!
How dare you point a finger at me?
You little...
Hold on.
(Jong Kook explodes.)
What are you doing?
- Why did you swear?
What was that?
I am sorry.
I admit that I made a mistake.
He officially apologized.
- Listen.
- This is unbelievable.
(The desire for information points
made him lose his senses.)
It was so scary.
Let me say this again.
Here is what I think.
Even if you have bad looks,
you can improve them with effort.
- You can change them.
- That's right.
Thus,
- face reading...
- It's nothing more.
isn't science.
I am sure some people
have seen this on social media.
- People who look similar...
- All right.
- Don't talk about social media.
- This is important!
- This is really important!
- All right.
- Tell the story.
- This isn't the time...
- to talk about social media.
- This story can persuade everyone.
This story can persuade everyone.
This isn't the time
to talk about social media.
You don't even have
a social media account.
How could you shut me down
like this?
Listen. Your looks...
are passed down...
- from your parents.
- Stop it.
They are related to the environment
you're brought up in.
There is a saying,
"You live as you look."
- It's about face reading.
- Yes.
- "You live as you look."
- A simple way of explaining it.
- However,
as you live,
you see so many people
who don't live as they look.
Look at me. I am like that.
- Se Chan is like that.
- Look at his face.
- But you live as you look.
- That's right.
You are well-known
to represent that saying.
Why did he rope me into this?
Why?
- Why did he rope me into this?
- I don't live as I look.
- You live as you look.
- That's not true.
Listen. Look at Se Chan's face.
- Does he look like a good student?
- No, he doesn't.
(It's a heavy blow.)
Hey, that's...
Isn't that a personal attack?
You should watch what you say.
- Doesn't he look dumb?
- Speak for yourself!
You have the same look!
Are you belittling him?
- Are you belittling him?
- We are saying it's science.
- You should watch what you say.
He just looks dumb!
- Seriously.
- You punks!
This is...
This is a personal attack.
- Don't land a personal attack.
- I know. You shouldn't do that.
- It's just wrong.
Suk Jin has the face of a man
who gets okay grades...
and leads a diligent life.
- His life is following his looks.
- Seriously.
Listen.
- I will tell you this.
- Okay.
When Suk Jin debuted
in the early 1990s,
people in the show business said...
that he has the face of a host
who will lead the future.
Did they say that about Suk Jin?
- He became a host.
- No.
Who said that?
It isn't science!
- While he hosts shows...
- Did people really say that?
- If it's between A and B...
- He can work as a host.
I can work as a host.
He is the Yoo Jae Suk of YouTube!
- He became a host.
- While he hosts shows...
- When I was a rookie...
- I am sure...
- Many people on social media...
- No, no. Don't talk about that.
(He cuts off Kwang Soo again.)
This isn't the time
to talk about social media.
Let's not talk about that.
- Can't I talk about it?
- Jae Suk is right.
Don't talk about social media.
- We are done.
- Let's see the result now.
B won.
Haha, So Min, Jong Kook,
- and Kwang Soo claimed...
- It's A.
- that face reading is science.
- There is no doubt about it.
If you found them persuasive,
choose A.
- Are we A or B?
- We are B.
- Choose A.
- A.
- It's A.
Let's see
the staff members' choice. One,
- two,
- Face reading isn't science.
- three.
- It's A.
(What will be
the staff members' choice?)
- It's B.
- B!
- More people chose B.
- That's right. It isn't science.
- It isn't science.
- More people chose B.
- Good job. Jae Suk, you did well.
It was hard.
What should I do?
- I have no information points.
- Me neither.
You have one last chance
to win information points.
The second mission is
your last chance to win points.
The lower you go,
the more points you will win.
It's Patience Prevails.
I am not good at that.
Two people will be on one team.
With your backs touching,
you will play limbo while one of you
carries the other on your back.
On the limbo stick,
brushes with wet paint are attached.
Even if you get paint on your face,
you succeed
if the stick doesn't fall.
But you fail...
if the stick falls
or a member's feet touch the ground.
The height you passed will be
the team's record.
1st place gets 7 points.
2nd place gets 5 points.
3rd place gets 3 points.
4th place gets 1 point. It will be
given to each team member.
We need to place second
at the very least.
Your team member is important.
It's a matter of who teams up
with Jong Kook.
- That would be incredible.
- Kwang Soo is too tall.
We will pick the teams now.
Let's do this.
You will team up with the member
who picks the same color.
- Please.
- 2, 3.
Yellow.
- Kwang Soo.
- Three.
- Blue.
Red.
- Three.
- Red.
- Yellow.
- Yellow. Okay!
(Seeing her team member
makes her legs give out.)
- Hey, what about you?
- Green.
- Yellow.
- Yellow. Okay!
Green.
- I'm your partner.
- Oh, it's you.
- That's not bad.
- Ji Hyo, this is good.
- Yes, this is good.
- What's this?
- So Min.
- You should carry me on your back.
(The crazy height difference makes
Se Chan sigh.)
We must not pair up with each other.
- I clearly told you before.
- Why does this keep happening?
I don't like this situation either.
We can't... Gosh. Please let me
go now. I'm begging you.
We're in trouble.
Let me win a race at least once.
- Shall we go last? Or third?
- Kwang Soo, if you do this well,
- I'll give you 10,000 dollars.
- Okay.
- This is important.
- You guys go last.
Se Chan promised to give me
10,000 dollars if I do this well,
and it made me so happy.
He said he'll give me 10,000 dollars
if I do well.
With that money,
you won't be in the bottom place.
Exactly. He said he'll give me
10,000 dollars.
- I'm a generous man.
- I'm so excited.
I wouldn't offer petty cash
like 50 or 100 dollars.
- I'll give him 10,000 dollars.
- I'd do anything for that money.
I'm jealous.
Oh, man. That's too low.
That's too low.
- Just keep going.
- The brushes will fall off at once.
- Hold my arms tightly.
- Okay.
- I'll put my hands on my knees.
- Got it.
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
- That's exactly my point.
- That makes sense.
- This won't be easy.
- I'll wrap your arms like this.
- Wait.
- Hold on a second.
- I'm ready.
- It's hard because you can't see.
(Lifting up)
You should lie down
just like Haha did.
(Jong Kook carries Haha who gained
weight recently on his back easily.)
Go now. Go, go.
- Keep going. Go.
- That's too low.
- Keep going. Yes.
- Can I keep going?
- Keep going without stopping.
- You can move as you are.
(What a stable position.)
- Keep going.
- Really?
- Is it okay?
- Keep going.
- Keep going, Jong Kook.
- Bend down a little. A bit lower.
(As Haha got scared
and asked him to lower him,)
(he lowered his body
with all his might.)
(With a large gap
between the brushes and Haha,)
- Okay!
- Okay.
(they passed without getting
any paint on Haha.)
(It was a textbook play.)
Great job.
We passed.
- Here we go.
- You can do it!
- Ji Hyo, tell me what to do.
- It's Ji Hyo's team's turn.
- I'll tell you.
- Okay.
- They pair up together often.
- I'll tell you.
- Ji Hyo, can we go now?
- Yes, let's go.
- Go. Keep going.
- Can I go as I am now?
Go.
- Maintain the height.
- Okay.
Jae Suk, go down a little.
Just a little lower.
- I just did.
- Okay. Good. Go now.
(Jae Suk tried to lower his body
as much as he could.)
Oh, my gosh.
(Her body touched the brushes!)
(When they were halfway through,)
(Ji Hyo's body touched the brushes.)
- Wait. Go down.
- I just did.
Keep going as you are. Good.
Okay.
I just did.
(Ji Hyo prevented from touching
brushes again by tilting her head.)
- We did it, Jae Suk.
- Okay. Good job.
- Why is everyone so serious today?
- Let's go.
Why are you all so serious?
Next!
Let's do this. I'll turn the game
around in three years. Watch me.
People probably think
we can't do this.
But we can do this.
- We can succeed.
- Let's prove them wrong.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Okay!
He can pass the first level.
He's been working out at home.
I've been working out at home.
Okay. Suk Jin, let's go.
Go, go. Go straight. Hurry up.
- Her feet might touch the floor.
- Suk Jin, go straight.
- Oh, no.
- Be careful.
Go, go. Go straight. Hurry up.
(Suk Jin is going forward
with his wobbly legs.)
(Give me a moment.)
- You're out.
- Let me take a break.
- No, we're not.
- They're out.
Let me take a short break.
Okay. Suk Jin, focus.
- What?
- Focus.
But they keep talking to me.
- Go with that height.
- Okay.
By the way, are you playing the game
with your uncle?
(2021 New Year's Special,
Athletic Contest with Uncles)
Is this a New Year's special?
- Okay.
- Are you in the center?
- Go now.
- Here we go.
- Hey, you look so scary.
- Suk Jin.
Wait, Suk Jin.
- How high is it?
- Your feet mustn't touch the floor.
- What did you see?
- You should see the bar.
(But the weak niece hasn't even
lifted up her head to see the bar.)
- What did you see?
- You should see the bar.
- Suk Jin, I can't see it.
- Hey, take a look.
- I can't see it.
- Lift up your head and look at it.
- Wait for a second.
- Come on.
- They won't make it.
- You should see it.
- Take a look at it.
- Wait.
(She's taking a break on her uncle's
back unintentionally.)
- I said, look!
- She can't lift up her head.
Suk Jin, you're pulling her arms
too hard.
- Lift up your head and look.
- So Min, you should take a look.
- I can't...
- Or you can't pass.
(Big Nose started moving backward
without checking the height.)
Okay. Go. Go down a little.
No. Lower. Lower.
(The bar started swaying.)
Go down. Lower.
(They failed in the end.)
(Suk Jin's legs gave out
after only a few steps.)
- Lower...
- Oh, no.
(Big Nose is still too weak
despite exercising.)
Gosh. I can't believe...
My thighs hurt so much.
(She's paying a silent tribute
to her uncle who was humiliated.)
Hey, you should've looked at it.
(While the 2 weakest members are
feeling sad about failing Level 1,)
(someone is preparing for his turn
while taking off his shirt.)
(Wiggling)
(He's willing to take off 1 layer of
his bottom clothes to move freely.)
Let's just check the height.
Try it.
(The beanpole in leggings tries
carrying the dumpy guy on his back.)
- Grab my thighs.
- Kwang Soo.
- Where? Here?
- Support your body like that.
Try to hold it by yourself.
(What?)
- Kwang Soo, this won't work.
- That won't work.
- They can't even...
- Kwang Soo, this won't work.
They might fail in front of the bar.
(They'll definitely fail
in front of it.)
- They might fail in front of it.
- Wait, Kwang Soo.
- Stop.
- It won't work?
Kwang Soo, you...
You have such a skinny butt,
Kwang Soo.
- That's not true.
- I was lying on your back,
- and all I could feel was the bone.
- Stop it.
By the way, where did you
get these leggings?
Why are you asking that?
It's okay as long as the bar
doesn't fall off.
I'll bend down this much, so you...
Stop. You're too tall.
- Come up higher.
- Like this?
- Yes. That's good.
- Here we go.
- That's good. You look stable.
He didn't have to take off
his pants. Why did he do that?
- That's good.
- Kwang Soo, tell me what to do.
- Where did you get your leggings?
- Keep going.
That's not important now.
- I like leggings too.
- Keep going.
- Okay.
Hang on. I don't think
these are leggings.
They're leggings.
Get your hands off me!
- Look.
- They're leggings. Stop.
- Look here.
- They're unique.
- This is...
- Let's go.
Hey, stop. Wait. I said, wait!
(His leggings are at risk
of being damaged.)
- Wait. Hey.
- Goodness.
(The leggings man is facing a crisis
in front of the bar.)
- Stop. Wait a second.
- Gosh.
Why? What's wrong?
Why do you want to come down?
Put him down, Se Chan.
- Why did you tell me to stop?
- It's okay now.
- Do you want to come down?
- Stand up for a second.
- I think...
- Hey! Stop.
- Hey, you can go now.
- Hey, stop!
Wait.
(Se Chan has no idea what crisis
Kwang Soo is dealing with.)
- His leggings...
- Bend lower.
- You should bend lower.
- Gosh, my leggings.
(Bouncing)
Oh, gosh.
- You should bend lower.
- Gosh, my leggings.
(Se Chan tries to lower his body
as much as possible, but...)
Oh, no.
Gosh.
You're out.
Hey, your leggings have...
a zipper.
It's not a zipper.
- It's not?
- It's not a zipper.
(He ended up getting paint
on his leggings for nothing.)
Oh, my. Will we be able to
pull it off?
- Okay.
- I'm dizzy.
This is the final match.
If both teams succeed,
we'll give you all bonus points.
Sounds great.
- It's hard to step backward.
- I think we'll fail this time.
- It's too low.
- It should be lower.
It's really low.
That's too difficult.
That's impossible.
Let me see. I think I should
squat as low as I can go.
Let's move diagonally, Jong Kook.
- No. Let's stand straight.
- Will you go straight?
This is almost
physically impossible.
- Just a second.
- Really?
- Wait.
- Okay. This is good.
Jong Kook, go now. Just go.
- Wait.
- I'll hold this position.
It's okay. Keep going.
Just a slight touch won't
make the bar fall off.
- Stop.
- You can still succeed.
- Just a little lower.
- You have no choice.
You should go lower.
- It's okay. Keep moving slowly.
- Wait.
Jong Kook, stop.
- You'll fail because of his belly.
- You should move slowly.
- Look at his belly.
- How much have you been eating?
Why is his belly sticking out
so much?
Hey, I'm feeling good now.
Oh, gosh. Hold on.
Hey. Hey, you...
(Between the brushes and Jong Kook's
back, he's feeling happy somehow.)
(Because of Haha's confession,)
(Jong Kook lost his balance.)
- Why?
- His belly is...
sticking out too much
to pass the bar.
(Jong Kook and Haha failed
Level 2.)
- Ji Hyo, this is...
- I don't think we can do this.
If you succeed,
you will get seven points.
- Would you pay 30,000 dollars?
- We'll probably fail, Ji Hyo.
Hold on.
This is impossible.
(Even the strong Jong Kook failed
to clear 95cm.)
- Ji Hyo, here we go.
- Okay.
Let's go.
- I'll move now.
- I'll try to hang steadily.
Let's go, let's go.
Jae Suk, you need to go
much lower than this.
This is physically impossible.
You're right. This is impossible.
(Her legs have almost passed.)
- Jae Suk, go down. It's too close.
- It's over.
- Go down, Jae Suk.
Ji Hyo, does your body touch
the brushes?
Yes... I mean, no. Dad.
I won't touch it.
Did she just call him "Dad"?
She called him "Dad".
No, Dad. I won't touch it.
(She's so flustered
that she made a mistake.)
- "Dad!"
- Ji Hyo, are you all right?
- Yes, Jae Suk. I'm all right.
- Okay.
Is this "Dad's Challenge"?
(At every step he makes,
the bar sways.)
Gosh. This is too low.
Oh, no. It'll fall off.
No, I think he can pull it off.
(They're moving backward slowly
getting paint on Ji Hyo.)
- Ji Hyo can't do anything about it.
- No.
(95cm is too low to pass under it
while carrying someone on the back.)
- No, it's okay.
- Ji Hyo can't do anything about it.
Go slowly.
(It's okay?)
(Jae Suk is passing under the bar
little by little.)
It's okay.
You can do this, Jae Suk.
- Oh, no.
- Be careful.
- It's okay.
- It'll work.
- Will that work?
- It's okay.
- It'll work.
(Meanwhile, they already passed
the halfway point.)
- It'll work.
- Will that work?
- It's okay.
This is unbelievable.
- Awesome.
- Jae Suk.
This is unbelievable.
We can do this.
- We're almost there.
- It's working.
They did it.
(Jae Suk fell backward
at the last moment.)
(If they succeed, they'll obtain
7 points as the sole winning team.)
The bar didn't fall off.
We made it. We made it.
(Jae Suk and Ji Hyo cleared 95cm.)
We made it.
(Jae Suk succeeded the hardest 95cm
with his strong mindset.)
Ji Hyo, we made it.
(It's hard to believe he succeeded.)
(They're excited about
the unexpected success.)
- I can't believe we did it.
- Jae Suk, you're awesome.
- Great job!
- I'm so excited.
How did he do that?
- I'm so excited!
- Ji Hyo!
- Jae Suk!
- I can't believe this.
(The 2 investors hit the jackpot.)
I can't believe we pulled it off.
(After buying 2 Level 2 Information,
they'll still have 1 point left.)
Everyone seems so crazy
about getting information.
You're all crazy
Why would you be so serious?
- We did it, Ji Hyo.
- I didn't expect it.
(They were more serious than ever
during the last mission.)
Jae Suk and Ji Hyo are the winners.
Each will receive seven points.
- Oh, yes!
- All right!
I'm going to buy some information.
(The 2017 Stock Prices)
What should I buy this time?
You sold 750 shares
of F Biotechnology...
and cashed out 30,000 dollars.
So this is the amount I have left
after cashing them out?
Do you want to give them
another chance?
- Of course not. Why would we?
- Just once.
I'll give you some money.
What do you say?
No, I won't accept it.
Give each of us 5,000 dollars.
- 5,000 dollars for each?
- You'll spend only 30,000 dollars.
- But if you give us the money...
- Okay!
- Okay.
- Is he that rich?
- I'll give each 5,000 dollars.
- 5,000 dollars. Okay.
How much money does he have?
(So 30,000 dollars was deducted
from his account.)
Really? But I still have this much
in my account?
(He still has over 56,000 dollars
left in his account.)
My gosh. I had more than
100,000 dollars.
This is good.
(Suk Jin, in 2nd place,
has less than half of Se Chan.)
I think I should go all-in for this.
Since this is the last chance,
I'm going to...
How much money
does he have... What?
My goodness. He's incredible.
How much does he have?
He still has almost 60,000 dollars.
I also have 15,000 dollars in cash.
- Gosh. What?
- Why do you have so much money?
Why do you have so much money?
It feels like I'm playing
with babies.
While they're contemplating whether
or not to invest 500 dollars more,
- I'm thinking of 10,000 dollars.
- That's amazing.
While I'm dealing with amounts
higher than 10,000 dollars,
I see you guys talking 500 dollars.
It doesn't draw my attention.
Gosh.
(The other investors have a feeling
of relative deprivation.)
Gosh, this is so difficult.
Does anyone want to sell
information to me?
(Yang and Rich even buys
information with money.)
I'll pay you if you give me
useful information.
May I offer you 1 piece
of 3-point information?
Really? Tell me what kind first.
- IT.
- What?
- Which one of them?
(A black market for information
opened in an instant.)
What else should I buy?
I've seen a sight like this
on a news show.
- What did you say?
- I've seen this on a news show.
- Gosh. It's giving me a headache.
- Everyone was...
- whispering to each other.
- How much?
This is no joke.
Up to 5,000 dollars?
- How many shares of B can I buy?
- B Entertainment?
I mean, we're using fake money.
Here's 5,000 dollars.
They're all whispering
to each other.
Why is it taking you so long
to calculate it?
Why is everyone so serious?
Hello.
I'm Jeon So Min, the life
of the party on Running Man.
From my experience
in stock investment,
I learned that making an investment
by following your hunch...
can lead to failure.
That's why I've decided...
to go all-in for one company.
(The interview with the disoriented
citizen ended.)
Se Chan, I have information
on B Entertainment.
- Sorry?
- B Entertainment.
I'm sorry,
but I'll give you 100 dollars,
so get lost.
- Thank you.
- Okay?
- If you give me fake information...
- This is real information.
Don't do that to me.
(B Entertainment announces
production of...)
("Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks".)
Hold on. Oh, gosh.
(Hold on!)
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks" will be
released next year?
- This is the information I got.
- That movie was a huge flop.
(He's saying something very harsh.)
That won't be useful.
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks"?
If you go to Se Chan, he'll tell you
to get lost offering 100 dollars.
You can get 100 dollars easily.
(It's a high-paying job as long as
you can endure humiliation.)
- He just blabbered nonsense.
- What did he say?
He advised me to buy
B Entertainment's shares...
because "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks"
will be released.
(It's useless information
that no one would buy.)
- Don't leak the information.
- That's why I told him to get lost.
Don't leak useful information.
G Foods...
- G Foods?
- Can I buy that much?
- Sorry?
- Haha and Jong Kook's tonkatsu...
is about to be released.
- Here. Get lost.
- Thank you.
He said that his tonkatsu product is
about to be released.
- Go on.
- It's about to be released.
- It's around the corner.
- It's coming soon.
Kwang Soo, come with me.
Let's go and buy some information.
(Following Se Chan)
Kwang Soo, I'll get information...
(Kwang Soo joined him
without much thought.)
on I Chemical.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Chemical companies did well
from 2017 to 2019.
- I think it's D IT. I saw it.
- I see.
- Okay.
- You check out D IT.
And I'll check out I Chemical.
- Okay. Let's meet up here.
- Okay.
(Haha will check out D IT. Jong Kook
will check out I Chemical.)
All right. Oh, dear.
I'll get a hint on I Chemical.
- Which level would you like?
- Level One, please.
(I Chemical increased sharply.
Could there be good news again?)
(Crude oil prices skyrocket.)
(Crude oil prices skyrocket?)
That's great news.
"Crude oil prices..."
- Is this information on I Chemical?
- Yes.
(What does oil price have to do
with a chemical company?)
Is an oil price increase
good for a chemical company?
Is it not good?
(Information only confuses
him more.)
Is an increase in oil price
good for a chemical company?
- Okay.
- Got it.
Does oil have anything to do
with a chemical company?
No, oil is...
It has something to do
with the oil price.
- It means the oil price increased.
- I see.
- The energy...
- So they're not related?
If it increased sharply,
we have to figure out
how it'll affect the stock price.
But we can't because we didn't
learn things like that.
We're done for.
It's so difficult.
I Chemical.
- I Chemical stock went down, right?
- Yes.
- Check out I Chemical.
- I'll do that.
- Then I'll get information on...
- E Biotechnology.
- E Biotechnology?
- Yes.
Okay.
(So Min got Level 1 Information
on I Chemical too.)
"Crude oil prices skyrocket."
Suk Jin.
What did you find out?
It said that
crude oil prices skyrocketed.
- Is that it?
- Yes. "Crude oil prices skyrocket."
If there's less demand,
the stock price will go down.
- Am I right?
- Yes.
- I Chemical.
Did you hear
that the oil price increased?
If it increased...
That means it's just the beginning.
- What?
- It's just the beginning.
- Is that what it means?
- If the oil price...
- No. That means...
- Are you saying it's good news?
Is it good news? Isn't it bad news?
Suk Jin, think about it.
If the oil price goes up,
then...
(The increase in crude oil price)
There will be more demand
for alternative energy.
(As a result, I Chemical stock will
increase as an energy company.)
- Come with me.
- Why?
I'll explain it to you.
Cameraman, won't you follow us?
(Cameraman, won't you follow us?)
I'll explain it to you.
(Rushing)
We're having a discussion.
(The cameraman unintentionally
forgot about him.)
I mean, we're...
What he meant by that...
There can be several ways
of interpreting the news.
Since oil prices increased,
there might be more demand
for alternative energy.
- Then it won't affect their stock.
- It's possible.
You're right. It said
that the price skyrocketed.
Then I should invest
in I Chemical.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- It will definitely rise.
- Okay.
- I'm sure this is right. Let's go.
- I think we're right.
- I'll invest half in it.
I think we're right.
- D IT?
- D IT and I Chemical.
I'll buy as many shares as I can.
- D IT and I Chemical?
- Yes.
(After long, hard thought...)
I'll buy I Chemical's shares.
(Ji Suk Jin's account balance)
200 shares.
(He invested most of his money
in I Chemical.)
I'll invest the remaining money
in E Biotechnology.
- All in E Biotechnology?
- Yes.
(He sold his F Biotechnology shares
and bought E Biotechnology.)
(Jeon So Min's account balance)
I will pull out of everything
and invest in I Chemical.
(So Min invested all she had
in I Chemical.)
I'll sell half of the shares,
and invest in C IT.
(As a novice, she invested
in several companies.)
Mr. Yang.
Can you give me 27 dollars?
- How much?
- 27 dollars.
Are you sure you didn't mean
250 or 270 dollars?
I said 27 dollars.
But if you give me 270 dollars,
I'd be grateful.
I hope you don't think...
- that I'm arrogant.
- Never.
- I'm not doing charity, you know.
- Of course.
Can you do the mosquito dance
just for me?
(Can you do the mosquito dance
just for me?)
(He drooled.)
Forget it if you don't want to.
- I'll invest in other companies.
- It's not like that.
(Inner conflict)
- Forget it if you don't want to.
- No. I'll do it.
I could invest in other people.
I know that it went down
and went back up.
But I'm not sure whether it happened
in 2019 or 2020.
(A giant mosquito bit my foot)
(Satisfied)
(He paid 250 dollars
for the mosquito performance.)
- Thank you for your performance.
- Thank you.
- I really enjoyed it.
- I'll ask for it again.
- Okay.
Se Chan, what about me?
(The 2nd show,
The Human Magnet Show)
How is it stuck on there?
That's amazing.
- Honestly...
- How long can it last?
How do you do that?
Here's 500 dollars for you.
- How does it stay attached to her?
- It's for your magnet show.
- Really?
- Yes.
(While many investors gave in
to capitalist society...)
Jae Suk, I'm at the bottom.
Please help me out.
Then let's share the information
we got with each other.
Information? Okay. I agree.
I'll get information
on that company.
A biotechnology company?
- F Biotechnology.
- F Biotechnology?
I'll get information
on F Biotechnology.
(Jae Suk came to buy information
on F Biotechnology as he promised.)
Can I get information
on F Biotechnology?
- Level 1 or 2?
- Level 2.
(He bought Level 2 Information
on F Biotechnology.)
(F Biotechnology put the rumor about
its clinical trial failure to rest.)
(And its stock price increased.)
(F Biotechnology stock prices
will increase!)
(It increased a lot,
but it will increase even more?)
(He found out that F Biotechnology
stock will increase again!)
Thank you.
(He found out that F Biotechnology
stock will increase again!)
- So many people have come here.
- What did you find out?
- You look excited.
- Sorry?
- Which company did you check out?
Which company did you check out?
Well, I just...
He won't tell us.
Ji Hyo!
(He calls Ji Hyo
to share the information!)
F Biotechnology stocks will rise.
- F Biotechnology?
- Yes, its stock will rise.
It may not increase sharply,
but buy some of its shares.
(With the information
that she got from Jae Suk...)
I'll invest all I have
in F Biotechnology.
(Staying alert
not to let anyone hear him...)
I'll pull out of I Chemical
and invest in F Biotechnology.
- Will you sell all of it?
- Yes.
(Yoo Jae Suk's account balance)
Let me see. How much is it?
I have 28 dollars.
I'll buy extra shares of I Chemical
worth 20 dollars.
It's 35 dollars.
Oh, that's last year's price.
Gosh. I should've bought it
last year.
Then I'll just have to hold on.
(He has no choice but to hold on to
I Chemical stocks for another year.)
Hold on to it!
(Lee Kwang Soo's account balance)
First...
(Se Chan got information on
I Chemical from Kwang Soo.)
I'll buy 250 shares
of F Biotechnology.
(Earlier on, Jae Suk found out that
F Biotechnology stock will rise.)
Thank you.
(And Se Chan
observed him carefully.)
(You look excited.)
(Se Chan sensed his excitement
from his smile.)
(After looking around,)
(he followed Jae Suk.)
(Jae Suk and Ji Hyo shared tips
without knowing anything.)
(Se Chan slyly approached them
without missing the chance.)
(And he successfully eavesdropped
on the news about the increase!)
(He quickly bought as many shares of
F Biotechnology as he could.)
(Could Se Chan hit the jackpot
again this year?)
(Time's up
for the investments of 2017.)
Let's find out.
Since I earned a lot
in the first year...
- I just need to beat Ji Hyo.
- I can't give up to the end.
I hope I don't end up
at the bottom.
You're incredible.
That's not true. I have more money
in here... Why do I have money here?
He looks different somehow.
Where do you get so much money?
- Where did all the money come from?
- How much are these worth?
- They're 500-dollar bills.
- 500 dollars?
You look handsome today.
After the prices are revealed,
I'll...
hand out some pocket money.
- Sure.
- Thank you, sir!
- Sir.
- How about this?
Once the prices are revealed,
- throw your money into the air.
- What do you say?
Hold on a second.
- That's not a bad idea.
- Right?
- Just throw it.
- Wait a second.
I should change these into bills.
Throw money into the air
in smaller bills...
depending on the stock prices.
- Where will you throw them at?
- 2,000 dollars.
In the air?
We're all done here.
(He's ready to receive the money.)
- Mr. Yang!
- I...
- Once the price skyrockets...
- Live long and prosper.
I...
(Money will rain down
if the stock price skyrockets.)
- What are you doing here?
- It should be done.
- Did you go all-in?
- Yes.
Well, I invested
10,000 to 20,000 dollars...
in the stocks I have.
Unbelievable.
- He can't lose, can he?
- I can't.
Patience will prevail.
But you haven't been patient at all.
How can you be patient
with just 50 dollars?
Just buy yourself
a snack or something.
- You...
- With 50 dollars?
How much do you have in total?
I have more than Ji Hyo.
- Really?
- You'd be surprised.
It's all about who ends up losing.
- It's the New Year.
- Happy New Year.
- Just this once...
- I...
- Patience will prevail.
We're aging too much today.
Come on. Let's do this.
(Ji Hyo and Jae Suk invested
everything in F Biotechnology.)
Gosh, please.
Let the price skyrocket.
(Se Chan also invested
a lot in F Biotechnology.)
Let the price skyrocket.
Hold on a second.
(The stock prices are revealed.)
Ji Hyo, check out F Biotechnology!
Guys!
Here you go!
(The 2018 Stock Market)
(F Biotechnology: plus 150 percent,
I Chemical: minus 14 percent)
Ji Hyo, check out F Biotechnology!
(F Biotechnology skyrocketed
and ended at 150 percent!)
Jae Suk!
(F Biotechnology: plus 150 percent)
(Meanwhile, I Chemical plummeted.)
(Kwang Soo was betrayed
by I Chemical.)
Ji Hyo, check out F Biotechnology!
Guys! Here you go!
(Chairman Yang's asset increased
by investing in F Biotechnology.)
(It's raining money!)
The stock price skyrocketed!
It skyrocketed!
(The money has small investors
spinning out of control.)
Jae Suk!
(The polarization of wealth
has become more serious.)
- No way.
- Unbelievable.
I sold F Biotechnology
and bought E Biotechnology.
I lost money
on all the investments I made.
F Biotechnology.
We should've invested
in F Biotechnology.
- You too, right?
- I'm in the red.
- Okay, I'm good.
- Jae Suk,
but the oil price went up.
- What?
- Why did I Chemical drop?
It's obvious it will drop.
- But the oil price went up.
- I Chemical...
That probably has nothing
to do with I Chemical.
But that was
the information I received.
But if the oil price goes up...
(An increase in cost
will lead to less earnings.)
Wouldn't I Chemical's stock price
go up?
Oh, no.
F Biotechnology...
I shouldn't have sold
the stocks I had.
I kept on mentioning
biotechnology companies.
(Even in a mock investment,)
(biotechnology keeps
disappointing him.)
(Meanwhile, Yang and Rich
now has over 70,000 dollars.)
You earned more once again?
You earned another 100,000 dollars?
My balance is now close
to 100,000 dollars.
(Chairman Yang
is close to having 100,000 dollars.)
- Unbelievable.
- I should get myself a driver.
I keep...
- I keep earning money.
- You should...
- give yourself a nickname.
- Like what?
- Dongducheon Braised Monkfish.
- Braised Monkfish?
- That's worth 500 dollars.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
He earned a lot as well.
(Jae Suk won the jackpot
with F Biotechnology too.)
(An increase of 150 percent
couldn't taste sweeter.)
(Nice!)
How many zeroes are there?
I have close to 10,000 dollars now.
(She went from being in the red
to having 10,000 dollars.)
What do I do?
I'm doomed.
Which jerk said to be patient?
Who said that?
When will mine go up?
(He waited, but the stock price
fell to the floor.)
Kwang Soo...
He's got nothing.
Let me see.
There's nothing I can do now.
How much do you have?
29,000 dollars? Wait.
You have 2,900 dollars?
(You have 2,900 dollars?)
But I have more than 3,000 dollars
in my hand right now.
Hold on a second.
Aren't you going to invest that?
- Should I invest it with you?
- I mean,
I was told to be patient.
You're just being stubborn.
I'm leaving the stock market
once I earn back my seed money.
(He couldn't look
more pitiful from behind.)
There's no way I can come in last.
I should enjoy my life
from here on out.
You must be smelling
the scent of money from here.
(The tall investor reacts
to the scent of money.)
Maybe a seagull will snatch it up.
Are there no seagulls here?
Maybe one will snatch it up.
All right!
(Smirking)
The humiliation...
I'll have this change my life!
Here I come!
(August of 2018)
Time sure flies.
(It's already the fall of 2018.)
(The 2018 Stock Market)
I Chemical and J Shipbuilding.
J Shipbuilding is on the rise.
J Shipbuilding
has been doing better.
(Suk Jin looks to J Shipbuilding
to change things around.)
Wait. What was its original price?
300 dollars?
Kwang Soo,
- check J Shipbuilding.
- J Shipbuilding?
I'll check I Chemical.
- Biotechnology...
- I Chemical should do better.
I'll get information on it.
It should be on the rise by now.
Check J Shipbuilding, all right?
(They agree to check J Shipbuilding
and I Chemical respectively.)
(Kwang Soo's here for
information on J Shipbuilding.)
- I'll check I Chemical.
- You have 60 points.
You can buy
the Level One Information.
"The US invests in
solar energy generation."
(The US invests in
solar energy generation.)
Isn't this a Korean company?
(The US invests in
solar energy generation.)
I'll get information on the chemical
and shipbuilding industry.
This is about
the shipbuilding industry.
(A large heavy industry company
wants to take over J Shipbuilding.)
(The US invests in
solar energy generation.)
These are both good news.
Can I get some information too?
(The pointless man enters.)
Did you check on...
- the shipbuilding industry?
- Yes.
I'll trade the information
for 500 dollars.
Really?
- Okay, I'll share.
- The shipbuilding industry.
You must've earned quite a lot.
I'll give you 500 dollars.
Kwang Soo,
I'll give you 1,000 dollars not to.
Sure thing.
(Kwang Soo changes his attitude.)
- Come on.
- Good.
- Must you be like this?
- Gosh.
You're already in a solid lead.
Still, I can't afford to
let you earn any more.
- You're in second place.
- The information...
is crucial though.
I'll buy it for 500 dollars.
Give it to me first.
Let me see it.
There's nothing I can do
with this money anyway.
I don't get what this means though.
"The best radish is..."
- Are you kidding me?
- What does this mean?
"The best radish is..."
(Stop fooling around.)
- Hand it over.
- This was the information.
- Give it to me.
- "The best radish is..."
- "Joseon radish."
- Hand it over!
How is that the information?
- "The best radish is..."
- Hand it over.
- I don't get what this means.
- "The best radish is..."
- Is it Joseon soy sauce?
- Joseon soy sauce?
Joseon radish is the best?
Hello,
I'm Jeon So Min,
the life of Running Man.
As you can see,
they've teamed up as duos.
Meanwhile, I've been off on my own.
Do you invest in stocks?
You don't?
Who here invests in stocks?
Anyone? Mr. Kang.
Do you invest in stocks?
- A little.
- Do you?
C IT,
J Shipbuilding, and I Chemical.
Which one should I invest in?
- C IT.
- C IT?
(So Min's ears prick up
at his answer.)
- Are you sure?
- No, I...
So Min, why are you all alone?
Well...
- Are you and Chan Hee a team?
- Yes.
- We are.
- He invests in stocks too.
- So I heard.
- Yes, that's right.
He invests in stocks.
Mr. Kang.
Thank you.
What use would he have
for that money?
He would have no use for this.
He gave me some information.
Thank you.
- This is killing me.
- Let's get to work, people.
(It's already November.)
What matters the most...
is how we do in the latter years.
- Ji Hyo...
- Do you have enough for...
three pieces of information?
No, only one.
Should I get the information?
Wouldn't the stock price rise?
- Check on B Entertainment.
- B Entertainment?
- We'll share, right?
- Of course.
(She'll buy information
on B Entertainment.)
(What's the Level 2 Information
on B Entertainment?)
Okay, here you go.
(What's the Level 2 Information
on B Entertainment?)
(No Japan Movement: B Entertainment
gets linked to patriotism.)
"No Japan Movement."
(The stock price rises.)
B Entertainment gets linked
to patriotism...
and the stock price rises.
(B Entertainment's
stock price rises?)
We'll go for B Entertainment.
I'll go all-in.
- Thank you so much.
- Let's do this.
Ji Hyo, that was
a Level Two Information, right?
(Ji Hyo decides to go all-in.)
I'll sell everything I have...
and buy B Entertainment's stocks.
(B Entertainment: 7,764 shares)
I'll readjust my portfolio.
- B Entertainment, please.
- B Entertainment?
- Yes.
- With everything you have?
J Shipbuilding is on the rise.
(J Shipbuilding: plus 25 percent)
How much was that originally?
300 dollars?
(He's been analyzing
J Shipbuilding for minutes.)
(Suk Jin's been eyeing
J Shipbuilding for a while now.)
The shipbuilding industry
had a hard time winning contracts,
but it's been solid these days.
The shipbuilding industry
hit bottom in recent years.
(On his own,
he analyzes the industry.)
I'm a little confused though.
I can't remember if the industry...
started to tick up in 2018 or 2019.
The shipbuilding industry
gets better, but when?
(He's been waiting for the industry
to be on the rise.)
I should just go all-in.
To win, I need to take a chance.
It's already hit bottom.
(Suk Jin mumbles by himself.)
J Shipbuilding.
I'm going all-in.
- You'll sell the other shares?
- That's right.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo...)
I have 1,300 dollars.
- I Chemical.
- I Chemical?
(He invests everything he has
in I Chemical.)
It should be on the rise by now.
It should be.
It can't just continue to
plummet like this.
That I'll give you.
- I Chemical's a good move, right?
- I'm bored now.
I Chemical?
I Chemical...
Yes, it's about time
the stock price went up.
It ticks up slightly
only to plummet.
Those tend to skyrocket.
What's your take on J Shipbuilding?
Not bad, guys.
(Suk Jin makes it seem obvious
that he invested in J Shipbuilding.)
I invested 20,000 dollars.
(I invested 20,000 dollars.)
To win, I need to take a chance.
- I had to go all-in.
- Our conversation...
"I poured it all in.
It went all in."
Those expressions...
- "We pumped into it."
- "I went all-in. I bet everything."
- "I bet everything."
- The things we say...
- In the end...
In the end, being in halfway
doesn't mean anything.
I don't think I can ever
invest in stocks.
- You need to invest everything.
- It's making me dizzy.
It's better to just
work hard instead.
- I'm not making any money.
- It's here again!
- Keep going!
- Let the price go up!
Happy New Year!
Let's be healthy!
Merry Christmas!
We're aging really fast.
- Please...
- Ji Hyo.
- Jae Suk.
- Let's go, let's go!
J Shipbuilding!
- Please...
- J Shipbuilding!
(Ji Hyo and Jae Suk invested all
of their money in B Entertainment.)
(Kwang Soo decided to stick
with I Chemical until the end.)
J Shipbuilding!
(And these four safely invested
their money in various stocks.)
(How will the stock market
of 2019 turn out?)
(This year, last year, fluctuation)
- 500 dollars!
- Yes!
(This year, last year, fluctuation)
Jae Suk!
I can't believe this.
(The 2019 Stock Market)
(B Entertainment increased
by 50 percent.)
(I Chemical increased
by 7 percent.)
(J Shipbuilding decreased
by 20 percent.)
- 500 dollars!
- Yes!
(B Entertainment increased
by 50 percent.)
Jae Suk!
(They gained a 50 percent profit.)
- Ji Hyo!
- Jae Suk.
- Yes!
(They're about to
turn their lives around.)
That was amazing, Jae Suk.
Ji Hyo!
(It increased!)
Seven percent?
(It increased by 7 percent?)
(J Shipbuilding
dropped by 20 percent.)
That's it, we've all gained
50 percent.
- That's amazing. Jae Suk.
- We made it.
Suk Jin, J Shipbuilding's
stock price dropped.
- It's down again.
- I told you about IT, didn't I?
- We...
- He invested in J Shipbuilding.
Jae Suk.
Your hunch is amazing.
You can just leave
F Biotechnology as is.
If you just leave it there,
it'll keep increasing its value.
(Crooning)
Won't a goose fly by
and pick this up?
(He smells the money going loose.)
(Kwang Soo the goose appears again.)
(The penniless birds have gathered.)
(Crooning)
(A collision occurs.)
(Give it to me!)
(They were meant to be rich
stock investors in the beginning.)
Hold on, your lips cracked.
Oh, no. I bumped my lips into his.
It's so gross.
- We don't even have pride.
- It's about time it increases.
At 100 dollars...
It's the last round, right?
- It's the last one, right?
- It is the last one.
But I know how this round
will turn out.
I don't think I'll get 2nd place.
I was in 2nd place before.
Now I have 16,000 dollars.
Oh, no.
How come J Shipbuilding
is not increasing at all?
(Kwang Soo's account balance
increased by little.)
The price increased,
and this is all I have?
Why did I think of
the word "holding out"?
How much did you make, Jae Suk?
I have around 60,000 dollars.
- What? Really?
- You earned that much?
- Yes.
- But this can't be.
(He can almost afford
to buy an E-Class.)
You earned that much?
(Jae Suk is behind Se Chan
by 16,000 dollars.)
He earned a lot.
I invested steadily.
I have only 74,000 dollars?
- What did you say?
- Why did you say it like that?
- What?
- What did you say?
- That's a funny way to put it.
- You pronounced it wrong.
- Are you okay?
- I meant 74,000 dollars.
In virtual games like this,
it's okay
as long as I don't place last.
1st and 2nd places,
and the last one.
The rest means nothing
other than those three.
The ones in the middle
mean nothing.
I'm sorry,
but who are you talking to?
(Embarrassed)
Who are you talking to?
There's no one around.
No one is listening.
There was no one who nodded.
- What's worse is that...
- He just said whatever he wanted.
What's worse is that
the cameras weren't shooting him.
- No one's listening to you.
- The thing is...
Who are you talking to?
I was talking to everyone.
- Everyone?
- I was talking to everyone.
- Oh, Dongducheon?
- Yes.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
You picked the right one.
(Counting how much Ji Hyo has)
- What's going on?
- She picked the right one.
What happened, Ji Hyo?
(She has 23,000 dollars already?)
Look at this. Ji Hyo...
(Gosh, you poor thing.)
- Ji Hyo.
- She earned 15,000 dollars.
- Ji Hyo, you did it.
- Jae Suk.
- Thank you!
- Did you make a lot?
- Jae Suk.
- Did you go all-in?
It's all thanks to you!
(Thanks to her mentor,
Ji Hyo was revived.)
- IT stocks?
- Will I Chemical increase?
(Kwang Soo realizes
he's in trouble.)
It will increase, but I don't think
it will increase by a lot.
It's good that you invested
in I Chemical.
If I Chemical doesn't increase,
I have no hope.
Should I switch to IT stocks?
IT stocks aren't bad.
- You think they'd work?
- I just...
(Unlike I Chemical,
IT stocks got positive reviews.)
(Ji Hyo rose to the top
by investing in B Entertainment.)
(If he wants to beat Ji Hyo,
he needs to win big.)
- Information on D IT, please.
- Okay.
(With the points he saved,
he buys information on D IT.)
Who doesn't know this?
Everyone around the world
knows this.
("COVID-19 breaks out.)
(The high-level information
Kwang Soo got)
(He earned information that
everyone around the world knows.)
Does that mean the price dropped?
(But this is his first time where
he got all the words from the info.)
Jae Suk, it's D IT.
(When he has no clue,
he asks Jae Suk for help.)
If COVID-19 breaks out,
will the price increase?
Game companies'
stock prices increase...
because everyone stays inside.
(Game companies' stock prices
increase due to COVID-19?)
You mean IT stocks?
Because of games?
Of course.
(D IT already increased
by 43 percent.)
(Will it increase again
due to COVID-19?)
Invest it all in D IT.
I'll go all-in on D IT.
- You're going all-in on D IT?
- Yes, this is the last round.
I can't remember it clearly.
Shipbuilding stocks did increase.
- I think you're right.
- Right?
- A major company takes it over.
- Does it?
- I saw the hint.
- You did?
I told you, a major company
takes it over.
That's why 20 percent dropped.
That's right. That's why the major
company is taking it over.
- If it takes over...
- What will happen then?
- It will increase instantly.
- I invested 100 dollars in it.
If a major company takes over,
its price will increase instantly.
Okay. I'll buy them all.
- Didn't I do a good job?
- You did.
If you make a lot,
share some with me.
But I was going to buy
these stocks anyway.
I'll buy 200 dollars more.
(Suk Jin spends all his money
on J Shipbuilding.)
I should bet to win.
It will increase, right?
I'll invest it all
in E Biotechnology.
All of it.
Please invest all of it in D IT.
So that's all for
the 2019 stock market, right?
I think IT stocks
will increase a lot too.
(The nouveau riche is being chased
by Jae Suk.)
I'm going to invest it all...
- in C IT.
- What?
(The two richest investors
invest in C IT and D IT.)
Please gather around.
It's okay as long as
I'm not in last place.
I'm in last place right now.
Who is in last place?
Happy New Year!
We're almost there! Please!
It's Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
(They spend
the last Christmas together.)
(All of their fates
can be changed.)
- The bell is going to ring!
- Please, please.
- It's the last round, right?
- Please, IT stocks!
(The results
will determine the winners.)
Please, please!
(Currently,
Se Chan is in 1st place...)
(with his investment in C IT.)
(Jae Suk, who invested in D IT,)
(is in 2nd place.)
(Ji Hyo invested in D IT. Jong Kook
invested in E Biotechnology.)
(J Shipbuilding,
C IT, D IT, D IT)
Please!
(What will be the results
of the last stock market?)
(The 2020 Stock Market)
- Yes!
- Jae Suk!
IT!
- IT!
- Jae Suk!
(C IT increased by 67 percent,
D IT increased by 60 percent,)
(J Shipbuilding decreased
by 50 percent.)
(D IT made it!)
Ji Hyo!
(He's overwhelmed by the profit
he made after a long time.)
C IT increased by 67 percent.
(C IT increased more than others?)
Wow, B Entertainment
increased by 100 percent.
Look at J Shipbuilding.
It decreased by 100 percent.
B Entertainment
increased by 100 percent.
(J Shipbuilding decreased
by 50 percent.)
(He looks like he just lost
half of all his fortune.)
B Entertainment
increased by 100 percent.
(J Shipbuilding's price plummeted.)
Suk Jin.
Are you okay?
He lost all his money
on J Shipbuilding.
Suk Jin!
I'm Suk Jin who invested
in J Shipbuilding!
(J Shipbuilding's stock
didn't increase in the end.)
- What happened, Suk Jin?
- I told him several times.
- He was so stubborn.
(He needs to be alone for a while.)
It decreased by 100 percent.
(He ended up losing
50 percent of his money.)
- Gosh.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- I told you to buy B Entertainment.
- Thank goodness I sold it.
I Chemical dropped again.
Thank goodness you sold it.
- The rankings must've changed.
- We don't know how they changed.
Suk Jin...
- Suk Jin.
- I'm Suk Jin...
who invested in J Shipbuilding!
Well done, Suk Jin.
I'm Suk Jin who invested
in J Shipbuilding!
- His face turned red for real.
- I'm so dizzy.
Seeing Suk Jin react that way
makes it feel so real.
I know. What is this?
- But...
- He's horrible with stocks.
it's because Suk Jin only
trusted his guts.
- He never listened to the others.
- I know.
It's the same in reality.
How could a stock worth 250 dollars
drop to 10 dollars?
- How could he...
- I know.
Won't that put me in last place?
Let's check out the rankings.
I put everything in biotechnology
stocks because everyone told me so.
Me too.
I was in second place.
Please, please!
The ones in 1st and 2nd place
get prizes,
and the one in last place
gets the punishment.
3rd place is Ji Hyo
who made 37,000 dollars.
(3rd place, Song Ji Hyo,
37,182 dollars)
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- She went up to third place!
- Ji Hyo quietly...
- She was in last place.
- She even went below zero!
- I really did.
Many people make money by sticking
to the ones who are good at stocks.
When I followed Jae Suk,
the stock price dropped.
4th place is Jong Kook
who made 19,960 dollars.
(4th place, Kim Jong Kook,
19,960 dollars)
I made that much.
Fifth place is So Min.
- That's not bad.
- Not bad.
- In the last round...
- At least I'm not in last place.
6th place is Haha
who made 16,350 dollars.
- I'm safe, right?
- Yes.
The difference between
1st and 2nd place is around 10,000.
First place...
(Jae Suk invested quietly
and steadily in substantial stocks.)
(Se Chan led the stock market
from the beginning.)
is Se Chan who made
110,000 dollars.
- That's amazing.
- He made 100,000 dollars?
- 110,000 dollars!
- I should've invested it all.
I made 110,000 dollars
after spending 30,000 dollars?
Jae Suk made 93,000 dollars.
- He did well.
- 93,000 dollars.
- Wow, you're the master.
- My goodness.
- He did well.
- Now,
it's a battle among
the ones who made the least.
But my stock
increased by 60 percent.
- Among the two...
- Please.
I'm Suk Jin who invested
in J Shipbuilding!
In the previous round,
- I was in 2nd place.
- You're apart by 500 dollars.
My stock increased by 60 percent
in the last round.
The seventh place
who barely avoided the penalty.
(The difference between the two
is only 540 dollars.)
(Who came in 7th place
between Suk Jin and Kwang Soo?)
The seventh place...
(Who came in 7th place
between Suk Jin and Kwang Soo?)
Congratulations, Kwang Soo.
(Congratulations, Kwang Soo!)
(Lee Kwang Soo's account balance)
(7th place, Lee Kwang Soo)
Suk Jin made 8,260 dollars.
I'm Suk Jin who invested
in J Shipbuilding!
(His love for shipbuilding
cut his profit in half.)
Shipbuilding...
You went around and gave
lectures on stocks. Look at you now.
- This is...
- How did you...
How did it drop to that
from 20,000 dollars?
You set a new record.
He's getting the penalty
for six weeks in a row.
Didn't you fly a kite last week?
(He's getting the penalty
for 6 weeks in a row.)
- That's amazing.
- The week before that,
- he wrote a letter of apology.
- I did too!
- I saw him on my way home.
- He also made dinner with me.
That's amazing.
- It's really six weeks in a row.
- You wrote a letter of apology too.
But what did he do so wrong?
What did I...
I really thought I wouldn't
get the penalty.
I really thought
I wouldn't be in last place.
- I thought I'd never lose my money.
- You said that earlier too.
He kept saying he wouldn't
end up in last place.
- I thought I'd never lose my money.
- Seriously.
He doesn't accept the fact
that he's bad at it.
I was going after
the 1st or 2nd place.
- That's why I went all-in.
- His eyes are shining brightly.
Suk Jin, I think you're bad at it,
so stop investing in stocks.
That's not it. I never thought
I'd end up in last place.
- He thought he'd win.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
Today's prize...
Today's race
was Genius Investors Race.
This is the staple food of Koreans.
1st place wins 40kg of rice,
and 2nd place wins 20kg of rice.
It must be heavy.
You're giving us rice because
it's stock investment special.
But Suk Jin has to carry the rice
to their cars.
- That's the penalty.
- Gosh, that hurts my pride.
- But Suk Jin is way older than me.
- I know.
Put it in my trunk, Suk Jin.
- You're so cheeky.
- Please put it in my trunk.
- It's not easy to carry rice.
- It must be troublesome.
- They even brought a carrier.
- It must be heavy.
Oh, no. This is kind of sad.
What is this?
- It suits him though.
- It really suits him.
- A carrier suits me?
- There's a cane too.
It's an excellent
squatting exercise.
(He starts delivering the rice to
the houses of 1st and 2nd places.)
He made some money
in the beginning, and that was it.
(He had no idea it'll turn out
this way.)
(A shameful past
where he acted up and bluffed)
(Everyone, if you invest like I did,
you'll go under.)
My gosh. This is so annoying!
(A man's wailing ASMR)
Where is it? Where's your car?
Can you put this down for me?
(It's not that big of a penalty,
but he's a lot of work.)
Hold on.
(All the female staff
members ended up helping him.)
(He takes a short break thanks to
the help of the younger people.)
We need a rod to make it stand.
A rod?
Gosh, I shouldn't have
bet all my money on it.
Is this Jae Suk's car?
Did you put mine in my trunk?
I did.
You should've put it
in the passenger's seat.
Come on.
Don't invest too much
in one company.
Suk Jin, if you have any questions
about stocks, ring me up.
- Ring me up, okay?
- Gosh, this hurts my pride.
- You have to listen to me.
- He's a total rookie though.
That way, you'll succeed.
Bring the carrier back inside.
Gosh. Don't invest too much
in one company.
- Suk Jin, bring that rice.
- I'm on my way.
(Suk Jin bitterly went home
after delivering the rice.)
(A week later)
(Smiling broadly)
(Long life, healthy, blessing)
(A birthday table...)
(filled with words of blessings)
What's this? My goodness.
- Look at this.
- It's quite cold.
- Hello.
- This is...
Are you serious? "Age doesn't
matter, your heart is what matters"?
- What's this?
- You're telling us to tell our age?
- Gosh, that startled me.
- My goodness.
- I thought something bad happened!
- Hey.
- Here we go.
- Hey, hey!
It totally startled me.
- Don't we have to bow?
- By the way,
people don't really
have this kind of party.
Isn't this what you see at your
60th birthday party?
- Why would you put pears here?
- He's already 60?
Hold on.
Are we having the party early?
- Do we also light candles?
- Why did you put the candles?
Hello!
- Hello.
- Wow.
- What are you doing?
- What's all this?
- I haven't seen this for a while.
- What's this?
- Isn't this fake?
- It is fake.
- Right?
- Did he die? No, right?
- Come on, Haha.
- That's why I bowed only once.
- We all did.
Why did they have to use
that photo?
- I know, he looks like Im Ha Ryong.
- Out of all photos...
"Age doesn't matter,
your heart is what matters"?
I think it should be the other way
around for Suk Jin.
"Your heart doesn't matter,
your age is what matters."
That's right.
(Suk Jin's true heart only exists
in the stock charts.)
- Your heart doesn't matter.
- Your age is what matters.
- Look at the cake.
Even the font is so old-fashioned.
You didn't pay much attention
to Suk Jin,
and you just wanted
to make it funny.
- You're going to make him cry.
- Isn't this too mean?
It really looks like
an ancestral rite table though.
But he had a good life.
This is why everyone brought
their gifts for him.
I really got a good one.
- I...
- Actually, Suk Jin...
doesn't really like gifts.
- He likes things that are hopeful.
- That's right.
Something like information
on stocks.
Something like that.
Or introducing a rich man to him.
- Something hopeful like that.
- He likes that kind.
- Introducing a rich man.
- That's right.
- He likes new connections.
- He loves that.
Suk Jin doesn't care for gifts.
For a man of Suk Jin's age,
it's best to eat good foods...
and go to a good place.
- That's right.
- Right?
- Watching something fun...
- Us spending time with him...
is the greatest gift.
The best gift for him
is us calling him often.
- That's right.
- Exactly.
Talking to him on the phone
for more than a minute.
- Or sending a long text.
- Gosh, you brats.
Today,
you're the residents of
Running Village.
Is that so?
There's a joyous occasion
in Running Village.
That's right, it's a party.
It's the birthday party of the elder
of the village, Ji Suk Jin.
Based on
the date of our shoot, tomorrow,
- February 10...
- It's tomorrow.
- is Suk Jin's birthday.
- He's here.
Let's welcome the star of today,
Ji Suk Jin!
(Everyone warmly welcomes him.)
Suk Jin!
What's that? Why did they
make him wear those?
- I know.
- Don't make fun of him!
(Looking old)
(Why did they make him wear those?)
Don't make fun of him!
My gosh, we wish you good health!
Stop it!
Why am I the only one
wearing this?
I thought everyone else
was wearing this.
Let's put him up in the air.
Stop it! Don't!
(Dancing joyfully)
- Yes!
- Thank you!
- Suk Jin.
- Be healthy!
- Grandpa.
- We wish you good health.
- Stay healthy.
- So Min learned that dance.
- So Min is good at that.
- Hey, you.
(So Min's been showing the dance she
learned from the community center.)
You're good.
You're good!
So Min is good.
She learned it
from the community center.
- You're good.
- Hey.
- We should host him another one.
- I'm the only one wearing this?
- Suk Jin.
- Everyone else is...
- Congratulations.
- Wait.
- It looks warm.
- Congratulations.
Am I a man of nature or what?
- I'm not a man of nature.
- Only think of your health.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Let's see.
- Gosh.
- It's pretty.
What's so pretty?
- You're wearing rubber shoes too.
- Hey.
Don't give me that delighted look.
I hate it.
- Hey, I hate that face.
- You're his role model.
A role model.
- My gosh.
- It suits him.
- He looks especially delighted.
- He's 60.
He looks really delighted,
- so I hate it.
- I feel so happy today.
Hey! What's this?
What is this?
What am I, a grandpa?
Where did they find
those artificial flowers?
Long life and health?
This is insane.
There are many nice photos,
and you used this?
I had a photoshoot recently.
- But that makes him look like...
- What is that?
- Your photoshoot?
- He really looks like...
a grandpa.
(He finds it hilarious too.)
- What is this?
- Suk Jin.
That's what I wore
during a comedy skit!
It suits you so well
that I can't act up.
- I can't say much.
- I can't be flippant.
- Seriously.
- I had a photoshoot.
You know, I find that hilarious.
"Bravo your life!"
It's so funny.
Bravo, bravo
- Bravo your life!
- Life!
Bravo, bravo
Long life, health, and blessing!
Let's shout this together.
Ji-ravo, Ji-ravo!
Ji-ravo!
It sounds weird.
(Good words pour in
for the good day.)
Ji-ravo! Ji-ravo!
Ji-ravo your life!
- Ji-ravo, jee-ravo
- My life, my days
- Ji-ravo! Ji-ravo! Let's go!
- Ji-ravo!
It's like Haribo.
- The staff members are happy too.
- It's nice.
Everyone is genuinely happy.
It's a happy occasion.
You are the oldest member
on variety shows.
- Seriously.
- You have worked for many years.
- Call the Guinness World Records.
- He is living history.
Please live a long life.
- You are making history.
- Guinness World Records...
- would be a stretch.
- Seriously,
this is an incredible feat.
Only a few people born in
the 1960s are on variety shows.
- I know.
- Why are you being so serious?
- It's true.
- That's right.
We should be serious
when it's necessary.
What are you doing?
Show me your dance instead.
(She dances right away
upon Suk Jin's request.)
- He likes it.
- Suk Jin likes it.
- She is good.
- So Min.
- You know,
- your daughter-in-law...
- Her moves are beautiful.
- has beautiful dance moves.
- Seriously.
(The vending machine of dance
has beautiful moves.)
(He loves it.)
Seriously.
Her moves are beautiful.
Suk Jin is happy.
- You are happy, right?
- He is very happy.
- You know,
- She is good.
I didn't get...
why old people liked
traditional music so much...
- back in the days.
- Do you get it now?
I am starting to like it.
- Suk Jin is going along with it.
- Dance.
- I am starting to like it.
- He is asking her to dance.
I like these dance moves now.
So Min is good.
She is very good.
She is quite good for someone who
learned from the community center.
She is especially good at this.
Look at that.
(She twists her shoulders
and wrists excessively.)
- Look at that.
- She is good at this.
She likes that dance move so much.
She is good at this.
Presents are a must
at a birthday party.
The residents of Running Village...
prepared presents for Suk Jin.
They are for you.
My birthday is tomorrow, not today.
- It's fine either way.
- We prepared them with seriousness.
Maybe the daughter-in-law wants
to go first.
- These days,
- It must be a bamboo wife.
- Suk Jin...
- A bamboo wife.
- The thing is...
- Hey.
I have an actual wife.
- This is a new wife.
- Really?
A new wife.
- A new face?
- Yes. A new face.
Summer is coming up.
You should hug it
when you go to bed.
He always dreams of deviating
from his daily life.
No, I don't.
- I ordered it.
- It goes well with your outfit.
(It goes well
with the color of his outfit!)
But...
my wife might be displeased.
A new face.
It will cool you down in summer.
- It's cool indeed.
- Yes.
- There were different sizes.
- Suk Jin,
- it's covered. It isn't cool.
- You must remove the plastic bag...
to have the air go through.
Why would it be cool
when it's covered?
- He is ridiculous.
- It's nice.
He doesn't skip a beat
when it comes to telling a lie.
It's cool. It's nice.
- I prepared something...
- Will you go next?
- so that you can work out.
- What?
- What is it?
- Jae Suk prepared a nice present.
I don't joke around.
Is it a mat?
I prepared it
so that you can work out.
- At-home workout is all the rage.
- That's right.
I prepared it
so that you can work out.
What is it?
- Gateball.
(Gateball!)
- He prepared it with seriousness.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Gateball.
- It's nice.
You should try it.
- I am not old enough to play this.
- You can play it at home.
- It will be a nice exercise.
- All right.
It will be a nice exercise.
Jae Suk is right.
I should have thought
of that present.
I play powerful sports.
I move around a lot.
- A sport like this.
- It's for an at-home workout.
It's for an at-home workout.
That's right.
- You should play it.
- That's right.
- Use it.
- Play gateball.
- Work out.
- Gateball.
Speaking of working out,
you should take this
after a workout.
- It's a supplement for seniors.
- Hey!
- It's protein for seniors.
- It's nice.
- Is this product placement?
- It's protein.
No, this isn't product placement.
- It's protein for seniors.
- Hey.
It's for people who are
as old as your mother.
I swear I saw what took place
at Jong Kook's van this morning.
Gap Jin was putting
this supplement in a box...
when he said, "That's too much.
Take out a few."
He took out a few of them.
(My protein is precious.)
Let's see what Ji Hyo brought.
After you work out and take protein,
you can use this
when you take a shower.
- A shower.
- For you,
I prepared hair growth shampoo.
(Scalp treatment shampoo)
- Scalp treatment shampoo.
- Is this product placement?
- No.
Ji Hyo is really thoughtful.
She said no.
Shampoo and conditioner.
I prepared them...
- for your hair.
- She is thoughtful.
You should take care of your hair.
These are shampoo and conditioner.
- They are nice.
- Right.
Suk Jin doesn't like them.
- You should have bought a big one.
- You are going...
to use them.
Suddenly...
It's Kwang Soo's turn.
I thought of Suk Jin's health.
- To buy this,
- You know...
I went to many places.
- Health is the best.
- Seriously.
I am a healthy man.
In the new year...
We want you to be healthier.
Quit smoking e-cigarette.
- Blow bubbles instead.
- What is that?
Bubbles.
It's for your lung capacity.
- Lung capacity.
- It's for your lung capacity.
Lung capacity? Hey.
Are you that worried about
my lung capacity?
Are you that worried?
I use this a lot in the restroom
at home.
Why?
- I have kids.
- Kids.
- Don't use it in the restroom.
- Why not?
If you slip, you will die.
- Don't use it in the restroom.
- You will die.
You will die.
- If you are bored...
- How heartwarming!
After you shampoo your hair,
- you should blow bubbles.
- If you are lonely...
It will be fun if you use it
during a bath.
If I shampoo my hair...
and blow bubbles in the restroom,
- I will look like a madman.
- No!
You should try it.
- Seriously.
- You might find it fun.
I think you will like it.
I went to many stores to find it.
It's like a festival.
Suk Jin, congratulations.
Health!
- Use it with caution.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Health is the most important.
- All right.
(He continues to blow it.)
- You are doing well.
- "You are doing well"?
- Hey.
- It's so nice.
You are doing well.
That's a big bubble.
You pop the bubbles like this.
It's also a good eye exercise.
A good eye exercise.
I went to many stores to find it.
- What's your present?
- I want Suk Jin to open it.
- Really?
- Yes. It's an actual present.
- Will something pop up?
- No, no.
- Isn't it a bag?
- Yes, it is.
- I prepared a crossbody bag.
- A bag?
It's nice.
(I see.)
(A mission bag for the member
who loves Running Man)
A crossbody bag.
(People who give the presents
have way more fun than Suk Jin.)
- Hey.
- A crossbody bag.
You lose it often.
- I use it at other places.
- It's an extra bag.
I bet you got this...
from the production crew
because you forgot to get a present.
I prepared this as a joke.
There is a real present.
- He went to the department store.
- A real present.
It's no joke.
- Hey.
- A real present.
He actually got a nice present.
Why did you get a nice present?
My goodness.
I got it for real.
To be honest, I don't really like
designer items.
- You like them.
- Suk Jin.
- He looks so happy.
- You can exchange it.
Why can't I stop smiling?
G Brand.
- G Brand.
- Seriously.
Open it.
G Brand.
I got it for real.
There is a receipt too.
- He checked Suk Jin's size.
- He asked the stylist.
I need this to get a refund.
- If I don't like it...
- A refund?
- Are you going to get a refund?
- That came out wrong.
An exchange.
(Se Chan became generous
after making a lot of R money.)
- This is incredible.
- Se Chan is amazing.
- He got shoes.
- I flexed.
(He flexed for the oldest member.)
- He got shoes.
- I flexed.
It's an actual present.
Do you know my size?
- I asked your stylist, Ha Na.
- Really?
(Se Chan checked his size
for a surprise present.)
- Ha Na.
- Yes.
(Peek-a-boo)
(Forget this.)
(He wants a refund
for the cheap rubber shoes.)
(Laughing)
(He got fooled again.)
(He wakes up from his dream
and kicks the air angrily.)
They suit your outfit.
I agree.
- You should put them on.
- Put them on.
- I am so angry.
- Hurry over here.
- Put them on.
- They suit your outfit.
- No!
I won't put them on.
Hurry up.
- I won't put them on.
- Why are you so slow?
The brand is called Fool's Gucci.
Fool's Gucci.
The original shoes were a bit off.
- Seriously.
- These shoes are perfect.
- He looks cool.
My goodness.
- All right.
- I won't wear them!
- These are...
- Fool's Gucci.
- These are K-UGGs.
- K-UGGs.
- You look cool.
- You are set.
- Your outfit is finally complete.
They are shiny too.
Those are K-UGGs.
This is driving me crazy.
- This is driving me crazy.
- They are nice.
- They are perfect.
- All right.
- His previous shoes were a bit off.
All right.
If this makes you happy...
Everybody is happy.
This is nice.
Give me the box.
I need to use it again.
- I need to use it again.
- That's good.
Didn't you use it on
"My Little Old Boy"?
That's right.
It comes in very handy.
- It's nice.
- You used it.
In any case...
In any case, thank you.
(Price is just a number.
It's the thought that counts.)
- Now it's my present that's left.
- What is that?
- It's really big.
- I put in a lot of effort.
It's really big.
You went through a lot.
- Your career spans over 30 years.
- Yes.
- It spans over 28 years.
- 28 years.
I think...
you lived diligently
without taking a proper break.
I want you to sit down
and take a rest.
- Is it a massage chair?
- That way,
you will be able to plan the future.
So I prepared this present.
Sit down, Suk Jin.
It's a proper present.
- What is it?
- It's a drawing book.
Sit down and plan your future.
It's nice.
My goodness.
Artist Ji.
- It suits his outfit.
- It does.
The hat, outfit, and shoes
are a complete set.
Keep a picture diary
of what happens every day.
- Keep a picture diary, Suk Jin.
- Here is the bamboo wife.
This is... This is...
(Keep a picture diary
of your remaining days.)
(They are so considerate
of Suk Jin.)
Give him the present.
Make sure you keep a picture diary
every day.
Seriously.
Father.
Make sure you keep a picture diary
every day.
Okay?
- What?
- Weather, clear.
(Suk Jin's happy day)
Suk Jin, you can color it too.
- I see.
- Song Yi loves it.
(All of them root
for his healthy and long life.)
- It's so nice.
- Shall we take a photo?
- Let's take a photo.
A group photo.
(A group photo is a must
at a birthday party.)
Long life, health, and blessing.
Thank you.
It was nice.
- It was nice.
- Did I hear wrong?
- What?
- Cameramen talk to each other.
Yun Sang just said,
"Tight shot
on the ancestral rite table."
Hey, Yun Sang!
"Tight shot
on the ancestral rite table."
- I am serious.
- This isn't an ancestral rite!
- The ancestral rite table?
- I heard it somewhere from here.
What were you thinking?
Who called it
the ancestral rite table?
I heard someone say that.
You don't know
who Yun Sang is, do you?
Yun Sang?
(Flustered)
A special segment for Suk Jin.
(Which one of them is Yun Sang?)
Ji Suk Jin's Find Yun Sang!
Yun Sang has been on the team
for 11 years.
Yun Sang has been with us
from the early days of the show.
Find Yun Sang!
(For 11 years, Yun Sang has worked
as a cameraman for Kwang Soo.)
(Suk Jin even rooted for Yun Sang.)
(He was on TV many times
as Kwang Soo's cowardly partner.)
(Kwang Soo even hosted his wedding.)
(The living fossil of Running Man,
Choi Yun Sang)
(Where is Yun Sang?)
It's the birthday event
for Mr. Ji-ravo.
Find Yun Sang.
- Find Yun Sang.
- Will he succeed?
Yun Sang has been with us
from the early days of the show.
It's either one of them.
Ji-ravo.
- It's either one of them.
- He narrowed it down a lot.
I saw them
from the early days of the show.
He narrowed it down a lot.
- It's either one of them.
- Ji-ravo.
Suk Jin still has it.
"Suk Jin still has it."
This is fun.
This is...
Yun Sang?
(What?)
Yun Sang.
You didn't answer,
so it must be you.
Yun Sang.
(It's nice to meet you, Yun Sang!)
- Yun Sang.
- Happy birthday.
(He found Yun Sang!)
- Ji Suk Jin!
- Ji-ravo.
- This skill comes from experience.
Ji-ravo Show!
It was so obvious.
- Try putting the ball through it.
- He didn't answer.
- Long life, health, and blessing!
- Stand over there and do it.
Please give him a round of applause.
- Ji-ravo, jee-ravo
(He dreams of a hole-in-one moment
in his life.)
I can't help
but try hard to succeed.
(He plays the background music.)
(Dancing)
(A path to the bravo-worthy life)
Suk Jin, you can do it!
- You can do it!
- Okay!
It's a piece of cake.
(He swings hard
with the members' support.)
(He was always the 1st victim
of Name Tag Elimination.)
(The members' tough affection
that continued on for 11 years...)
(gave him a hard time at times.)
(But he made people laugh
with his weakness.)
- Suk Jin, you can do it.
- You can do it.
(He puts 11 years of sadness
into the ball.)
(Goodbye.)
Ji Suk Jin!
This is driving me crazy.
He still has it.
- He did a good job.
- This is nice.
He is still energetic.
Suk Jin still has it!
Of course I succeeded.
(Take this.)
(Ji-ravo's time flows backwards.)
This is nice.
Suk Jin has strong arms.
- He still has it.
- This is nice.
Suk Jin looks happy.
(Thanks to Ji-ravo,
everyone has a happy time.)
It's so nice.
This is fun.
We will see you next week.
Bye.
That's it for today's Ji-ravo Show.
That was funny.
The residents of Running Village
congratulated Suk Jin today.
The village head...
sent a present to Suk Jin,
the oldest resident,
to wish him a long and healthy life.
This is the real present.
Seriously.
Why wish for a long and healthy life
when I am in my 50s?
- Is it a letter?
- It's a letter.
(What is this letter?)
"Dear Mr. Ji Suk Jin."
"Happy birthday to Mr. Ji Suk Jin,
the oldest resident of the village."
"Were you surprised
by the empty box?"
I haven't checked the box yet.
"For your birthday,
I prepared a surprise event."
"At a place in the village
that is related to 'House',"
"I hid the gold I prepared."
Gold?
"I hope you will find it well."
(Is gold hidden in the village?)
(The village head's
special present,)
(gold is somewhere in the village.)
(The birthday party for Suk Jin
takes a back seat.)
(Even the birthday man
becomes obsessed with the gold.)
(Jae Suk's Home, Kwang Soo's Home,
Jong Kook's Home, Suk Jin's Home)
(A secret is hidden
inside the village.)
(Not all houses are the same.)
(In the mysterious houses,)
(find the hidden gold!)
(The prize of gold...)
(makes everyone greedy.)
(But the box is empty.)
(The village head's present,
gold is missing.)
(It's a scary birthday party.
Where is the gold?)
Who took it?
(Into the House,
It's Time to Find the Gold)