- What's this? - Hello, CEO Ha.
Hello, CEO Jeon.
I started my own business.
What business am I in? Why do I have crayons here?
I should recruit good artists to increase sales.
I learned the business working for CEO Ji.
It's not easy to learn how to run an entertainment agency.
I'm experienced in this business.
What is this?
It will be hung up at the entrance.
You should write down the name of your agency.
- Now? - Yes. Write it down now.
I'm not good at drawing.
Shouldn't this be outsourced?
The CEO isn't supposed to do draw this himself.
It's J Entertainment.
Except for Se Chan, all members have a J in their names.
Jong Kook, Jae Suk, and Ji Hyo.
I don't care about Se Chan.
They all have a J in their names.
Jae Suk, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo.
They all have a J in their names except for Se Chan.
So it's J Entertainment.
DK Entertainment.
Dirty Mustache Entertainment will take care of all your businesses.
Dirty Mustache.
It's JBR World.
It's the world for Petty Gang.
It's a global firm that spreads to the world.
It's Cocoa M Monkey by Physical Contact.
Physical Contact.
I've always wanted to run my own business.
You are the CEO of a new agency...
that will lead Korea's show business industry.
And you need to sign a contract with as many celebrities as you can.
So I have to sign a contract?
The CEOs will fight against other CEOs,
and the celebrities will fight against other celebrities.
Do you see the congratulatory money for your business on the desk?
Yes.
It's for operating your agency, so you can use it as you please.
Do I get real money?
No, it's not real money.
300 dollars?
Do you know when I'm struck with reality?
It's when I find crumpled up R money in my pockets as I undress at home.
"Why did I try so hard to get this money?"
As soon as I go home, I just throw this away.
A lot of celebrities will visit your office soon.
You will negotiate the pay...
and sign a contract with the celebrities you want.
I should sign contracts with good people.
I should share the money with the celebrities.
It's a match among the CEOs.
Are you a CEO or an artist?
Is this a nail salon?
- That sounds good for you. - Isn't that it?
- No. - Is this a cafe?
- No, it's not. - Cocoa...
- Cocoa... - That's not true.
This is a major company.
We shouldn't be doing this.
We should reach an agreement on the distribution of money.
- I know. - The ratio should be...
You are not going to offer more than 50 percent, are you?
- Of course not. - It shouldn't be more than 5 to 5.
- Once we agree on this... - Because...
- You can't run a business on that. - If one of you offers...
too much money,
the rest of us will be in trouble.
The problem is that Se Chan has nowhere to go.
Because...
Even guys like Se Chan...
can be useful if he works 24 hours a day.
It's not like that.
It is a lot better to have one artist who's worth every penny.
- He just eats a lot. - I'm sorry to say this,
- but... - He just eats a lot?
- He eats a lot. - Hey.
- Who is that? - Se Chan.
You're a top star who's here to sign a contract with your new agency.
Am I a top star?
All right. I'm a rising star.
- What do you do? - I'm a comedian.
- A comedian? - Yes.
Take a look around...
and negotiate your pay with an agency you want.
I see.
You will fight against other celebrities...
while the CEOs will fight against other CEOs.
Oh, really? My gosh.
Look at the poor handwriting.
It's so lame.
This is...
Jeon So Min, my gosh.
She looks like a fraud already.
You should come.
DK. Dirty Mustache Entertainment.
"Let's make money. Money. Let's get rich and enjoy, achieve,"
"and share. Let's create a meaningful life."
- This sounds good. - Let's become rich!
- Welcome, Shareholder. - This place sounds good.
- Gosh. Welcome, Mr. Yang Se Chan. - Hello.
- I wanted to hear your offer. - Right.
- Have a seat. - Okay.
- I just want to hear it. - Do you want coffee or green tea?
- I'm okay for now. - Solomon's seal tea?
No, I don't need any coffee.
I would like to get right down to business.
Okay.
- You've been doing well recently. - Right.
So, I... Let me be straightforward.
How much you're willing to give me is important.
How much were you thinking?
Your T-shirt looks so shabby.
- What? - This.
My gosh. This kid.
I'll set you up with a stylist.
- You work alone, right? - No.
- I work with three people. - Stop lying.
- Three people dressed me like this. - Se Chan.
You work alone.
- You're going to dress me up? - First,
I'll get you a stylist.
- You could sit here. - Hold on.
You can sit here.
I like sitting at the head of the table.
I'll honor your wishes.
- In return, I have a condition. - What is it?
Shave your dirty mustache.
If you shave your mustache...
If you're willing to show me your clean face without a mustache...
- Will you shave it? - Okay. Let's go!
- Are you serious? - Yes. Let's go.
Okay. Put it in writing.
No, you can't do that.
- No. - I'll put poop on my hands.
- I'm serious. - It's fine.
Let's play fair!
Hello.
You became a free agent, right?
- What? - You're a free agent.
I become a free agent in July.
What is this? "DK"?
What's this?
I'm changing the interior. Hello.
- Are you the CEO? - Yes.
- This place doesn't suit me. - No, wait.
- You're so capable... - Gosh. This.
- We just started anew. - Is that so?
- This is a bit overwhelming for me. - Hold on.
When the CEO puts a photograph of themselves next to potted plants.
I'm willing to negotiate the terms of your contract...
to fit whatever you want.
- It's usually 7 to 3, - Right.
but in this current situation,
would you be willing to do 8 to 2?
- Is that a bit too much? - Then...
- The celebrity gets eight? - Superstar Yu.
Is there a problem here?
Why don't you come into my office, Superstar Yu?
- Come in for a bit, Superstar Yu. - "Superstar Yu"?
- Nobody is coming into my office. - Hold on.
- Come on in. - Get in line.
- Come with me! - You have no business etiquette.
Hold on.
- Come in. - Hold on. What is JBR?
It's the world for Petty Gang.
- Petty Gang? - It's the Petty Gang World.
The competition between the free agents is stiff.
Okay. I know. Of course.
- This place is crazy. - The competition is stiff.
Se Chan.
What is this? Hold on.
It's money.
Gosh, what is this?
Hold on.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Goodness. - We have a common ground.
- Right. Have a seat. - Gosh, this is...
This is nice.
I was listening to what was going on next door,
and he was trying to seduce you with money.
This is a bit...
- Aren't you doing that too? - No.
- Then I'll be leaving. - No, hold on.
- You're seducing me with money. - No, I'm not.
- This is just a gift. - It's a gift?
- I'll accept it as cab fare. - This is...
Don't think of me as a CEO.
Just think of me as a close friend.
I'm giving you allowance...
- as a friend. - Allowance?
- It's a gift from your heart. Okay. - Right.
What do you specialize in at this agency?
To be honest, you can do...
- whatever you want here. - I see.
Right, and...
As for how we split the pay...
I listen to everything my celebrity wants.
- Is that so? - I'll let you do whatever you want.
I'll be direct with you.
You just need to get rid of the one thing that bothers me.
- Okay. - I really hate...
the thing that bothers me.
Are you willing to...
Your mullet really bothers me.
I cut my mullet...
- From here... - You want me to cut off the rest?
- The rest bothers me too. - You want me to...
- Yes. - cut everything off?
There's a part that flares out.
If you're willing to cut it off for a neat look,
I'll sign the contract...
I'll sign the contract for 6 to 4.
- 6 to 4? - I'll even consider 6 to 4.
The CEO next door said he'd shave off his dirty mustache.
He agreed to it.
He agreed to shave his mustache?
He said he'd shave off everything. That's what he said.
- Then I... - He's very ambitious.
I would love to sign a contract with someone who's willing to shave...
because I hate it when something bothers me.
I don't like it...
when my CEO gets teased...
by other CEOs and artists.
Wait. Hold on.
Are you saying that I'm getting teased...
for having a mullet?
Of course.
You are definitely getting teased.
I hate that.
I don't have any artists in my company yet,
but if I had at least one person,
I would throw...
this coffee in your face.
- This hot coffee? - Yes.
- Is that so? - I'm not one to back down.
- You don't? - No, I don't.
- Hello. - Hello.
I'm Top Star, Song Ji Hyo.
Since you're a free agent now...
Thank you.
All of the agencies...
look a bit sloppy.
I'll take a look around.
In Running Man, the person to have is Jong Kook.
"JBR". Hold on, I...
I'm going to take a look around first.
Superstar Kim!
- Superstar Kim! Come in for a bit. - Why?
- Superstar Kim! - You're touting.
- No. It's not that. - Hold on.
- Have a seat, Superstar Kim. - Okay.
- Have a seat, Superstar Kim. - Where?
- Over here. Have a seat here. - Here? Okay.
- Okay. - Superstar Kim.
- Listen to what I have to say. - Okay.
I'll listen to what you have to say.
- Listen... So this is... - Yes?
- This is the world of Running Man. - Right.
- I think the best star here... - Yes?
is Kim Jong Kook. It's because...
- Thank you. - Yoo Jae Suk is nothing.
- It's not that. - Thank you.
We have to look at your capabilities.
- In the games, who has the brains, - Right.
- speed, - Speed.
- and power? - Power.
Who is it?
It's none other than Kim Jong Kook.
- Honesty, - Right.
- nobody else needs to come. - A celebrity...
needs to be acknowledged...
- for their worth. - Of course.
- I'm for real. - This is the best.
Yang Se Chan, Song Ji Hyo,
or even Yoo Jae Suk,
doesn't compare to you.
You are worth a hundred of them.
- 9 to 1? - 9 to 1?
Isn't 9 to 1 too much?
- What? - Who is that?
- It's Jessi! - Jessi!
Hey.
- Hey! - Hey!
Jae Suk!
Hey, come on!
- Hey, come on! - Hey!
- Jessi! - Hi.
Physical Contact. Physical Contact Entertainment.
- We love physical contact! - Yes.
This reminds me of Hwagae Market.
I feel like I'm at an awards ceremony.
Oh, my. Wooyoung.
Oh, my. Hello.
I...
- Hello. I... - Hello.
- never met CEO Jeon before. - My gosh. CEO Jeon.
What... What are you doing?
Do you like to fish?
CEO Jeon. What are you doing?
She looks like something's frustrating her.
- Hold on, CEO Jeon. - Yes?
Superstar Song, come here.
- Come here. - Okay. Let's have a meeting.
It's not just a meeting. Come have a seat.
- I'll have a meeting with you. - To be honest,
I'm willing to stop here because...
What are you taking out?
I have money.
What is that?
- I'll give you 100 dollars each. - Really?
If you sign with me, I'll give you 100 dollars each.
- This is an incredible deal. - Jong Kook...
I'll give you 100 dollars each,
and the terms of our contract will be...
8.5 to 1.5. Let's do that.
- 8.5? - They're offering 9 to 1, but...
- 8.5 to 1.5? - It's 9 to 1.
8.5 to 1.5.
- I like it. I'll sign. - Okay.
- I like it too. - Okay. I...
I'll go with that.
- I'll sign with you. - I'll sign with you.
Okay!
I really...
Superstar Kim.
- I'm done. - Superstar Song.
Let's work hard together.
- Let's work hard together. - Right.
- Goodness. - Keep this hidden.
- You have a good mentality. - Seriously.
Shall we take a photo together? Here.
- Oh, really? - Let's take one together.
- Let's take a photo. - We need to take a photo?
This is a bit... This is a bit old-fashioned.
- I'm old-fashioned. - We...
I'm a bit old-fashioned.
We're a global company.
We will go abroad.
Sign the contract first.
No. You have to shave your hair off first.
You're signing a contract with an entertainment agency...
The celebrity gets 6, and the CEO gets 4.
This is an incredible deal.
Another agency is talking about a 9 to 1 contract.
The rumors are floating around.
There aren't any 8 to 2. They're all 9 to 1.
Jae Suk. Let's work together.
- We can be Co-CEOs. - This is...
Here, Jae Suk.
I'll give you 9.5, and I'll take 0.5. Okay?
Sign here.
- 9.5 to 0.5. Let's do it. - Is it...
- Is it okay to do this? - Let's do it.
Yang Se Chan will come in when he sees you.
It's because I don't like seeing you enjoy it.
6 to 4.
- I don't like your mullet. - Yoo Jae Suk signed with me!
Okay!
- I'll leave then. - No. Hold on.
- He'll shave and get 6. - No. It's not that.
He signed!
He signed with me!
Wooyoung signed with me!
For example, if you...
have a conflict with it because of another shoot,
- I'll go someplace else. - No, it's not that.
I'll cut it.
I can cut my hair.
I'll cut my hair.
Having a mullet isn't that important to me.
I...
I want CEO Lee...
Jessi has signed with me!
Be quiet!
- Hold on. Okay. I'll be quiet. - Be quiet.
- My gosh. - I need to announce it like this.
I can cut it. Can you hold this for a second?
You have five minutes left!
- You should get a haircut. - The movie was just an excuse.
He thinks it looks cool.
I'm not good at stuff like this. I'm cutting it for real.
This is how I feel.
This shows how I'm feeling.
Fine. I like that.
For you, Se Chan...
My hair means nothing.
Really?
So...
What's the big deal about my hair?
I can even shave my head.
If you move to another agency,
I'll kill you.
I cut my hair for you.
Se Chan.
I'll...
- If you say anything stupid... - All right.
Put it down.
- This coffee is really hot. - I get it.
I'll sign the contract.
- Sign it. - Okay.
All right. I don't want 6 to 4. Let's make it 7 to 3.
- Sign it. It's 6 to 4. - All right.
You may go to your agency now.
- Okay. - I'll see you later.
- Okay. - Okay.
Before we start the first schedule,
you will hold a press conference to promote...
your agency and artists.
A press conference?
You will give a presentation at the press conference.
We're doomed.
He can't give a presentation.
And the artists will get paid after showing off their talents.
What?
Then it's good for So Min's agency.
Jae Suk, you should show your ab muscles.
I don't have ab muscles.
- You don't? - I don't.
You work out a lot.
And he should give a presentation.
So is it like a talent show?
Each team will give a presentation in turn.
The other 3 CEOs, 1 director, and 1 writer...
will give marks to your presentations.
And when the presentations are over,
each CEO and artist will get their own scores.
And you will get paid according to the scores...
from 1,000 dollars for first place to 100 dollars for the last place.
When all the missions are over, the two CEOs...
and the two artists with the least money will get a penalty.
Gosh, we're in trouble.
Jae Suk, I have a question.
You're a famous MC, so I have faith in you. But...
What's your question?
What are you good at?
- I... - I just want to hear it.
The thing is, I don't have a specialty.
- I can do a lot of things. - I know.
- Exactly. - Just a little.
I'll make Jessi a global star.
She speaks English, and she can act as well.
She can show her acting by crying or getting angry...
You should do that.
Can you do things like that?
- We should try acting. - Right. Acting.
We should do something new to get high scores.
A serious love scene.
What are you looking at?
It's not like that. A serious love scene.
It's not like that. Don't pick a fight.
Why does your acting start like that?
- I don't know. - Jessi.
Are you a bully?
- Let's say you two are lovers. - So...
- there should be a storyline. - Sure.
- Let's fight. - We should fight.
What are you looking at?
- What are you staring at? - What?
- What's the matter? - You looked at me first.
Well... Are you a bully?
Yes.
Are you?
- Hey. - All right.
Okay. I'll start by saying "What are you looking at?"
I have great expectations for you.
- All right. I'll go first. - Do you want me to go under?
Okay. I will...
Trust me. I'm strong on practice.
- I trust you, but what can you do? - I'm serious.
I need to know.
Excuse me. What are you looking at?
You looked at me first.
- I didn't. - Are you picking a fight?
I am. What are you going to do about it?
- Why are you picking a fight? - So what are you going to do?
- What do you think? - How was it?
- How was it? - How did you like it?
- It was... - I showed my wrath suddenly.
These days, my anger...
Give me my money back.
Give me.
- All right. - I can do this.
I'll...
Can you do any impressions?
I...
I'm an artist.
I do music and art.
What? "We've signed a contract"?
What? "We've signed a contract?"
- Like "We've got married". - What's the name of this agency?
It's Physical Contact Entertainment.
- It means... - I have a headache.
So we should be intimate like family.
- We have a lot of things to do. - Tell me.
What can we do?
Jong Kook can show off his strength.
So I was thinking about doing this.
You can crack a nut with your buttocks.
- Cracking a nut with your buttocks? - With the buttocks?
How would I do that?
He has muscular buttocks.
Put a walnut on a chair and...
- By sitting down? - By sitting down.
You can crack it like that.
You don't have to squeeze your buttocks to crack it.
You can do it though.
- Cracking a nut by squeezing them? - You can do it,
- but it's not necessary. - I can do that.
- You can, right? - Of course I can.
- We don't have to try that hard. - I know.
And...
- It's not easy to break an egg. - Right.
So you'll try breaking it with your arm.
- With my arm? - On here. You can do this.
I'm sorry, but...
is this a super strength show or something?
Is this a super strength show or something?
No.
Because Kim Jong Kook...
has already reached the top as a singer.
- It's already been proven. - I see.
- So you should show something new. - I see.
CEO Lee, let's do this.
Specialty?
It's not about the specialty. Tell me how you will introduce me.
First...
Se Chan. You're good at finger flicks.
- I am. - I know.
- It can be your specialty. - It is my specialty.
But... I'm a celebrity.
But my specialty is just a finger flick?
You don't have to feel that way.
Oh, okay.
That's a great specialty.
- I know. It's a big deal. - Sure.
So how are you going to introduce me?
Can you put a dent in a car?
That's not my specialty, CEO Lee.
- In other agencies... - Think about them.
Jessi and Jae Suk are...
preparing a show.
And what you want me to do is just a finger flick?
I'd rather pay a penalty and cancel the contract.
We have to show something to get more money.
- Should we prepare a performance? - We should.
There's something that only you can do.
- Actually... - I'm still an active comedian.
If I put together some skits I'm doing now,
I can perform here for a couple of hours.
Kwang Soo, we should give a performance.
I should do the chorus thing.
- "Psychorus"? - Yes. Let's do "Psychorus".
That's something only we can do.
- Sure. No one else can do it. - You're right.
We should pick an easy song.
It should be exciting and has lyrics that are easy to remember.
And it should be something for which we can sing the chorus.
It's Jae Suk's song.
It's Yoo San Seul.
- We will sing Yoo San Seul's song. - A trot song.
Right. We can give a performance with a trot song.
- We can make fun of his looks. - Good.
His everything is ugly
It will be a diss song.
Gosh, this is...
All right. We will start the press conference...
where each agency will introduce their artists.
A press conference.
- We will go public... - You're the most...
- pathetic CEO here. - He's lost a lot of weight.
- That's not true. - You're...
And I saw you walk around with short and quick steps.
Like this.
I put my artists first all the time.
- You do? - They come first.
- That's the basic. - Sure.
Did anyone of you sign a contract of 9 to 1?
- What? - A contract of 9 to 1.
We did.
- Some of us did it as well. - He signed a contract of 9 to 1.
It's better than that.
That doesn't matter anyway.
Your CEO wants to be a celebrity.
What?
Your CEO is very ambitious.
What kind of CEO wears sunglasses like that?
I found that out after signing the contract.
- That the CEO has her own dream. - That's right.
She wants to be a celebrity.
She wants to make her debut using her artists.
The CEO...
"If things don't work out, take a detour."
Excuse me. Let me tell you something.
I've been in many competitions like this before.
Competitions?
Shall we go first?
- She always grabs something. - Will you go first?
How much can you offer?
It's a pun.
- My artist is good at puns. - How much can you offer?
How much can you offer?
- Hang on. - How much?
You are...
The artists in my agency keep telling me...
to say, "What time is it now, Jessi?"
He's supposed to say it himself.
- Why would I say that? - CEO Lee.
- I mean... - You should embrace my joke.
- I'm not a celebrity. - "What time is it now, Jessi?"
You should set an example.
"What time is it now, Jessi?"
We will now begin the press conference to introduce new artists.
The other three CEOs will...
give marks to each presentation...
on a scale of 0 to 5.
And we have two more members to represent the crew members.
They are Director Choi Hyung In and Writer Han Ah Reum.
- Please give us good scores. - That's only fair.
She's a fashionista director.
Right.
- I thought Hyung In was... - She's all dressed up.
And Ah Reum usually wears a cap.
- Ah Reum and Hyung In. - They look great.
They're all dressed up.
- What's this? - It's Dirty Mustache.
DK Entertainment may introduce their artists now.
Nice to meet you. We are DK Entertainment.
Okay.
I'm Dirty Mustache.
- I won't say much. - We're serious.
We have the most popular celebrities here.
What do you think they are doing here?
That's dirty.
Why is that?
This is a free place.
Everyone.
Is this a PR video or something? What is this?
We are...
- Oh, and... CEO Ha. - Yes?
Tell them the terms of my contract.
Everyone will get in line to sign with you.
I can't reveal that.
- Just tell them. - What is it?
- I can't reveal it. - It must be unusual.
- What are the terms? - Wait. Why did you say that?
- Don't reveal it. - Why? Answer me.
- Why would you reveal it? - He'll get to sign with more stars.
- Jessi, cover your ears. - No.
- Jessi, cover your ears. - No, I won't do that.
- Let's talk about it later. - Oh, I guess...
- their terms are different. - Why must I?
- Jessi, how much did he offer? - Do they get paid differently?
- I think they're paid differently. - Let's talk later.
- That must be the case. - CEO Ha...
Jae Suk, the terms of our contracts are the same. Am I wrong?
- Is yours higher than mine? - It's not like that.
- It's not that. - Is he paid more than me?
No.
- I'm sure they're paid differently. - Really?
- Haha. - If that's the case,
Jessi must be upset.
- Trust me. That's not true. - Hyun Ju.
- Is it true? - No, it's not.
- Are you paid higher than me? - I said, it's not true.
- No. - That agency isn't transparent.
- Come back here. - What a dirty business!
- I... - You've been lowballed.
- Jae Suk, do you get 100 percent? - No.
- No, he doesn't. - No.
Hey, I get paid a lot too.
- Why did you say such a thing? - Come on.
- Why would they bring that up? - What kind of presentation is this?
- I mean, - Hey!
why would they reveal the profit-sharing ratio?
- I'm going to... - Jessi.
Hear us out before getting angry, okay?
- You know what I mean, right? - "What Type of X".
- Okay. - Let's go!
- Let's go. Let's get it. - Yes!
Here we go.
Play it louder.
- What? They startled me. - What?
- She's so fabulous. - Jessi!
DK!
- Come on! - DK! Hey!
- DK, DK! - Okay!
DK, DK!
I'd like to point out something.
- That was... - Hey, hey!
Listen. It was...
Excuse me, Jessi. Jessi.
I'd like to clarify something.
It's about your choreography we just saw.
Kwang Soo came up with that dance move.
- Kwang Soo did? - Yes.
- This dance move. - Did she copy his dance move?
- What's that? - That's different.
Show them. He did it first.
See? He did it first.
- Hey, I'm sorry, but... - He did it first.
- You're being unreasonable. - Jessi, you copied his dance move.
- Did I dance like that? - I saw the same dance move.
- It's different. - Exactly.
- No, it's different. - Hey! PSY would never have...
made me do a dance move like that.
Why would she yell at me?
- Just drop it and sit down. - She could've just said it.
- Why would she yell at me? - That's how she talks.
- Okay. Let's accept it. - She didn't yell.
- That's how she talks. - All right.
- That's not all. - Okay.
- She'll show you her dance. - Okay. Let's go.
- Let's see. - Go ahead.
Shall we play the song now?
Let's treat each other...
- Hey! - You know...
My gosh.
- She yells at everyone. - What's this?
This is what's called "talent", okay?
- What do you mean by that? - She just keeps yelling.
If I...
- I told you! - She doesn't care if they're...
- on her team or not. - If I...
If I stop working with this agency,
it wouldn't be because of the CEO,
but because of the celebrity under the same agency.
I'm ready. Let's go.
Play it louder.
- What song is this? - It's "Dance Monkey".
- Oh, that. - Hands up!
Put your hands up!
- Put your hands up. - She'll sing this song?
Did we do something wrong?
She's singing live!
It's a live performance!
- She's singing live. - This is amazing.
She's singing live.
This is really awesome.
Here we go!
- She's so incredible. - Oh, my.
Isn't she amazing?
Jessi!
- Join my agency! - She's incredible.
- Come join us, Jessi! - That was awesome!
- That was insane! - That was amazing.
She did too well when she was the first one. I'm worried.
- Come on! - You saw that, right?
- You saw that, right? - DK Entertainment's superstar...
- Jessi is... - What else do you want?
- Are you satisfied? - That's not all.
- Come on. Come on. - That's not all.
- We should fight now. - Next up is...
- Korea's best MC... - That wasn't all?
- that you all know. - That wasn't all?
It's Yoo Jae Suk's turn.
Thank you.
You'll show your talents only with a mic?
- Yes. - That's a bold act.
I'm sorry,
- but you have no special talents. - That's not true.
- Right here? - I'll just...
- I thought you had no talents. - I will...
- show you just a few things. - Please be quiet.
- You have talents to show us? - Be quiet!
Jae Suk can't do any impressions either.
I can imitate a helicopter sound.
You can do that?
- What was that? - He did it so halfheartedly.
- He has no talents. - Good job.
- He has no talents. - What's that?
- That was good. - I can do it.
- Good job. - Is he a little kid or what?
That was good.
- He'll show you his sense of humor. - Yes.
- He can make good acrostic poems. - Really?
- Give him any words or names... - I'll improvise.
- Any names? - I'll improvise.
Does any one of the staff members want to try it?
- Who? - Chan Hee.
- Cameraman Kang Chan Hee. - Kang Chan Hee.
- Make one with his name. - An acrostic poem.
- Kang Chan Hee? - Start now. 1, 2, 3.
- Kang! - Kang!
Kang Chan Hee.
- Chan! - Why are you speaking in a dialect?
Closely looking at you...
- Good. - Hee!
How ugly!
Thank you.
- Any names would do. - Let's try another name.
This is just the beginning.
- I bet he prepared this one. - Yes.
- Let's give him another name. - I can do it with the name...
- of staff members I've never met. - Wooyoung!
- Wooyoung! Wooyoung! - I can do it.
- Wooyoung. - Pardon?
- Wooyoung. - Okay.
- Ready? 1, 2, 3. Woo! - Woo!
Wooyoung.
- Wait. - What's that?
- That made me uncomfortable. - What was that?
- Why... - Go on. Continue.
- That's not a talent. - Go on.
- He did it in the same pattern. - I can improvise.
You did it exactly the same way.
I can improvise.
You call their names first.
- It's just the same. - How about he tries another name?
- Then this time, I will... - How about Bo Pil?
read your fortune as well.
- What do you mean by that? - I'll make an acrostic poem...
with one of your names...
that predicts your future.
- He'll read our fortune? - That sounds great.
- I will... - Hold on.
Are you saying that fortune-telling is your talent?
- Yes. - That's right.
- You can read others' fortune? - I can read...
- only 5 people's fortune in 1 day. - I've never heard that before.
- An acrostic poem to tell fortune? - Me!
- I want to get my fortune told. - That sounds unrealistic.
- I can read your fortune. - CEO Lee.
- It's Jeon So Min, right? - Yes.
Okay. Jeon... Jeon...
He's shaking so much.
Jae Suk, shall we give you five minutes?
Do you want to take a break?
His lips turned purple.
Don't worry about me.
- Jeon So Min. - 1, 2...
- Three. - Do you want to know your fortune?
- Yes, I do. - All right.
- An acrostic poem too. - Are you trying to buy more time?
- No, I'm not. - You're buying time to think.
- No. I can do it right away. - Really?
- 1, 2, 3. - He's bluffing.
Journey into your past life.
So!
- That must be... - Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, your lips are so blue.
I haven't seen him that anxious in a long time.
He can't stop moving his legs.
- It's because... - He lacks a sense of humor.
I mean, your hand is shaking so much.
Keep quiet.
You can't stop doing the helicopter impression.
He didn't shake the mic to make that sound.
He ruined the company value that Jessi increased.
- Jae Suk ruined it. - Should we write down the score?
0.3 points.
We did well. Okay. Great.
They prepared a lot.
They're doing "Psychorus".
Are you going to do "Psychorus"?
Is it allowed to do his comedy skit he does on another show?
Jessi did the same.
She promoted her new song too.
My gosh. So what are you going to do?
We're going to do Se Chan's comedy skit.
We need your help. We'll pay you.
We'll cast Jae Suk and pay him for his performance.
Are you asking me to sing?
- Yes. - You just have to sing...
40 seconds from the beginning.
- 40 seconds? - How much will you pay him?
I get paid differently...
for a live performance and a lip-syncing performance.
- Why is it so complicated? - How much for lip-syncing?
- Pardon? - It's 20 dollars.
- Only 20 dollars? - Really?
Make it to 50 dollars. It's 50 dollars.
- What about a live performance? - 100 dollars.
- Twice as much? - Yes.
- 100 dollars? - 100 dollars.
But I don't lip-sync the whole song.
I do sing some parts over the recorded voice.
I have only 100 dollars left.
And I should spend it all to hire you?
Then how about 20 dollars for lip-syncing...
- 20 dollars? - 40 dollars for singing live?
Yes, 40 dollars.
Can you mix them for 30 dollars?
- Singing and lip-syncing? - Yes.
- 30 dollars. - Can you do it for 30 dollars?
- Sing just a little bit. - Okay.
- Just sing when you want to sing. - Okay.
- 30 dollars. Okay. - You have to pay him first.
I can give you a discount if I don't have to...
- sing the whole song live. - That's funny.
- It's funny. - Oh, right. I'm sorry,
but will you upload a video clip?
- Pardon? - Of course, we will.
Or else, why would we do this?
- He'll charge you more. - You have to pay me more.
You have to pay extra 20 dollars.
What's the point of doing it if we don't upload the video?
- We can do it all for 20 dollars. - What?
- What song will he sing? - Which song?
- Does it have to be him? - We need Yoo San Seul's song.
- We already prepared a script. - We need a trot song.
You mean, "Hapjeong Station, Exit Five"?
- "Redevelopment of Love". - "Redevelopment of Love".
I can sing that song.
Come on.
We should be paid by him.
- How much? - You should pay us...
- How much? - if you want to sing.
Turn me over completely
No, that's not good enough.
- No way. - I can do it.
- No. - Wait.
- How much? - I'll charge you...
- You should pay us. - I'll charge you only 10 dollars.
Including the video clip...
- Then... - I'll charge you only 10 dollars.
Including the video clip, I'll charge you 40 dollars.
- 40 dollars? - All they want is money.
- 40 dollars. - Why must I spend 150 dollars...
- Let's settle for 40 dollars. - out of the 200 dollars I received?
You see, I rarely perform...
as Yoo San Seul on other shows.
I know.
- They got him in their performance. - Okay.
- Here we go. - Okay.
Play the music.
- Is this "Redevelopment of Love"? - Yes, it is.
We dedicate this song to our mentor who taught us difficult idioms...
- on Running Man. - On Running Man.
- The ugliest man on Running Man... - The ugliest man on Running Man...
- is you! - is you!
- Completely ugly - Completely ugly
He's not singing.
- That won't make you handsome - That won't make you handsome
- Even his crooked teeth - Even his crooked teeth
- 550,000 dollars for total makeover - 550,000 dollars for total makeover
He wants to become a completely different person
But he'll be the same even if he were reborn
- He has low nipples - He has low nipples
J Entertainment will...
- Hold on. - give you a makeover.
Stop. Hang on a second.
- He should sue them. - That's all.
- Shouldn't he sue them? - I'm so upset.
- Tell us how you feel. - Hold on.
- He has low nipples - Hold on.
I will get ready to sue them.
- What do you mean? - Why?
- We properly... - How dare you...
- We didn't mean it like that. - ridicule me...
- in front of all these people? - That's not our intention.
- My career is over now! - We didn't try to ridicule you.
- That's not true. - We didn't humiliate you.
How dare they talk about my nipples?
- Exactly what made you upset? - They talked about my nipples.
Exactly what part?
"His crooked teeth" annoyed me too.
- We had no choice. - We had no choice.
- I'll sue them for defamation. - We said...
I fully understand him.
- You understand me, right? - He was humiliated on stage.
- No. - He wasn't humiliated.
That wasn't our intention.
- It was fun and moving. - Indeed.
Besides, you didn't even sing halfway through the song.
You didn't sing live.
We can't pay you the amount we agreed on.
- I said I'd lip-sync in some parts. - True.
I'm so upset because you didn't ask for my consent in advance.
Excuse me. You're so good at lip-syncing.
How about you appear on "I Can See Your Voice"?
- You're so good at it. - Do you think so?
- Yes, you did a great job. - I'm getting so many offers.
- You should talk to... - How much will you pay him?
- He's really good at it. - How much?
- Let's talk about it later. - Okay.
- I hope to see you on the show. - Okay.
- You did an amazing job. - Thank you.
He was amazing.
- Did you guys see his nipples? - What?
- Of course, we did. - Where are they?
- Point where they are. - Hey, hold on.
- Haha will... - Hey, look.
- I saw his nipples. - Don't tell them.
- Gosh. - Don't tell them.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
Lift his shirt up to his belly button.
- You two, don't do that again. - Gosh, seriously.
You should be grateful that I'm letting it go like this.
- We paid you. - All right.
You got some extra points for those lines at the end.
- Here's my autograph you asked for. - What is this?
Why do you keep giving me your autograph?
- Keep it. - I already signed with Se Chan.
Because of your ego...
I never asked you for your autograph.
- Why do you keep giving me this? - "Study hard."
Why would you tell me to study hard?
I just wanted to write something nice.
Next up is JBR World.
We'll begin our presentation.
- We'll introduce you to JBR World. - Ji Hyo looks so awkward.
Many talent agencies' names have "entertainment" in them, right?
But we used the word "world" instead.
It means that our company will become international.
And what JBR stands for is... It's my mindset for work.
I always tell myself to treat the stars I work with sincerely.
So JBR stands for...
"Ji Suk Jin backs you up with respect." That's what it means.
Are you sleepy?
- Just to wake you up. - Wait. Did you just slap him?
- Please stay awake. - I'm sorry.
First of all, JBR World has signed...
with Kim Jong Kook and Song Ji Hyo,
the strongest man and the ace of Running Man.
There were dating rumors about them.
What's the truth?
I assure you that it's not true.
- What if they break up? - They break up?
- Are you saying they're dating? - Look at Jong Kook's face.
They're dating?
Look at his face.
They've never been in a romantic relationship.
Why is he glaring at the CEO of my agency?
Calm down. I have a confession to make.
- Why is he glaring at him? - Actually,
I can't control Jong Kook.
So don't provoke him.
- As the CEO of his agency, - Don't provoke him.
- you should control him. - I can't do it.
- Try not to get on his nerves. - I didn't mean anything.
Kim Jong Kook, also known as Superstar Kim,
will show you his strength.
That sounds good.
- Do you want some walnuts? - Yes, I do.
Does anyone want to eat walnuts?
Me! Can you crack one right in front of me?
- Yes, he can do that. - Come over here,
- and do it in front of us. - Pick one.
- I'll crack the one you pick. - This one.
- This one? - Here we go.
- She picked the hard one. - But...
He broke his finger!
- Jong Kook just broke his finger. - No, I didn't.
- I didn't hit it straight. - You can do this.
- I missed it. - You can do this.
It was a mistake.
- I saw his finger shaking. - I missed it.
Jong Kook, try this one.
- Okay. - Let's try that one.
- His finger will swell up. - His finger...
It must hurt.
Stop it!
Jong Kook.
- Don't hurt yourself! - Let me try just one more time.
- Jong Kook, come on. - Let go.
- Let go of me. - Stop it.
I'll give you 0.3 points.
Stop it.
- It's done. Good job. - Okay.
- It's delicious. - Great job.
- He did it. Give him a hand now! - Listen.
- Come on. Give him a hand. - He's scary.
- We've seen him cracking it before. - Hey.
He did a great job.
- Next up is Ji Hyo. - Yes.
As for Ji Hyo...
She gets lucky all the time.
Today, she'll prove that it's actually her ability.
It wasn't just luck. She made it happen.
We prepared eggs here for an egg breaking game.
Half are cooked, and the rest are raw.
She'll pick out three eggs that are cooked...
and break them in front of you.
We won't mark on the eggs. She can memorize the locations.
I'll put the cooked ones here.
This one is raw. Why are there more raw eggs than cooked eggs?
She'll pick out a cooked egg and break it before you...
three times in a row.
- Did you mark the eggs? - No.
Can we reposition the eggs?
- Sure. Check them. - We should check them.
- Are you sure? - You want to reposition them?
- Go ahead. - Of course, we should do it.
- Why can't you trust us? - We should check them first.
We would never pull a trick.
Half of them are raw.
All right.
Let's begin.
In all three attempts,
she'll choose a cooked egg,
and break it to prove it.
Hit it on your forehead, okay?
- I hope she picks a raw egg. - What do I do?
- If she does, end your show, okay? - Okay.
- Do you think you can do it? - Both of you like breaking things.
Let's go.
Hit it right on your forehead.
Are you sure it's cooked?
You shouldn't shake it.
Now, hit it on your forehead.
- Be more confident. - One.
- I don't think... - Two.
Three. Go!
- Okay! - Really?
- Look. - I picked the right one.
Okay. Let's move on.
- Next. - Okay. Next.
Okay!
- Let's go. - She won't be so lucky this time.
- You can get lucky once. - Gosh. I'm worried.
There are four boiled eggs...
and five raw eggs left in the case.
Are you sure?
- Are you sure? - Okay.
- Let's go. - If she succeeds again,
- I'd be really surprised. - Okay. It's a boiled egg.
1, 2, 3.
Okay!
Oh, my. Really?
- Twice in a row? - Okay.
- Aren't they all cooked? - Okay.
- No. Not all of them are cooked. - One more time.
Isn't she amazing?
- Then... - Let's check the eggs later.
- check the eggs afterward. - Okay.
Check them.
Okay.
One more time. Just once more.
Will she succeed?
- I have faith in you. - Here.
- I'll cook it if it's raw. - Cook it.
Here I go. 1, 2, 3.
2, 3.
- No way. It doesn't make sense. - Come and take a look.
- That doesn't make sense. - It makes no sense.
- It's true. - No way.
- Check them yourself. - Try it.
- Pick one and break it. - No way.
Break it.
He chose a raw egg.
- I told you it was real. - She actually pulled it off.
- I was surprised by Ji Hyo too. - We didn't pull a trick.
- But we repositioned them. - It was real.
- I said, it was real. - She actually did it.
- Try it. - She picked out the right ones.
CEO Jeon.
Stop it already.
What happened? How did she do it?
She actually picked the right ones.
- She's incredible. - It was real.
Hey, seriously, I think it was amazing.
- Right? - Yes.
- The stars of JBR World. - She got lucky.
Please give them a round of applause!
Thank you.
I slept peacefully thanks to you.
Last but not least, Cocoa M Monkey by Physical Contact.
Let me introduce the artist at my agency.
Why are you covering me?
So you can make a great entrance.
I'm sorry,
but did you two break up recently?
- No? - No.
- Anyway... - You know,
CEO Jeon falls in love easily.
Dating within the agency...
- isn't allowed. - There are some agency CEOs...
- marrying a star at the agency. - True.
- That's not the case. - Many fall in love like that.
- There are some couples like that. - Come on. Stop it.
I can't tell you that because it's my private life.
- What? Just tell them. - It's my private life.
- Tell them. - That's not necessary.
- We... - You can just say it's not true.
I guess she has something to hide.
What makes this agency so suspicious is...
that the CEO is a bit strange.
- Her behaviors are all strange. - It's hard to read her face.
- She's cheesy too. - That's not true.
He'll begin now. Enjoy his performance.
Oh, he'll dance.
Awesome!
He's incredible.
Wooyoung is such a great dancer.
He really is a great dancer.
He's a great dancer.
Of course.
What's going on?
He can dance to any type of song.
He's good.
He really is a great dancer.
He's so good at this. He's amazing.
He's so cool.
He's amazing.
He's really talented.
Wooyoung, you're awesome.
- This is amazing. - He's really good at dancing.
- He's such a great dancer. - He's good.
- He's awesome. - I'm amazed.
My, Wooyoung is such a great dancer.
- That was amazing. - No one can beat him.
- He's such a great dancer. - Great job.
- Where are you going? - By the way,
- Wooyoung did all the work. - You're a great dancer.
Wooyoung is such a great dancer.
- He's an amazing dancer. - Indeed.
- I'm surprised. - This isn't his first rodeo.
CEO Jeon.
Could you perhaps dance for us instead?
Okay.
- She's just crazy. - Look at her expression.
Her expression does it all.
Look at how confident she is.
- Ms. Jeon, can you do this too? - Her eyes.
Her eyes do all the work.
- Her turns are good. - Did you see her eyes?
That's right.
- Mr. Ji loves it the most. - I know.
- Mr. Ji... - You're the best.
I always deliver.
- Like this. - Dance for him often.
The ones who love her dancing are Suk Jin and our cameraman.
They were clapping.
They absolutely love this.
- The result is out. - Okay.
The one in 1st place will receive 1,000 dollars...
and 100 dollars will be deducted...
with each lower ranking.
I wouldn't mind at least 600 dollars.
The CEOs will receive their money depending on their contracts.
The money you earned will be all yours.
In first place is...
Out of 25 points,
this person received 20.7 points.
This person received 20.7 points.
It's Jessi.
I gave you a high score.
- Jessi. - I gave you a high score.
It's my first time winning on Jae Suk's team.
Jessi, you'll receive 1,000 dollars...
and split it with Haha accordingly.
In 2nd place with 18.5 points...
is Wooyoung.
You get 900 dollars.
In 3rd place and getting 800 dollars...
is Ji Hyo with 16 points.
In eighth place is Haha.
And in the last place...
Why is Jae Suk in the bottom two after that performance?
He did a good job.
- That's what you all said. - Why do I have a low score?
And I was in a duo act, remember?
He did what I did.
Is this a joke?
One received 4.75 points while the other got 2.3 points.
- 2.4 points? - No way.
The one with the lowest score only gets 100 dollars.
With 2.3 points...
- is Jae Suk. - Okay!
Kwang Soo's happy to be in ninth place.
Right...
How much do I get?
- Unbelievable. - You get 200 dollars.
We'll settle the payments at our next location.
It's now time to renew your contracts.
- Sir. - Hold on for a second.
- Jae Suk. - Yes?
You see...
- You'll have to work... - Yes?
a little harder.
I only say this because...
you've put us in the red.
That's just mean.
- That wasn't my intention. - That was harsh.
I think we should give it one more chance.
First of all, I'd like my payment...
You've got nothing going for yourself right now...
and haven't shown me anything, so renew the contract.
Let me give you your money first.
Since you received 100 dollars, you get 95.
Your contracts...
- are up for renewal. - Suk Jin.
- I mean, Mr. Ji. - I'd like to renew your contracts.
You should spend some of your money.
No, this is for me to keep.
We should get a signing bonus.
I'll give you 100 dollars each.
I'll give you that.
- Really? - Hand it over then.
- I will. - We'll take it right now.
But my cut...
- Your cut? - It should be 7 to 3.
- Because... - We'll have to reconsider.
We'll listen to some other offers.
- Wait. - We'll hear them out.
- We'll hear their offers. - Just their offers.
- Because... - That's not all, you know.
The signing bonus is one thing.
- Just hear me out. - We might earn more later,
- so 100 dollars... - To renew our contract,
you have to consider what our friendship costs.
- Ji Hyo. - But...
- 7 to 3, you say? - You see...
- Let's shop around first. - That wasn't my only offer.
- Sure thing. - There's more!
- We'll ask around first. - All right.
Unbelievable.
I need to win big in this next round.
- Wait. Okay, how about this? - Go ahead.
I know you two are dating.
Which is why I'll...
We'll only sign with the same agency.
- I... - Yes?
- We move as a set. - I'll make sure...
this doesn't get out.
- I know it all but... - You'll keep it a secret?
I will...
Will you keep it a secret?
- Are you sure? - I know your secret.
- Will you keep it a secret? - I'll stop all articles.
- Okay. - Okay?
- You'll stop the rumors? - No articles will be published?
Sign with me for 50 dollars.
- 50 dollars? - 50 dollars?
Guys, wait. JK, please.
- Not for 50 dollars. - I have proof, you know.
At another agency...
I have a photo.
- What photo? - Is he insane?
I mean it. Should I show you?
- Okay, I hear you. - CEO Ha.
- Sure. - CEO Ha.
So you and me...
We'll receive the penalty at this rate.
Anyway, I've offered you everything I have.
- Okay, good. - There we go.
What do you say to 9.5 to 0.5?
- What? - 9.5 to 0.5.
- I'll get to take home a lot. - Sure.
I'm down.
- Here? - Yes, here.
What I honestly want to do is sign you for life.
To prove our partnership, I suggest 7 to 3.
Really?
Jessi.
- Just run. - Jessi, wait.
- You should give up 280 dollars. - What will you offer me?
How much will you offer me?
- What? - I'll sign for 1,000 dollars.
Why? I'll sign for that much.
Please finalize your deals.
No, not yet.
It can't be over just yet.
Hold on. I haven't signed anyone.
- Let's sign the contract. - 8 to 2.
Give me 200 dollars.
- Se Chan, go. - Okay, fine.
- I heard you. - Let's do this.
- On one condition. - What's that?
Draw a unibrow.
- Okay, fine. - Show me you mean it.
You only have eyes for me.
Please finalize your deals.
- Everyone's taken. - Jong Kook.
Hey! Jong Kook!
- Ji Hyo, come back. - How much?
- Come quick. - Name your offer.
- What? - How will we split the money?
- It'll be the same. - What?
It'll be the same as before.
- The same as before? - Yes, with something extra!
- The same as before? - 50 dollars.
The same as before?
Yes, with something extra! Ji Hyo, too.
A signing bonus of 50 dollars.
Should I tell the world that you're dating?
You don't want that.
I haven't signed anyone yet.
- Wait. - I'll give you a better offer.
Suk Jin.
I think it's over for you.
- What if you can't sign anyone? - What time is it?
- Here. - What if you can't sign anyone?
Then, 10 to 0!
- 10 to 0. - 10 to 0?
- Let's go. - 10 to 0?
- 10 to 0 is insane. - Let's go.
- 10 to 0? - 10 to 0.
- 10 to 0? - You can't offer that.
What happens if a CEO can't sign any celebrities?
The agency will be shut down,
and the CEO will have to sign with another agency.
You'll have to sign with an agency yourself.
- Really? - Hold on.
- I just mean that... - 10 to 0. Seriously?
I... Jessi, you haven't signed with an agency yet, have you?
- Don't be ridiculous. - CEO Ji.
Just sign with an agency as a celebrity.
I...
That suits you better.
- Okay. - It's a 9 to 1 deal.
- Cheers. - This will be fun.
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, can at least one of you join me?
10 to 0!
Please finalize your deals.
I'll split 10 to 0!
Suk Jin has made his debut.
Goodness, Junior Ji.
- Junior Ji. - How about you sign with me?
You're many years my junior.
- How much do you have? - What?
- How much do you have? - I think...
about 500 dollars.
To register for the shutdown, you must pay 300 dollars.
Why must I shut down my business?
- Was that always the rule? - Must I be shut down?
Must you pay to shut down your business?
Is this how one's business is shut down?
Suk Jin, why don't I get you on "Dongchimi" next week?
How about "Flaming Youth"?
You should start with "Flaming Youth".
- "Flaming Youth". - Right, "Flaming Youth".
- "Flaming Youth"... - That's an option.
- Then... - Please step back.
- Step back. - Who'll sign him?
- Then... - I'll sign him.
- No, I will. - We will.
How about 8 to 2...
with a signing bonus?
- 8 to 2. - A bonus...
Here. I'll sign with them.
An 8 to 2 split with a signing bonus of 50 dollars.
It would've been funny if he signed you as a manager.
Lucky Kwang Soo.
Here's your first gig as superstars today.
You will play to be the last man standing...
- in Informal Talk Golden Bell. - Informal Talk Golden Bell?
Yes, Informal Talk Golden Bell.
A randomly chosen person...
will come up with a question in his or her head.
It'll then be asked to anyone of their choosing.
The question will be answered. If you get it wrong,
you'll be eliminated.
The agency will come last.
Having signed a lot of people will pay off.
No second chances?
You're right.
Wait, it's a quiz?
Shouldn't you have told us that beforehand?
You should've signed with me.
Didn't you see how I was last week?
Unbelievable.
Asking the questions isn't easy either.
- Of course. - You need to know it first...
to ask others.
Exactly.
What's something that only I would know?
The name of the game is Informal Talk Golden Bell.
- Right. - Sure.
You're all supposed to be the same age,
so you must be informal with each other.
Say any formal words and you'll be eliminated.
I love games like that.
Me too.
- We're to speak informally. - Can I be informal with you?
You always have been.
Yes, you always have.
We can't say "oppa" or "hyung", right?
No, you're all supposed to be the same age.
Wooyoung's the luckiest.
I'm the one who has most to lose.
Doesn't Suk Jin have it the easiest?
- Exactly. - Suk Jin...
is already informal with everyone.
I made the right choice signing Suk Jin.
It's impossible for me to make any mistakes.
- But we... - He's informal with everyone.
Jessi has never been formal with me before.
- You've never been that way. - What do you mean?
- You're always informal. - Hey!
Hey, what?
Treat me like you always have.
This is the best game for Suk Jin and Jessi.
- How annoying. - Here we go.
You know what an Informal Talk Game is, right?
- Of course. - Go!
- No one's talking. - Be informal with each other.
Suk Jin, stop shaking your legs.
The game has begun.
It's not like I have to speak formally.
- The rules are different. - Of course not.
Suk Jin, you can't get upset though.
We're all the same age, right?
Jessi's kind of flustered though.
Jessi, you can speak informally with everyone.
- We're all friends here. - Be informal with the staff too.
What's your surname? Park, Lee, or Kim?
Shut it.
It's Ho.
- Her surname is Ho. - Jessi...
It's Ho Hyeon Ju.
- Okay? - Jessi Ho.
- That's right. - Ho Hyeon Ju.
Gosh, this is...
Hey, Jong Kook. Say something.
Why are you so sullen?
- Jong Kook. - Why are you so sullen?
Use your words, Jong Kook.
I don't use words.
- Hold on. - My goodness.
- This is... - Friends say that...
- to each other, okay? - This is ridiculous.
This is the Informal Talk Game.
How are we supposed to play the Informal Talk Game?
- This is the Informal Talk Game. - "I don't use words."
You should use words since this game is about talking.
- Is he a thug? - What is this?
- Seriously. - I don't use words.
I usually don't use words.
- Is that so? Okay. I got it. - Yes.
I don't use words either.
- We are a team. - I am sorry, Se Chan.
Sir, may I write a question now?
No, you can't write it yet.
- Hold on. - Hold on.
You spoke formally.
I was talking to the producer.
You have to speak informally even to the producer.
From now on, speak informally to the production crew as well.
- Really? - Really?
- All right. - To the production crew as well?
- To the production crew as well? - Speak informally to everyone.
- Hey. - All right.
Chan Hee. Hey, Chan Hee.
- Chan Hee. - Film us over here.
Film us over here.
Are we speaking informally to everyone?
- We shouldn't do that to Chan Hee. - Chan Hee.
- Chan Hee. - We shouldn't do that to Chan Hee.
We shouldn't touch Chan Hee.
We shouldn't do that to Chan Hee.
- We shouldn't touch Chan Hee. - Seriously.
- Hey! Punk! - Leave Chan Hee out of this.
- That's right. - We shouldn't do that to Chan Hee.
- Okay. - Hold on.
Chan Hee must be angry.
- His face is red. - Leave Chan Hee out of this. Stop.
Stop.
Chan Hee, don't be upset.
Chan Hee, that's how it is.
The first question is important,
so let's play rock-paper-scissors, shall we?
- What? - Do you speak informally too?
Why are you speaking informally?
- Why are you speaking informally? - What was that?
- Do you speak informally too? - What was that?
Are we playing the game with everyone in the building?
- Hold on. - Hey.
Maybe he proposed the game to speak informally to us.
Hey, Beanpole, say something.
Am I Beanpole?
Who else would be Beanpole?
- It's a nickname. - Listen, everyone.
Sometimes, I use my fist without thinking.
You should move out of the way.
Sit down!
All right.
Which Ho Clan is your family from?
Be quiet.
The Be Quiet Ho Clan?
Which Ho Clan is your family from? You don't know, right?
You don't know those things, right? You should know.
What was that?
- You should know. - What was that?
- You are so childish. Suk Jin. - What was that? Seok Sam.
- You are so childish. - What was that?
- Suk Jin, you are so childish. - Seok Sam.
It was such a petty revenge.
Seok Sam.
Seok Sam, don't be like that to your friend.
Steamed Monkfish, be quiet.
- Steamed Monkfish? - Steamed Monkfish.
- Be quiet, you punk. - "You punk."
"You punk"?
- What? - Don't swear at your friend.
Why not?
I could hit you!
Suk Jin, hold yourself back.
- Suk Jin. - Are you scared?
- What? - Are you scared?
I will hit your temple with my knuckle.
Hey, hey. Stop talking.
You are one who needs to stop talking.
Seriously.
- Seok Sam. - Stop talking, you punk.
Seok Sam must be in a good mood.
He looks so awkward.
- Seriously. - He was serious.
- Hey. - Stop talking.
I can't believe this guy.
- For goodness' sake. - For goodness' sake.
- For goodness' sake. - Go ahead.
Any one of us can give the question, right?
Shall I give a simple one?
- You shouldn't do that. - You shouldn't do that.
Give a hard one that can finish off a team.
I don't know if I can do that.
Kook Jong is unexpectedly knowledgeable.
- He is pretty smart. - Yes.
He is pretty smart. Isn't that right, Kook Jong?
You are going to die.
What? I just...
Se Chan.
None of your clothes match the color of your hat,
but I can help you with that.
That means he will make me bloody.
- Gosh, Kook Jong. - I can help you with that.
Let's watch what we say.
I want to ask them a question first.
- Go ahead. - Go ahead.
He must have a question in mind.
It should be a general knowledge question.
- Come on. - Ask a general knowledge question.
- Ask a general knowledge question. - General question.
I can take out two members. Shall I go first?
You can't take out anyone.
Hold on. Listen.
You probably won't get it right, Beanpole.
- Don't copy someone's answer. - We won't do that.
- In any case, - Cover your answer.
it's more advantageous for you if your team members get eliminated.
That's right.
All right. Give me...
- the name... - Oh, my goodness! No!
of the Russian president.
- The full name? - Give me the full name.
He knows that from playing games. He always goes back to it.
Gosh.
- Don't look. - I expected something harder,
- Se Chan. - Don't show your answer.
- I expected something harder. - This is bad. I have no idea.
Amor Putin.
Remivonyar Putin. Remivonyar Putin.
Give me the full name of the Russian president.
- You don't know. - I do know. I do remember.
I expected something harder.
I know the answer.
I don't know.
Some members will be eliminated.
- He chose the right team. - Se Chan...
doesn't know much...
- other than that. - Seok Sam.
You shouldn't say that so loudly.
All of them might get eliminated.
Didn't you write the same answer the last time?
Was it incorrect?
Didn't I get it right?
Be quiet!
Hold on, Jessi.
- Hold on. - My goodness.
What was that? Hold on.
- Jessi, what was that? - Jessi.
Jae Suk, that was like a comedy skit.
- It was fun, right? - It was so much fun.
- You should whisper. - It was fun, right?
- It was fun. - It was so much fun.
It was fun.
"Be quiet!" That was perfect.
- It was so much fun. - "Be quiet!"
- "Be quiet!" - What a fun comedy skit!
All right. Did you write down the answer?
The four of you will reveal your answers first.
1, 2, 3.
Reveal the answers.
I am not sure.
- Putin. - The two of them knew.
- Se Chan, reveal the answer. - I don't know the first name.
- Vladimir Putin. - Okay. I am not sure.
- I got it right. - Putin.
The two of them knew.
Seeing the answer brings back memories.
Kwang Soo, what did you write?
- What did you write? - What did you write?
- General... - General ID Putin?
- I could only remember Gorbachev. - General...
Gorbachev!
My goodness.
Beanpole, I knew you would fail.
We lost two members.
- Jessi and Kwang Soo are out. - Okay.
Does that mean I can't play?
- That's right. - I can't even ask a question?
She can't even ask a question?
What kind of a rule is that?
- This one will be hard. - Ask about the capitals.
It's a matter of choosing which team to eliminate.
- The team might get eliminated. - This one...
will be hard.
- It will be hard. - Ask about the famous capitals.
Which country?
Jae Suk, you should ask the other team.
You know that we have no hope.
I think this question will eliminate the entire team.
Jae Suk, it won't be entertaining if it eliminates the entire team.
Hey, Big Mouth.
You should stop chattering.
I like your mustache.
Hey, you with too much space between the eyebrows.
- Look at his eyebrows. - Hey, Glasses.
- You are wearing glasses too. - I can't believe you.
- They are going to fight. - Punk,
- did you call me Glasses? - All right!
- Glasses. - Glasses.
Glasses was a popular nickname in our time, right?
Be careful what you say, okay?
This team doesn't have anyone who can ask a difficult question.
You are right. Let's end that team.
- End that team. That's right. - That's right.
- Seok Sam. Seok Sam. - You have a point.
We need to end them when we have a chance.
Will it be about the capitals?
When I ask a question about the capitals...
- Would you make a promise? - I don't know about the capitals.
If one member survives... What?
- You spoke formally. - Hey.
- Yes! - Suk Jin.
- Come on. - What was that?
- Sit down. - This is driving me crazy.
Why did you suddenly speak formally?
Hey, good job!
- He was acting up. - Good job.
- He was acting up. - Hey.
- He was acting up. - He was acting up.
- I knew he would mess up. - Why did you speak formally?
- Everyone is younger than you. - This is driving me crazy.
You are the oldest.
Seok Sam, this is ridiculous.
It's okay. All right. Good luck!
- Seok Sam. - For goodness' sake.
Jae Suk, you are the only one left.
Then I...
I don't know much about capitals, big brother.
Jong Kook is out.
- Why? - "Big brother".
"Big brother".
Why did you do that?
Did Jong Kook speak formally?
The only knowledgeable member should have known better.
- Jong Kook is so nice. - Seriously.
Sit down. It's your fault, you punk. Sit down.
This is exactly why I am keeping quiet.
Jong Kook is eliminated.
Let's end this team so that we can place second.
- Okay. - End this team.
All right. That's a good move.
- Here comes the question. - Go ahead.
- I know this one! - The level of difficulty is right.
(The answer is Buenos Aires.)
- I think this is a good one. - We need to place second.
- You know the answer, right? - Yes.
- What's the capital of Argentina? - This is...
I know the answer too.
It can be confusing since there are many syllables.
- I know this one! - The level of difficulty is right.
- You know the answer, right? - Yes.
I know the answer too.
Please write down your answer.
(Unsure)
It can be confusing since there are many syllables.
- Argentina? - Messi.
You know, he is smart.
Please write down your answer.
Why did you have to ask a question about the capitals?
(CEO Jeon's devastated as she's not good with capitals.)
- Argentina? - Messi.
I don't know much about the capitals.
You know, he is smart.
Gosh, I...
Why did you have to ask a question about the capitals?
(Laughing)
I don't know much about the capitals.
Se Chan drives me crazy. Is that really your answer?
Gosh, I...
Doesn't it seem like an answer?
Se Chan drives me crazy. Is that really your answer?
A little bit. I...
(You think so?)
I have no idea.
Doesn't it seem like an answer?
Se Chan.
All right.
A little bit. I...
I have no idea.
Se Chan.
All right.
(Team CEO Jeon reveals their answers.)
- All right. - 1, 2, 3.
- For goodness' sake! Maradona? - Luxembourg?
(Shocked)
(Madrid, Maradona, Luxembourg)
This is insane.
- For goodness' sake! Maradona? - Luxembourg?
Madrid?
(The world of various wrong answers)
- Luxembourg? - This is insane.
- Luxembourg is a country. - I mean...
- Luxembourg is a country. - A, A
- Argentina - Argentina
- Lu, Lu, Luxembourg - Lu, Lu, Luxembourg
(She guessed from the song lyrics.)
- A, A... That's how the song goes! - You know,
she hugged the sketchbook as if she had the correct answer.
(She was serious about keeping her answer secure.)
I don't know the answer.
Jae Suk, reveal the answer.
(Jae Suk's answer is Buenos Aires.)
No, no.
- Buenos Aires. - That's right!
(Empty Heads act like they knew the answer.)
All right.
All three members are out.
(Jae Suk's quiz on the capital eliminated Team CEO Jeon.)
I didn't know all of them would get eliminated.
All of us got eliminated.
Now, one of you will give a question and attack.
(It's time for Team CEO Ha to attack.)
Why...
Mustache.
(Give them a nonsense quiz.)
Give them a nonsense quiz.
They have no sense, so give them a nonsense quiz.
- Hey! - Ji Hyo will give a question.
"They have no sense, so give them a nonsense quiz"?
They have no senses.
(They have no chance anyway with common sense.)
Give them a nonsense quiz, Mustache.
Ji Hyo will give a question.
(Ji Hyo from Team CEO Ha will give a question.)
Will Ji Hyo give a question?
Go ahead.
(Hesitant)
- I... - You can be mean. Hurry up.
- Hey. - There you go.
- Go ahead. - Change your tone.
(Who directed "New World", the movie Ji Hyo appeared in?)
Who directed "New World", the movie I appeared in?
Gosh, he might know the answer.
- I love this director. - He might know the answer.
(Unsure)
- This question... - The director of "New World".
- Do you know? - He is a well-known director.
- It isn't Park Chan Wook. - No.
(Jae Suk doesn't seem to know.)
No.
- P. - What?
(The initial of his last name is P.)
- P? - P.
She gave him a big hint.
That means his last name is Park.
It's right.
Park Hang Seo.
(Chuckling)
So Min heard that his initial is P and went,
"Park Hang Seo".
(Park Hang Seo is the best among all Coach Park.)
You are so sharp.
- Park Hang Seo. - You are so sharp.
That's just...
So Min, you are sharp.
(Empty Head is amazed by her creativity.)
- Park Hang Seo. - It's a good answer.
- I don't know. I have no clue. - My goodness.
(Jae Suk who struggled to the end reveals his answer.)
- Jae Suk. - Come on.
Park Soo Chan.
(He tries to come up with a plausible name.)
Reveal the answer.
(The name of "New World" director is...)
- The answer is Park Hoon Jung. - Park Hoon Jung.
(Park Hoon Jung.)
I had no clue.
Director Park, I am sorry.
(After the first schedule,)
The two of you placed first.
(Haha and Ji Hyo placed 1st.)
I eliminated myself...
(Jong Kook's early elimination turned into a blessing.)
- and saved you guys. - Jong Kook, it's all thanks to you.
- I know that. - I save you guys.
I know that. You are good.
(Boss)
- Give me a bonus. - All right, all right.
Since the two of you placed 1st, you get 1,000 dollars each.
(1st and 2nd places get 1,000 dollars each.)
- Jae Suk, you get 800 dollars. - 800 dollars?
(Jae Suk who placed 3rd gets 800 dollars.)
Since So Min, Se Chan, and Wooyoung placed fourth,
(So Min, Se Chan, and Wooyoung who placed 4th get 70 dollars.)
they get 700 dollars each.
That isn't much.
The 5th place, Jessi and Kwang Soo get 200 dollars each.
(Jessi and Kwang Soo get 200 dollars each.)
Let's move on to the last schedule.
(Three agencies will set off for their last schedule.)
Okay. I will do better this time.
- Look at this. - What is this?
(Three agency CEOs and top stars' last schedule)
I think we will do something embarrassing.
The smell makes me want to wash my hair.
(What's the last mission that takes place in a slippery studio?)
What is this?
I think the floor is slippery.
(Top stars arrive one by one.)
This is no joke.
This time,
CEO Lee needs to work hard.
(He suddenly has a mole on his face.)
I need to put a mole on you.
(During the break)
(CEO Lee lost in a bet and got a giant mole from Se Chan.)
Everyone,
(The giant mole stands out.)
the last schedule requires...
both physical and variety show skills.
(The last mission requires physical and variety show skills.)
- It's the Running Arcade. - Arcade.
(Running Arcade)
- So Min, our lives depend on this. - Yes.
Here is the game you will play.
Two members will face each other.
(You'll face each other and spin when the production crew says so.)
Let's say the production crew says, "Spin once. 1, 2, 3."
Then both members need to spin once at the same time.
But there will be a word on your back.
(You win if you say the word on the other member's back.)
Look at the other member's word and answer correctly to win.
- We just need to read it? - Yes.
The words on the backs must be hard.
(It will be a difficult word with 4 to 5 syllables.)
- That's right. - Hard words.
How hard?
(The level will be adjusted for Jessi who isn't fluent in Korean.)
Jessi, you will get the word you know.
Really?
The winner will receive 500 dollars...
(The winner gets 500 dollars instantly.)
and the loser will receive 100 dollars.
(The loser will get 100 dollars.)
This isn't a team competition.
(It's a chance to win money regardless of the team.)
No, it isn't.
You see the spoons on the floor, right?
Draw one each.
(They'll draw a spoon for the tournament.)
1 and 2 will go against each other. 3 and 4 will go against each other.
(Everyone draws a spoon.)
- Let's draw a spoon each. - Let's draw a spoon each.
- I am number 1. - I am number 3.
(Tournament, Jong Kook versus Wooyoung)
(Suk Jin versus Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo versus Se Chan)
- Come on! - Me?
(So Min versus Jessi, Jae Suk versus Haha)
Gosh, I will go against CEO Lee.
Why do I need to go against Jong Kook?
(Sad)
Numbers 1 and 2, please come on out.
(1st round is Jong Kook versus Wooyoung.)
This isn't easy. Wooyoung.
Hey, Wooyoung. This is hard.
(The floor is too slippery to even stand on.)
- Is it very slippery? - Is it hard?
It's very slippery.
Hey, hey. This is no joke. Come here. It's even worse here.
(Slippery)
This is...
- Oh, my goodness. - How will you spin?
(Balancing oneself is a struggle.)
You have to spin like this.
(It's important to stay in balance and spin fast.)
Hey, I can't spin.
This is hard.
You need to spin fast to see the other person's word...
(You must spin first to get a chance to answer.)
- and have a chance to answer. - We spin twice, right?
I will tell you how many times and count to three.
(You must spin as many times as the production crew says.)
(Creme brulee)
Why are the words so hard?
(Eucalyptus)
All right.
- Jong Kook. - Okay.
(The 1st round begins with difficult words on their backs.)
Okay. Let's begin.
Oh, my goodness.
Spin twice. 1, 2, 3.
(Both of them flinch.)
- This won't do. - You...
(Wooyoung spun first.)
He saw it.
- He saw it. - The word was visible.
(He can barely see...)
It's hard to figure out the word even when you see it.
(the mysterious word.)
Show us the triple axel, Jong Kook.
Let's go. 1, 2. Go!
(His attempt to appear cool results in slapstick comedy.)
(Flustered)
(What? I think I see the word.)
(His face is red from embarrassment.)
(It has been a while since he showed slapstick comedy.)
This is it!
(Chuckling)
Keep going.
My goodness.
- That's good. - Look at the word.
(Jong Kook can't even stand still.)
Wooyoung, look at the word when he falls down.
- This is fun. - You can't stay on the floor.
(The audience loves his heavy slapstick comedy.)
This is fun.
One spin remains.
(Wooyoung's last spin)
(Jong Kook can't possibly read the word as he's pretty fast.)
- He did a good job. - He spun twice.
(He's nervous after falling once.)
He spun very fast earlier.
- Spin the other way. - The other way.
(He takes a deep breath...)
(and prepares for the triple axel.)
(The war of nerves begins.)
(Gosh!)
Look at the word. Look at the word.
(Flustered)
We should protect Jong Kook's dignity.
(They've found something Jong Kook can't do aside from ball games.)
Jong Kook.
It's so funny to see you fall.
It's the first time I had so much confidence...
during a match against Jong Kook.
Let me answer.
(Does he know the answer?)
(Wooyoung will go first!)
Creme broller.
(Creme broller)
(Incorrect)
Creme broller.
(He was close!)
- It's so hard. - What is...
(Thinking)
All right.
Let me answer.
(Jong Kook shouted out, "Let me answer"!)
(Eucalyp...)
Eucalyp...
(Will he get the correct answer, "Eucalyptus"?)
Eucalyps.
No, no.
("Eucalyps" is incorrect)
Eucalyps.
No, no.
(Gosh, he was close.)
Both of them were so close.
(They're both close to the answer.)
I think it's the word I know.
- I am certain you have heard of it. - I am certain of it.
After you do three spins,
(It's three spins this time.)
you will get one more chance to answer.
(The person who got more syllables right will win.)
Then the person who got more syllables right will win.
- Syllables? - Both of you are nearly there.
(They only have one chance now.)
1, 2, 3.
Let's go.
(Wooyoung begins to turn on the spot.)
Did they mix it up?
One spin.
Hold on.
Wooyoung doesn't fall down.
(Unlike Jong Kook, he's swift and stable.)
Hold on.
(Balance)
It's because he dances.
It will be game over if one of them falls down.
(Screaming)
(His sense of balance failed as soon as Jae Suk was done.)
- Two. - Fall on your back.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook spun twice.)
- He saw the word. - That's good.
What will it be?
(He throws his body and lands on his butt.)
I will give him 10 points.
(His slapstick comedy deserves 10 out of 10.)
- He didn't see it. - 10 points for slapstick comedy.
- Since Kim Yoo Na... - 10 points for slapstick comedy.
(His triple axel is better than Kim Yuna's.)
- It's fun to see Jong Kook fall. - It's fun.
- Seriously. - He is cute.
- It's so rare. - It's so rare to see him fall.
(This game makes Jong Kook look humane along with ball games.)
He is cute.
Now, you will get a chance to guess the answer.
(The result will be decided depending on their accuracy.)
- Wooyoung, go first. - Let me answer.
("Creme brulee" is correct.)
Creme brolee.
(Eucalyptus)
You will recognize the word once you hear it.
Eupocalyse.
(Wooyoung is closer to the answer. He wins.)
Wooyoung won.
It was "Eucalyptus".
- It was "Eucalyptus". - Eucalyptus.
(Eucalyptus is a type of plant used as medicine or spices.)
Eucalyptus.
(It's known as koalas' food.)
The plant koalas eat.
You were off by one syllable earlier.
(1st round ends with Jong Kook's loss.)
Numbers 3 and 4.
(Suk Jin versus Ji Hyo)
It's Suk Jin versus Ji Hyo.
It's a big match.
(This round is expected to be funny.)
Here comes Suk Jin
Yes, yes, yes
(Slippery)
This is no joke.
Here comes Suk Jin
(Since his company went bankrupt, victory is his only chance.)
Move out of the way
Did the Informal Talk Game end?
These words are easy.
(The words are pretty easy this time.)
Gosh, these words...
- These words are easy, right? - Yes.
All right.
(Round 2 begins.)
- Make 1 spin. 1, 2, 3. - I can't see the word.
What is it?
(Teasing)
Suk Jin has a beautiful form.
(They try to read each other as they must each turn once.)
Okay, okay.
He has a beautiful form.
(He's getting ready by straightening his knees.)
He has nice knees.
Suk Jin has a nice body.
Seriously.
- I... - Let me answer.
- What? - Asian black bear.
("Asian black bear" is correct.)
What?
Did she see it?
(He leaned forward to pull his pants down.)
(Staring)
- Let me answer. - What?
Asian black bear.
(She just read the word she saw.)
(Thanks to his foolishness, she had an easy win.)
What? Did she see it?
What?
("Asian Black Bear" ridiculously lost his opportunity.)
- What did Suk Jin do? - What was that?
She saw the word when you pulled down your pants.
What happened?
(The winner leaves the game without a single use of her energy.)
He showed her the word...
while he was pulling down his pants.
- That was no fun. - Why...
(The game is over after a short knee exercise.)
You ruined this fun game.
I shouldn't have signed a contract with him!
(I saved you from your bankruptcy.)
- What was that? - When he pulled down his pants...
Ji Hyo, you are the best.
Did you see it when I pulled down my pants?
- Why did you make it boring? - Suk Jin, that was just wrong.
(The rookie Suk Jin lost his opportunity with his vain loss.)
I can't believe it.
Good luck.
(The next game is...)
Next up are Se Chan and Kwang Soo.
(between Se Chan and Kwang Soo.)
Okay.
Okay. Let's go. Let's go.
(Galapagos Islands, an archipelago in the Pacific Ocean)
(Einspanner, espresso with water and whipped cream on top)
These words are hard.
Kwang Soo wouldn't know the word.
(Sighing)
They wouldn't know even when they see the words.
(These words aren't in their vocabulary.)
Two spins.
Kwang Soo wouldn't know the word.
(They'll need to turn two times.)
- Come on. - He would know.
Come on.
(Triple axel)
(He decided to spin in the air.)
He spun.
He spun. Come on.
(He's gasping for air after just one turn.)
He was in the air.
It could be confusing for Kwang Soo.
(Trying to read)
(They spin at the same time.)
Se Chan, you have one more turn to go.
(Se Chan must spin one more.)
- This is... - I will see it no matter what.
- I will see it no matter what. - But you don't know this word.
Wouldn't Kwang Soo know?
(Glaring)
I know. I will see it no matter what.
He would know.
(The smell of money...)
He is using money.
(makes him bow.)
Okay, okay.
(He shows off his slapstick skills in gratitude.)
All right. Here you go.
(A dollar is enough...)
(to have him on the floor like a dog waiting for a snack.)
Okay.
- Throw it behind him. - This is funny.
Spin, Se Chan.
(Se Chan leisurely makes a turn by distracting Kwang Soo.)
Spin.
(It's a perfect strategy for Kwang Soo.)
Why are they so funny?
(They now need to make three turns.)
Three spins. 1, 2, 3.
Spin first.
They can't guess the words.
Did you spin once?
(After Kwang Soo's mosquito jump,)
He saw the word.
(Superstar Yang also makes a turn.)
Did you spin once?
He saw the word.
(He briefly exposed his back.)
Hold on.
You were right in front of me! You saw the word!
- Step back. - He doesn't know what he saw.
(Kwang Soo used his height to look down on it.)
Kwang Soo doesn't know what he saw.
- He doesn't know what he saw. - He doesn't know what he saw.
(But he doesn't know.)
What was that?
- Seriously. - You saw the word clearly.
You saw the word clearly.
(Compared to his eyesight, his vocabulary is too weak.)
- Don't you know? - You saw the word clearly.
- You saw the word clearly. - Don't you know it?
Did I see "Garlic"?
(He saw a word that starts with G.)
Garlic...
Let me answer.
Galas papa.
(Galaspapa)
- No, no. - You are close.
(He's pretty close.)
- Do I have one spin left? - Yes.
(Se Chan needs to make another turn.)
I will end it this time.
Just spin.
I will give you 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars is a lot. - 10 dollars.
(He's tempted by the large sum of money.)
- 10 dollars. - 10 dollars is a lot.
Close your eyes.
- What? - Close your eyes when I spin.
The two of them are making the game dirty.
I will close 1 eye for 10 dollars...
and 2 eyes for 20 dollars.
Okay. I will put the money on the floor.
(Pretending to throw money on the floor)
(He quickly turns while Kwang Soo is staring at the floor.)
He didn't see it.
- He spun so fast. - He is so good at spinning.
(He's an expert at skating on soaps.)
- He is so fast. - I will guess the word now.
- I completed the spins. - Let me answer.
Galas pepper.
Einspepper? Eins...
(Se Chan only saw "Eins", Kwang Soo only saw "Galas".)
What comes after "Galas"?
You are nearly there.
Let me answer. Galas pass.
(But they're not even close to the answer.)
- Einsupepper. - No.
Einsperm.
(They spit out all English vocabularies they know.)
Galaspar.
This is driving me crazy.
If you just look at the word and shout it out,
I will count it as a correct answer.
Just go for the word.
Gosh, I don't want to make this game so dirty.
(Changed Rule: Just do whatever it takes to read each other's back.)
CEO Lee, you and I go way back.
(They used to be in the same agency.)
This is a bit too much.
CEO Lee, come on.
(Superstar Yang is hesitant, but CEO Lee is already ready.)
The thing is, I don't have much money.
CEO Lee.
Se Chan, use your muscles.
(Slapping)
(Superstar Yang attacks first.)
What is going on?
You can't rip it off.
- There you go. - That's good.
(Rubbing)
He is trying to put it in his eyes.
He plays dirty.
(He tries to rub Se Chan's face with soap water.)
Se Chan is winning.
(Tossing and turning)
This is like the UFC.
Come on.
(What?)
(He throws 2m-tall Kwang Soo on the ground.)
(2m-tall Kwang Soo falls to the ground like a drunk man.)
He is nothing.
(The UFC enthusiast is excited.)
On the slippery floor, he is nothing.
That's some technique.
(CEO Lee is hopeless...)
That's so funny.
(in the face of Se Chan's techniques.)
- It's a nice technique. - That's some technique.
This is the best.
- The back... - The floor is slippery.
(Kwang Soo tries to pressure Se Chan's face.)
I knew this round would get dirty.
(Beanpole uses his specialty.)
Kwang Soo won't go easy on you. You know how he is.
Go between his legs.
(He fights with seriousness.)
This is so funny.
(It has turned into a dog fight a long time ago.)
Se Chan!
Look at his facial expression.
His expression changed.
Come on.
- Hey. - He went insane.
Kwang Soo went insane.
(Se Chan flips over the crazy man.)
- Kwang Soo went insane. - Kwang Soo went insane.
Kwang Soo went insane.
It's like an amusement park.
I knew this would happen.
(He can almost see the word.)
He is looking at the word.
- Kwang soo pulled it towards him. - He is looking at it.
Se Chan's arms are shorter.
(He finally grabs it.)
Let me answer.
Galapagos Islands.
Correct.
(CEO Lee won.)
Einspanner?
- Correct. - What is that?
(Se Chan has never heard of Einspanner.)
Coffee.
It's a type of coffee.
- It was so hard. - I know.
(He lost, but it was a good fight.)
"Galapagos Islands" is a bit better.
What is that?
An archipelago. Galapagos Islands.
An archipelago?
Are you pretending to know it now?
(CEO Lee wins...)
I had no idea.
(after a 10-minute bloody fight.)
Kwang Soo won.
Yes!
(After the two remaining games are done)
- Okay. - It was a great match.
Now, everything is over.
(Wooyoung, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo,)
After I pay up, we will calculate the total.
(Jae Suk, and So Min win 500 dollars each.)
For goodness' sake.
The CEOs will fight against other CEOs,
(Out of the 3 CEOs, the first two places will get prizes.)
and the celebrities will fight against other celebrities.
(Among the 7 celebrities, the top 4 will get the prize...)
(and the bottom 3 will get the penalty.)
Okay, everyone.
(It's time to announce the final results.)
I will announce the rankings of the three CEOs.
Only the last place gets the penalty, right?
(The rankings of the CEOs will be announced first.)
Yes. Only the last place gets the penalty.
Had I remained a CEO, I would have avoided the penalty.
With 1,961 dollars, CEO Jeon So Min takes 1st place.
(CEO Jeon takes 1st place.)
1,961 dollars?
CEO Jeon!
(She placed 1st thanks to Superstar Jang.)
People who didn't recruit many celebrities are the winners.
(Recruiting 1 witty celebrity was the best tactic.)
I should have only recruited the indispensable ones.
In second place is...
(CEO Lee's J Entertainment has Jae Suk, Suk Jin, and Jessi.)
(CEO Ha's DK Entertainment has Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
In second place is...
(Who'll be in the 2nd place?)
CEO Lee Kwang Soo with 986 dollars.
(CEO Lee is in 2nd place.)
Okay!
My goodness.
- Thank you. - See?
(He was able to win 2nd place by collecting small sums of money.)
You should be grateful to us.
You are right.
CEO Haha with 620 dollars will receive the penalty.
(CEO Ha of DK Entertainment will get the penalty.)
So Min and Kwang Soo will receive the prize.
(The two CEOs will earn prizes.)
The prize.
Now, the six superstars and Suk Jin.
(It's time to announce the artists' ranking.)
"And Suk Jin".
(1st to 4th places will get prizes, but the rest will get penalties.)
- What? - "And Suk Jin".
The 1st, 2nd, 3rd, and 4th places will receive the prize,
and the 5th, 6th, and 7th places will receive the penalty.
The 5th, 6th, and 7th places.
With 2,355 dollars, Song Ji Hyo takes 1st place.
(Superstar Song wins 1st place.)
Really?
She is unrivaled.
She has so much money.
(Thanks to her great results, she outperformed everyone else.)
With 1,485 dollars, Kim Jong Kook takes 2nd place.
(Superstar Kim is in 2nd place.)
Me?
- It must be the signing bonus. - The signing bonus.
(He ends up in 2nd place by using his strengths often.)
I signed a contract with the right company.
In third place is...
Yoo Jae Suk with 1,405 dollars.
(Yoo Jae Suk is in 3rd place.)
Congratulations.
(He feels somewhat bad.)
Among the remaining 4, only 1 will avoid the penalty.
(Only 1 out of 4 artists will survive.)
- Who are the four? - Me and...
Wooyoung, Jessi, Suk Jin, and Se Chan.
(Only the 4th place will be exempted.)
Will I be exempt?
Only one will avoid the penalty.
Only one.
I will announce the fourth place who will avoid the penalty.
(This person persevered in the cutthroat show business.)
Congratulations.
(Which celebrity placed 4th?)
Yang Se Chan.
(Yang Se Chan is in 4th place.)
Why?
(He barely misses the penalty.)
Lucky!
I am proud of him.
- What did he do? - With 1,280 dollars,
- Yang Se Chan placed fourth. - Okay.
Come on.
I won't receive the penalty.
Except for the four people who will receive the penalty,
(The prizes for today's winners)
everyone will be given the hallabong set from Jeju Island.
(Hallabong gift set just arrived from Jeju Island)
Really?
Hallabong is nice.
I will announce what the penalty will be.
(The 4 members' penalty gets revealed.)
The penalty is...
The penalty is making 100 autographs for the fans.
(They can go home after signing 100 autographs.)
My autograph is really easy. Watch.
(Anyone can tell that it belongs to Jessi.)
- Here. - This is mine.
I made it that way.
How is that "Ha"?
(It's not Dream's doodle, but Superstar Ha's autograph.)
Haha.
It's not easy to make 100 autographs.
(The time passes.)
Your wrist begins to hurt.
I made 100 autographs already.
(Starting with Jessi,)
This is the last one.
(they all finish their 100 autographs.)
- All done. - Yes.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(We thank Jessi and Wooyoung for joining us.)
Thank you.
(It's another day at work...)
Se Chan!
(or not!)
It's Yang Se Chan!
Se Chan!
Please show us your gums!
I haven't brushed my teeth yet.
What is this? Did the shoot begin?
(They turn into idol singers overnight!)
- What? What? "You are handsome"? - You are handsome!
You are so pretty!
- Song Ji Hyo is coming! - Come on!
(But their fame doesn't last long.)
(The popular idol group appears!)
Is Brave Girls here?
(They topped the military charts...)
Rollin', rollin', rollin'
(as well as regular music charts.)
(Brave Girls came back as the top idol group.)
We always said that we wanted to visit Running Man.
(They finally star on Running Man as they hoped.)
(The members show...)
Isn't this too much?
(how things are done on Running Man.)
This isn't enough.
(Best reactions!)
We told them to do whatever they want,
and they are doing as I said.
(So we prepared this.)
Gosh, this is intense.
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(The tenacious idol artists...)
(getting used to a variety show)
How did this happen?
You look great.
(How would the day end?)
(Idol Star Project, A day of Brave Idol Artists)