(A strange energy covers
the peaceful Running Village.)
(And there's a mysterious pot.)
Hello!
Hello.
Stay quiet.
The camera isn't even on yet.
- Hello.
- This feels strange.
Hello.
(What's happening in this place?)
Today,
- you will travel back in time.
- Is that so?
- That's what we're doing.
- We're going back to the past.
We have four guests who are
perfect for the Joseon Dynasty.
- Joseon Dynasty?
- How dare you!
There they are.
Sung Hoon.
- There's Dong Jun.
- Dong Yoon!
Dong Jun is back after a long time.
- Hello.
- And there's Sae Rok.
(A fierce battle against evil
spirits trying to destroy Joseon.)
(Korean exorcism fantasy drama,
"Joseon Exorcist")
I'll stop it before
it becomes the living dead.
(Jang Dong Yoon
playing Prince Chungnyeong)
Why do they not die?
You have to save his life
before they do.
(Park Sung Hoon
playing Prince Yangnyeong)
Is there any way to get rid of them?
(Kim Dong Jun playing
an acrobatic actor, Byuri)
(Keum Sae Rok playing an acrobatic
actress with secrets, Hye Yum)
(Jang Dong Yoon, Park Sung Hoon,
Kim Dong Jun, Keum Sae Rok)
It's "Joseon Exorcist".
We have four actors from the drama.
- "Joseon Exorcist".
- Please give them a big hand.
"Joseon Exorcist".
It's set in Joseon Dynasty.
I heard Sung Hoon...
is So Min's close friend.
- Really?
- Is that true?
- We did a drama together.
- Which one?
- What was the drama?
- A one-act drama.
What is Sung Hoon like?
Sung Hoon looks cool,
but he's very weak.
- He's clumsy.
- Right.
If he fights against Suk Jin,
Suk Jin might beat him.
Seriously? He must be feeble.
Sung Hoon, do you not work out?
Never.
That's good.
He's...
- perfect for our show.
- I know.
He would be like
the second Kim Hee Won.
What's your hobby, Sung Hoon?
- I like to lie in bed.
- Good.
- He's just like Suk Jin.
- You're like me.
He likes to lie still.
My gosh.
- It's not that everyone...
- You're right.
- has to work out hard.
- I agree.
- His arm is so soft.
- I like that.
- He's so skinny.
- It's like a sticky rice cake.
And we have Jang Dong Yoon here.
(Next to the weakling is the pure
and elegant guy, Jang Dong Yoon.)
Dong Yoon is really handsome.
Hello. I'm Jang Dong Yoon,
and I'm playing Prince Chungnyeong
in "Joseon Exorcist".
- He has a great voice.
- Wish me good luck.
- I like his voice.
- I'll try my best.
- It sounds so good.
- You know what?
- Dong Yoon is...
- What about him?
He got a full mark in math
on the college entrance exam.
- My gosh.
- He's smart.
This isn't a quiz show though.
(The young men who stopped
robbers with their wits)
(He became the talk of the town
after catching a robber.)
(Handsome)
(He was on the news
and made his debut later on.)
I feel so small.
I got four points in math.
(I got four points in math.)
Then you should just
focus on your studies.
- Hang on.
- Why did you...
Then you should just
focus on working out.
I do work out.
I spend half of my time working out.
He got into the harsh world
of show business instead.
Dong Yoon is...
(He's handsome.)
Hello.
(Hello.)
What makes you so happy?
I just met eyes with Dong Jun,
so I said hello to him.
- Why did you say hello like that?
- This is crazy.
It's just...
I couldn't wave at him.
You're wearing...
- an old lady's jacket today.
- Gosh, no.
She's even wearing a pearl necklace.
It's like you're attending
your kid's school play.
- Hey, stop that.
- I'm all dressed up today.
Next to Dong Yoon,
- we have Keum Sae Rok here.
- Welcome.
I'm acquainted with Sae Rok.
I said I'd make you become a star.
And you became
the most searched word that day.
- I did.
- Right.
And I even did a TV commercial.
I made Sae Rok a star.
(Sae Rok met
the star-maker, Big Nose.)
(Without Suk Jin's help,)
(she became the most searched word
with her powerful shoulder dance.)
(She made herself a star
with her abdominal shout.)
(Suk Jin didn't do anything.)
He's a star-maker.
I was surprised too.
I made a joke about
the search word rankings.
I said she was number four,
- and she really was ranked 4th.
- I was ranked 4th.
That's how it started.
You should do the same thing
for your stock investments.
Mr. Shipbuilding.
"I'm Suk Jin who invested
in J Shipbuilding."
Today, with the actors
from "Joseon Exorcist",
you will have the Running Dynasty
Records Race.
And you will be
in a hierarchical society...
where the king's words are the law.
- What does that mean?
- Oh, really?
So what matters is
who will become the king.
You will decide the king right away.
- What?
- Is it a random game?
- A random game?
- I want you to pick one scroll.
If Kwang Soo becomes the king,
things will get bloody today.
- I know.
- No, I'm...
- You know what I mean.
- I want to be the king.
- Should we just pick one now?
- Yes.
- Just pick one.
- We don't know who'll be the king.
I really want to be the king.
- I'll put you guys in prison.
- You don't want me to be the king.
I'll just pick what's left.
(I picked it first.)
And?
- Okay.
- All right.
- One.
- Hang on. Let me open it.
- Two.
- The last one...
Three.
- Darn it.
- What's this?
It's empty.
- Is it Dong Jun?
- I didn't see it yet.
What is this?
- I think it's you.
- It's him.
- You're the king.
- Oh, no.
I'm the king!
We have a horrible king.
- He can't be the king.
- This isn't right.
Take off Ji Suk Jin's pants.
- Take off his pants right away.
- Hey.
- And send him...
- Okay.
- to the mountain.
- The mountain?
Am I the king?
- I can't believe he's the king.
- He's our king.
It's a hierarchical society.
So today's king is Yang Se Chan.
- All day?
- Yes.
- What?
- All day?
It won't change at all?
In today's race, there will be
three different classes.
The first is the nobles.
They are King, Queen,
Premier, and Vice-premier.
These four people are nobles.
- And there are four eunuchs.
- What?
And there are four slaves.
- There are slaves too.
- I'd rather be a slave.
- A slave is better than a eunuch.
Don't you think so?
Those who are in the same class
are in one team.
Each team will earn rice...
through each mission.
You will get rice according
to the results of each mission.
The king gets to decide
the classes of all members.
And he can switch the classes of
two members before each mission.
Can I do that?
- And he can do that all day?
- I'm the real king.
That is, those who want
a better social status should...
get on the king's good side.
We should be nice to Se Chan.
We will be discriminated against
for sure.
I'm so glad that
I've always been nice to Se Chan.
It's started already.
Okay. I'm going to win today.
- I have to flatter Se Chan.
- He's my favorite.
I don't like to flatter others.
You're dressed like a slave.
Look at his pants.
During the race,
the king can talk down to everyone.
And the rest should use
honorifics to the king.
- That's so nice.
- This is crazy.
I love that. It's great.
Now, Se Chan, you should
decide the classes...
of the 11 members as the king.
- My gosh.
- I'm nervous.
My goodness.
Hang on. So I'm the king.
- Pick the queen first.
- I see.
(He should select the queen first.)
(She takes
one step forward quietly.)
Hang on. Why are you
acting like that already?
Could you dance for me?
(She shows off her dance moves
for the king.)
That's the filial dance.
That makes me feel uncomfortable.
Oh, dear.
- Oh, what is going on?
- Sae Rok is a good dancer.
- My gosh.
- Please, Your Majesty.
She looks beautiful.
She dances well.
Her dance...
- Her dance was beautiful.
- She dances well.
Can a man...
- become the queen?
- It's possible.
It can be a man.
(All right then.)
(They all dance together
in the unbiased Running Man.)
- Good.
- Hey.
Gosh, look at them.
You guys are unbelievable.
Stop that. Enough.
- Come here.
- That's dirty.
- It's not dirty.
- My gosh.
Hey, look at him.
He has long hair.
(He shows off his feeble charm.)
I'll select the queen.
- What?
- The king is...
That's because
he's never been a king before.
I've never done this before.
- Just let it go.
- Hey.
- Kings can make mistakes.
- There are...
kings who aren't so smart.
- He's right.
- It can happen.
"I'll select the queen."
- I'll...
- It's hard...
- select the queen.
- to be the king all of a sudden.
My gosh.
The queen is...
(The queen is...)
We don't know it yet.
It might be you, So Min.
(Is it So Min
whom he sees every day?)
(Is it Sae Rok whom he met again
after a long time?)
I think the queen
has been decided already.
The queen is...
Keum Sae Rok.
She's the queen.
- Yes!
- All right.
This is what the queen should do.
- He has an ulterior motive.
- There are two people left.
- Premier and Vice-premier.
- I think it's hard...
to be the Premier
and the Vice-premier.
I think they will be
Jong Kook and Haha.
For Premier and Vice-premier,
you should choose the people
whom you're comfortable with.
- Okay. Good.
- Yes.
What about me?
Shut it!
How dare a slave talk to the king?
- He's a slave.
- A slave?
- Are you a slave?
Otherwise, you should be a eunuch.
I don't want you to be my eunuch.
You should pick someone educated...
for the Premier.
He got the perfect score in math.
Hang on. That sounds
like a good idea.
But I don't want him
because he will stand out.
(He's out because of
his outstanding looks.)
Then why don't you pick this guy...
who's smart but ugly?
Right. He's uglier than me,
- but he's smart.
- He is smart.
I want Jae Suk to be the Premier.
- Really?
- You're successful.
- He's not good-looking.
- But he's smart enough.
- That's right.
Your Majesty.
If you want someone ugly,
I can be a perfect fit.
He looks horrible.
- What's wrong with your face?
- Your Majesty.
He looks like a middle-aged man.
What happened to your face?
What's wrong with your face?
What's wrong with him?
The medicine is too strong.
What happened to your face?
All right then.
I want someone quiet...
and obedient for the Vice-premier.
He's obviously a eunuch.
Long hair.
Those who hold high office
should take good care of me.
Considering regionalism and kinship.
I like the members of Team Slave
except for Suk Jin.
- I like my team.
- You do?
This is nice.
Why did you push me?
- Your Majesty.
- Team Slave has good members.
- What?
- What's that, Hyeong Gu?
- Hey, Hyeong Gu.
He's a eunuch.
It's an urgent
public appeal from the capital.
Hyeong Gu.
He joined SBS
through open recruitment.
Really?
You went to a good college.
Life must be so hard.
Is this what you want
to do with your career?
- Yes, it is.
- Thank you.
You may leave now.
Your Majesty.
- He must've studied hard.
- Please take a look at this.
(What does the appeal that Eunuch
Hyeong Gu brought say?)
Read it for me, Premier.
Okay. I'll read this for you.
"Your Majesty, there are..."
"evil spirits that possess
people's bodies..."
"and disturb the public order
outside the castle."
How terrible!
"And two of them made
their way into the castle..."
"and are hiding among people."
"Please hold a trial..."
"and make sure
to arrest the evil spirits."
I got you!
- You're busted!
- I'm not an evil spirit.
- Are there evil spirits here?
- I got one already.
- Okay.
- It's not me.
- I'm not an evil spirit.
- I smell something fishy.
I think this guy...
- And that...
- and the guy in strange pants...
That slave. It's him.
I think the slave is an evil spirit.
There are...
two evil spirits here
hiding among people.
- This is hard.
- There are two.
I think I know who they are.
You can eliminate
the evil spirits through a trial.
If you eliminate
all the evil spirits...
through three trials today,
humans will win.
And the two humans...
with the most rice
will get the prize.
And the evil spirits
will get the penalty.
Do the evil spirits know
about their identity?
They know
that they are evil spirits.
But if at least one evil spirit
survives, the evil spirits win.
They will win the prize,
and two humans with the least rice
will get the penalty.
Now I'd like you to change
into your costumes...
and move to the first court.
Okay.
(They will change their outfits
and move to the first court.)
Hurry up.
(The Running Dynasty of King Se Chan
begins with hidden evil spirits.)
You don't look good
with a real mustache,
but the mustache drawing
looks great on you.
"You don't look good
with a real mustache?"
- Is there a camera?
- How could you...
- say such a thing to the king?
- I'm sorry.
(Eunuch Kwang Soo
forgot about his identity.)
If you're a eunuch, act like one.
Come here.
Do you want to draw a mustache?
A eunuch can have a mustache.
- Can a eunuch grow a mustache?
- Sure.
(It's possible
only in Running Dynasty.)
A eunuch can't grow a mustache.
What's that mole for?
All right. It means you're mine.
I picked you. You're dismissed.
- Next.
- Hello.
Come here. I'll fix
your dirty mustache.
Don't make it look really dirty.
It's really is dirty.
(He makes it look even uglier.)
(He draws a mole again.)
You're dismissed.
I'm upset with you these days.
What are you upset about?
We should play the King Game
together later on.
Let's do that.
Number 1 and 4 should kiss. Okay?
Darn it. I'm number four.
- What's your number?
- I'm number one.
Good.
(They have fun
playing the King Game.)
Go on in.
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
The ignorant king is in power.
We're in trouble.
Did you come early to sit here?
No, it's not like that.
I just got changed and came here.
(He glanced at him
and burst out laughing.)
My gosh.
You look like a real eunuch
in that costume.
Hey...
Do not speak to us casually
like that.
Right. We're in different classes.
(Their social classes are effective
even on the bus.)
But...
- Don't act like you don't know.
- Are you serious?
You should apologize to him.
Has it begun already?
Hey, but you...
"Hey"? Hey, Ji Suk Jin.
Gosh, seriously.
- Keep it together.
- You don't even have it.
What did you just say?
- But that's true.
- How dare you?
Not now. I'll let you do it later.
I'll let you do it if you promote me
to a eunuch.
I have the authority to do
what I want as your king.
How dare that punk have pictures
taken in a cool pose like that?
He's posing for pictures
when he's a mere servant.
He even has female fans too.
No one follows the King.
You two will have a unibrow.
- No.
- Come here.
(After drawing unibrows
on the servants...)
You're a eunuch.
Yes, Your Majesty.
- Wait.
- I want to watch.
But I thought eunuchs
have no body hair.
It is I, your king, that decides.
Do not say anything.
- My apologies.
- I hate your mullet.
I used to hate another punk
with a mullet.
I'm glad you're here.
Just stay still.
(His sin is having a mullet.)
- Wait.
- Stay still.
I think I know what you're drawing.
Don't move. This will look great.
- Queen, you may get on the bus.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
You look so pretty.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
- Go on in.
Won't she get a mustache?
(Relieved)
(Eunuch Kook, understands the power
structure, surrenders to the power)
Jong Kook is waiting quietly.
(He's done drawing a circle.)
I shall think of you
as my little brother.
Go on in.
Thank you
for your boundless generosity.
Next.
(Eunuch Kook is the last to go.)
- Aren't you Kim Jong Kook?
- Yes, Your Majesty.
You are quite muscular for a eunuch.
I do not know where the testosterone
comes from.
I shall help you produce
even more testosterone.
- Come closer.
- I don't think that's possible.
Don't you all think
that our king is too ignorant?
"Ignorant"?
- I'm sorry.
- That's treason.
- But the King is too ignorant.
- As a matter of fact,
the Premier deserves the throne.
- I agree.
- Of course.
I also think that's right.
He's practically ruling the country
on the King's behalf.
(They're starting to plot a revolt
against the tyrant.)
- Stop it.
- You have control over him.
You are the King to us, my lord.
Do I have the face to become a king?
Yes, my lord.
I'm pretty sure that Jae Suk will
have to change into...
a slave's costume later.
He'll go down step by step
and end up being a slave.
That's possible.
(Airhead King is getting on the bus
after drawing on the others' faces.)
Why are the slaves sitting there?
Come forward.
- Pardon?
- Come forward.
- But...
- Hurry up and come.
- This has been my seat for so long.
- How dare you?
- That's funny.
- How dare you talk back to me?
- Sit in the front seat.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Go to the front seat.
Where should I sit?
Do not think it's a joke
and do as you're told.
- Exactly. How dare he?
- Where should I sit?
- A mere slave...
- Oh, I can sit here.
How dare you sit with a backrest?
Can't I even sit with a backrest?
Sit on the floor, not a seat!
- I shall allow it just this once.
- Run now!
(Everyone else is
as mean as the King.)
All of you must impress me today.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
The King speaks like a thug.
"A thug"?
- I didn't mean it like that.
- How dare you?
How impudent! That little punk.
"Punk"?
You shouldn't say such a vulgar
expression as the Premier.
- Those impudent punks.
- How dare you?
Slave Ji, how dare you
raise your voice?
I shall not let this slide.
Slave Ji.
Sell all the stocks you own
this instant.
Sell all of them!
- How can I sell them?
- That is impossible, Your Majesty.
- The stocks he owns...
- No one will buy them.
His stocks are not worth much
even after selling them.
Then forget what I said.
(Slave Ji's stocks are worth
chump change.)
His stocks are about to be delisted.
Is that so? Then you may
hold on to them.
We can change our social classes
except for the King, right?
That's correct. Except for the King.
(It's possible to change
their social classes, but...)
By the way... I'm asking this...
- out of curiosity.
- Yes?
Are you the manager of these two?
That's irrelevant to the context.
- This is set in the old days.
- I mean...
Why are you shooting
another show here?
Are you shooting "The Manager"?
- No.
- "The Manager"?
Don't be ridiculous.
Are you here as Dong Jun's manager?
- Or as Dong Yoon's manager?
- No.
That suits him well.
Why aren't you two saying anything?
Why would you pat me?
All right.
I shall tighten the discipline,
Your Majesty.
Correct.
- "Correct"?
- You can just say, "Go ahead."
- What was that?
- You see...
- Are you intimidated?
- You can just say, "Go ahead."
You see,
- I've never...
- You are so ignorant.
- played a role as a king before.
- Are you intimidated?
- He's never played...
- "I have no experience, my lord."
I have no experience, my lord.
- "My lord"?
- Wait.
He looks like a pushover.
- Who are you to control me?
- That is not true, Your Majesty.
- My apologies.
- He keeps trying to control me.
- This is what's called "regency".
- Exactly.
You must take him down.
- Do you know what "regency" means?
- Do you know what it is?
I believe that it means
"refreshed areas".
- Airhead!
- I know what it means.
Please lift the restrictions
on the greenbelt.
What is he talking about?
Eunuch Ha, how come you have
three children as a eunuch?
Before I lost it...
He was a step ahead.
My, I didn't know he was so virile.
- Sae Rok, why are you so quiet?
- Yes?
Why?
- She's so playful on set.
- Really?
Sae Rok, what do you do on set?
I'm not playful.
You're the most playful one there.
- Please show us.
- No, I'm not.
Actually, Ji Hyo is also
quite playful off camera.
- When can we see that?
- Ji Hyo...
- Ji Hyo is...
- When can we see that?
the type that acts playful
when the camera goes off.
She's playful in real life.
- That's true.
- But when the camera is rolling,
she becomes shy, and it's been
that way for the past 10 years.
Meanwhile, Suk Jin acts playful
on TV shows,
but he's actually very quiet
in real life.
He doesn't even greet me back
when I say hi to him.
That's true.
- Right.
- He doesn't speak until he's paid.
I guess it's true.
Suk Jin, why is your hand
so sweaty?
What? It's because I'm hot.
- What?
- Aren't your hands sweaty?
- No, see it yourself.
- Something must be going on.
Are you one of the evil spirits?
- No, I'm not.
- You must be.
- I'm just feeling hot. That's all.
- He's suspicious.
I'm really feeling hot.
I'm sure he was given the role.
No. That's not true.
You're blushing too.
- No. It's not the case.
- It wasn't because of his pants.
Jong Kook, touch his hand just once.
- This is...
- If you're not...
an evil spirit, you must be
going through male menopause.
- It's because...
- That was...
an awesome punch line.
I hope he's an evil spirit.
I can finally smile
as I'm relieved now.
You became so talkative suddenly.
Queen, which of us are
the evil spirits?
Before I answer that,
I have a question.
Go ahead.
Is it possible that you are
one of the evil spirits?
- Of course.
- Yes.
Can the King be an evil spirit?
(The King may be
an evil spirit too!)
Of course.
- The King may be one of them too.
- Right.
I have a good feeling about this.
I may be one of them.
How about we choose one
before we arrive?
(Who are the 2 evil spirits
acting as humans among them?)
(Running Palace where the King
and the ministers discuss affairs.)
This place is decorated
like a period movie filming set.
It looks amazing.
(There are
solemn-looking thrones too.)
- It looks nice.
- Look how the chairs are placed.
- How nice. I'm so upset.
- Let's sit down.
Did you really have to place them
like this?
- Of course, I know.
- Sit down quietly.
- Give us some cushions at least.
- Just sit down.
What about the slaves?
Oh, yes. I can sit on the throne.
(Airhead King and Queen Keum are
sitting on the thrones.)
Queen, please sit.
- Did you really have to do this?
- Do you want to sit here?
No, that's okay.
(Everyone found their seats
according to their classes.)
Starting with the slaves...
Why hasn't the Vice-premier
come yet?
- She went to the restroom.
- She went to poop.
Oh, she went to poop?
How dare you describe
the act of the Vice-premier...
as "pooping"?
- You punk.
- Then...
Not every eunuch is the same.
Refrain yourself
from saying anything disrespectful.
That ignorant punk.
- He sounds like a eunuch.
- Oops.
- What was that?
- It's just...
- He sounds like a eunuch.
- It's not like that.
- He sounds like a lowlife.
- It's my old habit.
- "That ignorant punk."
- What kind of king...
Actually, His Majesty used to be
the lowliest...
You brat!
How dare you say that
as a mere premier?
You might become a slave if you
keep acting like this, you brat.
- Please forgive me.
- "You brat."
- No king would put on such a face.
- Please forgive me.
You all will be killed when I speak
the way I used to speak again.
(It's almost a threat.)
I'm trying to act solemn,
but if you keep acting up like this,
- I might go back to the way I was.
- Your Majesty,
please forgive me.
- Do not provoke His Majesty.
- I'll go back to my old self.
- Your Majesty.
- Do not provoke him again.
While I am acting
with grace and dignity...
I beg your forgiveness,
Your Majesty.
- So Min, what are you doing?
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
This is my baby, Your Majesty.
- Who is the father?
- Is he in here?
(Her baby looks like someone.)
Is the father of the baby
in this room?
- He's right here.
- Here.
- He's here.
- Take...
Take...
Take that crazy woman out of here
immediately!
- What do you think you are doing?
- She's crazy about role-playing.
- Isn't this...
- No. Please.
- Did you draw the King's face?
- Please don't do that.
- How dare you...
- He's my baby.
(Genes are powerful.)
- How dare you...
- He's my baby.
Send her to prison!
- Send this crazy woman...
- How dare you...
- Please. I beg you.
- She gave birth to the King's baby.
He's my child.
- You wench!
- "You wench."
You wench!
(Queen Keum got furious as she saw
the baby that looks like the King.)
The baby looks just like the King.
- What kind of role play is this?
- She drew the King's face...
Doesn't he look just like the King?
- Send her to prison.
- How dare you draw his face?
- He's my baby.
- He looks just like the King.
- Then Sung Hoon starts crying.
- Look at him.
- He turns out to be Sung Hoon's.
- He looks...
He has a similar mustache
to Sung Hoon's.
But he looks just like the King.
This is hilarious.
(Crying her heart out)
Director, let's begin.
This is the first trial where you
can eliminate an evil spirit...
before you carry out the mission.
We must eliminate the evil spirit.
Every one of you is free to talk
about the person...
that you think is the evil spirit.
But the King will
select the person...
to be tried.
After the discussion?
- The King has all powers.
- It'd be the best if he's one.
Exactly.
However, the King may also be
one of the evil spirits,
and you may oppose
the King's opinions.
Those who are against his opinions
can revolt against him.
- That's great.
- Revolt?
The revolt succeeds...
if more than half of you
break the dried gourd with the head.
In that case, you'll select the one
to be tried through a vote.
Let's eliminate him before we begin.
If the evil spirit is caught,
the evil spirit will stay as a slave
to the end of the show.
Really?
If the evil spirits lose the race,
the one with less rice...
will receive a penalty twice.
(The evil spirit with less rice will
receive a penalty twice.)
If you put an innocent person
on trial,
the evil spirits will choose
one person...
to take all the rice that person has
behind your backs.
And they will share the rice.
The evil spirits must complete
a hidden mission...
before each of the three trials.
(The evil spirits must complete
a mission before the trials!)
The evil spirits had a mission
to complete on your way here.
- Did they complete it?
- Oh, gosh.
(The evil spirits already completed
their 1st hidden mission.)
- They drew a mole on the face.
- Did they complete the mission?
(They drew a mole on the face!)
He has a mole under his eye.
(Is the mole under the eye
the mark of the evil spirits?)
He drew a mole under the eye.
Why?
He drew that mole.
(Slapping)
Was it the hidden mission?
What? I didn't draw it.
I didn't draw this mole.
I bet it was the hidden mission.
The King drew it.
(The person who drew the mole is...)
(the King.)
I am not an evil spirit.
Why would I have a mole
under my eye?
- See?
- That makes sense.
That's not true. I drew moles
on randomly chosen members.
(Taken aback)
- Your face is so red!
- Look at his face.
No. That's not true.
- He got caught.
- Trust me.
Hey, change your clothes.
Take that off now!
Listen. I'm telling you the truth.
- Why is your face so red?
- No. I was just taken aback.
I'm really not an evil spirit.
(He really is suspicious.)
- I know who the evil spirits are.
- By the way,
the King also has a mole
under his eye.
Do you think I would
make it that obvious?
- What was the hidden mission?
- Listen to me.
I would never do that.
I just stopped drawing moles.
What? Se Chan is crying.
- Hold on. I have...
- Trust me.
- Why would I do that?
- Se Chan, don't cry.
I think...
- I'm really not an evil spirit.
- Investigator Kim.
- I'm not. Trust me.
- I swear.
- Jong Kook, hold back for a while.
- Here he goes again.
- It's not the right time.
- I have things I want to say.
- Wait a little longer.
- But I can't.
- I'm sure he's an evil spirit.
He became the King
when he's an evil spirit.
- That's right.
- This is the true regency.
We had a similar mission before.
- Wait. Hey...
- They lured us into choosing...
- Eunuch Ha.
- Yes?
He became the King...
when he's also an evil spirit.
And you call this the true regency?
I don't think that's what it means.
That darn stupid regency.
Do you even know
what "regency" means?
(Chuckling)
That doesn't make sense.
(Laughing)
(Haha's mistake made
everyone laugh.)
- Let's drop it. It's a happy day.
- How many of us would know?
(Stroking)
(It's such a great day.)
Oh, boy.
- The Queen... The Queen...
- How many of us...
- The Queen is laughing hard too.
- Please...
- Leave her alone.
- I think she's fake laughing.
Isn't this funny, Your Highness?
What is your opinion, Your Highness?
I think... Since my...
My husband...
The King's face turned red.
- So I'm suspicious of him.
- His face did turn red.
- His face is still red.
- You're right.
I also suspect the King.
- What?
- He drew moles on two people.
- And his face turned red.
- You're corning me like this?
- "Corning"?
"Corning"?
You mean "cornering".
- It's not "corning".
- Just tell me one thing.
Why did you draw moles on our faces?
So Min drew a mole on my face.
So I thought it'd be funny
to draw a mole on everyone...
thinking of you all as my children.
While doing it...
I'm sorry.
- He stopped drawing it.
- Actually...
It's all because of Eunuch Kim.
I shall clear my name.
- I shall...
- Please don't.
prove that I'm not an evil spirit...
- Please calm down.
- I shall take my clothes off...
- to prove...
Please calm down.
Do not stop me!
- Please don't.
- Because of Eunuch Kim...
- Your Majesty, please calm down.
- I don't want to play this role.
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
Please explain so we can understand.
- For that petty thing...
- Unfortunately, there's no one...
who can torture that eunuch
in this country.
(No one in this country can
torture that eunuch.)
- This is unfair.
- No one can punish him.
My wish is to get a chance
to slap him in his butt.
I'm so upset.
Let's move on for now.
Since we're all confused,
how about we choose the opposite?
- What do you mean?
- I think it can be a solution.
How about we put Eunuch Lee
on trial?
(Let's put Eunuch Lee on trial!)
My gosh. This isn't right.
- I know you picked him...
- This isn't right.
- just for fun.
- When it's hard to decide...
I can't put him on trial
just because you think...
- it'll be funny.
- When it's hard to decide...
It's best to put him on trial,
Your Majesty.
Please do not play along with him.
He's just being playful now.
- Stop it.
- Then how about Eunuch Park?
He won't stop shivering.
- He's been shivering all day long.
- He's not an evil spirit.
- Right, Sung Hoon...
- We should wait for now.
By the way,
Sung Hoon really looks...
He does look so weak.
- Indeed.
- He looks so weak and fragile.
He was the first person
who lost it.
Did both evil spirits complete
their missions?
Both of them have a mission,
and both completed it successfully.
- Really?
- I see.
(Both of the evil spirits
completed their missions!)
- Let's talk!
- Here they are.
(From the opening
when everyone was watching...)
- This is ridiculous!
- What about me?
(And even in the bus where
they were all sitting together)
(They completed their missions
without letting the humans know.)
I'm sure they did something
on the bus.
- While we were talking on the bus?
- Think carefully.
(Who could be the evil spirits?)
I was sitting at the back, you know.
And I think Dong Yoon is
an evil spirit.
- What did he do?
- Dong Yoon...
- What did I do?
- hit Sae Rok in the head...
and joked around with her.
(Dong Yoon must've joked around
with her to complete the mission.)
- Dong Yoon...
- He must be an evil spirit.
kept joking around with her
like hitting her head.
- But...
- Hitting her head...
- we all do that on set.
- sounds too simple for a mission.
Dong Yoon?
Dong Yoon, you were given a role,
weren't you?
- No.
- That's funny.
No. I'm telling you the truth.
But he always does that to me.
- He always plays jokes...
- That means...
he has a crush on her.
(That means he has a crush on her!)
(What?)
- How dare you lay sight...
- Is that so?
on the Queen as a slave?
That means he has a crush on her.
- Is anyone out there?
- This is like a soap opera.
- Set in the Joseon Era.
- How dare he?
(The handsome slave who falls
in love with Airhead King's woman)
(The Joseon Dynasty Drama,
"The Queen and the Slave")
Are you in love with the Queen?
I heard that social status doesn't
matter in love.
(I heard that social status doesn't
matter in love.)
That little...
- You little...
- I think...
- I think I'll lose her to him.
- To be honest...
- Your Majesty.
- I think I'll lose her to him.
- To be honest,
I think that Dong Yoon is
a better match for her.
How dare you?
I think I'll lose her to him.
Hold on. Then... Hey, Eunuch Lee.
(He suddenly spoke casually to him.)
"Hey, Eunuch Lee"?
- "Hey, Eunuch Lee"?
- That was funny.
Hey, Eunuch Ha. Why?
How are the eunuchs ranked?
- In the order of employment.
- Eunuch Kim is first in rank.
Eunuch Kim is first in rank.
- I'm the head eunuch.
- I see.
Did you see Dong Yoon do it?
- Do what?
- What do you mean?
Why would you speak casually to me?
- Aren't we in the same rank?
- He has seniority over you.
- We're not in the same rank.
- You rude punk!
- Hey, he's your senior.
- They were hired at the same time.
- How dare you?
- Even though we're eunuchs...
- I didn't realize it.
- who don't have it...
I thought we were in the same rank.
Let's have Sung Hoon
slap him in the butt.
- I didn't know.
- Lie down.
It wasn't like that.
- I have seniority over Sung Hoon.
- I won't let this slide.
But...
- The youngest always does this.
- Prove you're not weak.
- Show us.
- But I didn't...
- That was so weak.
(Did he really hit me?)
That was so weak.
- Sung Hoon, your hand must hurt.
- It doesn't hurt at all.
That was so weak.
- I hit him as hard as I could.
- Come back to your seat.
- He's so weak.
- What was that?
He's so peculiar.
- It didn't hurt at all.
- Even though we're eunuchs...
Didn't Dong Jun do
anything suspicious?
- Dong Jun?
- I'm not an evil spirit.
Dong Jun came on Running Man
many times before.
He seems quieter than the last time
he came on the show.
- You see...
- He's been too quiet.
It'd be easier for him to play
an evil spirit.
When we were on the bus,
Dong Jun...
- held my hand like this.
- No way.
- Really?
- Did he really do that?
- So...
- That's because he pitied you.
- I did it out of pity.
- He just felt sorry for you.
- Out of pity?
- Yes.
But men rarely hold...
- another man's hand.
- True.
- I like Kwang Soo.
- Isn't it odd?
(It's hard to read Dong Jun's face.)
(While they were on the bus,)
(Dong Jun suddenly held
Kwang Soo's hand.)
(Could that be the hidden mission?)
No, that's not why did it.
It's hard to tell if Dong Jun
and Dong Yoon are evil spirits.
I'm suspicious of Dong Yoon
and Sung Hoon.
- Dong Jun is suspicious too.
- I think...
You see, the Queen
may also be one of the evil spirits.
- Don't you think?
- Right. She may be one of them.
- That's possible.
- If you think about it...
Could it be Sae Rok?
That's so random.
Now that we know about the hidden
missions, it'll get harder for them.
Anyway, we'll put the person...
- that Mr. Yang chooses on trial.
- Correct.
- Your Majesty, tell us...
- I will...
- who you think it is.
- I'm sorry,
- but did you call him "Mr. Yang"?
- The most suspicious person.
Was that a hidden mission?
(Why did he suddenly call Se Chan
"Mr. Yang"?)
- "Mr. Yang"?
- You called him "Mr. Yang".
I was just being polite.
Do you want me to speak in a girl's
voice because I'm a eunuch?
(Do you want me to speak in a girl's
voice because I'm a eunuch?)
(The sorrow of a eunuch's life
without such ordinary freedom)
- That's not how you address a king.
- I was just being polite.
- That's not appropriate.
- I just addressed him respectfully.
- It's time to make a decision.
- Okay.
Your Majesty.
Gosh. This is so complicated.
I think that one of the evil spirits
is among our members,
and the other is among the guests.
You have to choose just one.
Will you choose
one of the members?
By the way,
why is So Min so quiet today?
Exactly. She's been too quiet too.
- So Min?
- She's holding the dried gourd...
I find it suspicious
that she drew a mole on my face.
- Gosh, I'm not an evil spirit.
- Could drawing on it...
- Hold on a second!
- Gosh, I'm not an evil spirit.
(Could that be her mission?)
Could drawing on it...
- be her...
- Is that her mission?
- No. I drew it for no reason.
Hold on a second!
So Min drew a mole
on the King's face.
- Gosh.
- On the King's face.
(So Min drew a mole
on the King's face.)
- This is driving me nuts.
- Vice-premier Song...
She drew a mole on the King's face.
I'm really not an evil spirit.
- What?
- Was that your mission?
You drew a mole on my face
and drew my face on the dried gourd?
- That's suspicious.
- Try to remember.
Try to remember when I drew a mole
on your face, Your Majesty.
Jae Suk and Jong Kook were...
See? She keeps making excuses
without denying it.
- You can put me on trial, but...
- Exactly. If she's not,
she wouldn't mind going on trial.
- That's right.
- I mean, why do I always...
She became so talkative suddenly.
Jong Kook always
eliminates me first.
Premier Yu, I've made my decision.
- Please tell us your decision.
- I'm not one of the evil spirits.
You know that I don't talk much
when we have male guests, right?
I shall...
put Jeon So Min on trial.
- Gosh.
- I don't think so.
(I shall put Jeon So Min on trial.)
- I'm not an evil spirit.
- We can break our dried gourd.
I said I'm not!
It hurts.
She even smashed the face
of the child she cares about.
- It isn't me.
- I don't think it's her either.
- Then...
- I don't think so.
The King made his decision.
It really isn't me.
I'm sorry but...
- You know me, right?
- It can't be.
Guys, please.
The mission was completed...
on the bus
where I hardly did anything.
Have a seat for now.
If he's right though,
that means he's an evil spirit too.
If he's right,
he'll be taken off the hook.
- It's not me.
- It's not her.
- I doubt it's her.
- Then...
I'll reveal the result
of the first trial.
If So Min is an evil spirit,
she'll drink all of
the sophora root tea...
and stay as a slave forever.
That's bitter, you know.
The bitter flavor will linger.
Then...
- I don't think it's her.
- So Min...
- Is she an evil spirit?
- She isn't.
(Is So Min an evil spirit?)
Is she an evil spirit?
- She isn't.
- See? What did I tell you?
(They failed to find the evil spirit
in the first trial.)
- What?
- See?
It isn't me.
Since you accused
an innocent person,
the evil spirits
will steal the rice...
from the person they choose.
Please put on the blindfolds
in front of you.
After taking their blindfolds off,
the evil spirits will choose
the person they will steal from.
I said it wasn't me.
- Why did you end up choosing me?
- The majority ruled.
The King made up his mind
quite fast if you ask me.
- I'm suspicious of him.
- It's not me.
His actions were questionable.
All right.
The evil spirits will
take off the blindfolds...
and choose a person.
(The evil spirits will now
steal from one of the people.)
(That's when...)
(Dong Yoon takes off his blindfold.)
(That means...)
(Earlier, Dong Yoon entered
an empty room alone.)
What's this?
Did someone leave this behind?
(His curiosity gets the best of him,
so he opens the pot.)
(At the very moment...)
(The energy of the evil spirit
gets sucked into Dong Yoon.)
(That's how Dong Yoon
became an evil spirit.)
Am I at Joseon's palace?
Let's have some fun then.
(Let's have some fun then.)
(Glancing)
What else am I supposed to say?
Are you serious?
Do you do things like this
on Running Man?
(He overcomes the silly lines and
enters the Running Man Universe.)
You're joining us today on
the Records of the Running Dynasty.
You two are the evil spirits
living among humans.
Evil spirits?
While keeping
your identities a secret,
you must complete hidden missions.
Every time you fail your missions,
a letter from your name
will be revealed.
For your first mission,
you'll be making three hearts...
- at the camera.
- Hearts?
One must do so
during the opening scene...
while the other does so on the bus.
Must the both of us succeed?
(The humans open the show
unaware of the situation.)
(While everyone is focused
on the King's power...)
(He succeeds in making
his first heart.)
(While the others were busy
with their statuses...)
(He easily makes his second heart.)
(While the others were focused
on Se Chan being the King)
(He was bold enough
to make two hearts in the end.)
(Dong Yoon was able
to carry out his mission.)
Choose a person.
(The two evil spirits
even survived the trial.)
(The evil spirits chose the person
they will steal the rice from.)
Please put your blindfolds back on.
(Whose rice was stolen
by the evil spirits?)
- You can take them off.
- Can we?
Wait, it's already done?
All right.
- Who are they?
- The evil spirits...
The human
chosen by the evil spirits...
was Jae Suk.
All your rice...
now has been split
between the evil spirits.
- Then he's not an evil spirit.
- No, not Jae Suk.
Wait. You never know.
Yes, it could be a trick.
- To not be suspected.
- Exactly.
It could've been done on purpose.
- He could've chosen himself.
- Of course.
That's possible.
Before we begin the first game,
the King...
can swap the status of two people.
Your Majesty!
I will be by your side
with a gyeonmajiro attitude.
Gyeonmajiro?
That's a nice attitude to have.
(Laughing)
Gyeonmajiro?
Gyeonmajiro...
I too will have
a gyeonmajiro attitude.
To make it fun for me...
(Glancing)
It'll be fun...
to see the Premier swap places
with Eunuch Lee.
Okay!
(A change in rank)
Swap places.
(Airhead King appoints people
just for his own amusement.)
Swap places.
Get going.
(Jae Suk goes from Premier
to a eunuch.)
- I need a mustache.
- A mustache?
Let me give him a beating first.
Sure thing.
The Premier can do what he wants.
Get down on the ground.
Do as you please.
This is for being cheeky earlier!
Take that.
It serves you right.
Do as you wish Premier Lee.
- Darn it! This is so humiliating.
- Hey.
You're the lowest in rank among us.
(You're the lowest in rank
among us.)
(Their ranks are decided based
on who first became a eunuch.)
Kiddo, can you clean this up?
Kiddo, clean this up.
- Unbelievable.
- Clean this up.
You can let one more person
trade ranks.
Unbelievable.
- I want to be Vice-premier.
- I wish to be Vice-premier.
Your Majesty, I wish to be a queen.
- The Vice-premier...
- How dare you!
Your Majesty.
(Who will be blessed the King?)
You sure are pretty.
(You sure are pretty.)
That's out of the blue.
- This is utter nonsense.
- Who do you think is pretty?
This just doesn't make any sense!
Are you kidding me?
Seriously?
No one has ever said
that to me before.
There wasn't even any build-up.
- What...
- I mean...
Unbelievable.
Gosh.
- You must've flirted with him.
- How pretty.
You can be my queen.
(Me?)
You will now be a slave.
(Slave Ji turns his life around
by becoming Queen.)
- Slave Ji.
- This isn't bad.
- It's not bad.
- A rise in status.
- He's been blessed by the King.
- Sae Rok's a slave now.
- Sae Rok...
- Goodness.
This is upsetting.
"You sure are pretty" was hilarious.
- Goodness.
- Suddenly?
He needed a reason,
so he went and said
"You sure are pretty."
Suk Jin seemed
embarrassed by that statement.
Higher.
(Slap!)
Right? The Queen
is of a higher status.
(Queen Ji shows his true colors.)
How dare you lay your hands
on the Queen?
You shouldn't.
Can a queen have such a husky voice?
You. You're awfully quiet.
Weren't you up here
just a moment ago?
Close your mouth.
Close your mouth!
I told you to close your mouth.
Yes, Your Highness.
Close your mouth!
(What an insult.)
- Gosh.
- you.
- You know I like you, right?
- Thank you.
He suddenly got to be a queen.
(The 1st trial ends with
the Airhead King's appointments.)
I sure am pretty.
So pretty.
(Se Chan's people change locations.)
No, don't do this.
You're giving me the creeps.
- Don't do this.
- Honey!
In the first game,
you'll be explaining words
in the format of old poems.
This is Syllable Count Poem.
- That sounds difficult.
- Just the sound of it...
Each team will take turns.
The three explaining the word...
will do so
by keeping the syllable count...
- of 4, 3, and 4.
- No way.
- 4, 3, and 4 syllables.
- Like a poem.
Sounds like fun.
- 4, 3, and 4 syllables.
- 4, 3, and 4.
Each team will get three words
to explain.
Once the game is over,
you'll be able to scoop up rice...
and the amount will depend
on how well you do in the game.
- Let's do this.
- You're all good with words.
- Team Eunuch.
- Let's go!
Let's have some fun.
1, 2, 3.
(Let's party!)
Let's have some fun.
Go, go!
Let's do this.
Here we go.
Give them the word.
(Starting with Eunuch Yu, which
word must they explain first?)
(Playing the field)
(He must start off
with 4 syllables.)
You can do this. I believe in you.
- Of course.
- I believe in you.
- "Of course." Are you done?
- "Of course."
- He said his.
- No way.
- "Of course."
- Just let him have that.
- But he said it.
- "Of course."
- Seriously?
(Sung Hoon must explain
in just three syllables.)
(Groaning)
(He suddenly lets out
an elegant grunt.)
(The modern-day concept
is hard to explain.)
What's with his pose?
- Go ahead.
- What's wrong?
We got off to a bad start.
Prior.
(Playing the field:
Of course, Prior)
- Will they, won't they?
- Playing the field!
- Nice!
- Are you kidding me?
(Thanks to Jong Kook's wit,
they get the first one right.)
I already knew
when Sung Hoon said his word.
- I can't believe it.
- What a relief.
Okay, nice one.
This...
(The next word
is trickier to explain.)
(A sitz bath)
While seated.
(A sitz bath: While seated)
(Sighing)
- He needs to say a good one.
- While seated.
It's not an easy one.
Warm.
(A sitz bath: While seated, Warm)
While seated and warm.
Anus bath.
(A sitz bath is a bath
for the anus.)
- Nice one.
- Nice.
(The immature wording
gets Jong Kook the answer.)
- A sitz bath.
- Nice!
- I already knew what it was.
- Nicely done!
I told you to just
make sense, right?
Haha was right to say it.
- Can one say that?
- If not,
it could've been lower-body bathing.
I have to give them credit for that.
I knew it was a sitz bath though.
Nicely done.
You're getting the hang of it.
- Nice!
- It's perfect.
Nice!
(Nolboo)
With Heungboo.
(Nolboo: With Heungboo)
They're brothers.
Budaejjigae.
Nice one!
Nice.
Nolboo.
(Team Eunuch got
all three questions correct.)
- Nice.
- Team Eunuch got all three right.
That was funny.
- All right! Let's go.
- Let's do it well.
So Min is the oldest on her team.
I'm the leader.
I'm the leader, you guys.
- Get ready.
- This is great.
- Here we go.
- I'll do my best.
You guys look fresh!
Get ready, set, go!
(The first word is "eunuch".)
Those guys...
(Eunuch)
"Those guys"?
Refers to. It refers to those guys.
- Why would you say "refers to"?
- I know you can...
(The last player makes a complaint.)
- I know you can wrap it up!
- Why would you be so serious?
Why would you be so serious?
- She put on a straight face.
- Don't be so serious.
- You blew your chance.
- "Refers to".
Come on!
You should've said
a four-letter word instead!
Maybe she's an evil spirit.
Maybe this is her mission.
It is eunuch.
Sae Rok is doing a good job!
(Pork cutlet)
Swings.
- That's a good approach.
- That's a good one.
Lined up.
To sell this food.
I don't know what that is.
- You know the food he likes!
- She doesn't know this?
She's behind in trend.
- It's...
- So Min is old-fashioned!
Maybe she got it wrong on purpose.
Oh, she's not an evil spirit.
Seriously, this guy...
- I can't do this.
- I know you're not it.
- I know you're not it. Sit down.
- Come on.
So Min is not an evil spirit.
- You got it wrong on purpose, no?
- They said she's not it.
- You're an evil spirit, aren't you?
- I'm not!
- Aren't you an evil spirit?
- Hey.
- Why are you so bad at this?
- So Min.
Can the evil spirit
leave her body for a second?
Can it leave and go back in?
It's pork cutlet.
- I didn't know that.
- Hey.
- She's only interested in love.
Kim Jong Kook and Haha's...
- Right! You should've said that.
- Then she'd have gotten it right.
(He apologizes right away
for his poor writing skill.)
I'd have gotten it right.
She'd have said the answer
right away.
- Of course.
- She'd have figured it out fast.
Their pork cutlet is the best.
I'll send you some.
So Team Slave
got all three questions wrong.
They did well,
but I couldn't get it right.
(Disappointed,
but they accept the result.)
Well done.
What's our score?
(Right then)
(Evil Spirit Dong Yoon
cuts across the set...)
(and heads to the back.)
Well done.
Good job.
- That was close.
- Only if they got one right.
- Well done.
- Okay.
- You did well too.
As a result,
Team Eunuch is in first place.
(Why did Dong Yoon go around
and tell them they did well?)
(Before the shoot)
Here's the hidden mission
the evil spirits need to accomplish.
The second mission is to touch
the name tags of everyone.
Touching their name tags?
- You can divide the mission.
- We can do it together?
Got it.
(They received the hidden mission
to touch everyone's name tags.)
(From then, they looked for
every chance they could get...)
(to touch everyone's name tag.)
Well done.
(He managed to touch most of their
name tags before the mission ended.)
(Who is the other spirit
that touched the name tags?)
We did it.
Now it's time to take the rice
according to the ranking.
The 1st place team
can scoop 3 times.
The 2nd place team
can scoop 2 times.
And the 3rd place team
can scoop 1 time.
Move the rice to your pot.
We never know.
All right.
- It goes deep.
- He can scoop out a lot.
Wow, Kwang Soo is taking
a lot at once.
You scooped out a lot.
(Taking a full bowl of rice)
He filled the entire bowl.
- That's amazing.
- You're amazing.
That's as much as
a bowl and a half.
(Pouring the whole bowl
into his pot securely)
- He got the most rice.
- Let's give it up for him.
There's a lot!
(His great performance
calls for a round of applause.)
Wait a minute.
What's this, Kwang Soo?
No one interrupted him too.
There's another name tag
on top of his.
He poured the rice
into Jae Suk's pot.
(Changing the pot)
(He donated the rice
to someone else's pot.)
Is this for real?
(The owner of the pot magically
changes in an instant.)
(While Kwang Soo is scooping out
the rice,)
(Jae Suk put his name tag
on Kwang Soo's.)
It's like "The Usual Suspects".
He peeled off Kwang Soo's tag
and his name was there.
Kwang Soo must really like Jae Suk.
And the 3rd place team can scoop
1 time. Move the rice to your pot.
The 1st place team
can scoop 3 times.
There's a limit to how much
I can scoop.
Let's move on to the second trial.
Let's go!
Let's go.
(Will they be able to find
the evil spirits this time?)
My seat is right next to the King's.
(The people of Running Dynasty
gather in the court.)
That means someone
pulled off the hidden mission.
(Evil Spirit Dong Yoon seems excited
to have finished all the missions.)
It was really hard to play the game
and look for the evil spirits.
- But I've never looked for them.
- You looked for them?
We can just depend on Jong Kook.
- But when he does observe,
- I observed everyone.
we tend not to.
I'm sure I've found one this time.
- You did?
- Hey.
(He's sure that he's found
an evil spirit?)
(Dong Yoon gets nervous as Jae Suk
is sure to have found one.)
I have a few suspicions,
but let's see
what they have in common.
We're reassured
since we have a detective.
We need to catch one this time.
We must catch one.
I'll switch your status.
- During the mission...
- It's all up to him.
- The eunuch here...
- I think he wants to say something.
- Eunuch Kim seems to have...
- The youngest eunuch.
observed everyone thoroughly.
- Eunuch Yu, our youngest...
- Eunuch Yu,
- go ahead and speak.
- He made a mistake this time.
(An evil spirit made a mistake?)
What kind of mistake?
- Let's hear him out.
- Let's hear about it.
(A mistake?)
I think the hidden mission was to
touch our name tags.
Name tags?
(Jae Suk figured out the
hidden mission of the evil spirits?)
Toward the end... Do you remember?
After Team Slave was done
playing the game,
Dong Yoon...
Who sat next to me?
- He touched my name tag too.
- He touched our name tags.
(While Dong Yoon was doing
the hidden mission,)
(they got suspicious
of his behavior.)
"Well done."
- That's right!
(They agree with the claim
Jae Suk is asserting.)
- Let me tell you the reason.
- Yes.
I can explain.
- Go ahead then.
- All right.
Let me explain.
I only touched their shoulders.
- You only touched their shoulders?
- Yes.
If you can't explain yourself well,
- you'll have to be tried.
- That's right.
We must have him tried.
Yes, we must. I'm sure it's him.
- I'm telling you, it's not me.
- Then this must be what happened.
Then why didn't you touch
my name tag?
- I know.
- Don't be too disappointed.
But he didn't touch my name tag.
You could've not felt it.
(That's what happened.)
(Is that so?)
Let me explain.
It must be hard
to touch everyone's name tag though.
- Go ahead then.
- It must be hard.
First of all, I did not
touch everyone's name tag.
Then the mission must be
to touch only a few.
- No, that's not true.
- Maybe you had to touch three.
It's my habit to encourage people
while grabbing their shoulders.
- But he's never done that before.
- He's never done it?
- No, it's just that...
- He's never done it before.
- You only skipped out on me?
- It's not that.
Why would everyone get so sullen?
- We're here to investigate.
- Their friendship is damaged.
Maybe he was told to touch
only the male members.
But you need to remember this.
If Dong Yoon isn't the evil spirit,
we need to catch two at once
in the next trial.
We need to catch one now.
I told you, I'm sure about this.
But what if Dong Yoon
is not an evil spirit?
- We need to catch one now.
- Let me tell you one more thing.
- Here's one more.
- We'll hear you out.
But...
Dong Yoon was playing the game
on this side, right?
Yes, he was on that side.
He went around the room...
and came behind us
to tell us we did well.
He didn't have to
go around the room.
- He didn't have to.
- That's right.
- He could've just said it there.
- No, that's not true.
So that's what happened.
I told you it's him.
(It must be him.)
You must've been in a hurry.
Why did he go around the room?
(Now everyone is sure
that Dong Yoon is the evil spirit.)
- We're now sure that it's him.
- You got the wrong guy.
Why did he go around the room?
Why did you do that?
Tell us your reason.
- Well, that's...
- You didn't touch So Min's.
- Why did you touch everyone else's?
- Are you usually that affectionate?
He didn't touch mine.
I'm usually affectionate toward...
- If you can't explain yourself...
- Okay, you can put me on trial.
(You can put me on trial.)
You can, but I'm telling you,
it's not me.
Toward the end...
Seeing how confident he is,
it feels like we got the wrong guy.
Isn't it much easier to catch
an evil spirit...
once they get someone wrong?
Did you hear what he just said?
Then you can... Even if I'm tried,
- it's my loss.
- Since we're confused,
let's just put Kwang Soo on trial.
(When you're confused,
just pick Kwang Soo.)
(He's always suspected
when they're not sure.)
Do you want to get a beating?
(Do you want to get a beating?)
Do you want to get a beating again?
(His threat is not scary at all.)
When we're confused,
just pick Kwang Soo.
(They will save that option
for now.)
Please make your decision.
- All right, then.
- Let's just stick to Dong Yoon.
- Your Majesty.
- If everyone agrees,
- Let's just pick him.
- I'll pick him then.
- Your Majesty.
- Let's go with him.
- We should try him.
- All right.
- Even in the first game...
- I'll put Dong Yoon on trial.
- But he seems so confident though.
- I know.
- I don't think it's him.
- Your Majesty, it is him.
- We could be wrong.
- How dare you?
Then who's the other person
that touched the name tags?
- There must be another one.
- This is crazy.
I didn't touch everyone's name tag.
Let's just see if he's the one.
- Okay.
- All right.
All right. Dong Yoon is...
(Dong Yoon is...)
the evil spirit.
He is the evil spirit!
(They managed to catch Dong Yoon
only after two trials.)
- I will... I will...
- Your Majesty.
- think...
- We managed to catch him.
very highly of you.
We managed to catch him!
You evil spirit!
- I am going to...
- You wicked evil spirit!
How dare you touch our name tags?
(Evil Spirit Dong Yoon drinks up
the sophora root tea.)
- Gosh, this is really bitter.
- That's enough.
Is it good for my health?
- Okay.
- Of course.
- Then...
- We caught him.
Don't finish it. It's really bitter.
He acted so well until the end.
(She quietly runs away.)
- Why did you leave quietly?
- What?
What do you think you're doing?
- Nothing.
- What was that all about?
What?
- She gave...
- So Min.
Have you ever brought us candy...
- when we drank something bitter?
- I know!
- Is today Valentine's Day?
- What was that all about?
- You just gave him candy?
- Valentine's Day?
Why did you do that
when we caught an evil spirit?
Because it's bitter.
What was that?
You're an evil spirit, aren't you?
(What was that?
You're an evil spirit, aren't you?)
No! They said I'm not!
- You see?
- Okay.
If we didn't try her earlier,
we'd have kept suspecting her.
- Of course.
- I know.
Look what she just did.
- We did a good job.
- We really did.
That was a great choice.
Now it's time to change your status.
(Time for King Se Chan's
personnel reshuffle)
Obviously,
Eunuch Kim and Eunuch Yu
did a wonderful job.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
But I was offended...
by Premier Lee.
Me? Why?
- What did I do?
- If I do not know the answer,
you are supposed to butter me up
and tell me the answer.
How dare you keep your mouth shut?
But I...
Your Majesty, I am all ready.
- Your Majesty.
- I'll switch Premier Lee...
I'll give you my rice.
- You're speaking informally to him?
- I'll give you my rice.
And before the next mission starts,
I'll wire you some cash.
Cash?
Your eyes tell me
that you are going to betray me.
(His offer to bribe
doesn't work on the King.)
I will switch Premier Lee...
(Your Majesty!)
with...
- Eunuch Yoo over there.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
I will switch him back
to being a premier.
- He's back to his position.
- But...
(A glorious return of Premier Yu)
Move!
It's better to stay as Queen.
I'm so lazy to change the costume.
You're lazy to change the costume?
What's wrong, honey?
I just realized...
how ugly you are.
(The Queen needs to be
switched fast.)
I need to switch you
with someone else.
Your voice is beautiful.
(Your voice is beautiful.)
Will you be my queen?
- My goodness.
- Come on up!
That seat is really uncomfortable.
- Get out of here.
- Okay.
- Get out of here!
- Move!
Hey, you're the youngest now.
My goodness.
I am? Gosh.
- All right!
- How gross.
- He's so cute though.
Queen Jong Kook is so cute!
- I need to erase my mustache.
- You should.
Now I'll tell you the rules
of the final mission.
In the final mission,
you could be a prey
or you could be a hunter.
It's called
the Ironic Survival Game.
It's a survival game
where you'll use a toy gun.
- It sounds fun.
- Sounds like fun.
You'll each attach five balloons
to your body.
We'll give you 30 bullets.
- It's that game.
- We're using balloons again.
You can't shoot at just anyone
on the opposite team.
At two different spots
in this building,
there are two roulettes
with your names on them.
You should spin the roulettes,
and the name you get
will be your target.
- I see.
- We have different targets.
So we don't know
who will be our targets.
Your target will be changed
every two minutes.
The person you get after spinning
the roulettes...
will be your target for two minutes.
When all of your balloons pop,
you'll be out.
The ranking of the teams will be
determined by who remains last.
The final winner
can scoop out the rice.
All right. I got good team members.
- Of course.
- You picked the good ones.
Let's move to the starting point
of the last mission.
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
Since I got busted already,
I think I can do a good job
in helping the other evil spirit.
Wish me luck!
(He has to pull off the hidden
mission with the other evil spirit.)
Hold on.
- Haha.
- Yes?
- Are you busy?
- Why? What's up?
Can I put my forehead against yours?
- What?
- Can we put our foreheads together?
Oh, you're just
doing the mission plainly?
What's this?
Am I becoming an evil spirit?
Will this make me an evil spirit?
- What was that?
- I'm off now!
I'm off! Was that okay?
Okay.
- Hey...
- Since we're on the same team,
- I know that.
- if I'm cornered,
you need to come and help.
You know that, right, King?
- Do not worry, Queen Jong Kook.
- Honey.
I will protect my queen.
- I'm here, and you're there.
(I'm here, and you're there.)
(He's the King's man.)
- Honey!
- Gosh. What is it?
It's so gross. It feels like...
- You need to protect me.
- Don't worry.
- How adorable.
- Honey.
You're so cute!
(Stamping his feet
with his big build)
I'll be waiting.
You need to come to me.
- Don't worry!
- Okay? To over here.
(Queen Mustache has too much
testosterone and is too cute.)
The race will start now.
Okay.
The targets are...
(Announcing the first targets)
(Who will be the first targets
that will be attacked by everyone?)
(The first targets are...)
Kim Dong Jun and Song Ji Hyo.
The first targets are
(They're the targets!)
(They run away first.)
This is driving me crazy.
Kim Dong Jun and Song Ji Hyo?
I'm coming! Bang, bang!
- Song Ji Hyo and Kim Dong Jun.
- Dong Jun?
We need to protect Dong Jun.
Wait a minute.
Where could Dong Jun be?
Song Ji Hyo and Kim Dong Jun?
Okay, no one on our team
is a target.
(They need to protect
their team members to win.)
I should hide in here.
(Ji Hyo plans to hide
inside a lecture room.)
Come in quickly.
(Dong Jun is
at the end of the corridor.)
Look for Dong Jun now!
(Jae Suk appears right then.)
Dong Jun is on Team Slave.
(He spots Jae Suk in red
from afar.)
Darn it.
(He quickly flees downstairs.)
(Eunuch Park Sung Hoon appears.)
(There's my target!)
(The first chase begins.)
(Sung Hoon does his best
to chase Dong Jun,)
(but Dong Jun
is getting farther away.)
(Dong Jun runs away relaxedly.)
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
(Paper Doll Sung Hoon
appears way too late.)
Why doesn't it work?
I can't shoot the bullet!
(Blaming the bullets)
(Relaxed Dong Jun...)
I can't shoot it!
(and the guy with a mullet
who runs as fast as he can)
Darn it!
Darn it.
(We can only hear
his sound of breathing.)
I could've shot him.
(Showing off his poor stamina
as soon as the chase starts)
Dong Jun?
I got him!
(Another guy
with a mullet appears.)
Hey, Dong Jun.
Haha! We need to finish him!
(Dong Jun ran into Haha
while running from Kwang Soo.)
(It popped!)
(Another one popped.)
Finish him!
(2 of Dong Jun's balloons popped
in an instant.)
No, no!
This is exhausting.
It will work. It's open!
It's open!
Here.
(Kwang Soo squeezed himself
through the door.)
(Dong Jun is in danger!)
He's out!
(Kwang Soo hit the balloon
when Dong Jun was about to flee.)
- Kim Dong Jun is out.
- All right!
- I did it!
(Kim Dong Jun is out.)
I couldn't do anything.
I was about to...
Kim Dong Jun is out.
(Right then, Dong Yoon puts
his forehead against Dong Jun's.)
The second targets are
Kim Jong Kook and Park Sung Hoon.
(The second targets are
Kim Jong Kook and Park Sung Hoon.)
- Hey, I'm on your team.
- Oh, right.
(He automatically aims his gun.)
My goodness. Hey!
- I'm sorry.
- That's quite upsetting, you know.
I'm so sorry.
- Who's the other one?
- Who's the other target?
Who's the other target?
- Oh, Sung Hoon?
- It's Sung Hoon.
(The tall guy with poor stamina
is the second target.)
He's over here!
- Come here, everyone!
- Run, Sung Hoon!
(He runs away first.)
- Run!
- Shoot him! What are you doing?
Why would I? He's on my team.
(Se Chan chases after Sung Hoon
right away.)
Run!
(Run!)
Run, Sung Hoon!
(Run, Sung Hoon!)
(He runs at full speed
without even turning back.)
- Who's the other target?
- Jong Kook.
Gosh, this is really exhausting.
(His breathing gets heavy
as though he's about to throw up.)
(He's about to pass out.)
They said you can't get out of bed
for two days...
if you shoot Running Man.
(They said you can't get out of bed
for 2 days after Running Man.)
I should stay in bed for three days.
(I should stay in bed
for 3 days.)
(While Sung Hoon announced that
he'll stay in bed for 3 days,)
(what has Dong Yoon been up to?)
How come...
(What has Dong Yoon been up to?)
Excuse me.
- What is it? What are you doing?
- Let me put my forehead...
Wait. Hey!
Hey!
Why would you...
I did it. I did it for him.
- But...
- I did it for him.
- Just do it for him.
- Yes?
(Dong Yoon is
openly doing the mission here?)
(Jae Suk puts his forehead
against Dong Yoon's for now.)
The current targets are...
Jae Suk and Suk Jin.
(Jae Suk?)
(Dong Yoon was right next to him.)
(He succeeds to pop
1 of Jae Suk's balloons.)
Hey! Hey!
(1 more balloon pops.)
Ji Hyo! Hey!
- Ji Hyo, I am on your team.
- Oh, you are right.
- I popped two balloons.
(Dong Yoon chases after Jae Suk.)
- I used up my bullets.
- You are out of bullets.
(Jae Suk succeeds to get away.)
(This is such an important moment.)
You are out of bullets.
Where is Suk Jin?
(Suk Jin is the other target.)
(The targets were announced
when Suk Jin was with Se Chan.)
(He shows his pitiful back
as always.)
(He runs to a dead end.)
You are out of bullets.
(He manages to prolong his life
because Se Chan is out of bullets.)
No way!
- Suk Jin, run!
- Help me!
- Suk Jin!
- Don't go that way!
(He runs into the muscular queen.)
(Screaming)
- Help me!
- Don't go that way!
(His scream fills the studio.)
- Suk Jin!
- No!
- Run!
Run!
- Why won't the balloons pop?
- Run!
- Help me!
(Everyone is obsessed
with the shooting game.)
(Even Dong Yoon joins the hunt
for Eunuch Ji.)
No!
- Help me!
- Run!
Run!
Run! Run!
(Kwang Soo the eunuch
blocks the door with his body.)
Run!
(He runs away with 2 balloons
thanks to Kwang Soo.)
No.
(Ji Hyo chases after him!)
- Suk Jin.
- All right.
- I am sorry.
- It's okay.
Isn't it time to spin the wheel?
(Bang! Bang!)
(Two balloons pop at once!)
(Ji Hyo popped 2 balloons
with 1 bullet.)
Did both balloons get popped?
Why did both balloons get popped?
Did she pop two balloons at once?
- Really?
- Did I do that with one bullet?
Suk Jin is out.
- Gosh.
- Suk Jin is out.
Did anyone else get eliminated?
I am the first one, right?
The race...
starts.
(After Dong Jun,
Suk Jin gets eliminated.)
Did you see Jae Suk?
- I popped two balloons.
- Where is he?
What?
Let me put my forehead
against yours.
- Why?
- Let me do that.
Why do you need to do that?
- What?
- What is up with him?
- Hey.
- What?
What are you doing? Stop it!
Stop it!
(Is Dong Yoon carrying out
a hidden mission?)
Let go of me!
I... I...
He is so suspicious.
Is there a way to make
more evil spirits...
- or turn someone into one?
- The current targets are...
Sae Rok and Se Chan.
(The current targets are
Sae Rok and Se Chan.)
(Sae Rok loses 3 balloons
because of Jong Kook right away.)
No!
(With no place to go,)
(the former queen gets taken out
by royalty.)
(Se Chan gets chases for a while.)
(He gets eliminated
when the last balloon pops.)
Se Chan and Sae Rok are out.
- No!
- The current targets are...
Jae Suk and Sung Hoon.
(The current targets are
Jae Suk and Sung Hoon.)
(Jae Suk tries to go
to a secluded place.)
(Panting)
(So Min sees him.)
(Jae Suk's location)
(While she prepares to attack,
Dong Yoon appears.)
Dong Yoon, come here.
Jae Suk is in here.
(Whispering)
(Jae Suk doesn't have
many bullets.)
Is that door open?
Do you want me to go in?
- Aren't you going to shoot him?
- I guess I should.
You are acting strange.
What is up with you?
(He turns around.)
You are acting strange.
(Why isn't Dong Yoon attacking
Jae Suk?)
You are acting strange. What?
- No, no.
- Hold on.
Okay.
So Min.
It's not like that.
You are acting strange.
(Is he trying to protect
a fellow evil spirit?)
That's so suspicious.
Why doesn't Dong Yoon want to shoot
Jae Suk?
The current targets are...
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
Gosh, the targets changed.
(An evil spirit candidate,
Jae Suk comes outside.)
That's so suspicious.
Why didn't Dong Yoon want to shoot
Jae Suk?
Why did he hesitate?
Who? Dong Yoon?
(Dong Yoon seemed to hesitate
when he could take out Jae Suk.)
Okay.
(So Min finds it strange.)
(The current targets,
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo)
(Kwang Soo the eunuch
was picking up bullets.)
What? That startled me.
What are those neon shoes?
Jong Kook is a target, right?
- Yes.
- Gosh, that startled me.
How do I open this?
I was going to go out
when Kwang Soo left.
Jong Kook is here.
What should we do?
(But they don't know what to do.)
(They spray water.)
(For goodness' sake.)
(He even spits out water.)
The current targets are
Haha and Ji Hyo.
Jong Kook.
(He gets caught
when the targets change.)
(It lands on his face.)
Haha, run!
Haha!
- You are here.
- Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, I have a bad back.
- He is here, Jae Suk!
- I have a bad back.
- Haha.
- We need to finish him off.
Come on.
- Haha!
- That stings!
- Ouch.
- Haha.
Turn around.
(Haha has 1 balloon left.)
Come on out.
My goodness.
I couldn't run away.
Haha is out.
- Haha is out.
- Sung Hoon.
The current targets are
Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.
(Kwang Soo and Jae Suk,
the new targets get announced.)
(Team Eunuch: 3, Team Slave: 2,
Team Noble: 2)
I have three bullets left.
With these three bullets,
I will make a difference.
(He is overly absorbed in the game.)
What are you doing?
Dong Yoon, hold on! Listen to me!
(Dong Yoon attacks Kwang Soo
when his guard is down.)
Dong Yoon, stop! Dong Yoon!
(If Kwang Soo gets eliminated,
Team Eunuch will place last.)
Kwang Soo and Jae Suk?
(While the two of them fight,
these people go after Jae Suk.)
(They spot Jae Suk.)
(The weak duo
goes after Jae Suk as well.)
By the way, Jae Suk is really fast.
I am exhausted.
(Kwang Soo's last balloon
is before his eyes,)
(but Dong Yoon keeps missing it.)
(Jae Suk is being chased.)
- The other way.
- The other way?
It's too late for that.
Please.
(The last targets will determine
the result.)
Come on!
(Kwang Soo is using strength
and Jae Suk is using speed.)
I refuse to go out.
(The two targets must survive
to keep the teams' ranks.)
(What will be the result
of the final race?)
Welcome back.
(The race ends.)
- Kwang Soo, did you survive?
- I survived.
Good work.
(The final survivors enter
the courtroom.)
I can't guess the result.
Firstly,
the evil spirits succeeded to do
the hidden mission.
- Was there another one?
- What could it be?
I guess there was something
other than the forehead touch.
I will announce the result.
The first place is...
(The 1st place)
Team Noble.
Then the other 2 teams placed 2nd.
They will scoop out rice two times.
Now,
shall we begin with the slaves?
(They get to scoop out rice
according to the result.)
It's game over.
The tables have been turned.
We don't have much.
After a general meeting,
the king will decide
who will be put on a stand.
This is driving me crazy.
- Jae Suk, I keep hearing tip-offs.
- What?
Some people saw...
how Dong Yoon avoided popping
your balloons.
This is bad.
Jae Suk is suspicious.
- Jae Suk is suspicious.
- That's right.
It must be true.
When you said
that Jae Suk is suspicious,
Dong Yoon said no.
- Is there a reason to say no?
- Seriously.
- I know.
He had no reason to say no.
- To be honest...
- I mean...
He got caught.
He is too pure.
Let me tell you this.
- I am not an evil spirit.
- He is changing the subject.
Think about the seating arrangement
we had on the bus.
If you think about it,
Jae Suk and Dong Yoon sat together.
They sat by the window.
- Jae Suk sat by the window.
- That's right.
- They were behind me.
- Yes.
- Dong Yoon tried to depend on him.
- Did they sit together?
They sat together.
Dong Yoon tried to depend on him.
That's why he sat next to Jae Suk.
If I am not an evil spirit,
you will be in big trouble.
- You have one chance.
- We are simply throwing out...
- ideas.
- Okay, okay.
Can I give you an alibi?
Go ahead.
Are you trying...
- to protect Jae Suk?
- An alibi?
Why are you protecting him?
- I mean...
- It's so confusing.
Why are you protecting him?
Are you trying to protect me?
You are making it look weird.
Everything he does seems suspicious.
- Dong Yoon...
- Look at that.
He lost control.
- He lost control.
- He lost control of the situation.
Are you trying...
- Dong Yoon.
- Give us the alibi.
- His ears turned red.
- He dug himself into a hole.
His ears turned red.
- I will talk.
- Okay.
Why did you take Jae Suk's rice?
- Why did you take it?
- I thought...
he would acquire a lot of rice.
(Simple)
Was that the reason?
Most people would have chosen
Jong Kook.
(Dong Yoon's words are unclear.)
- I can't believe him!
- Let's send Jae Suk to the stand.
- We have the answer.
- It's pretty clear.
Jae Suk is suspicious.
Dong Yoon and Jae Suk are
suspicious.
The other evil spirit must be
a veteran.
The Running Man members
are better at carrying out...
a mission such as touching
the name tags...
- in secret.
- That's right.
We should be suspicious
of Jong Kook too.
That goes without saying.
The other evil spirit must be
a Running Man member.
- That must be the case.
- But...
Kwang Soo...
Oh, he isn't Kwang Soo.
He resembles Kwang Soo.
- Seriously.
- He resembles Kwang Soo.
- I am here.
- He has long hair too.
- He resembles Kwang Soo.
- He looks the same.
- I see the resemblance.
I would believe it if someone said
that they are brothers.
Sae Rok, who do you think
is the other evil spirit?
- I think it's Jae Suk.
- Why?
- This is driving me crazy.
- Earlier,
So Min said repeatedly...
that Dong Yoon didn't shoot
at Jae Suk.
I suggested that we go and attack
Jae Suk together.
When I gave you his location,
you were like, "Why?"
He was hesitant.
- He wanted to go someplace else.
- So Min spread this story.
But So Min isn't an evil spirit.
- She isn't an evil spirit.
- Be honest.
- You aren't an evil spirit, right?
- Are you?
- She is too suspicious.
- I am not an evil spirit.
Let's send So Min to the stand...
one more time to be certain.
I am not an evil spirit.
Why are people so suspicious of me?
Dong Yoon was with me for a while.
- That's right. They were together.
- And...
Dong Yoon held people's hands
and put his forehead against theirs.
- That's right.
- When he did that,
Sae Rok ran away
and Dong Jun refused to do it.
Everyone ran away.
But Jae Suk went,
"Really?" Then he put his forehead
against Dong Yoon's.
All right, Dong Yoon.
(He let Dong Yoon hold his hand
and put his forehead against his.)
It's strange.
He is either an angel...
- or someone with a mission.
- No.
I let him do it
because I thought he was faking.
- I can explain clearly.
- Hold on.
You haven't explained
anything clearly!
- Hey!
- Wasn't it locked?
You haven't explained
anything clearly!
Jae Suk.
Why do you think
Dong Yoon keeps protecting you?
He is trying to hide his partner.
Everyone thinks
I am the other evil spirit,
so Dong Yoon is driving a nail
into the coffin.
He is doing this to
help the team win.
Are you saying he twisted it twice
to frame you...
when someone else is
the other evil spirit?
That would make him a genius.
So this might be a feint?
There is the fanny pack.
- You know,
- But an evil spirit...
your Highness.
If you are unsure,
choose Eunuch Lee.
Why do you keep framing me?
Why would he choose me?
I didn't do anything today.
Hold on. It's true.
(What?)
- It's over.
It's over. His rice is gone.
- His rice is gone.
- Let go.
- It's over.
(Eunuch Lee lost
all the rice he gathered.)
- Leave it.
- Don't touch the rice.
- Don't touch it.
It isn't allowed.
- It was a mistake.
- It doesn't matter.
- Leave it.
You spilled it.
- You spilled it.
- Leave it.
It's not like
someone else spilled it.
There are
about 12 grains of rice inside.
Who is the other evil spirit?
Who is it?
- You need to catch the evil spirit.
- Who is it?
Will Kwang Soo get the penalty
if we don't catch the evil spirit?
- Yes.
Then we won't need to do it.
Hold on.
Please make a decision.
Let me be honest.
Isn't it a bit late?
When the evil spirits removed
the blindfolds,
we heard music.
- But I heard a sound from my right.
- That's right! Who made it?
Who was to your right?
- I didn't hear anything.
- Didn't you sit over there?
- Did you sit here?
- No, no.
Sae Rok, Ji Hyo...
- Me.
- Jong Kook, Ji Hyo...
I don't think it's Sae Rok.
- I heard a sound.
- What sound?
- Okay.
- Jong Kook sat there.
I heard the ping of a rubber band.
That was me.
I kept doing this
since the blindfold wasn't in place.
I kept doing this.
The rubber band could be a big hint.
- I heard a sound.
- Seriously.
(Jae Suk becomes lively again.)
- Look at Jae Suk.
- I am serious.
- Jae Suk suddenly became lively.
- Look at Jae Suk.
He wants to hold on
to the smallest suspicion.
"That's right. That's it."
(He deduces without any reasons.)
He is in a hurry.
Seriously. Jae Suk is so funny.
- Jae Suk.
- Everyone.
What Kwang Soo said is a big hint.
- I heard a sound.
- The rubber band.
Earlier,
- I continued...
- He is coming up with excuses.
For goodness' sake.
The more you talk,
the more pitiful you seem.
Jae Suk,
this is what everyone wants.
That's right.
- This is what everyone wants.
- That's right.
- Kwang Soo is our plan B.
- Premier Yu.
I am not an evil spirit.
- Maybe he isn't one.
- I am really not an evil spirit.
Maybe he isn't one.
- At this point...
- Maybe he isn't one.
I think it's Jong Kook.
But I can't be sure.
- Then I will go up the stand.
- We can't be sure.
Do you want me to go up?
If you want me to go up,
I will do it.
If Jae Suk is an evil spirit,
he will get the penalty, right?
He is scary.
If I am not an evil spirit,
you will get the penalty, right?
I will go up.
(I will go up.)
- It's up to the king.
- I will go up.
- Come on.
I am serious.
- I will go up.
- No, no.
- Jae Suk is happy.
- I am serious.
No, no. Jong Kook.
Jae Suk is happy.
- Why are you smiling?
- It's Jae Suk!
Why is Jae Suk happy?
He is happy.
- Why are you smiling?
- It's Jae Suk!
- Jong Kook, I am sorry.
- I want him to get the penalty.
I am sorry.
- You were suspicious of me.
- I am sorry.
You aren't an evil spirit.
- You aren't an evil spirit.
- I will go up.
Sit down, evil spirit!
He couldn't hide his smile.
As soon as he turned around,
he showed a smile.
He smiled as he walked away.
He smiled.
My goodness.
- Let's go.
- Let's put Jae Suk on trial.
Okay. I agree.
- No.
- I put Premier Yoo on trial.
I can't believe Dong Yoon.
(Did he get caught up
in Dong Yoon's scheme?)
Jae Suk is so funny.
I will tell you after this.
Dong Yoon saw someone.
If Jae Suk is an evil spirit,
Team Evil Spirits will lose.
If he isn't an evil spirit,
someone else would be one.
You are frustrated
because of Dong Yoon, right?
- All right.
- It has to be Jae Suk.
It would be strange if he isn't.
Jae Suk...
- is...
- No way.
Jae Suk...
Let's see.
No way.
- Is...
- An evil spirit.
(Everyone is curious about
his identity.)
Not an evil spirit.
(He is not an evil spirit.)
(Jae Suk is a human,
not an evil spirit.)
You should have objected more.
(Dong Yoon won.)
- Why did you smile?
- Yes!
You should have objected more.
I objected as much as I could.
(Everyone is shocked.)
- Why did you smile?
- I...
Oh, no.
He really wasn't one.
Does that mean
Dong Yoon twisted it twice?
The evil spirits won.
(The evil spirits won.)
The one who succeeded in doing...
as many missions as Dong Yoon...
I am so curious.
- The second evil spirit is...
- Who is it?
(The second evil spirit's identity)
(The perfect execution
of the hidden missions...)
(and even more perfect acting)
Congratulations,
Sae Rok.
(Sae Rok was an evil spirit.)
What?
I said that two guests could be
the evil spirits.
Two guests.
(Two guests were the evil spirits.)
(Sae Rok, the second evil spirit
was daring and secretive.)
(A few days ago,)
(Sae Rok found a suspicious pot.)
What is this? A pot?
(She opens it naturally
as if she was told to do it.)
I finally got a body.
Shall I party now?
(Thus, Sae Rok was reborn
as an evil spirit.)
Today, we will have the Records
of the Running Dynasty Race.
You are the evil spirits
that are hiding among people.
Okay.
Evil spirits.
(Hidden mission 1,
Make 3 hearts in the car)
(She made hearts
even during a conversation.)
(Then the 1st trial took place.)
(Kwang Soo was suspicious
of Sae Rok and Dong Yoon.)
(Is it Sae Rok?)
(They kept a distance
and shook off people's suspicions.)
(Exchanging a signal)
Dong Yoon.
(They met up throughout
the missions.)
I will touch the red
and you will touch the green.
Come in a bit later.
Go to the restroom.
(Touching together)
(Touching)
(She remained confident
and avoided suspicion.)
The last mission is
holding hands for a minute...
while you are on the same floor
as another member.
(The last mission was hard.)
Hold other people's hands.
Link arms with them.
Do something, okay?
Okay. I will do it.
Do it right.
(As Sae Rok instructed,
Dong Yoon held people's hands.)
Oh, you're just
doing the mission plainly?
(He carried out a hidden mission
with Sae Rok in plain sight.)
(Holding hands)
(Although Sae Rok shouted,
she held his hand tighter.)
(We did it.)
Come here.
(They held hands
for over 3 minutes.)
Let's go, Dong Yoon!
(Sae Rok and Dong Yoon had
a perfect victory.)
Yes!
(The two guest evil spirits had
a perfect victory.)
(Their teammates are shocked.)
I was totally fooled.
The guests.
Since you always expected to see
1 member and 1 guest,
we gave the roles
to two guests this time.
They made us suspect each other.
I suspected Ji Hyo
until the very end.
I thought there would be
a Running Man member.
- Seriously.
- I was suspicious.
- Dong Yoon.
- Yes?
Why did you protect Jae Suk?
Was it a strategy?
- It was a strategy.
- Of course it was.
I can't believe him.
- It was a strategy?
- He did well.
I kept laughing and exchanging looks
with Dong Yoon.
- Really?
- Did you exchange looks?
I had no idea.
I got goosebumps at the end.
It was a strategy.
Dong Yoon didn't look
in this direction.
- He kept looking this way.
- Jae Suk.
- Sit down.
Stop pretending to be sharp
and sit down.
You should have said that earlier.
You didn't trust my words!
- I am sorry.
- It was so hard today.
Every time I said something,
he went...
(Sung Hoon's scorn
was more hurtful than suspicions.)
It was the most annoying.
Every time I said something,
he went...
(The look in Sung Hoon's eyes
hurt Premier Yu's pride.)
I couldn't believe it.
I thought it was obvious.
The prize of the day
comes from the West.
Western fruits
and a Western snack, macarons.
A Western snack.
The prize will go
to the two of them.
(They will have a taste
of the West.)
And the penalty for today
is flogging.
It's not like you're dying.
Se Chan, hit him hard.
- It won't kill you anyway.
- Make it hard.
It's just loud. That doesn't hurt.
It won't kill you.
- I'll begin.
- Oh, no.
This is for fun.
- It doesn't hurt, does it?
- It doesn't.
- There you go.
- It won't hurt.
(Thudding)
(The king's power)
That was amazing.
It sounded great.
Say, "I'm the king."
Well done. That was good.
- It felt great.
- That was great.
Good. Okay.
Good work today.
- Good work.
(We hope "Joseon Exorcist"
will be successful.)
This is the only variety show
that has...
two Grand Award winners.
I'm so proud.
(Yoo Jae Suk or Kim Jong Kook)
(Pick a captain you want.)
(They feel uncomfortable already.)
(They sign the oath that says
they will never get upset.)
(Will they be able to spend
the day without getting upset?)
(They show the Pumbaa dance
to liven up the mood.)
(That's when...)
(the Grand Award winner
starts acting high-handedly.)
(The members can't take it anymore
and run away from the captains.)
(They even ran away to a mud flat.)
(The Grand Award winners are
coming to find them.)
(It will snap, you fool.)
(Why are they all in that place?)
(Who will keep their promise and
upgrade the dignity of the award?)
(Yoo Jae Suk versus Kim Jong Kook,
Dignity of the Grand Award)