There's a joyous occasion in Running Village.
(Last week, in Running Village...)
(It was the birthday party of the elder of the village, Ji Suk Jin.)
- Gosh, that startled me. - It's the birthday party...
of the elder of the village, Ji Suk Jin.
(Happy birthday, Mr. Ji.)
(Ji Suk Jin, born in February, the oldest in Running Village)
Suk Jin.
Stay healthy.
(Stay healthy, Mr. Ji.)
You're good. So Min is good.
(The residents are excited about Mr. Ji's birthday party.)
Presents are a must at a birthday party.
(Presents are a must at a birthday party.)
It's cool indeed.
(It's cool indeed.)
It's covered. It isn't cool.
(It's covered. It isn't cool.)
- Gateball. - This is driving me crazy.
(Jae Suk got him a gate ball set.)
Make sure you keep a picture diary every day.
(Bravo to your shining variety life.)
Father. Make sure you keep a picture diary every day.
(We love the rest of your life.)
Bravo my life, my days
(Long life, health, blessing)
If this makes you happy... Everybody is happy.
(They had some good time together celebrating his birthday.)
Long life, health, and blessing.
(When the mood is heated up,)
The residents of Running Village congratulated Suk Jin today.
(Running Village head's letter arrives.)
The village head...
sent a present to Suk Jin, the oldest resident,
(A gift wishing Mr. Ji's good health and long life)
to wish him a long and healthy life.
- This is the real present. - Seriously.
Why wish for a long and healthy life when I am in my 50s?
Is it a letter?
(There's a letter in the gift box.)
It's a letter.
"Dear Mr. Ji Suk Jin."
"Happy birthday to Mr. Ji Suk Jin, the oldest resident of the village."
"Were you surprised by the empty box?"
I haven't checked the box yet.
"For your birthday, I prepared a surprise event."
"At a place in the village that is related to 'House',"
- "I hid the gold I prepared." - Gold?
"I hope you will find it well."
(The village head hid gold in the village that's related to house.)
"I think it'd be hard for you to find it by yourself,"
"so I'm giving you..."
"an important hint."
(Getting clues)
He just took it.
"And you can pick two members who are clever..."
(What's the clue that's revealed only to Mr. Ji?)
"and decode the clues I'm giving you with them..."
"to find the gold."
"The other five members will..."
"look for the gold individually."
Individually?
(Residents who aren't a member of Team Suk Jin...)
(can also look for gold individually.)
"If your team finds the gold first,"
"you can share it with your members."
"The other residents will find hidden hints."
"The resident who touches the box that has gold in it..."
- "will have the gold to oneself." - That sounds fun.
(If a resident who isn't a member of Team Suk Jin...)
"Those who fail to find my gift will get a penalty."
(finds gold, that person can have gold to him or herself.)
"If your team finds the gold,"
(If Team Suk Jin finds it, 2 people Suk Jin picks get a penalty.)
"you will get to pick two people to get a penalty."
"If one of the residents finds it,"
(If another resident finds it,)
"the winner will pick two people from your team to get a penalty."
(2 people the winner picks get a penalty.)
"Good luck, everyone."
(Find the hidden gold.)
- So it's like 5 to 3. - Right.
(Team Suk Jin with 3 members)
That sounds good.
Like the letter says, you will have a race where you look for gold.
It's called It's Time to Find the Gold Race.
(Find the gold that is Mr. Ji's birthday gift.)
(It's Time to Find the Gold Race)
I see.
Suk Jin, we'd like you to pick two clever members...
(Suk Jin can pick 2 smart people as his members.)
whom you want to be a team with.
We have many members who are good at petty tricks.
(They're all experts of petty tricks.)
- There are a lot. - That's right.
- Suk Jin is... - Haha is good at this.
Suk Jin has gotten penalties for the past six weeks.
(Suk Jin must overcome the disgrace...)
(of having a penalty for 6 weeks in a row.)
- That's right. - He needs to end it.
He should break the jinx today.
He's not so lucky.
(Members with petty tricks are...)
Who'd be good at tricks?
- So Min is good. - What about Kwang Soo?
So Min won't even look at him.
So Min, you should look at Suk Jin.
(They avoid his eyes to find gold alone.)
- Why would you avoid him? - Two members.
I've made up my mind.
(He picks two members after much consideration.)
Kim Jong Kook and Lee Kwang Soo.
- Darn it. - Okay.
- Kim Jong Kook and Lee Kwang Soo. - Darn it.
(They are recruited to Suk Jin's team against their will.)
Hey. What was that?
(They complain as they're forced to join unlucky Team Suk Jin.)
- No, that's not what I meant. - Seriously.
You don't have to do this. I don't want you anymore.
- Today is a good day. - Hey.
(Denying the reality)
Hey, Kwang Soo. Hey.
(His lips are pouting big time.)
- Try to smile. - Hey.
Today is a good day.
- What are you doing? - He didn't answer.
(As the members don't look happy,)
Hey, I don't want you on my team.
(Mr. Ji's about to sulk.)
I don't need you either.
- I'm really... - Yes!
(Acting excited forcibly)
I need to break the jinx of six penalties, Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
Hang on.
Aren't the three of you the ones who wrote the letter of apology?
- That's right. - They did.
(3 people of Running High met again.)
You three wrote the letter of apology.
And you flew a kite with me.
(Refer to Episode 542, Refer to Episode 539)
That's right.
Why are we doing this on such a good day?
(It turns out they're penalty mates.)
- He's right about that. - Okay.
I often meet them at the ending.
(They met often for the ending.)
Exactly.
So your team is decided.
(Team Mr. Ji forms wishing to avoid the penalty.)
Before we start the mission,
we will play the first game for hints.
(The first clue before the mission)
Like I said,
(There are clues on gold throughout the village.)
there are hints hidden in the village.
Unlike how we normally do things, in this round,
you will go to a random place in this village...
(8 people will stand in a place where they think gold is...)
where you think the gold is hidden...
(with a tracking device.)
carrying your tracking device with you.
Once you are done choosing your place,
(Once they are done choosing their place,)
the device of the member who's closest to the gold will go off.
(the device of the member who's closest to gold will go off.)
And for the next 15 minutes,
(Based on that information,)
you will look for the gold or hints.
(they'll search for gold or clue for the next 15 minutes.)
We even have tracking devices.
(The one who stays closest to gold...)
(will find out the approximate location of the gold.)
But even if your device doesn't go off,
(But even if the device doesn't go off,)
(they can still find the clues about the location of the gold.)
you can still find hints about the location of the gold.
So you should try to look for the hints.
- We should find the hints first. - Now, I want you...
(They'll set off to a place where they think gold is hidden.)
to move to places where you think the gold is hidden.
- Okay. - Let's go.
A place where I think the gold is hidden?
Hang on. Where should I go?
(The residents have to guess the location of the gold.)
There are many houses.
So...
I should go to a place where I think the gold is hidden.
(Only the device of 1 person who's closest to gold will go off.)
- Right. - Any place in the village.
In this whole village?
(There's gold somewhere in Running Village.)
The whole place?
We have hints.
- Right. We have hints. - We can see the hints first.
(Mr. Ji received a clue from the village head.)
Let's see the hints and move separately.
(Team Suk Jin will scatter after sharing the clue.)
We can go to places that are more likely to have the gold.
We should think the five of us...
(It's an individual play for the rest of the residents.)
- are on the same boat. - Okay.
- All right, Jae Suk. - Us?
- We should scatter away. - Okay.
(They agree to scatter away and find the gold separately.)
2 will go up, and 3 will go down.
(Whose device will go off?)
We should scatter in all directions.
It says Haha's House.
(Haha's House near the slope?)
I guess they are all someone's house.
What's that?
It says House of Dolls.
(Haha and Se Chan found the House of Dolls near the parking lot.)
I'll go to House of Dolls.
- Did you feel that too? - I felt it.
(They smell something fishy approach it.)
Will you go that way? I'll stay here.
Take a look at it. I'll get in...
Will you get in the car?
(The House of Dolls)
What's all this?
(What's the house full of stuffed dolls for?)
There's a giraffe.
Giraffe.
(Suk Jin and his team check the hint first.)
Let's check the hint first.
"All the houses aren't the same."
(This is an important hint only for you.)
(Don't share it with other residents.)
(Hint: All the houses aren't the same.)
"All the houses aren't the same."
Suk Jin, there's House of Sports.
There are many houses.
(There's House of Sports right behind them.)
(The House of Sports)
(But in other buildings in the Running Village...)
(The House of Deep Sleep)
(There are many houses...)
(with different themes.)
(The House of Cooking)
(There are many mysterious houses in Running Village.)
(There are also the houses of the 8 residents in the village.)
(So Min's House, Ji Hyo's House, Jong Kook's House)
(Hyeong Gu's House, Jae Suk's House, Suk Jin's House)
(Se Chan's House, Kwang Soo's house, Haha's House)
"All the houses aren't the same."
(Running Village is filled with various houses.)
Suk Jin, there's House of Sports.
(But if all houses aren't the same...)
There are many houses.
I bet the gold isn't in one of these houses.
(Then the gold is...)
- There are real houses. - Like a doghouse.
- A doghouse. - Right.
There is a doghouse in the middle.
Will you stay in the doghouse then?
I'm just asking.
(His thoughtless teammate tries to...)
That's what the hint says.
(put him in a doghouse on his birthday.)
Why would I go into a doghouse?
There's a doghouse, a birdhouse,
(Jong Kook goes for a doghouse or a birdhouse.)
and other things.
- It should be something like that. - Things that say house.
"All the houses aren't the same."
(Did the three of them solve the hint right?)
- Should we go into some house? - What would it be?
Let's go look for the gold. We're a team now.
(They move to places where they think there might be gold.)
- Okay. - Okay? Good luck.
- I'm serious about this. - Let's do this seriously.
House of Books?
(So Min and Jae Suk visit the House of Books.)
Are we on the same team?
Sure. We're a team.
(They should find a place where the gold is hidden in.)
(Scanning)
I don't think it's here.
(He doesn't think the gold is in a cute place like that.)
I'll stay here.
(Whispering)
(Jae Suk quickly moves to another house.)
I don't think this is it.
The house Jae Suk abandons...
is more likely to be the correct answer.
I pick this place. I'll stay here.
(Se Chan picks an open space near the three-way intersection.)
I pick this place.
(He's located at the very center.)
I'll stay in the center.
I should've put on warmer clothes.
(Mr. Ji grumbles and walks by with two cameras on him.)
Suk Jin, you're the lead today. You have two cameras.
That's not true.
(Being treated like the star after a while,)
- All members are the leads. - This is so cool.
(he says things to look tough.)
I'll give you the gold if I find it.
Okay.
(Who will find the gold that's a birthday gift for Suk Jin?)
We did many important things around here.
(Kwang Soo tries to find out the gold based on his experience.)
I personally think it's around here.
Because we did a lot of things here before.
(So Min, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan)
(Kwang Soo chooses a large lawn beneath the uphill road.)
- Is this your choice? - Yes.
If I'm close to the gold, will you tell me that?
Your tracking device will go off.
The one who's closest to the gold.
(This is it.)
(Thumbs-up)
- Is this product placement? - No.
(He just gave a thumbs-up out of habit.)
Is this product placement?
I could put this on my dog's collar and let it out, right?
(I think it's product placement!)
(What else should I say?)
(Ji Hyo even dances with the device to cover the production cost.)
(Meanwhile, in the 3-story villa...)
It might be one of these two.
Suk Jin, it's Ji Hyo's house.
Ji Hyo won a lot of gold.
Ji Hyo won a lot of games and won gold.
(The two think it's Ji Hyo's house as she won a lot of gold.)
So I bet it might be in Ji Hyo's house.
All the houses aren't the same.
(Jae Suk is upstairs in the same building.)
Hang on. Hyeong Gu's House?
(Hyeong Gu's House)
Is there Hyeong Gu's House?
I should stand here. This is strange.
(He chooses to stay in front of the suspicious Hyeong Gu's House.)
Hyeong Gu's House doesn't sound right.
Ji Hyo's House.
(Jong Kook visits Ji Hyo's house as he said earlier.)
(Ji Hyo's House)
Am I supposed to make a guess with what I see?
There's nothing special in here.
(Right at that moment...)
(The frame of the family motto is in the living room.)
"When it's big, have a close look."
(When it's big, have a close look.)
"When it's big, have a close look?"
(Does the family motto of Ji Hyo's house mean something?)
I'll stay here.
(He decides to stay in front of Ji Hyo's House.)
- Have you made up your mind? - Yes. I pick Ji Hyo's house.
- I've made up my mind. - Is that your choice?
(Suk Jin: 1st floor, Jong Kook: 2nd floor, Jae Suk: 3rd floor)
- Yes. - Okay.
I think it's here.
(Haha picks the House of Dolls that he found at the beginning.)
- Have you made your choice? - Yes. I have a feeling.
(Jong Kook, Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Ji Hyo,)
The thing you pick first is mostly correct.
(Haha, Se Chan, Kwang Soo, and So Min)
The device of the person closest to the gold will go off.
- My gosh. - We're at an advantage.
(Whose device will go off?)
If Jong Kook's device or Suk Jin's goes off...
(Beeping)
(The person who's standing closest to gold is...)
(Yang Se Chan.)
(There's the gold near the three-way intersection.)
Am I the only one who can hear that?
(He's caught by Haha.)
What are you looking at, you old man?
- Haha, my device went off. - I know.
(Se Chan at the center is the closest to the gold.)
I told you. It's in the center.
I won't tell anyone.
(They promise that they won't tell anyone else.)
Haha.
(There's the gold somewhere near Se Chan.)
It must be somewhere near here.
This is amazing. It was Se Chan.
(Haha got a great piece of information by chance.)
Haha.
It must be somewhere near here.
(Where's the gold then?)
The device of the person closest to the gold just went off.
Mine didn't go off.
(The rest of the residents have no idea of the location of the gold.)
That means it's not in here.
I hope it was Suk Jin or Jong Kook.
(My team)
- You can continue. - Find the gold?
(They can look for the clues for 15 minutes.)
Yes. You can look for it now.
I should go ask them.
Did your device ring?
- Did yours go off? - I think it was Suk Jin's.
(Kwang Soo walks up without knowing Se Chan's device beeped.)
What?
Suk Jin's device went off, so he's going around alone.
(False information)
He's acting like the protagonist.
(Trying to secure his information by using Mr. Ji)
Are we supposed to look for the gold now?
(Pretending ignorance)
How would we find it when we don't know where it went off?
(They try desperately to pretend they don't know.)
Aren't you going to tell us where the device went off?
We're not telling you.
We can't find it when we don't know where the device went off.
(Se Chan and Haha scatter away keeping the secret to themselves.)
I should smell the gold.
The smell of gold.
(Se Chan)
Can I go in here?
(Se Chan hovers around the place...)
Hang on. Where was I earlier?
(looking for gold.)
It must be somewhere here.
There's a strange doll in here.
(Jae Suk is searching the residents' houses.)
(So Min's House)
"When up high, check down below?"
(There's a family motto in So Min's House too.)
"When up high, check down below."
(Jae Suk boggles at the phrase.)
What's that?
(He walks down the stairs to check down below.)
Does that mean it's not in a high place?
(Jong Kook's House)
"I'm always watching you?"
(There's another motto.)
Look at that.
What?
(Kwang Soo spots the same frame in Jong Kook's House.)
So this is the clue.
(Passing by)
(He leaves Kwang Soo right away as he's in a different team.)
This is the clue.
(He steals Kwang Soo's shoes on his way out.)
(He walks away with Kwang Soo's shoes smiling.)
(Then Kwang Soo tries to leave.)
Those are my shoes.
(He steals the cameraman's shoes.)
No.
(The cameraman follows the shoe in his stocking feet.)
(They steal each other's shoes in relays.)
- Oh no. - What?
Did you find something?
(Catching the shoe thief)
- Did you find anything? - Were these your shoes, Yoon Sang?
(Yoon Sang lost his shoes to Kwang Soo.)
Yoon Sang, I'm sorry.
(He filmed in his bare feet because of the thieves.)
These are Yoon Sang's.
I'm wearing Yoon Sang's shoes.
- I'm sorry. - Hey.
(They took others' shoes without hesitation.)
I had no choice.
(He gets his shoes back.)
Jong Kook, there's a clue.
"When it's big, have a close look."
- That's the clue. - Hey.
(Sharing the motto they found)
There's a clue in my house too.
Each house has...
(Jong Kook also found the motto while exercising.)
Each room has a clue.
Each room has a clue on the wall.
"I'm always watching you."
(Ji Hyo's House, So Min's House, Jong Kook's House)
We should put them together.
(They might get something if they put the three together.)
I will go to my house.
It's around here, so I guess it's in the house.
(Se Chan and Haha make a guess based on Se Chan's location.)
It might be in the building.
(Right next to where Se Chan was standing,)
There are Jae Suk's House...
(there are Suk Jin's and Jae Suk's Houses.)
and Suk Jin's House. But the problem is...
Jae Suk's House has a lot of R stickers in it.
(The two houses have a living room.)
- Really? - Yes.
Haha, the clue is...
(While they only take shots in the dark...)
Someone in here... Gosh.
- Haha. - What?
- Did you find it? - Haha.
(Se Chan found something.)
- There's something. - It's just paper.
Well done.
Hang on.
(What's in the envelope that Se Chan found?)
Take a look at it.
What is this?
I remember what this is.
(A picture in the envelope)
Isn't this the thing about the Yoo Family?
We played yutnori here.
- And the room on the right is... - That's the place.
(It's a photo from the last time they filmed in this place.)
Suk Jin's room.
I know that.
It's Suk Jin's room. And the one on the left is...
- What? - Why?
- It was the same back then. - Jae Suk's House?
(On the left and right of the living room in the picture,)
(there are Suk Jin's House and Jae Suk's House.)
They are steaming songpyeon.
They're making songpyeon.
It says R.
(And there are four people in the picture.)
(One of them is...)
(Yoo Jae Suk.)
Jae Suk, where... Why...
Nothing.
What's with that mischievous smile?
- I'm just looking around. - What are you doing?
- What are you up to now? - I'm just looking around.
What's with that mischievous smile?
(Does he have a secret that others don't know?)
(The 1st search is over.)
Time's up.
- Please gather around. - Okay.
(After the first search...)
(The place for the first mission has toy hammers in line.)
(What's the mission?)
This is where I got pregnant.
- What? - I was pregnant here.
(Why So Min suddenly talks about being pregnant?)
That's right.
You should get over the skit.
You completely fell for a woman.
(Se Chan and So Min were a newly married couple...)
- I fell for a woman? - Hey.
(on last Chuseok in episode 523.)
What's going on?
(So Min was absorbed in the skit and went too far.)
(Her joke embarrassed even her husband.)
Hey. Stop that.
Do you have an upset stomach?
(Do you...)
- Don't do anything strange. - No. Wait...
(That's how So Min came up with the best meme.)
This is where you found out you were pregnant.
(Baby Pouty Mouth might have been born here.)
- Right. I was retching. - That's right.
Happy birthday, Suk Jin.
(By the way...)
You keep saying that. That's enough.
(Irritated out of the blue)
(Suk Jin is tired of answering all the congratulations.)
Why are you angry? Can't you be happy?
I'm not angry.
Long life, health, and blessing!
- We should do this when we can. - That's enough.
(Still...)
We should do this when we can.
(Something occurs to So Min.)
My dad came to my room yesterday.
I was wrapping the bamboo wife for him, and Dad asked what it was.
(So Min was packing the bamboo wife for Mr. Ji.)
So I said it was a birthday gift for Suk Jin.
(So Min's father saw it.)
Then he asked how old Suk Jin is, so I said...
- he was born in 1966. - That's correct.
I also said that he's quite old now, and my dad said,
"Hey, he's still so young."
(Suk Jin is still very young compared to So Min's father.)
- My dad said... - It's understandable.
- You're right. - Her father must feel that way.
(One's life begins at 56 years of age.)
"He's still so young."
That's what seniors always say.
- Say hello to your father, So Min. - "He's still so young."
When elderly people like him see a man who was born in 1966,
(Born in 1966 in the era when the life expectancy is 100...)
- He's like a baby to them. - he looks so young.
- He's in the prime of his life. - He's the youngest in such a group.
(Baby Big Nose still has a long way to go.)
- Today, you have two missions. - Okay.
To celebrate Suk Jin's birthday, we prepared...
missions that would be easy for Suk Jin.
(Customized missions for Big Nose)
You must be at an advantage.
I guess we'll play some games I can win.
(Pleased)
Then they're probably not physically hard...
(It's obvious.)
- if it's advantageous for him. - We don't have to be strong to win.
(The missions won't require any physical strengths.)
We rarely see toy hammer games on TV shows these days.
- They're all simple, easy games. - Simple and easy?
- Simple and easy? - The games we've done before?
Did you really have to put it like that?
You could've used some other words like "cute".
You mean some old games? Good. Let's do this!
(They're all petty missions customized for Big Nose.)
All right. Let's do this.
The first mission is...
the upgraded version of Catching Rats,
the game played in the show that Suk Jin hosted...
(They are nostalgic missions he hosted during his prime days.)
- during his best days. - I know that game.
(It's an upgrade version of Catching Rats.)
Catch rats, catch rats
(First Mission: Daring Rats)
- It's Daring Rats. - I remember that game.
- Suk Jin will do it well. - Catch rats, catch rats
(If that's the case...)
- Squeak, squeak, squeak - I don't...
(He doesn't remember.)
- remember the rules clearly. - He has an advantage.
- So Youn, are you ready? - Yes.
(This is the young Big Nose during his best days.)
- Yes, I'm ready. - Shall we begin now?
Okay.
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
(After the song, the 1st player says the number of the rats to catch.)
- How many rats? - How many rats?
Three rats!
(Players can say either "Caught it" or "Missed it".)
- Caught it. - Missed it.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Hooray! - Hooray!
(When all the rats are caught, everyone says, "Hooray".)
- Two rats! - Caught it.
- Missed it. - Missed it.
Caught it. Oh, gosh.
(You're out when you do the wrong motion or miss the timing.)
- Catch rats, catch rats - How many rats?
(Nostalgic)
For example, you say, "Three rats."
(For example, if it's "three rats"...)
- "Caught it." - "Caught it" or "Missed it".
After three people saying "Caught it", we all say...
- "Meow"? - "Hooray."
- Oh, right. - Hey, you're still young.
- What's wrong with you? - I mean, he hosted the show.
(He doesn't remember the rules of the game he hosted.)
- There you go. - Okay.
- Back then, he was the MC, - Actually, I...
(Testimony of Jae Suk, his colleague at the time)
but he only followed the staff's decisions.
(Ji Parrot)
- I bet he didn't care. - I see.
(He was more loyal to following the staff's orders.)
- He was like a parrot. - He was more like an avatar.
- He was an avatar. - He didn't participate in it.
(He admits it.)
- That's true. I didn't. - The directors were Shin Won Ho...
(The staff members were: Director Shin Won Ho,)
- Oh, right. - And Na Yeong Seok.
(Director Na Yeong Seok,)
- That's right. - What?
- He must've been close to them. - Won Ho and Yeong Seok.
- You worked with Na Yeong Seok? - And the writer was Lee Woo Jung.
(and the writer was Lee Woo Jung.)
(What a fantastic line-up of staff.)
- They're very successful now. - Indeed.
All the people who worked with him became so famous, but he...
- If you think about it... - Hey!
(He's the only one who didn't get famous.)
- Why? - Yeong Seok,
Won Ho, and Woo Jung...
tend to keep working with the same people.
- They all have that tendency. - That's right.
(Big Nose is the only person who's not in that group.)
- They always do that. - Then why...
And the people who worked with them became top stars.
- It's true. - Really?
(Bitter)
Director Shin hired the same actors for his new dramas.
- They all do that. - It's like a shortcut to success.
Suk Jin, what happened? Did you fight with them?
I'm not the type who argues with others.
(Pacifist)
- Do you think I'm that type? - He's right. He's an individualist.
(He failed to make the friendship last long.)
- He's an individualist. - I don't argue with others.
We talk on the phone from a distance and root for each other.
(Nowadays...)
(A sideway tackle)
Who would talk on the phone when they're close by?
(Jae Suk criticizes harshly on Suk Jin's birthday.)
- That's why we use a phone. - Come on, Jae Suk.
Why?
- Today is Suk Jin's birthday. - He's still so young.
(Please calm down.)
- It's his birthday. - He's in the prime of his life.
(He's only strict on Big Nose.)
You see, I'm grateful...
- that all three of them are... - Yes.
doing so well, and I don't have to worry about them.
I always cheer for you, guys!
Who worries about whom?
- Won Ho, Yeong Seok, and Woo Jung! - Right.
- You guys are the best. - Won Ho, Yeong Seok,
(Suk Jin is doing well.)
- and Woo Jung, - Yes.
you have nothing to worry about Suk Jin.
- He's taking good care of himself. - I'm doing fine.
(I'm fine. Let's talk soon again from a distance.)
- Don't worry about me. - Of course.
We added a new rule to this game.
(There's a new rule added to the current rule.)
You can say, "Caught it", "Missed it", or "It ran".
- What's that? - "It ran"?
When a player says, "It ran",
(When a player says, "It ran",)
(one of the rats that were caught will be excluded from the count.)
one of the rats that were caught will be excluded from the count.
That is, there will be one less rat that you caught.
Oh, I see. We can take one out too?
(In the upgraded version, they can take a rat out too.)
- That sounds so difficult. - So we have to catch one more.
If you do the wrong motion,
(Lose a point when: the wrong motion, miss the timing,)
- miss the timing, - We do the motion too?
or count the rats incorrectly, you're out and lose one point.
(or count the rats incorrectly.)
Gosh, seriously.
Oh, that's so cute. It's a rat.
(There are hairbands and the nostalgic song.)
- There's a song too. - They play the song too.
I haven't heard this song in a long time.
- It's an old song. - Thank you.
(They all wear the hairbands.)
After that, we'll hear, "How many rats?"
What do we do with this toy hammer?
- You hit others with it. - When someone makes a mistake.
Kwang Soo, what else could we do with a toy hammer?
- Pardon me? - Use your head.
- Would we crack walnuts with it? - Jae Suk.
(Why are we suddenly talking about walnuts?)
I never said anything about walnuts.
- Don't waste my time like that. - Hey!
- He's just nervous. - He's right.
He's doing his warm-ups.
(He picks on Kwang Soo out of fear of games.)
Gosh, seriously.
Play the music.
(Rat Song starts.)
(From Dirty Mustache Rat...)
I haven't done this in a while.
(To So Min Rat who looks perfect with the headband.)
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
- How many rats? - How many rats?
- Six rats! - Caught it.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- It ran. - Caught it.
- Hooray! - Hooray!
- No. That's not right. Is it? - No.
- He said... - You're all out.
(It's chaos from the beginning.)
- We didn't catch them all. - We were wrong.
We had one more rat to catch.
Oh, right. She said, "It ran."
- Everyone was looking around... - I think we did correctly.
and followed him as soon as he said, "Hooray".
(Once a person says, "Hooray," others follow.)
None of us was sure.
Five.
- We had one more rat to catch. - Exactly.
But he was the first one to say "Hooray".
- No. - You're out.
(What? Did I?)
It wasn't me. Suk Jin said it first.
- Listen to me. - No, no.
(The teamwork breaks down as if they are after each other.)
- The two of them caught rats. - I was mistaken.
- The two of them caught rats. - Forget it!
- Listen. Hey! - We can't even play the normal one.
- Let's try one more time. - I can't play the original game.
(It was a trial round to help them better understand the game.)
He was the one who should be out.
- Let's call it a practice. - Good.
Let's focus, everyone.
(The real game starts.)
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
(Cutting off)
- How many rats? - How many rats?
Four rats!
- Caught it. - It ran.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Caught it. Hooray! - Hooray!
No, we caught only three rats.
- Caught it. - It ran.
(After shouting, "It ran",)
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Hooray! - Hooray!
(he said "Hooray" before anyone else said it.)
We caught only three rats. I didn't say "Hooray".
- We caught 3, right? - We needed 1 more rat.
- We had to catch one more. - What's wrong with you?
- Why? - My gosh.
(Acting confident)
- I raised my arms because of you. - Take him out. It's not fun.
I raised my arms because of you.
(He really needs a vaccine for his fear of games.)
- Because of me? - Yes.
You're so lousy at games!
- He ruined the strawberry game too. - Okay. Got it.
(The destroyer of games)
- We had one more to go. - Okay.
Jae Suk, you lost one point.
- Why? Why? - Okay.
You said "Hooray".
- You looked so confident. - You were the only one.
(Everyone fell for it because he was so confident.)
But they said it too.
I did it because of you.
Raise your hand if you don't understand the rules.
- Jae Suk, raise your hand. - No. I know the rules.
These two caught rats, right?
Everyone, let's just not say "It ran" for the time being.
(Let's just...)
- We can just not say it. - That's right.
(They voluntarily refuse "It ran" from their options.)
- Don't say it. - Right.
- Let's stay safe. - Don't say it.
(They hastily agree to change the rules to save face.)
- Let's stay safe. - It's a promise.
- Okay. Good. - Also, about the number of rats,
- choose a small number like one. - Don't say "It ran".
- Just don't say it. - Until we get used to this game.
("It ran" is not an option until they get used to the game.)
- Never say "It ran". - Let's get used to it first.
- I won't let it slide if you do. - I'll make it really easy for you.
(I'll make it easier.)
- Okay. - What number will it be?
- How many rats? - I'll say three.
(A pregame notice)
- Okay. - Keep that in mind.
(Acting bold)
- Let's begin. - 1, 2...
- Say "How many rats?" - Okay. Ready, go.
- How many rats? - How many rats?
- Three rats! - Caught it.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Hooray! - Hooray!
- Three rats! - Caught it!
- Caught it. - Missed it.
- Caught it. Hooray! - Hooray!
- Five rats. - Caught it.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Hooray! - Hooray!
- Two rats! - Caught it.
- Caught it. Hooray! - Hooray!
Caught it.
- Two rats! - Caught it.
(He was extremely nervous from the start.)
- Caught it. Hooray! - Hooray!
Caught it.
(He made a mistake because he was too nervous.)
Why? Why can't you do that?
- Why? Why? - Why? Why?
What's the problem?
Why do you always get so nervous?
Why are you lousy at everything else but hosting a show?
Don't make us play simple games! He always ruins it.
- He's so lousy at this. - I'm not good at this.
(Incurring resentment)
Why?
I'm not good at playing games like this.
You should've said the number of rats to catch.
We didn't even say "It ran".
(He can't even handle the basic game.)
He said he caught a rat.
- I'm not good at this. - He caught it.
He didn't even know when to say "Hooray", so he looked at us...
and followed us.
(Swaying his arms a bit too late)
- We should all say it at once. - He gets flustered.
Let's try to continue more rounds without stopping.
(Please.)
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
- How many rats? - How many rats?
Seven rats!
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Missed it. - It ran!
Caught it.
(Buffering)
Missed it.
- We agreed not to say "It ran". - Why did you do that?
What's wrong?
(Everyone got angry over the violation of the rule.)
Why did you say that?
Why can't I say it when the rules allow it?
- We all agreed not to say it. - But it's allowed.
(That's not fair.)
Why did you do that?
(They target him by cornering him.)
- Why would you do that? - You were told not to.
- Why would you try to stand out? - Don't do what you're told not to.
- Just don't do it. - What did I do wrong?
- What? Don't do it as we agreed. - What did I do wrong?
- We all agreed not to say it. - We all agreed.
But it's allowed to say "It ran" according to the rules.
- That's not the point. - I didn't do the wrong motion.
(Angry)
- But we all agreed on it. - When will we ever get used to it?
(If we stick this way...)
It might take us a few days to learn how to play this.
Shut your mouth.
You ruined everything. So shut it.
- I ruined everything? - Hey!
You ruined it.
(It's your fault.)
- Ji Hyo was enjoying herself. - Hey.
- Right. I'm sorry. - Kwang Soo.
(Swaying)
You start the game. Say the number of rats.
- And let's not... - Catch rats
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
You start the game. Say the number of rats.
(Suk Jin tried to be an MC after a long time.)
- And let's not... - Catch rats
(But Jae Suk cut him off.)
Catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
Suk Jin, don't talk to the players like that.
"Hey, say the number of rats."
(Big Nose's unilateral style is very old-fashioned.)
- What was that? - Just because it's his birthday.
- He speaks like an old man. - Also...
- Today is my birthday, you know. - He's so bossy.
Don't call a big number like seven.
It makes it harder to play this game.
- Too many rats... - No more than four rats.
- He's a bossy man. - Under five.
(His old-fashioned style even sets the number of rats.)
- Gosh, seriously. - Don't make it confusing.
And don't say "I couldn't catch it."
- You mean "It ran". - "It ran."
(He lost his focus a long time ago.)
- Suk Jin, come on. - Just say "Missed it".
- Don't say it either. - My gosh.
- Ready, go. - Say "How many rats?"
(The game resumes with Ji Hyo.)
- How many rats? - How many rats?
Four rats!
- Caught it. - Missed it.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Caught it. Hooray! - Hooray!
- Three rats! - Caught it.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Hooray! - Hooray!
Seven rats!
- Missed it. - Caught it.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
It ran.
- Gosh, you. - Why?
(Ji Hyo punished him.)
- You were told not to say it! - What's wrong?
(He violated the rule of no "It ran".)
I told you not to say "It ran".
(Kwang Soo who said it last time is punishing him most harshly.)
You should never say "It ran"!
(Hammering)
- I told you not to say it. - What? Why?
(The person who said it before gets punished too in this game.)
- Was it you? - Why would you hit me?
Was it you?
Why would you hit us?
It can happen, you know. A rat ran away.
- On such a happy day like this? - We all agreed not to say it.
- My rat ran away. - We all agreed.
Exactly.
Hey, we were enjoying the game without stopping.
- He's right. - But you ruined it.
- It was fun. - Don't act like a know-it-all.
- I was flustered. - Hey, don't act up.
I had no choice but to say it.
- Ji Hyo could've just moved on. - Exactly.
But she hit me right away. Gosh.
(She's ridiculous.)
(She's sensitive to the word "It ran".)
- That was funny. - Why did you say it?
- Who was out? - Ji Hyo lost one point.
(Ji Hyo loses a point.)
- Oh, good. - Let's begin.
He was the one who was hit, but she lost a point?
(He got hit for playing right.)
Ji Hyo was the one who was out.
Ji Hyo, say "It flew away" while doing this motion.
This is not fun at all.
(Angry)
You just say "Caught it".
(The old fossil hosts.)
Okay. I'll do whatever I want.
(Ji Hyo resumes the game.)
- I never said "Missed it". - Fine. I heard you.
It's easy to count.
How many rats?
(Loud)
- Two rats! - Caught it.
We should sing the song first.
(The introduction is necessary.)
(Too lazy)
We don't have to sing it every time.
But that's part of the game.
- We don't have to do it every time. - Yes, we have to.
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
(He does what he's told.)
Why won't you sing it?
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
(He reluctantly sang the song with a fake smile on his face.)
Why won't you sing it?
(He got upset right away.)
- How could I sing along? - He sang it in his own style.
Let's take a break.
(Suk Jin caught all the mice alone.)
- Why didn't you sing along? - What was that?
- What's wrong with you? - Catch
(He begins again with his face turned red.)
- Rats, catch rats - Catch rats
Squeak, squeak, squeak
(With Suk Jin's contrived introduction,)
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
(Jae Suk resumes the game.)
- How many rats? - How many rats?
- Three rats. - Caught it.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Hooray! - Hooray!
Four rats.
- Missed it. - Caught it.
- Caught it. - Missed it.
(Ji Hyo had been fully concentrated since a long time ago.)
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Caught it? - Hooray!
(Only she didn't raise her arms.)
- Hold on a second. - What was that?
- Gosh. - You were too late.
- Ji Hyo, come on. - What was that?
You sounded unsure. Say it confidently.
(The news of catch ends in question.)
- Be bold. "Caught it?" - This isn't a quiz.
- It's not a short-answer question. - It sounded like a question.
(What's so hard about it?)
- Understood. I'm sorry. - Don't make it sound like that.
(The game keeps stopping.)
- Got it. - Why would you ask a question?
- It's "Caught it" or "Missed it". - Exactly.
- It's that simple. - Ji Hyo.
Since you keep making a mistake, Suk Jin hasn't been out yet.
I won't be out.
- Let's switch seats. - Let's do that.
I played this game for years. I will never make a mistake.
(Feeling confident)
- Where should I sit? - Come over here.
- Suk Jin, sit between us. - Okay.
If I make a mistake,
I'll let Se Chan hit me in the forehead.
- Are you serious? - I'm confident.
That wouldn't be special. We all get hit in the forehead.
I meant finger flick, not the toy hammer.
(I'll get a finger flick.)
- Really? - Yes.
(Suk Jin's acting rashly.)
- Se Chan can hit really hard. - Here we go.
Instead... There must be something I get.
- "Something you get"? - You'll get to eat later.
Oh, you're right. That would work.
- And you got one year older too. - You should eat something.
(They want Suk Jin to eat something.)
- He got one year older. - Exactly. You got one year older.
That's what he got.
- Oh, I got one year older. - Yes, you did.
(Accepting)
- I didn't realize that. - You're one year older now.
- That's good enough. - Great.
(After Suk Jin gets a year older, the game resumes.)
Ready, go.
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
- How many rats? - Six rats!
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- It ran. - Caught it.
- Caught it. Hooray! - Hooray!
- Three rats. - No. You counted wrong.
(There was still one mouse left.)
- We had one more rat to catch. - That's right.
- What's wrong with you? - What's the problem?
Don't be anxious.
We were doing great. Why did you ruin it?
(Blaming)
- Gosh. - We were having fun.
(The person who ruined the rally the most)
Jae Suk, it's because you said "It ran".
- Gosh. What's the problem? - He said it like he didn't care.
(He says "It ran" then disregards.)
Why did you say it?
What's wrong? Am I not allowed to say it?
(Shameless)
Gosh. He says there's nothing wrong with it now.
Why did you say "It ran"?
(He's a hypocrite.)
He says it's okay because he did it.
Then let's say you're older than me.
(Old fossil)
- I'm sorry. - You're older than me from now on.
That's weirdly convincing.
(Running Man is the place of old fossils in Korea.)
It makes you feel like you're wrong.
- My gosh. Kwang Soo will go first? - Okay.
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
- Catch rats, catch rats - Louder, louder!
Louder!
Are we in the military?
(Following Old Fossil Yu, Battalion Chief Yoo appeared.)
- Is this a boot camp? - Be quiet.
I'm just saying you should be more excited.
(Strict)
- Right, It wasn't cheery. - You were frowning.
(They're excited that they never got hit.)
- Boost your cheery energy. - Sing it louder.
(Focus, newbie.)
- Move your shoulders up and down. - Hey, be more excited.
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
(Disciplined like a private)
- How many rats? - How many rats?
Six rats!
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Caught it. - Missed it.
- Caught it. Hooray! - Hooray!
Four rats!
- Caught it. - It ran.
- It ran. - Caught it.
(A series of "It ran")
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Caught it. Hooray! - Hooray!
Did we count correctly?
Yes, we did.
(No one was sure when they raised their hands.)
- Did we count correctly? - Yes, we did.
- We did it right. - Let's be honest.
Raise your hand if you just guessed.
- I followed my hunch. - Me too.
(Me. Same here.)
(They're ashamed of themselves.)
- I guessed. - This is unbelievable.
- Ji Hyo, let's begin. - Ji Hyo.
Five rats.
- Caught it. - Missed it.
- It ran. - Caught it.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Hooray! - Hooray!
- Three rats! - Caught it.
- It ran. - It ran...
- That doesn't work. - That'd be minus one rat.
- Caught it. - It ran.
It ran...
- That doesn't work. - That'd be minus one rat.
(He's out because there's no rat left to run away!)
All right. That was good.
(It's time for them to hit him with their toy hammers.)
Why can't anyone hit him?
- Hey! - Cheer up, Jong Kook!
(They give applause instead of hitting him.)
- Why won't you hit him? - Hit him now!
- Why won't you guys hit him? - Why did you hit him so lightly?
(Tapping lightly)
Why didn't you hit him?
Why did you hit him so lightly?
- I didn't want to mess up his hair. - What was that?
Did you guys see him hit Jong Kook?
(Scary Jong Kook's hair must not get messy.)
- Why? - He just tapped him on his head.
Let's move on already. We should continue.
- This is so funny. - Gosh, seriously.
(Tapping lightly)
Here. Are you satisfied now?
- By the way, we've improved. - Suk Jin...
Suk Jin...
tried to be as polite as he could be.
(It was a polite touch.)
He hit Jong Kook like this.
After hitting Jong Kook, he even asked if it was good enough.
- To make sure he wasn't upset. - His hair...
I didn't want to mess up his hair.
(One more light tap)
How many times did you hit me?
(Angry)
Three times.
He spoke in a cute way.
(He tries to calm him down by acting cute.)
I hit you three times. Why?
(I'll let it go since it's your birthday.)
- Let's try to keep going. It's fun. - Let's do this.
Catch rats, catch rats, squeak, squeak, squeak
(Suk Jin resumes the game.)
- How many rats? - Six rats!
- Caught it. - It ran.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Missed it. - Caught it.
- Caught it. Hooray! - Hooray!
Suk Jin is out.
- Caught it. - Caught it.
- Caught it. Hooray! - Hooray!
(He raised his hands too early.)
Suk Jin is out.
- Why did you do that? - Suk Jin.
I'm starting to get confused when it's almost over.
Hang on. Suk Jin promised to let Se Chan hit him in the forehead.
(Before)
Shut it. It's over now.
(How dare you.)
- It's over now. - But a promise is a promise.
(As Suk Jin acts shamelessly, everyone complains.)
You made a promise.
- But it's over. - You should keep your promise...
- because it's your birthday. - You promised.
- Do you want to hit me? - Consider it as a birthday noogie.
(Suk Jin)
No, I don't, but it's a birthday noogie for you.
(But he promised.)
- What do you mean? - Or apologize to the viewers...
- for making an empty promise. - Why did you even make a promise?
(To viewers)
- Earlier... - You said it yourself.
Hey.
(He revealed his forehead in the end.)
All right. My forehead is still fine. Here.
- Happy birthday, Suk Jin! - Go ahead.
My finger will hurt too since it's winter.
(Se Chan's known for his strong finger flick.)
- I know. - Exactly.
- That's true. - Right.
It hurts both ways.
(Regretting)
Why did I make this promise?
I realized it was a mistake right away. Take it easy.
(Scared)
Hit me just hard enough to make the sound.
They can increase the volume later.
- And I'll overreact. - Okay.
(The professional comedian lived his life...)
- You really are a professional. - Of course.
(without any sincerity for 56 years.)
You know what can be done in the editing process.
- Here I go. - Okay.
(The professional finger flicker begins the execution.)
- Somehow it makes me feel... - Okay.
So Min, dance for him as his daughter-in-law.
- Do we have some toilet paper? - I will...
(A performance wishing for her father-in-law's safety)
- When you hear me hit him, - Then start dancing.
- start dancing. - "Here we go!"
- Can you... - Yes?
- Can you play gugak music for me? - Of course.
(There's even background music support.)
Can you play some music too?
- On someone's phone? - What?
So Min, that's great.
- She prepared herself properly. - Yes.
(Flapping)
(His daughter-in-law's filial dance...)
That's great. So Min, way to go.
(touches him and makes him snort.)
- She's such a good daughter-in-law. - Play it as soon as I hit him.
(Touched)
- Your daughter-in-law... - She's a great dancer.
- She's... - All right.
(Her dance has elegant hand moves...)
So Min, wait over here until I hit him.
(and the beauty of moderation.)
She's amazing.
Suk Jin seems happy.
(Smiling)
- He looks happy. - He's finally smiling.
(He's so touched that his cheeks turn red.)
- He's blushing. - You see...
- His daughter-in-law is... - You're doing well.
such a great dancer.
- She drew my attention. - Yes.
(One more fan here)
Please make the pain go away.
- Through a laugh. - Make me laugh.
She's like a laughter therapist.
This is so funny.
(A laughter anesthetic has been injected.)
Your daughter-in-law learned to dance properly.
- Here I go. - All right.
(A blow loaded)
(As soon as the finger flick signal was sent,)
(So Min started performing.)
Here we go!
(The anesthetic wears off.)
Happy birthday, Suk Jin.
(Happy Birthday, Grandpa Big Nose!)
All right. Here we go.
(His sons are giving him a palanquin ride on their arms.)
- I wish you a healthy, long life! - Great!
I wish you health!
(She reflects her heart for him in the tissue.)
- I wish you health! - I wish you a healthy, long life!
He must be really happy.
- Stay healthy. That's all I want. - He must be happy.
(Father)
He must be really happy...
(Father's so happy that he can't raise his head.)
- seeing that he's smiling. - He's smiling happily.
- Happy birthday! - Thank you.
- So Min! - Cheers.
(Have a drink.)
This is amazing.
(Children are happy to see how healthy their father is.)
- Happy birthday. - Happy birthday.
(Thank you, my boys.)
All I want is for you to stay healthy.
(The eldest son practiced juggling toy hammers for this day.)
That's incredible.
He's juggling toy hammers.
(This is fun.)
Toy hammers?
That's great.
(The second son performs the fire blowing.)
(Their father got drunk by their cute performances.)
Why would he climb up on my back suddenly?
- Gosh. - Happy birthday!
(The father who just got hit...)
(and his children are all happy now.)
This is so good.
I'm happy as long as you're enjoying this.
Jong Kook, you should demonstrate some ssireum skills.
- I'll do that. - His forehead is so red.
- Suk Jin, are you okay? - It hurts so much.
(The finger flick helped him boost his energy.)
- Oh, gosh. Look at him. - Suk Jin.
- Look at his forehead. - Are you all right?
(The good son gave his father an injection to boost his energy.)
- You got one year older. - It hurts.
Suk Jin, it looks like there's a road on your forehead.
- You got one year older. - I see a road on your forehead.
(There's a road across his forehead.)
- It's okay. - His forehead is so red.
I think you should buy that land since there's a new road.
It's quite bumpy.
It's okay.
(It began with catching a rat and ended with catching Suk Jin.)
It made a loud noise.
The results are out.
(Announcing the result of the first mission)
Only the people in the top three will go out...
to use the tracking chance...
(Only the top 3 will get a tracking chance.)
that I told you about earlier.
- Only three of us? - Yes.
The first place is...
(Who could be the 1st person to obtain the chance?)
- Se Chan. - Really?
- Me? - Se Chan?
- I didn't make many mistakes. - He was out only once.
- Only once. - The second place...
(Who are the other 2 people to get the chance?)
are Kwang Soo and So Min.
(So Min and Kwang Soo)
- Oh, yes! Okay. - Okay!
Okay. The youngest members won.
Let's join forces together. It's been a while!
(The 3 winners are the youngest members.)
We can go anywhere we want, right?
- See you later. - I'll see you later.
- So Min, make sure to find it. - We should...
After all the eight of you finish searching,
(After 8 people finish searching,)
(only 3 people get time to track the location.)
we'll give the three of them the tracking chance.
(2nd gold search time)
- We must find it. - It must be us to find it.
- Even if it's not me. - You can split up.
- Can we start searching? - I'll go through every place.
(When all 8 people are done searching for 15 minutes,)
Let's search every place.
(3 winners will get the location chance separately.)
I didn't go into that place earlier.
We have to win by any means.
(Where is the gold?)
I'll go up there.
(Haha is going into the House of Props.)
"House of Props".
Since it went off there, it must be somewhere around here.
(Se Chan)
(The House of Props, Se Chan's previous location)
(Considering the distance, the House of Props is likely the right place.)
House of Props. Right. I'm sure of it.
(He found a hint.)
(He found it unexpectedly while looking for gold.)
(It's a photo hint again.)
Let me have a look.
Including Suk Jin, there are all eight of us here.
(It's the same place as the photo from earlier...)
(but with all 8 people.)
What does it mean?
(What does this photo indicate?)
Is this... Wait. Am I supposed to figure it out from this? Wait.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo and So Min...)
There must be something here.
(The House of Games)
I saw a clue being placed here.
(Finding something)
(So Min also found a clue.)
"It's darker under the lamp."
(It's darker under the lamp.)
(A new hint, "It's darker under the lamp.")
"It's darker under the lamp."
What could this indicate?
(It's hinting that the gold isn't far away.)
The phrase means that we miss what's...
- right under our noses. - Under our noses.
"It's darker under the lamp."
(Which place could be right under their noses?)
(Meanwhile, in the House of Sports...)
Did you find anything?
- Nothing's here, right? - Nothing.
(The House of Sports)
Did you find anything downstairs?
Yes, I did.
What did you find?
(On the hint...)
(He ponders for a while.)
"Even walls have ears."
(Giving him a false hint)
- What a liar. - How did you know that?
How did you know?
(Terrified)
- As if I couldn't tell. - But it made sense.
(Yoo Jae Suk, Ph.D., an expert of Kwang Soo)
It's an idiom you could think of.
(It's exactly...)
(It's the most difficult idiom Kwang Soo can come up with.)
It's exactly at your level.
"It's darker under the lamp."
(The actual hint)
As if.
- "It's darker under the lamp." - As if.
(Actually, he just doesn't trust anything that Kwang Soo says.)
Unbelievable.
(But I was telling the truth.)
You're in for a bad day today.
(While wishing each other the worst, they head to the House of Books.)
You're done for today.
Our teammates are here.
(So Min and Se Chan were already here.)
- Jae Suk... - Don't let them come in.
- First of all... - Wait!
You're supposed to find the pieces.
(So Min and Se Chan...)
No, we were just solving this puzzle.
(are solving a puzzle.)
(During the 1st search)
This is odd.
(So Min found the puzzle pieces strange.)
I see pieces to a puzzle lying around.
I see more over there too.
(It was obviously set up by the crew.)
Anyone can tell that they're not random.
It's odd, right?
(And she naturally found...)
Wait, I think I'm right.
The pieces are scattered around the place.
We need to solve this puzzle.
(the puzzle board.)
What's this?
(But it ended after putting 4 pieces due to lack of concentration.)
It must be someone's face.
I think this needs to be solved. Help me with this.
(Then she brought Se Chan as soon as the 2nd search began.)
There are two of them. When will we finish this?
(She had no one else but Se Chan to bring.)
We need to combine forces.
- We need to solve this. - Right.
(While solving the puzzle with Se Chan,)
(she was caught.)
You're supposed to find the pieces.
- Well... - That's not right.
(Se Chan hasn't been much of a help, and they got less than two pieces.)
This will take too long, so I give up.
(After seeing them solve a puzzle,)
This will take too long,
so I give up.
(they leave the scene feeling relieved.)
It's not worth it.
There's a puzzle here.
(Jae Suk joins in on solving the puzzle.)
("Up high" lingers on Kwang Soo's mind.)
When up high, check down below.
(He heads into a building to find higher ground.)
Must I go someplace higher?
(Will Kwang Soo be able to find something on higher ground?)
This is a tricky one.
Wait a second.
(Thanks to Jae Suk, they have someone's body.)
I think it's doable. It won't take long.
This goes here.
- Isn't this the place? - Yes.
No way. This is Jae Suk.
- It's you. - It's Jimi Yu.
(This is Jae Suk?)
It's you.
- It's you. - It's Jimi Yu.
Why is this of Jimi Yu?
- What's this? - Why am I in the puzzle?
(This tacky man has the face of Jimi Yu.)
The outfit seemed like Jimi Yu's.
Why didn't you tell us then?
(Then why didn't he say anything?)
- Hold on a second. - Weren't you going to share?
- Of course not. - You would've easily noticed.
(The puzzle is pointing at Jimi Yu.)
Wait a second. I had to make sure.
I wasn't certain.
Where was this taken? Do you remember this rope?
Of course I don't.
(That place...)
You didn't say anything when you knew it was you though.
That's not true. I just wanted to be sure.
- The mouth makes it obvious. - Right.
(This man with a unique dental structure...)
(Why has Jimi Yoo been offered as a clue?)
(There must be a meaning behind this.)
This must be a clue.
(The House of Games)
(Big Nose discovered another puzzle.)
It seems like one.
Wait, these eyes...
(Haha decided to help while passing by.)
Is this us? This could be you.
- That must be it. - It's a face.
I see someone's eyes.
(This puzzle reveals another person.)
Did I put this in the right place?
(The eyes seem to belong to a foreigner.)
"When up high, check down below."
(So Min's House)
(He figures that the gold is somewhere up high.)
"When up high, check down below."
What's this?
(There's a photo of So Min and Bo Pil in So Min's house.)
Why is this photo here?
(This photo...)
(is one that Jae Suk ignored after seeing it.)
(Kwang Soo takes it with him, though.)
Is it Bo Pil?
"I'm watching you." That could be his words.
(Come to think of it...)
(I'm watching you.)
(He's always watching the members.)
(It's darker under the lamp.)
"It's darker under the lamp."
A segment within a segment.
(The main director always sits in front of them.)
(It's darker under the lamp. I'm watching you.)
It's not odd for So Min to have her photo at her house,
(It's weird that her photo with the producer was in the room.)
but why would Bo Pil be in one?
(Kwang Soo makes an advance.)
(A pick-pocketing attempt)
(If he's right, Bo Pil would have the gold.)
- What's with him? - Unbelievable.
(What's going on?)
(But just then...)
What is he doing?
(He pulls out a jewelry box!)
Did you find the gold?
(Dumbfounded)
Is that the gold?
(So Min goes through the other director's pockets.)
(Kwang Soo dashed in and found the jewelry box.)
- Did you find the gold? - Is that the gold?
(Anyone who finds the gold will instantly win.)
(And the race will be over.)
(He hurries out and checks the contents.)
What on earth?
(You've been fooled. Find the real jewelry box.)
(A fake jewelry box?)
Seriously?
- "I hid the gold I prepared." - Gold?
(In the letter sent by the village head)
"I hope you will find it well."
(To Mr. Ji)
(Beware of the fake jewelry boxes.)
(Kwang Soo was the only one not aware of the fake boxes.)
(It was a fake box.)
What?
Are you kidding me?
(Kwang Soo runs back in with his hair flying.)
Let's keep solving the puzzle.
(How dare you play with me?)
- Why... - What's going on?
- What's wrong? - Tell me what this is.
(Kwang Soo was fooled by the staff's trick.)
- I don't know what that is. - What's going on?
- What's wrong? - Tell me what this is.
I don't know what that is.
What's going on?
(He checks the director's pockets out of disbelief.)
Stop frisking me.
(That's odd...)
Kwang Soo, is this what you're looking for?
I think it is.
What is it?
Anyone can tell that's a ssamjang container.
(Kwang Soo's not as stupid as one thinks.)
- How did you know that? - How did you know?
- It's obvious. - You see,
(I'm busy right now. Don't shove that in my face.)
- he's the famous... - Ssamjang.
- What's that you have? - What is it?
(Kwang Soo makes a wrong guess,)
I think it's an empty box.
(and the second search ends.)
The second search is over!
(The 5 who weren't in the top 3 leave first.)
Let's head out for now.
(The top 3 members get to use the tracking chance.)
I think someone's house was that way.
I doubt it'd be anywhere near here.
I'm lost.
(They might have a shot if it's one of the three.)
Will this tracking device really go off?
"I'm watching you."
(It's why the second tracking chance must be used wisely.)
(Which house could the gold be in?)
Who on earth is watching us?
"When it's big, have a close look."
If only I knew whose device went off earlier.
(Se Chan's more at ease...)
(since his tracker was the one that rang.)
It can't be down there since mine went off around here.
(The gold must be near where he first stood.)
Can't you tell me the distance between me and the gold?
(He decides to stand close to where he originally stood.)
Kwang Soo, stand down there.
(Se Chan sets a bait.)
Haha was at the House of Dolls and I was here.
(He tends to listen.)
Ji Hyo was in that house...
(Lying to send Kwang Soo away from him)
and Suk Jin was in that one.
No one stood down here though.
Meanwhile, I'll stand here.
(Nonchalantly, he steps to the spot he decided on.)
- The House of Games? - I'll stay here.
That can't be the spot.
(It has to be someplace higher.)
Hold on.
When up high...
(When up high, check down below.)
When it's big...
(When it's big, have a close look.)
"When it's big, have a close look."
(When up high and when it's big... This van is always watching them.)
"I'm watching you."
Could it be a dashcam?
- Here? - Yes.
(He stands somewhere up high.)
Near the House of Dolls.
(He starts searching the House of Dolls.)
Could it be inside a doll?
(The House of Dolls)
There's a clue in every house, but not in this one.
No way!
(He finds a clue in the passenger seat under the doll.)
What's this?
(It's a photo of something taken up close.)
I found a clue.
(It must be a photo of where the gold is.)
Will it ring automatically?
(Meanwhile, So Min...)
(She arrives at the House of Cooking.)
Right, then...
(She sits in the center of the House of Cooking.)
I'll sit here.
(The House of Cooking)
It all looks delicious.
(She only came in here because she's hungry.)
Please let my device ring.
(So Min, Se Chan, Kwang Soo)
(The three have taken their places.)
(Where the alarm first rang)
(The device closest to the gold will ring.)
(The device rang!)
(So Min's the closest!)
My device is ringing. I'm the closest.
(The gold is near me!)
You are currently...
the closest to the gold.
(So Min's the closest to the gold.)
You are currently the closest to the gold.
(She only sat here out of hunger, but she got lucky.)
Then...
This means I'm closest to the gold, right?
(The 2nd search ends.)
To the gold...
(Where the alarm first rang)
(Not so far away, the second device rang.)
My device is ringing. I'm the closest.
(Where the device rang next)
(So where exactly is the gold?)
Gosh, what a feast.
(Now it's time for the birthday boy that everyone's forgotten about.)
It must be Suk Jin's birthday meal.
Gosh, it's a feast.
(The level of his birthday party)
Are we allowed to eat this?
- No way. - Can we eat this?
(All festival dishes are here.)
This is a work of art.
It's Suk Jin's birthday after all.
Thank you for the meal.
(The table is filled with foods that will rejuvenate Suk Jin.)
The seaweed soup looks delicious.
- Thank you for the meal. - This is a feast.
So this is where I get my birthday meal.
(Feeling pretty good)
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
(Suk Jin's favorite, the official one-shot)
- Happy birthday, dear Suk Jin - Happy birthday, dear Suk Jin
(Singing enthusiastically to celebrate Suk Jin's birthday)
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
My gosh.
(Happy birthday, Suk Jin!)
I was carried by the members and got hit as a means to celebrate.
Jong Kook and I...
should bow first.
Right, of course.
Unbelievable.
- Please don't. - Let's do that.
(I'm sick of it.)
- Are you serious? - We should.
(Are they really bowing in a variety show?)
He means it.
Don't do it!
(It's a superficial gesture with clear intentions.)
Get Suk Jin's wallet, guys.
- We need to get the money gift. - Suk Jin.
(In hopes of receiving a money gift from him, they all line up.)
- Happy New Year, Suk Jin. - Happy New Year, Suk Jin.
(They proceed in haste in case he runs away.)
I wish you good health!
Thanks.
I hope everything you wish for comes true this year.
(After giving some superficial speech,)
You didn't have to make a deep bow.
- This is nice. It's heartwarming. - Sit down.
(they start to line up for money.)
Give us the money now.
- Please give me the money now. - I'll treat you to a good meal.
Where is the money?
I'll treat you to a good meal.
(He's trying to avoid the situation.)
Suk Jin, 2,000 dollars will be enough for me.
(The money)
Since I'm younger than Jae Suk, I can do with 1,800 dollars.
(Kim Jong Kook, Bow Pyramid, 1,800 dollars for every bow)
My gosh.
(It's time to taste the meal the staff prepared for him.)
- It looks good. - The seaweed soup looks good.
- It really... - Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food.
We're having a feast thanks to Suk Jin.
(It's also a good warm meal for members who eat meal boxes.)
It's nice.
They came early in the morning to make all these dishes.
(As many people's effort was put in, we wish Big Nose good health.)
This is good.
I usually have a simple meal on my birthdays. This is amazing.
I think they prepared a game where we get splashed with something.
(It's the second mission to get the location.)
It's Kwang Soo's favorite game.
(It looks like a mission involving flour that Kwang Soo likes.)
This is the last mission.
This mission is similar to the game Suk Jin played as a kid.
(It's similar to the game Suk Jin played as a kid.)
- Me? - It's a modified version...
(It's a modified version of Rice Barley Game.)
of Rice Barley Game. It's called In a Split Second.
(Second Mission: In a Split Second)
It's a game where we pick either barley or rice.
Rice, barley.
Two people will play the game at a time.
(Two people will play the game.)
You'll be using your face instead of your fist.
(They'll be using the face instead of fists.)
The opponent will wear the cylinder cardboards...
(The opponent will wear the cylinder cardboard...)
and use the pot lids covered in flour to play defense.
(and use the pot lids with flour on to play defense.)
The one playing offense...
(The one playing offense can pick either barley or rice.)
can pick either barley or rice...
and put their head in between the opponent's pot lids.
(He'd need to move his heads up and down.)
You need to move your head up and down.
(by putting their head in between the opponent's pot lids.)
- You succeed if you don't get hit. - Oh, up and down?
So in the end, we'll all be covered in flour.
(Simply put, it'll be a party of flours.)
There's no way we can avoid it.
You can yell out barley as many times as you want,
(They can yell out barley as many times as they want,)
but you can yell out rice only five times.
(but they can yell out rice only five times.)
If you yell rice and avoid getting hit, you'll earn one point.
(One will earn a point if he or she yells rice and avoids getting hit.)
(One will lose a point if he or she fails.)
If you fail, then your point will be deducted.
So we can hit however we want when they yell barley?
This game is meant for Kwang Soo.
(It's definitely a game for Kwang Soo.)
- It totally is. - No, it's not.
What's important in this game is the lineup.
You can play against one person only.
(Only the winners will get the hint to the location.)
You play offense and defense with the same person,
so the lineup is very important.
He's right.
It's important. The lineup is important.
(What's the line-up?)
Then let's decide with this.
- We can play Game of Wits. - Game of Wits?
How can we decide the lineup...
- through that? - Let's just give it a go.
- There's a way. - 1st place and 2nd place will...
- That's it. - Oh, really?
Let's get ready.
Start.
(Game of Wits starts.)
One!
- 2! - The 2 of you can go first.
The two of you can go first.
(The first line-up is ready.)
That's not fair!
- But... - Isn't this clever?
(The line-up is made based on reinterpreting Game of Wits.)
- But... - We'll play against each other?
- This is how it's done? - We didn't win the game?
He's such a great MC.
- There's no number 3 and 4? - Number 1 and 2 can go first.
(Satisfied)
You two can play against each other.
Se Chan and Kwang Soo, please step forward.
- How... - How do we play?
- The one playing defense... - They're going to play for real.
(In the end, everyone will do what they're told.)
And the one playing offense...
They're going to listen to Jae Suk and play.
They're so naive.
- Flour party - I can only say rice five times?
(They only get 5 chances to call rice.)
- I can only say it 5 times, right? - Yes, you only get 5 chances.
(Earn a point if successful, lose a point if failed.)
But if you get hit, we'll deduct a point.
If you manage to not get hit, then you'll earn a point.
(They're excited at the potential flour party.)
You need to use all five chances to finish the game.
- Don't hit when I yell barley. - I'll stay away from them.
- I can only hit him in this zone? - That's right.
Let's practice first.
(The defense will have his or her arms fixed,)
- No, move your head up and down. - You need to go up and down.
- Try it. Is this how he goes? - Yes, that's it.
(the offense will have to attack up and down.)
Up and down.
- I hit him like this? - Doesn't he have to move...
(Advising)
- back and forth? - You should go forward more.
We tried moving back and forth, but it wasn't fast enough.
(They don't listen to the staff and advise to move back and forth.)
So the ones playing defense need to play fair.
- If he's in the zone, then... - Down here?
(It's easier for Kwang Soo to move back and forth.)
- Like this? - I think that'd be better.
- Try it. - Or maybe not.
- Try going as fast as you can. - I think that'd be better.
(Practice moving back and forth.)
You can go back and forth then.
- Barley. - So this should work better.
It's just a practice round.
(Se Chan attacks Kwang Soo without prior consent.)
- Barley. - So this should work better.
- It's just a practice round. - He said barley.
(He learns how to play the game while being hit.)
- I can hit him when he says barley. - Yes, he can.
Barley is equivalent to safe.
(He is allowed to hit when it's "barley".)
You can say rice whenever you want.
(Barley is irrelevant to winning, and one can name rice only 5 times.)
- That's right. - It's safe.
Barley is safe.
You've played Rice Barley Game before. It's exactly the same.
(It's a very simple game.)
- You need to go fast. - Ready, go.
Barley. Barley.
(Moving forward)
- Is this how I'm supposed to play? - Wait a minute.
- What is this? - Yes, it's allowed.
- This is... - Is this how we play?
(It's the consequence of not listening to the staff.)
It is.
- But this is... - He should move fast and say rice.
- Say rice and move out fast. - I need to say rice fast?
(He still doesn't know what he did wrong.)
- But... - No, that's not it.
I dodged, but he hit me anyway.
Kwang Soo, you can't ruin the game.
We can't play the game now because of you.
(He's saying the same thing several times.)
So if you move up and down, you can dodge fast.
I think moving up and down would work better.
He needs to go down fast.
(He tries moving up and down.)
- Let's practice. - Move up and down.
- Try going down. - Barley.
(He's trying to rig the game.)
- It works. - It works.
- This works, Kwang Soo. - That's it.
- This works. - That's good.
(Is it really working?)
- Then I'll play now. - Okay.
(They begin the first round after figuring out the rules.)
Barley!
That was close.
- "Rice". - Barley!
Is this how we play?
Hey, you're bad at this game.
(Mr. Ji bursts out laughing.)
- I moved really fast. - You're bad at this game.
He puts his head right in the spot for me to hit.
(The flour show by a stupid giraffe.)
(Laughing)
It's like Suk Jin is watching a variety show on TV.
(He forgot his role in the show and just enjoyed the game.)
I love this game.
It's hilarious.
This is perfect for Suk Jin's birthday.
- He's having fun. He seems happy. - He loves it.
It reminds me of the Rice Barley Game I used to play.
(Mr. Ji is laughing hard in his eventful birthday party.)
I'm having so much fun.
- I need to pass my head through. - Yes, you need to pass through.
(He catches his breath.)
Rice!
(He brutally fails the first attack and loses a point.)
- That's minus one point. - You got hit.
- That's right. - You got hit.
- I need to avoid getting hit? - Of course.
I can play offense later, right?
He's in big trouble.
(He's having fun playing against the stupid brother.)
- You need to move really fast. - By the way,
(Se Chan)
you look like the Magic Monkey.
He really does!
(Even its protruding mouth looks like Se Chan's.)
Hey.
- Doesn't he look like one? - He looks like Abu in "Aladdin".
- Do I really look like it? - Yes.
(The confident monkey...)
(and clueless Kwang Soo)
Let's play, Kwang Soo.
- You need to pass through fast. - Or you can...
- You need to miss the hit. - I'll make sure to succeed now.
(I'll succeed for the remaining rounds.)
You need to say rice after deceiving him with barley.
- Barley. Barley. - That's it.
(Nodding)
- Barley. - You don't have a knack for it.
- That's it. - That's how you play.
- Barley. Barley. - Move fast so he can't hit you.
(He makes a fuss...)
Barley. Barley. Barley. Rice!
(and manages to succeed.)
Barley. Barley. Rice!
- Okay! - Wow.
You have only one chance left.
(He finally succeeds in his first attack.)
- Okay. - All right.
You're quite good.
I can hit him before he says rice, right?
(Preemptive)
- Kwang Soo is good at games. - Barley.
- He's good at them. - Barley. Barley.
Wait. He hit me when I didn't even go down. Is this allowed?
- I need to defend too. - Is this allowed?
- I need to defend too. - Hey, hey!
- I need to defend, don't I? - He can't hit me...
(A nondiscriminatory offense by the Korean monkey.)
- when I didn't attack, can he? - That's right.
It's because there's a battery in me.
Se Chan didn't do anything wrong though.
- Right. - So this is allowed?
(He tries to protest in a flour-covered face.)
- Of course! - You're not good at this.
You need to keep saying barley until you get a chance to say rice.
(He's making a fool of Kwang Soo without even batting an eye.)
Barley, barley.
- Barley. - The space is too tight for him.
Barley.
(He gets hit anyway...)
- Barley. - Okay.
(even if he uses a different rhythm.)
Barley.
I pity him now.
(Slapping)
(Kwang Soo avenges the monkey.)
Why did you hit me? Kwang Soo, I was only defending!
(The fool covered in flour finally explodes.)
Kwang Soo. I was only defending!
Are you sure this is how we play?
(He's checking again.)
- Why wouldn't you yell out rice? - He should hit me...
- You went down! - only when I attack!
You should hit me after I yell out barley.
How can you hit me when I didn't yell out anything?
What's the point of saying barley and rice then?
You need to go down when you yell out rice.
I didn't yell out anything, so why did you hit me?
(It makes Mr. Ji laugh again.)
You need to go down when you yell out rice.
You hit me when I didn't yell out anything,
(The Chinese opera actor finally explodes.)
so when can I yell out rice?
That's when you go down.
You need to do a better job.
Are you Toshio or something?
(The game resumes.)
I'm going to start now.
(Be calm.)
Barley.
- That's how you should play. - Yes, go slowly and get the rhythm.
There you go.
He's such a fool.
(He yells out barley after breathing calmly.)
- It's tense. - Barley!
Barley!
Gosh, I should've yelled out rice!
I should've yelled out rice!
- I thought too hard. - Why didn't you yell out rice?
I thought too hard.
Why didn't you yell out rice?
It was a battle against myself.
I gave you a signal this time.
(He got the opportunity but yelled barley instead.)
- Yell out rice already. - It was the right speed for rice.
I should've yelled out rice.
You have only one chance.
(He only has one more chance to call rice.)
- You have only one chance. - If Se Chan does well...
(Flinching)
Wait. Don't give me signals.
Don't give me signals.
(He unknowingly send signals for the confusion.)
You have only one chance.
Barley. Barley.
- You should've said rice. - Rice!
All right!
(He succeeds in his final offense.)
Kwang Soo's final score is minus one.
(In the end, Kwang Soo loses a point.)
- Minus one? - Yes.
(The result isn't bad compared to the flour he collected.)
- He did well. - It's not easy, but he did well.
I should go down at once. You...
(Collecting all the flour as he's desperate to get revenge)
That's enough already.
(It's evident that Kwang Soo's play will incite headaches.)
Kwang Soo is gathering all the flour.
- You can't put your arms down. - Okay.
(Bloodthirsty)
He looks so scary.
Gosh, if you get hit by those...
- I mean... - You can only start when I'm ready.
- He's so determined. - He is.
- Lift your arms a little. - He's just going to hit Se Chan.
(It doesn't matter if he yells barley or rice.)
He's clenching his teeth.
- Look at his face. - I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, but he's gone mad.
- Look at my finger. - I can see it.
- You're okay, right? - Yes.
(Will Kwang Soo who's gone mad be able to get his revenge?)
- This is... - He can go fast if he wants to.
(Dancing)
- Look at him. He's good. - He's twerking.
(His pelvic twerking gets on Kwang Soo's nerve.)
- Play until your energy runs out. - He's twerking.
Rice!
(He easily scores 1 point.)
(He scores another point right away!)
- I'm going to go again. - He's good!
(Mumbling)
Rice!
(He gave away 3 points to 3 consecutive rice calls.)
- Wait. - What's wrong?
(Why can't I do a good job?)
- Why aren't you doing anything? - I have two more chances.
Why aren't you doing anything?
(He couldn't even swing once and lost 3 chances in a row.)
- You should yell out barley too. - I will.
- I will yell out barley. - You should say barley a few times.
(He forces Se Chan to say barley the next round.)
- Okay. I'll say barley first. - You can't only yell out rice.
- You want me to say barley first? - You should say it a few times.
Barley, barley, and then rice? Got it.
- Twerking. - "Twerking"?
(He moves his pelvis again.)
(The twerking master gets ready to play.)
You're good, Se Chan.
That's so hot.
(His angle of arms is narrowing as he gets more impatient.)
It looks like a skit from "Comedy Big League".
(Shaking)
There's not enough space here.
Sir, there's not enough space here.
- Should I make more space? - Yes.
(He tries to prevent Se Chan from penetrating.)
Please make some more space.
He's dying to hit Se Chan.
He doesn't care about the game. He just wants to hit Se Chan.
Rice!
(He succeeds again.)
You dodged again? Hold on a second.
(There's only one chance left, but he's far from hitting Se Chan.)
- That's good! - Se Chan earned four points.
- I earned four points. - Kwang Soo hasn't hit him once.
Rice!
It hasn't even started!
- Rice! - It hasn't even started!
You brat. It hasn't even started!
(He pays back outside of the game.)
- Rice! - How could you play right away?
(He gets hit about 20 times,)
- I'm done. - Good job!
(and he barely hits him 2 times outside of the game.)
- We'll accept that. - For real?
All right!
(Kwang Soo loses 1 point, Se Chan earns 5 points.)
Se Chan won five points.
Well done, Se Chan.
(Se Chan wins.)
- That was a neat finish. - Well done, Kwang Soo.
I can't hit as fast as I want to.
- I can't hit fast. - It's Ji Hyo versus So Min now.
(It's Ji Hyo versus So Min.)
Hang on. I want to practice first.
(They get more nervous as they saw the previous game.)
That's a good attitude.
- She's fast. - She is.
It's not that easy to hit.
- Right. - I'm serious.
Let's begin now.
(So Min begins the Rice Barley Game.)
- It's nerve-racking. - Yes, it must be.
It's nerve-racking. Barley.
- You need to find the right timing. - I should've said rice.
Barley.
(They seem to be having a good time for now.)
You can't go down with So Min.
- She can't help it. - It can't be helped.
- It's only natural. - It can't be helped.
(Hitting)
- I didn't say anything! - It can't be helped.
(Ji Hyo just smacked her.)
I didn't say anything!
I'm so sorry, So Min!
(Grabbing)
Don't give up, So Min!
(She apologizes sincerely by rubbing flour on her.)
- So Min. - I didn't mean it. I'm so sorry.
(Ji Hyo expresses how sorry she is by applying flour on So Min.)
I didn't mean it.
- I'm so sorry. - Ji Hyo means it.
Ji Hyo is really sorry.
- You'll be covered in it anyway. - It's okay.
It's hilarious.
Rice!
(So Min succeeds in her attack.)
Good job.
- Okay. - You should keep it up.
I shouldn't meet her eyes.
(Rice Barley Game with no eye contact)
Barley! Barley!
(Hitting)
Barley!
- Ji Hyo. - Aren't you just beating her up?
- She keeps... - Ji Hyo keeps beating her up.
- Don't do that! - She's so harsh.
She hits So Min all she wants and hugs her to say sorry.
(Immersed)
So Min went down as she yelled out barley.
(Hugging after the attack for the 2nd time)
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo followed her and hit her.
It's because I keep losing strength to keep my arms up.
If she gets hit...
It's because I keep losing strength.
(She attacks So Min mercilessly before she loses her strength.)
(Nervous)
Rice!
(So Min has earned 2 points so far!)
(Smack)
What was that?
(Ji Hyo hits So Min again when she didn't do anything.)
- You just hit her? - Why did you hit her?
Weren't you going down?
- Song Jeoktoma is back! - You weren't going down?
(By now, it seems she's doing it on purpose.)
I thought she was going down.
- That's so cunning of you. - Why did you hit her?
She just smacked her.
She kept mouthing something.
(It's the side effect of fake mouthing.)
She kept doing that, so I thought she'd go down.
- Song Jeoktoma, you're impressive. - I thought she was going down.
(So Min earned 2 points.)
- Song Jeoktoma. - It's my turn now.
- Run, Song Jeoktoma. - Look at this, Ji Hyo.
(Refilling flour)
- You need to coat them thoroughly. - Look at this, Ji Hyo.
(Hitting)
(What was that?)
(Delinquent Ji Hyo kicks Kwang Soo in the head.)
She kicked his head. Wow, she...
(They look like real siblings after working together for 11 years.)
She kicks his head now.
Isn't the purpose of this game to get flour on our faces?
(Sad)
She precisely hit the crown of his head.
(It just felt offensive.)
- It didn't hurt though. - I think...
Kwang Soo's been hit a lot. Ji Hyo must have a lot of experience too.
(Throwing her jacket)
- She's tough. - Okay.
(As soon as he receives her jacket...)
- All right. - Good.
Why do you always go through the pockets when you find a jacket?
I was looking for a hint.
- I was looking for a hint. - He has a habit of stealing.
(He reacts automatically when he sees pockets.)
- I thought there'd be a hint. - I mean...
I was just checking.
You don't even hide and go through her pockets.
(The powdered thief doesn't meet the Clean Running Man precepts.)
- No, that's not true. - He has issues.
(Ji Hyo begins Rice Barley Game.)
- Let's play. - Barley.
- Wait, so when I say barley... - You need to go down fast.
Barley.
(So Min's arms are extremely slow.)
- She's quite slow. - Put down your head fast.
So Min is quite slow.
- Rice! - That's it!
You only need to say it fast.
- Put down your head fast. - So Min can't catch up.
You only need to say it confidently.
(Will she say it or not?)
Barley!
- Barley! - Wait a minute.
- She can't hit her like that. - You...
- So Min hit her like this. - You can't go down with me.
(So Min attacked Ji Hyo's head without reason.)
That's not true.
- She hit her like that. - That's not true.
(She just hit me for no reason.)
- She followed me down. - No!
- She definitely followed me down. - How can the game proceed...
if she keeps going down Ji Hyo?
No. That's not true.
(Ji Hyo and So Min's intentional mistakes are getting interesting.)
Don't hit the back of her head!
(They're satisfied by their dirty match.)
- That's not true. - She hit the back of her head.
- That's not true. - So Min, you...
- You hit me right here. - No, I didn't.
(Song Jeoktoma joins by mentioning the area.)
- That's not true. - That's not cool, So Min.
How could you... Gosh.
(So far, So Min's doing well with reckless defense.)
- I won't go down from here. - From here?
From here?
(The game resumes.)
- That's it. Stay there. - Stay here.
You need to be in the spot where her head passes through.
(Will she say it or not?)
Just go down fast.
This is fun.
Rice!
(She succeeds in the delayed attack.)
Wow, she played with So Min.
- Wow, she used a fake move. - "Rice!"
(Even the audience fell for Song Jeoktoma's fake move.)
I totally fell for it.
That was really well-played.
- We should play like that. - She's good at this game.
(But as she fails the rest of her attacks, So Min wins.)
I think she hit my ear too hard.
It's time for me and Haha to play.
(The Precious Sister's game ended on a good note.)
- It's time for me and Haha to play. - Okay.
(Round 3, Jae Suk versus Haha)
It's all about speed.
- It's... - He's at it again.
Hang on. I'm not ready yet.
(He never stops boasting before playing the game.)
He's got a good posture. That's good.
- You need to go down really fast. - Of course.
That's it.
- He passes through so fast. - That's it.
(Will he be able to show what he got this time?)
(Nimble)
Here we go.
- Okay. - Can I start?
(Relaxed)
- He has a bad back though. - Right.
- I'll start now. - His back must hurt then.
Rice! Rice!
Wait a minute.
(He's covered in flour after yelling out rice twice.)
Are you okay?
(The miracle of saying rice twice in a row)
Jae Suk.
You only yelled out rice twice, and you're covered in flour already.
You're covered all over with flour after saying rice twice.
(The patient with game fright is in a mess.)
He yelled out rice only twice, right?
How could he be completely covered in flour after only saying it twice?
He looks the same as Kwang Soo now.
(Kwang Soo feels lost too.)
- What happened? - I got it now.
- You said it's all about speed. - Okay, I got it now.
- I should calm down. - He must've been hit on the nose.
(Brainwashing himself)
- You should calm down. - He was hit on the nose.
(He lost two chances with no gain.)
Here we go. Barley.
(This time, he decides to go slow.)
Haha doesn't hit him when he says barley.
Barley. You're not hitting me when I say barley.
I don't think he'll hit you even if you say rice at this rate.
Barley!
"Rice."
Barley! Barley! Darn you...
(The guy who's not good at games is rich with flour now.)
- Hey. - You basically asked for it.
- You went down at the right timing. - Haha hit you at the right timing.
(The nation's sandbag even goes along with the rhythm.)
- You put your head there to be hit. - Is that so?
- Yes. - It was really rhythmical.
You failed twice already.
(He has three chances now.)
Twice?
Barley! Rice! Rice! Rice!
Didn't he cheat?
(He said rice all 5 times and failed.)
- My goodness. - Didn't he cheat?
(During the process)
That was hilarious.
- You put your head there to be hit! - What's wrong?
(Haha can't believe that he won.)
- You're terrible at games. - You're not fast at all, Jae Suk.
He got the lowest score?
(Jae Suk records the lowest score by failing all 5 times.)
Yes, he got minus five points.
That's the lowest.
Wait, that's Big Nose!
- That's Big Nose! - He turned into Mr. Big Nose.
(Aren't those the glasses with a big nose?)
His nose is attached to his glasses.
How did only his nose get hit?
(The attack was done on his nose mainly.)
- Only his nose was hit. - Right, only his nose was hit.
Your nose...
If you play defense well,
(False hope)
- you still have a chance. - Of course.
Haha has gained weight recently, so he might not be as fast.
(Haha is not as fast because he recently gained weight.)
- You're so ugly. - It's scary, right?
Rice!
(After shaking him up, Haha succeeds in his attack.)
- That's acceptable. - Is this allowed?
- Of course it's acceptable. - Rice!
- There he goes again. - What was that?
- Focus, Jae Suk! - Don't be fooled by what he says.
(He gained 2 points easily.)
Haha is using an advanced skill.
(The man with a dirty mustache keeps flinching.)
(Big Nose is tensed up.)
Rice.
(Swift)
- Darn it. - That was amazing.
(Angry)
- Keep going! - I'm going to hit him this time.
(He gets his hips working again.)
(Hitting)
Jae Suk.
- No! You can't do that! - What's wrong with you?
(A fight between men covered in flour breaks out.)
What's wrong with these guys?
(Their punches are so soft.)
No, you can't do this! Stop!
My gosh, he's so annoying.
Stop it!
(Jae Suk's pride is too high for his low game skill.)
Jae Suk is upset!
Jae Suk is upset.
Haha knows when to be annoying.
- You should hit him at least once. - I should do that.
(I'll hit him at least once.)
- You should hit him at least once. - You should hit him at least once.
You can't let him take five points.
(Haha starts teasing Jae Suk again.)
- He must be really annoyed. - That's cute though.
(Haha uses all his skills to annoy Jae Suk.)
He's so annoying.
(Darn him.)
He's getting into the beat.
(Crazy beat that drives Jae Suk mad)
- This battle... - It's exciting!
(DJ Bachelor Ghost)
(Getting into the beat)
Jae Suk is getting into the beat also!
(Big Nose Glasses couldn't resist getting into the beat.)
It's actually exciting.
I want to join them too.
(They're just excited.)
- Rice. - Darn it.
(Jae Suk allows the counterattack while getting into the beat.)
(It's Haha's complete victory!)
Here we go.
(That was a good game.)
This is so upsetting.
- Goodness. - Here we go.
(For the final round, it's Suk Jin versus Jong Kook.)
My goodness.
I think we got enough footage for the show.
You are right.
(He doesn't want to get flour on his face.)
I can't wait for this big match.
My goodness.
(This caption hasn't been used for a while.)
- It isn't easy, right? - If I am not careful,
I will hit him with my wrists.
(If he misses, it's deadly to both.)
You need to win.
The rules.
- He is fast. - He is good.
(He checks his waist before the game.)
He is fast. Suk Jin is fast.
- Didn't I hear a crack? - He is fast.
He is like a long-headed grasshopper.
(Every time he moves, there's a cracking sound.)
- He is fast. - All right.
He greets people so well.
He ran out of energy.
(Torturing his spine)
His back hurts now.
(He used up half of his energy in the warm-up.)
- He ran out of energy. - He is dizzy.
- It's like he has cupulolithiasis. - He ran out of energy.
All right.
Rice.
(He succeeded to land the first attack!)
So that's how you play.
- He got covered in flour. - He has a nice tactic.
Why are you covered in flour when you dodged?
Barley.
(He got flour on his big nose.)
(Giggling)
The daughter-in-law is happy.
- It's so much fun. - Suk Jin is aging!
(Seeing her father-in-law's struggle makes So Min laugh.)
Suk Jin is getting white hair.
(Mr. Ji got old right in the face.)
Mother-in-law will be happy.
Long life, health, and blessing!
(She fell for her father-in-law's antics.)
He is so charming.
The daughter-in-law is happy.
(Twitching)
- That's my father-in-law. - Three times remain, right?
Okay. That's it.
It won't be easy.
(It seems impossible to pass through Jong Kook's hands.)
Isn't this too narrow?
Okay, okay.
(He picks up his courage and passes through the hands.)
- You didn't say. - You didn't say.
- You didn't say. - You need to say "Rice".
You didn't say.
You need to say "Rice".
- You just passed through. - I didn't say it.
My goodness.
(He forgot to say rice in Rice Barley Game.)
- It hurts. - Father-in-law, good luck.
Okay. Look at this. This is speed.
(Mumbling)
This is speed.
He is bound to get fooled.
(Jong Kook doesn't get fooled.)
- Rice. - Father-in-law.
Father-in-law.
Let him go now.
(Suk Jin's final score is minus 1 point.)
Let's switch sides.
Okay.
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
Jong Kook will go this time.
- Okay. - Okay.
Jong Kook's tights will turn white.
My goodness.
(Putting on)
Seeing him makes my heart ache.
Seriously. He is living a cool life.
Suk Jin became so old.
- I don't know what to do. - Seriously.
His hair turned gray.
(His age clock is faster than others.)
My goodness.
How did that happen?
- Let's go. - We began, right?
- Yes. - Let's begin.
Rice.
(He wins a point easily.)
He is fast.
(He wins another point.)
He did it twice.
I bet he won't hit Jong Kook once.
(Suk Jin)
Suk Jin, isn't this too narrow?
Rice.
(Hitting)
(He ends up hitting Jong Kook after getting fooled many times.)
- Jong Kook! - Hey!
- It's Suk Jin's birthday. - It's his birthday.
It's Suk Jin's birthday.
- You hit me in the eye! - It's Suk Jin's birthday.
- I am so annoyed! - Jong Kook.
(Angry)
(He hit Jong Kook for the 1st time in 11 years.)
Jong Kook.
- I am so annoyed! - It's Suk Jin's birthday.
(Let's not do this on a good day.)
- I am so annoyed! - You can't do that.
I had to hit him once.
(The game ends without hitting Jong Kook for once.)
- I had to hit him once. - For goodness' sake.
I had to hit him once.
To the winners of the second mission,
(Se Chan, So Min, Haha, and Jong Kook got the tracking chance.)
Se Chan, So Min, Haha, and Jong Kook,
we will give the tracking chance.
- Okay. - Okay.
All right, all right.
What could it mean?
(They must choose the last tracking chance carefully.)
I don't understand the hint.
What could be similar to the photo?
I am 100 percent sure...
that the gold is moving.
(The gold is moving?)
Listen. In the beginning,
(This is where the device first went off.)
I heard the sound when I stood here.
(He was the closest to the gold out of 8 members!)
It will ring if you are close to it.
(The gold was located someplace close.)
(Se Chan)
That means it's somewhere around here.
It can't be down there. My device went off here earlier.
(During the 2nd tracking,)
What's the radius? Won't you tell me that?
(he situated himself nearby to narrow down the location.)
I will stand here.
You aren't the closest to the gold.
(But he wasn't the closest to the gold.)
I think the gold is moving.
(That's why Se Chan thinks the gold is moving.)
- It's moving, right? - Yes. I think it's moving.
If my device doesn't go off,
(He decides to choose the location he picked in the 1st round.)
that means the gold is moving.
The gold.
(4 people picked the location.)
I will stand here.
(Who is the closest member to the gold?)
(So Min, Jong Kook, Haha, and Se Chan)
I hope it goes off.
The device went off.
You aren't the closest to the gold.
(It's not Se Chan.)
It's moving.
(The device went off...)
Mine is going off, right?
(at Jong Kook's location.)
(The gold is somewhere near here.)
Look at this.
I need to look closely.
(Meanwhile, So Min went to Jae Suk's House.)
What?
Isn't this the background of Jae Suk's puzzle?
(In the puzzle)
I think it is.
(So Min spent nearly a day on the puzzle.)
I will spend a day on it. I need to figure out the place.
(She resumed working on the puzzle during the 3rd search.)
Hold on.
Where is this place?
Isn't this the background of Jae Suk's puzzle?
(Is the background...)
(Jae Suk's House?)
I think it is.
There must be something in here.
(So Min begins to search Jae Suk's House.)
What? Look at this.
(And...)
(Jae Suk quietly resumes the search.)
- Can I begin now? - Yes.
(It's the last search.)
(Who will take the gold?)
This is... Who is he?
Who is he?
He is American, right? Jong Kook would know.
(He seems like an American.)
He is American.
Who is he?
(It happens to be these three.)
Can we use the internet?
(Can we use the internet?)
Jong Kook!
- Jong Kook! - Yes?
(When you don't recognize an American, ask Jong Kook.)
- Did you find something? - It's an American.
- An American? - We don't know who he is.
Why is there an American?
You know Americans well.
- Why is there an American? - It's an American.
(He became the expert of Americans.)
Who is he?
What?
- Who is he? - Who is he?
Isn't he... No, that's not it.
- Is he a politician? - I think so.
(He looks like a politician.)
He has to be a politician.
That tie...
Is he a Republican?
(He doesn't know what that is.)
I mean,
(His head becomes blank after hearing the word Republican.)
politicians wear ties of certain colors.
What? Who is he?
The puzzle...
(Meanwhile, Se Chan...)
The puzzle points to someone.
(He searches the House of Books for more clues.)
(Staring)
Hold on.
What is this?
(One DVD is upside down.)
(It has a number sticker.)
Hold on. What is this?
(There is a number sticker on the "Les Miserables" DVD.)
What is this?
Number six.
(He finds another DVD with the number 6 sticker.)
What is this?
Number three, "The Way Home".
(He gets DVDs with stickers.)
Number four.
(Jae Suk appears.)
- Se Chan. - Jae Suk.
Jae Suk.
- There are numbers. - What?
I found these.
I am missing numbers 1 and 2. What is this?
(He has numbers 3, 4, 5, and 6.)
"House underneath is"?
What does this mean?
We aren't supposed to combine the first letters, right?
"House underneath is".
- "House underneath is"? - "House underneath is".
("House", "Go", "Under", and underlined "Gold")
Jae Suk.
We are missing numbers 1 and 2.
It's underneath someone's house.
- It's underneath someone's house. - You are right.
(Gold under the house)
It's underneath someone's house. Everyone has a house.
The missing letters could be "Suk Jin" or "Jae Suk".
(Is the gold under someone's house?)
- It's underneath someone's house. - That must be the case.
"It's darker under the lamp."
(Kwang Soo is hung up on the hint about the lamp.)
(He finds a hint in the duvet.)
"A wheeled house"?
(A wheeled house)
"A wheeled house"? The van?
(The House of Dolls)
House of Dolls is a van.
(Is a wheeled house referring to the House of Dolls?)
Kwang Soo, where are you going? Kwang Soo, come here.
(He calls the guys in his team.)
- What? - Where are you going?
Go to the car.
(In a rush)
I found a hint that read "A wheeled house".
- Okay, okay. - The car.
(Obsessed with the gold, Kwang Soo arrives in no time.)
Suk Jin, this is the only wheeled house.
- This is the only one. - "A wheeled house".
(Other guys are excited as well.)
- Is that what the hint says? - Yes.
- What? - Suk Jin.
(A wheeled house)
- We are close to winning. - What is this?
- Who is this? - Jae Suk,
(Meanwhile, at the House of Games)
- who is this? - Who is this?
(As soon as he sees...)
Jimmy Carter.
- Who is Jimmy Carter? - A former US president.
(The 39th president of the States, Jimmy Carter)
- Why is Jimmy Carter here? - I don't know.
Jimmy. Is it Ji Suk Jin?
The puzzle I saw earlier showed Jimi Yu.
What is Jimi Yoo doing here?
(The puzzles showed Jimi Yu...)
- What is Jimi Yoo doing here? - Why is Jimmy Carter here?
(and Jimmy Carter.)
(They can't find any connections aside from the names.)
- Jimmy Carter. Jimi Yu. - Jimmy.
Jimi Yu. Jimmy Carter.
There must be something between the dolls.
(Team Suk Jin's searching the House of Dolls thoroughly.)
There are more dolls in the trunk.
(The photo does seem to show a part of this car.)
Here.
Kwang Soo, you need to look underneath.
(The hint said, "When up high, check down below.")
- This is the only wheeled house. - It's underneath someone's house.
(Is the van the wheeled house in the hint?)
(In that case, is the complete hint...)
This is the only wheeled house.
("The House of Dolls, underneath is gold"?)
I don't see anything.
(However)
No?
Is there another wheeled house...
(Is there another wheeled house?)
- other than House of Dolls? - "A wheeled house".
Gosh.
(Jae Suk and So Min combine the hints.)
Jimmy. "House underneath is".
- I know. Jimi. - Jimi.
Is it underneath my house?
(Is the gold underneath Jae Suk's House?)
(After a few words, he runs to his house.)
My room. Jimi Yu.
(Is the gold hidden at Jimi Yu's House?)
Jimmy. "House underneath is".
What does it mean?
Jae Suk!
(Frozen)
What?
What? What is it?
(Exhaling)
- I am so shocked. - Why?
Jimi?
- And? "House underneath is"? - Jimi Yu.
Yes.
Jimi Yu's House.
If you take out Yu...
It's "Jimmy's House, underneath is gold".
Who is Jimmy?
Jimmy Jib, underneath is gold.
"Jib" is a homonym for "House". Jimmy Jib, the camera.
Jimmy Jib, the camera.
(Jimmy Jib)
"Jib" is a homonym for "House". Jimmy Jib, the camera.
I became so shocked just now.
(Goosebumps)
All the houses aren't the same.
('House" that is different from other houses.)
It must be somewhere else.
"When up high, check down below."
(When up high, check down below.)
(It always looks down from a higher place.)
"When up high, check down below."
"I'm always watching you."
(I'm watching you.)
(It always watches the members.)
Is it watching us?
I found a hint.
(They didn't recognize the details of the Jimmy Jib.)
There are lines.
What is this?
(The members were filmed using the Jimmy Jib.)
It's looking down from a higher place.
Bo Pil and So Min?
(It was actually a photo of the Jimmy Jib.)
It could be among the members.
(Something that watches everything...)
- That's what I am saying. - Seriously.
(among the members)
- Jimi Yu. Jimmy Carter. Jimmy. - Is there another wheeled house...
(Its name sounds similar to Jimi,)
- other than House of Dolls? - "A wheeled house".
(and it's a wheeled house.)
Is there another one that is hidden somewhere?
I am 100 percent sure that the gold is moving.
(The reason why the gold could move)
(The 1st search)
I think the gold is moving.
(Then the Jimmy Jib moved for filming.)
(During the 2nd search, So Min's device went off.)
Mine is going off, right?
(It was right behind Jong Kook!)
I think the gold is moving.
Jimmy Jib, the camera.
(The gold is hidden at the Jimmy Jib.)
"Jib" is a homonym for "House". Jimmy Jib, the camera.
(Even as they iterated the hints,)
(they had no clue.)
I became so shocked just now.
(The gold is at the Jimmy Jib!)
It's the Jimmy Jib!
(Haha finds out too.)
- There must be something. - What?
(Everyone learned about the location around the same time.)
Hey!
(Jae Suk arrives 1st.)
(When up high, check down below. When it's big, have a close look.)
Under the Jimmy Jib.
Where is it?
(He found the jewelry box.)
(The 1st person to touch the gold will have it for oneself.)
"The resident who touches the box that has gold in it..."
"will have the gold to oneself."
- Did someone take it? - Who took it?
Isn't this the end?
(Did someone take the gold?)
(I will take it.)
- "I will take it." - "I will take it."
(Did someone...)
Who took it?
(among the members...)
Who is it?
Let me see the handwriting.
(took the gold?)
I think it's Jae Suk.
It isn't me.
Jong Kook was here earlier.
But I didn't find anything.
(Someone was quicker.)
- I can't believe it. - Someone took it.
(The gold disappeared.)
Someone found the gold already.
(Someone...)
(has the gold.)
- Really? - Let's go to the final location.
(And that person is putting on an act.)
I am getting goosebumps.
Who is it?
(Someone is fooling the members after taking the gold.)
For goodness' sake.
It's so scary.
- It isn't me. One of them took it. - That's right.
(But everyone's in denial.)
Someone is acting.
(Who's today's winner that snatched the gold first?)
It's so scary. Someone has the gold right now.
I wonder who took it.
(No one figured out the winner until the end.)
It's so scary. Someone is acting.
The gold rings were hidden...
at the Jimmy Jib.
(Today's answer is "Jimmy Jib".)
That's right.
The mottos in the houses pointed to the Jimmy Jib.
(I'm watching you, When it's big, have a close look.)
(When up high, check down below.)
Had you gathered all the DVDs, the letters would have made,
(They would've found DVD numbers 1 and 2 with a closer look.)
"Jimmy Jib, underneath is gold." But you didn't find the 1st 2 DVDs.
(That was close.)
- We found them at the end. - We found them at the end.
But someone found the gold first.
(But one person found out this faster than anyone.)
- Seriously. - I am impressed.
Who found it?
This member even left a note because he or she found it early.
(The person even found it really early that he even left a note.)
- That's incredible. - It's 1 of the 3.
- Who is it? - Who is it?
- Against our expectations, - Did this member find it fast?
(This person has a keener sense of reasoning and gut...)
this member found it fast.
(than what the staff members expected.)
I hope it's a member of our team.
This member found the gold before anyone else...
(Found the gold before anyone else and acted throughout the race)
and acted throughout the race.
"If your team finds the gold,"
(The winner's team will decide the candidates for the penalty.)
"you will get to pick two people to get a penalty."
"If one of the residents finds it,"
"the winner will pick two people from your team to get a penalty."
And acted throughout the race.
(Who's the winner?)
Congratulations, Kim Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook)
My goodness.
Congratulations, Kim Jong Kook.
(My goodness.)
(The winner of the day is Kim Jong Kook.)
- How did you find it? - How did Jong Kook do that?
(The first hint was given only to Suk Jin.)
"All the houses aren't the same."
A doghouse. There is a doghouse in the middle.
(Jong Kook ruled out the regular houses.)
"I'm always watching you."
(As he would with dumbbells, he pulled up his reasoning skills.)
"When up high, check down below." Hey, come here.
It's "I'm always watching you."
"I'm always watching you."
A camera.
(During the first search, he suspected the camera.)
It's always watching us.
"When up high, check down below."
(He didn't follow the mainstream and stuck to his own opinion.)
"I'm always watching you."
"When it's big, have a close look."
Isn't it the Jimmy Jib?
(Suddenly)
Where is the Jimmy Jib today? Is it here?
(He suspected Jimmy Jib as soon as the 3rd search started.)
"It's darker under the lamp."
(He blatantly decided to sit next to Jimmy Jib.)
I think it's the Jimmy Jib.
I will stand here.
There is no reason for the Jimmy Jib to be here.
Mine is going off, right?
"It's darker under the lamp."
(Then he began to search the Jimmy Jib.)
There it is.
(He found the gold during the early phase of his 3rd search.)
My goodness.
(He became flustered too.)
My goodness!
(He succeeded to acquire 3 gold rings.)
How did this happen?
(The bright color of the gold made him grin from ear to ear.)
Hold on. But...
A piece of paper.
(Then Jong Kook asked for a piece of paper.)
Hold on. They would recognize my handwriting.
(He used his left hand to fool the members.)
"I will take it." I won.
(Thus, he even left a taunting message.)
- Who is he? - Who is he?
(He went to different places and meddled with people's business.)
That tie... Is he a Republican?
You guys are so mean.
You gave them such a difficult hint.
(To them, "Jimmy Carter"...)
Aren't you going to tell Kwang Soo and Suk Jin?
Suk Jin and Kwang Soo need to make an effort.
Suk Jin likes having hopes.
(He kept quiet to give Suk Jin hope.)
Hope keeps him going, so I will give it to him.
- I made the right choice, right? - Suk Jin.
(He gave Suk Jin the happiness of hope.)
He is so annoying.
- He is so annoying. - He is so annoying.
The hints were "A wheeled house" and Jimmy Carter.
(It's time for the person who found out early to brag.)
I was like, "It's so easy."
My goodness.
(Here is the gold.)
Okay.
(The three men got friendship rings.)
My goodness.
- They got friendship rings. - That's too bad.
(They can't help but feel annoyed at the three of them.)
- The rings are shiny. - I am jealous.
Why couldn't you tell from all those hints?
(Acting annoying)
We couldn't tell.
You guys are so slow.
I knew it was the Jimmy Jib.
(Lee Kwang Soo, the person who searched the car)
- I knew it was over there. - For goodness' sake.
This is frustrating.
- We will reveal the penalty. - Okay.
(The penalty for the two people from the losing team)
The penalty of the day is making a video for Suk Jin's birthday.
(Create a video to celebrate Suk Jin's birthday)
Two members will film a fun video to Turbo's "Happy Birthday to You"...
(They'd need to produce a video celebrating Suk Jin's birthday...)
so that it's a minute and 30 seconds long.
- That's so much work. - After the episode airs,
(to Turbo's birthday song.)
it will be revealed on Running Man's social media.
(The video will be released right after the program is aired.)
- On Running Man's social media? - It's so much work.
You have to come up with an idea too.
(It'll be a hassle to create a video for someone...)
- It should go... - It's so much work.
(who they don't even wish to congratulate that much.)
to someone who finds it annoying.
- I want Haha to do it. - I think Ji Hyo should do it.
(Haha and Ji Hyo each get a vote.)
Haha.
- I am okay with it. - We should see her dance.
(It has been a while.)
It would be funny if Ji Hyo does it.
(He grasps the opportunity and corners Ji Hyo.)
Ji Hyo would be a good choice.
- But I don't have an idea. - Do you want to do it or not?
I wouldn't mind it.
Then let's have Ji Hyo do it.
Haha, do you want to do it or not?
(Quickly)
I don't want to do it.
Let's have one who wants to do it and one who doesn't.
(He is at least as smart as Solomon.)
That's a good idea.
- Besides, - The two of you.
(Haha will represent people who don't want to do it.)
it will be convenient since you live in the same neighborhood.
(The Mapo Siblings will get the penalty.)
We made our choice. Haha and Ji Hyo.
Okay.
- Okay. - I don't know how to do it.
(They're already getting too lazy to do it.)
I can't wait to see it.
I don't have any ideas.
(After everyone went home...)
Ji Hyo, let's film it here.
(The two have no intentions of celebrating sincerely.)
Music, cue.
(They start filming at a strange angle.)
(Is this how a person who's celebrating supposed to look like?)
(She walks over...)
(and stares into the distance in this strange video.)
(The video will be uploaded...)
(on the official Running Man social media and YouTube.)
We did it.
Come and greet me.
(Evil spirits are rampant in the Running Dynasty.)
What is this cauldron for?
I finally have a body.
(The people are suffering because of the evil spirits.)
Your Majesty, evil spirits are rampant outside the city.
(Why is Yang Se Chan the king?)
If I find money, I will end you.
Make them kneel.
(Due to the tyranny of a king and treacherous subjects,)
- Yes, Your Majesty. - Stand still.
Do you know your sin?
I feel so victimized.
(the nation is in a bad state.)
We should forget about it since today is a good day.
- "Joseon Exorcist". - Exorcist.
(Jang Dong Yoon, Keum Sae Rok)
Don't exorcists get rid of ghosts?
(Park Sung Hoon, and Kim Dong Jun)
- Why else would you have a mole? - I didn't do it.
(Then, evil spirits enter the palace.)
- It isn't me! - Do you know your sin?
- An evil spirit. - Evil spirits have a mission.
(The evil spirits who want to take over the country...)
- Jong Kook! - Where are you?
Run away! What should I do? I am so nervous.
(go against the ones who want to save the country.)
Some are born as evil spirits.
- There! - Finish it.
(What will become of the Running Dynasty?)
(Records of the Running Dynasty, the Appearance of the Evil Spirits)