(On a beach in Ganghwa Island
where the breeze is still cold)
- This way?
- Are we going this way?
- Is there something in there?
- Why are we going in there?
Hello.
- What?
- Come on in.
- I'm nervous.
- What's all this?
(What is this?)
"In Suyu-dong..."
"With his whimsical charm..."
- "The grand award..."
- It's Jae Suk.
(He has won the grand award
15 times.)
(His whimsical charm
and positive attitude)
(He claims that's
when he had his first kiss.)
(He was the youngest comedian
who debuted through open recruit.)
(He started to become popular with
his character as a grasshopper.)
(It started with the 2005
KBS Entertainment Awards.)
(2005 KBS Entertainment Awards,
2006 MBC Entertainment Awards)
(2007 MBC Entertainment Awards,
2008 SBS Entertainment Awards)
(2009 SBS Entertainment Awards,
2009 MBC Entertainment Awards)
(2010 MBC Entertainment Awards,
2011 SBS Entertainment Awards)
(2012 SBS Entertainment Awards,
2014 KBS Entertainment Awards)
(2014 MBC Entertainment Awards,
2015 SBS Entertainment Awards)
(2016 MBC Entertainment Awards,
2019 SBS Entertainment Awards)
(2020 MBC Entertainment Awards)
(Yoo Jae Suk is an award collector
who won the grand award 15 times.)
There's Jong Kook.
Why are we doing this?
- That's Jong Kook.
- When did they...
Hey, what's all this?
(2020 SBS Entertainment Awards)
(His sweet voice and star quality)
(He shot to instant stardom
as soon as he debuted.)
(He won the grand awards
in three different Music Awards.)
(And in 2020, he won the grand award
in SBS Entertainment Awards.)
(Kim Jong Kook is the latest
grand award winner.)
Congratulations.
(This is a memorial hall for
the two grand award winners.)
- Hey, what's all this?
- Hello.
- What's this?
- Hey, I was born...
- What is this?
- I was born in Yongsan.
- What's going on?
- What is this?
- Is it a biography?
- A biography?
- Where should I look at?
It says "He was born
in Suyu-dong, Gangbuk-gu."
This is a museum.
- What is this?
- What's going on?
This is... My gosh.
- And what is this?
- He's not Admiral Yi Sun Sin.
- What's all this?
- What are we doing?
This should be in front
of a statue like that.
Gosh, the people who didn't win
the grand award are getting upset.
- This is...
- What are you doing?
It's not like I was born here.
Is it about his biography?
"He claims that's when
he had his first kiss."
- He claims?
- What are you doing?
- Did he claim that?
- Why did you add that?
My gosh.
I was born in Yongsan.
I'm from Seoul.
Just let it slide.
- It's a good day.
- What's all this?
- What is this?
- Why?
- I'm wearing it because I'm cold.
- What's with this?
What's that jacket?
- What about it?
- It's like a flower garden.
- It's...
- What's that?
(Is this too much?)
Still, it's cool.
I think I should take this off.
By the way, Suk Jin...
- Why?
- Why are you taking it off?
- Suk Jin.
- I was just about to start.
I didn't get to say anything.
- Because...
- I was about to start.
This is what I'm supposed to wear.
This cardigan belongs to my aunt.
Se Chan, weren't you wearing
this shirt earlier today?
I knew it. Someone stole my shirt.
Suk Jin!
I couldn't wear it.
Suk Jin, this is Se Chan's.
- You can't wear that.
- Hey.
- That's not true.
- It's mine.
After his stylist, Ha Na
who got paid per case quit,
- he got a new stylist.
- I know.
Stop talking about
the "per case" thing.
- Why?
- I'm not the one who paid her.
- Still...
- Oh, it was your agency?
We have a member
who gets paid that way.
He gets paid by the hour.
- By the hour?
- Hey.
- Is that you?
- He gets paid by case?
- This is crazy.
- By case.
Right. Suk Jin gets paid
by the hour.
- By the hour.
- That's right.
Anyway, I believe
Ha Na will be doing well...
- because she's talented.
- Sure.
She's not the type to boast.
He forgot about her already.
- Who?
- He forgot about Ha Na.
How would I forget Ha Na?
- You had Min Hee before.
- Do you remember Min Hee?
- Min Hee.
- Sure.
- Suk Jin is...
- When you met her before,
she said hello to you,
and you made a bow to her.
(He treated her like a stranger
after working with her for 5 years.)
- She worked for him for five years.
- That's impossible.
- After five years...
- That can't be right.
He's lying.
- That's ridiculous.
- That's absurd.
That sounds just like Suk Jin.
Yesterday, Suk Jin was...
I guess he's made up his mind.
He wants to remember the names
of our crew members.
- Seriously?
- Right. He kept asking me.
"Hey, what's his name?"
So I was like...
His name was Sun Myung,
but I said Sin Myung.
- And he tried to remember the name.
- That sounds exciting.
And I told him
his family name is Namkoong.
- I was...
- Is he Namkoong Sun Myung?
I asked Se Chan about
a crew member's name.
She was a woman, but he said
her name is Ko Chul Bong.
Her name is Bong Pal.
He asked what her job was.
- So...
- No one tells him the real names.
He asked me about her job,
so I said she made window frames.
- "She makes window frames?"
- All of a sudden, Suk Jin...
Window frames?
So you guys, don't be surprised...
if Suk Jin calls you by
a weird name.
- We will...
- Ko Chul Bong.
Hey, Bong Pal.
I asked, "Is she
a writer or a director?"
And he said "She's
in charge of the jimmy jib."
I said things like, "She makes
window frames. She drives a truck."
- A truck?
- He's so mean.
This is the only variety show
that has...
two Grand Award winners.
- Right.
- That's cool.
So we'll have a special episode for
Yoo Grand Award and Kim Grand Award.
It will start
in their memorial hall.
- Their memorial hall?
- This is a memorial hall.
It's not a memorial hall. My gosh.
These two are very shy
when we do stuff like this.
I hate stuff like this.
- Gosh, I really hate this.
- A memorial hall?
- What's all this?
- A memorial hall.
I'm no match for him though.
I just won the award once.
Jong Kook is another
grand award winner.
So today...
They are the pride, the core,
and the heart of Running Man.
With these two grand award winners,
we will have
the Dignity of the Grand Award Race.
- Finally.
- We have two hearts.
- This is...
- We're finally doing this.
First, Jong Kook and I feel
uncomfortable about stuff like this.
- He looks very shy.
- I'm feeling uncomfortable.
As you probably noticed,
Jae Suk is the captain
of Team Yoo Grand Award.
And Jong Kook is the captain
of Team Kim Grand Award.
So there will be teams.
The rest of the members will...
choose a captain they want
before each mission.
I feel uncomfortable already.
Do we get to pick the captains?
You should never sulk.
Then...
Gosh, Jong Kook.
There will be missions...
where the number of
team members won't matter.
So it's okay even if
one team has more members.
Oh, really?
You can just pick whichever team
you want.
Can we pick teams
after hearing about the game?
No, you can't.
Why not?
- It won't be easy.
- The members...
of the winning team...
will get double the number
of members in points.
But if you lose,
you will lose the exact
number of members in points.
So the member with the highest
score will be the winner.
And the two members
with the lowest scores...
and one member picked by them
will get a penalty.
- Really?
- Is it picked?
But the member with
the highest score is exempt.
Now I want the two captains
to sign a written oath...
that says they will never get mad...
- no matter what.
- That's good.
I'm telling you. I won't be mad.
You can't control my feelings.
So you can just pick
a team you want comfortably.
- Bring the written oath.
- Let them sign.
- All right.
- Even after the shoot.
I don't think
I need many team members.
Exactly. You don't need many.
I've never seen a contract like
this before. You shall never sulk.
I won't sulk.
We've been together for a long time.
You should never glower at me.
- I should read this carefully.
- What is the addition for?
The other members can add conditions
that they want.
You can't say, "Okay. I get it."
It's forbidden.
- "Okay. I get it."
"Okay. I get it."
Don't stare at us
for over two seconds straight.
- You can't say our full names.
- Don't call our names.
You can't whisper to others
while looking at my face.
(You can't whisper to others
while looking at my face.)
You can't stare at us
for over three seconds.
- That's good.
- Don't glower at us.
Don't stare at me with snake eyes.
Okay. That's good.
Hang on. You can't do that.
Look at that.
- Snake eyes.
- You can't do that.
- Don't glower at us like that.
- I won't do that.
I can stare at you
because I like you.
- You stare at us like this.
- You can't do that today.
They are not exactly
"the apple of my eye".
To get a star...
- You don't have to read that.
- He's changing the conditions.
Jae Suk won't let
things like this slide.
- He's changing it.
- Isn't it that you should...
- talk to your attorney?
- I check contracts thoroughly.
You're amazing.
"I can't pick the stars
for our members..."
"who are like the apple of my eye."
"Even though I can't do that,
I do care about them."
"Whatever decision they make,
I won't be mad..."
"Or resent them."
It depends.
Hey.
He can't change
everything like that.
I didn't change a lot.
What's this? "As much as possible."
- Just sign it.
- "For the members..."
I can see their characters.
He checks everything thoroughly...
while Jong Kook just signed it.
"I respect their opinions."
- All right. It's done.
- Don't say my full name.
- Not the full name.
- Read it for us.
I wrote it down. "I won't stare at
the members for over three seconds."
"I won't say, 'Okay, I get it.'"
(Don't stare at them for over 3
seconds and say "Okay, I get it.")
- I got goosebumps.
- You startled me.
That sounds so natural.
That's the tone of your voice.
- Se Chan, give this to them.
- Okay.
All right.
Like I said before,
you can pick the captain
of your team today.
The two captains will wait
in their own rooms.
The rest of the members will
go to their rooms in turn...
- Okay. Let's do that.
- This is Jae Suk's room.
- And this is Jong Kook's room.
- All right.
- "Okay, I get it."
- "Oh, Yang Se Chan."
- "Oh, Haha."
- "Oh, Lee Kwang Soo."
- "Suk Jin, I get it."
It's not like today is our last day.
- Hey, we have to add this.
- Write this down.
"It's not like
today is our last day."
- Write it down.
- We have to write it down.
Gosh, it's suffocating already.
Honestly, I'm not acting cool.
(The grand award winners are
waiting for the members to come.)
I think two will be
more than enough.
If no one comes, can I play alone?
My gosh.
(Someone has to come, right?)
Gosh. It's possible
that no one shows up.
I should brace myself for that.
(Whom will the members pick?)
Gosh, this is...
(Kim Grand Award's Room)
It's cold today. Where should I go?
Should I go into the room?
There's something I heard.
Today, the penalty will
be very harsh.
And the two losers get to pick
a person for the penalty.
Unless you win the game,
you might get the penalty.
- If you don't win...
- We should do this right.
We have to win no matter what.
- We have to win.
- I should be on the winning team.
We don't even know what it is.
Can you tell us what we're doing?
It's like a choice
between brain and brawn.
Jong Kook is smart too.
What? Are you saying
Jong Kook is dumb?
- Okay.
- You can't say that.
- Are you saying Jong Kook is dumb?
- Haha!
We can't do this to each other.
I'll go. I've made up my mind.
- Okay. You go on ahead.
- Hang on.
(So Min picks her team
while everyone's hesitating.)
I think...
one of them will get more members.
This is hard to choose.
(Will So Min pick the snake,
Kim Grand Award who holds grudges?)
(What's So Min's choice?)
You should appreciate this. Look.
- Are you choosing me?
- As soon as I got in here...
- You're still out of breath, right?
- My gosh.
You picked me right away.
- I know. I came right away.
- Okay. Good.
Jong Kook, I got in here
even before the cameras were ready.
- That's great.
- It was quick.
You should remember that.
Today, I'll be nice.
I thought you were
dressed too lightly.
I'll keep you warm.
You know what I mean.
- I was worried about you.
- Jong Kook.
I got here even before you sat down.
- How did you come in so quickly?
- I didn't even hesitate.
That's amazing.
What's with you, So Min?
They were still talking.
- Suk Jin even said this.
- What did he say?
Look at the sky
The white snow is falling
(Se Chan picked Jong Kook too.)
Se Chan.
Good. Okay.
Okay. This is nice.
I came here without hesitation.
You were later than So Min, but...
- I came right after her.
- Okay.
This is enough for me.
I don't need more.
Hang on.
I see a silhouette.
- Hey.
- My gosh.
Hang on.
This isn't bad. It's 4 to 4.
- Song Jeoktoma.
- Ji Hyo, this is...
This is enough. We're ready.
We don't need useless members.
I don't need the tall one.
(Unlike Kim Grand Award's room...)
Two would be more than enough.
I don't know
what games we're playing though.
Ji Hyo and Se Chan.
That would be perfect.
I just need Ji Hyo and Se Chan.
They are very smart.
- And I...
- We all are wearing white socks.
- We're a team.
- Next is...
- What's happening there?
- It's all white.
This is crazy.
Gosh, it's hard to choose.
It won't be physical
from the beginning.
(It won't be physical
from the beginning, right?)
- Are you alone in here?
- Gosh.
(Haha is here.)
You must've been so lonely.
You...
What's that?
Why don't you look grateful?
- Gosh, I should go.
- Haha, come back here. Haha.
They're having a party over there.
Come here, Haha.
I don't need many members.
I want only two.
It will be hard
to have a lot of members.
(He's just saying that
knowing he won't get many members.)
It's hard to have many members.
- Jae Suk.
- Hey.
You picked a captain
whom you can be comfortable with.
He's here.
- I'm here.
- You want to be at ease.
- My gosh.
- Hey, Jae Suk.
This isn't so bad.
Sure. This is good enough.
- I really like my team.
- This is really good.
I can control these guys.
I guess Haha went to the other team.
- Haha is...
- He didn't come.
He's...
Is he using me? Is it just business?
- I think so.
- Exactly.
So this is what Haha did.
I'm realizing it today.
I think he's using your
generous and cool personality.
Exactly. He uses me.
(He's turning into a poisonous snake
from Haha's betrayal.)
He uses me to attract investors.
I get it. Okay.
(Suk Jin also picks Jong Kook.)
All right.
(He greets Suk Jin with a bright
smile as if he wasn't mad at all.)
Did they go to the other room?
Gosh. What are you doing here?
I want to win the race.
- Right. He is...
- He's realistic.
I heard there will be
a harsh penalty today.
Suk Jin doesn't want
Jae Suk to be his captain.
That's not true. It's not like that.
That's not why.
- I had to come here.
- Sure. That's a good choice.
I never imagined...
But if we lose the first game,
I'll move to the other team.
We can't lose with so many members.
- Were you the last one to go?
- I was the last one.
I was talking about Haha.
- Haha picked the other team.
- Haha is...
Suk Jin, don't you agree?
- Jong Kook.
- I think...
- he's been using me.
- He's using you.
- He's using me for business.
- Right.
I can't deny it.
- I just realized it today.
- Jong Kook is...
- This isn't what you shouldn't do.
- That's why you signed the oath.
- I know, but...
- Don't be mad.
- I'm not mad.
But I just can't help it.
Suk Jin is done making his choice.
- Really? He went there?
- Seriously?
Good.
- We are the elite members.
- I see.
We are the elite members.
- You could've been really lonely.
- We are the best ones.
Gosh, Jong Kook will be...
We're the best members.
I have to do a TV show
with him this week.
Why?
Things are becoming clear now.
This is just perfect.
- This is the first mission.
- What is it?
I just hope
it's not something physical.
- Nothing physical.
- The first mission is...
one of the things that shows
the dignity of grand award winners.
It requires power, agility,
- Power?
- and craftiness.
It's called Two-body Hide-and-seek.
- What?
- Hide-and-seek?
Two-body?
The team members
except the captains...
can hide in any place you want
within this pension complex.
And the two captains will be...
connected to each other with a rope.
And they will look for the members
of their opposing teams.
As soon as you find a member,
the member is out right away.
(The two taggers should find
the members hiding in the pension.)
There will be only one round.
The tagger who finds out
all the members first will win.
They will be connected with a rope?
- So it's about strength.
- This is...
- He will be dragged along.
- This isn't right.
It's about strength
from the beginning.
We can't do this from the beginning.
I chose Jae Suk because I thought
it wouldn't be about strength.
We will be connected with a rope?
That's good for us.
Sure. I can drag Jae Suk around.
Jong Kook can drag him around.
We're going to win.
- We will definitely win.
- We will.
- It's between me and Jae Suk.
- Right.
- I can drag him around.
- You should drag him around.
Hey, we have an advantage though.
Even if we lose,
we don't lose
as many points as they do.
If we lose, will we lose six points?
No, only three points.
- Three points?
- See?
- That's what I mean.
- You like mud.
- Can you stay under the mud?
- Hey.
- I don't like mud.
- You do.
- Who would want to be in the mud?
- He's crazy about mud.
Stay under the mud.
You'll never get caught.
Hey, if you go into the mud today,
your feet will freeze.
- Hey.
- I shouldn't have heard that.
- That makes me want to do it.
- Hang on.
We will lose only three points.
So let's just think
we will lose the first game.
We should be strategic.
I don't want to lose the first game.
- I'll win no matter what.
- I'm just saying...
it's okay to lose.
It's only three points.
Don't try too hard.
You know what I mean.
- I want to try hard.
- Just enjoy.
I just realized...
that you're not popular.
I know.
He would've been in trouble
if I didn't come.
He was sitting all alone here.
If you and I didn't choose Jae Suk,
he would've been dragged
around the whole time.
- No need to play the game.
- Guys.
Like I said, you guys
should hide well.
- Okay?
- Yes.
So we should hide.
- We can win.
- We should hide well.
We can disguise and everything.
Just stay in a place
where we can't see you.
Please change into team uniforms.
- Okay.
- All right.
I'm sure we will win.
Our chances of winning
are like 80 percent.
(Kim Grand Award, Yoo Grand Award)
- What's this?
- It's pink.
This is...
Jong Kook's face looks big
on Jong Kook.
- But this looks small.
- It looks small.
There aren't many places
where we can hide.
It will be annoying
to have to search each car.
I think Jong Kook will stop me
from checking the cars.
Exactly.
I'm sure he will do that.
If they all hide in the cars,
and you can't go to the parking lot,
we will lose.
That's right.
- They're doing it already.
- Why did you choose me?
What are you talking about?
Why would you say that?
I mean, you guys
should do a good job. Okay?
(What's he saying?)
You're the one
who will look for them.
I know. I'll find them.
Why would you say that
folding your arms like that?
- You already gave up.
- I didn't give up.
I'm telling you, let's just relax.
I really want to win
in a situation like this.
(Unlike the captain, the team
members are very passionate.)
You should take off the flippers.
What? What flippers?
- What flippers?
- Hey.
- Your feet are huge.
No.
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Do we not have any plans?
- Try your best.
- You...
I'll try my best. And you know,
I have no strategy.
I'll just go see what happens.
I'll fight against the world.
Hey.
Things always don't go as planned.
I just fight against them.
You should at least fight.
So...
- You are on your own.
- Don't get beat up.
You know what I mean.
- It's an old saying.
- We should take care...
Exactly. Okay?
- Okay.
- Make sure to survive.
Jae Suk, regency
by the queen mother.
Okay.
A fresh breeze and a bright moon.
It's a fresh wind and a bright moon.
- A fresh wind and a bright moon.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk leaves
after correcting his team members.)
Gosh, I picked the wrong team.
Darn it. I'm doomed.
- You won't be here next time.
- Of course not.
Anyway, you will...
- Don't let him open it.
- Okay.
Jong Kook, so...
- It's not like...
- You're right.
- I will...
- I'll stop him from coming here.
We will hide in the closet
or something.
That's right. You should.
That's what you should do.
Okay.
(Kim Grand Award will drag
Jae Suk somewhere else.)
- Hey.
- Excuse me.
Let me tell you something.
- You can't do things by force.
- Jae Suk,
I don't do that.
But if that's...
what the directors want,
I have to try my best.
I'm not telling you
not to try your best.
- I have to work hard anyway.
- Just don't be...
- so rough.
- So what do you think?
- If that's what the directors...
- It's not like that.
- We should follow them.
- That's not true.
You're wearing a black outfit today.
You look like a wild animal.
A wild animal?
I'm just trying to make things go...
as the directors planned.
It's not like...
You may start hiding.
- Got it. Okay.
- You may hide now.
We have only three minutes.
- Is that enough for us to hide?
- Three minutes.
(While the 2 leaders are covering
their eyes and ears,)
(Se Chan is looking
for a place to hide.)
The beacon does not shine
on its own base.
(Ji Hyo is looking around nervously
for a while.)
The beacon does not shine
on its own base.
What? Se Chan is there.
There's no way they come in here.
(All 5 of them except for Kwang Soo
have hidden themselves.)
I'm running out of time.
(Meanwhile, the bare-footed
Kwang Soo hasn't hidden yet.)
(Running at full speed)
(Kwang Soo is running somewhere
hastily.)
10, 9, 8...
(I have only 10 seconds left?)
(The man who goes crazy
whenever he sees a mudflat)
(He's running
straight to the mudflat.)
I really want to win.
(The mudflat lover is running
on the mudflat barefoot to win.)
I'll risk my life to win this.
(Flapping)
(After scaring the seagulls away,
he's hiding behind rocks.)
(Lee Kwang Soo, can't help
going into a mudflat)
He'll never be able to find me.
Go.
(Talking to the drone)
Go away!
Get lost!
2, 1. Go!
(Will he not get caught?)
Let's go.
- Can I take this off?
- Yes.
- Let's go and find them.
- Let's go.
Wait. Your side...
Oh, is that your team's house?
This one is mine, right?
- This is your team's house.
- Correct.
Then I can just stop him
from coming into our house.
(Jong Kook's plan is to keep
Jae Suk away from his house.)
(Grabbing)
- Gosh. We won't go in there.
- All right.
- We'll go to mine too.
- Let's go to yours first.
- Let's check yours first.
- Let's do it the other way around.
- Yours is closer. Let's go.
- Let's go to your house first.
Let's go in.
- Come back here. It might snap.
- Come here.
- Come here now!
- Hey.
I said, come back here.
- This rope might snap, you punk!
- Come here.
It won't snap. Just come in.
Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
- Come here already.
- You can't do this. It's not fair.
- Gosh. Hey, Bo Pil!
- Stop it. Come over here.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Come on in. Take off your shoes.
- This is driving me nuts.
- Let's compromise with each other.
- Why are you doing this?
- Like I said,
we should create a situation
that our staff wants.
Gosh, seriously.
- That's how things work. What?
- Hey, they both left.
What do you mean?
Did they go out of here?
We don't have time for this.
We have to go around outside.
(At that moment!)
(Someone is lying in the bed!)
(The bulging shape on the bed...)
(made Jong Kook smile happily.)
(Flapping)
(I found someone.)
- What?
- Who is that?
Hold on.
(He just has to call the person's
name to eliminate him or her.)
(Unexpectedly, it turns out
to be Suk Jin.)
- Why...
- Why are you here?
(Why is he here when he promised
to hide in Kim Grand Award's room?)
- Hey. Hey!
- Suk Jin? What's going on?
You should've stopped him
from removing the blanket!
(Suk Jin? What's going on?)
(Suk Jin's strategy was
unbelievably clumsy.)
- What is he doing here?
- I mean...
- What's wrong with you?
- What is this?
- You're supposed to be in my room.
- Listen, Jong Kook.
That's not the point here.
Why are you here?
Why is he here?
- You're supposed to be in my room.
- It's a trick, you know.
Why would you keep it to yourself?
- You should've told me.
- I'm speechless.
- I can't believe him.
- Hey, remember what you said?
Obviously, I thought there would be
only the other team members here.
You should've stopped him
from lifting the blanket.
I was lying on the bed confidently.
- What's wrong with him?
- Exactly.
You should've stayed
at my house. Why did you come here?
This is driving me crazy.
- Why were you hiding here?
- You're driving me crazy.
- I'm speechless.
- Go away! Go!
I can't believe this. Hey!
- Be honest with me. Why here?
- Am I out?
Of course, you're out.
Did he do it on purpose?
- Is he a spy or something?
- Why would he do that?
Did he try to help me?
Is he a spy or what?
I'm not a spy. I wasn't trying to
help the other team.
But why...
Why did you try to help me?
(Someone started laughing
under the blankets.)
- But can you really hide here?
- Hey, go out and hide.
I'll lie down here.
Where?
(Haha hid himself
between the blankets.)
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Haha, it's not noticeable.
- Right?
(So Haha hid perfectly
between the blankets.)
- I didn't know you'd help me out.
- Don't come between us.
- Why would you come between us?
- My gosh.
I'm pretty sure that someone is
hiding in this room.
I told you both of my team members
went out of the house.
(Jong Kook started searching
following his hunch.)
Wait.
(He's looking at the blankets.)
(Will Haha be eliminated?)
Of course, you can do that.
Anyway, thank you, Suk Jin.
- Why was he hiding in that room?
- Exactly.
Thank goodness.
He didn't find me.
(Haha didn't get caught
thanks to Suk Jin.)
(Jae Suk found a pile of clothes
that looks suspicious.)
Someone is hiding here.
There must be someone here.
(I'm 100 percent sure!)
I'm sure there is.
(The hibernating frog
of Team Kim Grand Award)
(Why did you come out of there?)
- I found So Min.
- Hey!
Why are you all...
- Why are you all here?
- Hey.
- Is this a prank?
- It's odd. Hey.
- This is driving me nuts.
- Why would they help me?
Hey, So Min!
- That's not the case.
- I mean...
Why did you come to this house,
Jong Kook?
- Hey.
- Why were you hiding in this house?
- I didn't...
- Why did you want to come here?
- It's because this is your house.
- But why...
(It's because this is your house!)
- I came to find your team members.
- But we found your team members.
- This can't be happening.
Jong Kook, hurry up
and find his team members.
- This is ridiculous.
- We must win the first game.
- How did this happen?
- Hang on. Then...
This doesn't make any sense.
What's going on?
It's a bit strange.
I think it's a conspiracy.
- Right?
- It's a conspiracy.
- I mean, why would they do that?
- Your team members...
I'm pretty sure that the tall one...
Wait, Jae Suk. I'm sure
the tall one is around here.
Seagulls are flying in the sky.
(Hiding between rocks)
Seeing that those migratory birds
are flying away,
I think that winter is finally over.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you all did a great job this winter.
I mean, the entire year.
(Wink)
Somewhere on the mudflat
between rocks,
Kwang Soo is hiding.
Kwang Soo, don't cross the river.
(Kwang Soo, don't cross
the mudflat.)
That is your house.
That's right. This one isn't mine.
(Striding)
- Gosh.
- Come over here.
- What are you doing?
- Let's take a look around here.
We should search outside.
It must be hard for the tall one
to hide.
Wait. I think...
- I think someone's here.
- They're the sound team.
Nam Joong is here too.
- Why is Nam Joong here?
- Why is he here?
(The assistant director is putting
his hands together awkwardly.)
(Someone's here!)
I'm not feeling well.
- No. He's on my team.
- It's Se Chan.
(He's been arrested for showing
his gums too often.)
(Another member of my team?)
(It's Se Chan.)
Hey, you punk!
Why didn't you stay inside?
(All of his team members are
outside his house.)
Hey, why are you helping me?
Why did you come here?
- Why are you helping me?
- I don't understand.
Why did you come here? Why?
Have you noticed
that they were acting so awkwardly?
I told you guys to act naturally!
- You were all looking so awkward.
- I noticed...
that something was weird about
the staff members sitting here.
I get that, but why were you
hiding out here?
What's wrong with you all?
You could have just stayed
inside the house!
Why did all of you come out?
What's wrong with you?
I was afraid you two might
come into the house.
All you guys had to do
was stay inside the house.
- Hey, by the way...
- I mean, why...
Why are you helping me?
This doesn't make any sense.
I was going to
go in a different direction.
This makes no sense.
(We're in trouble.)
Jong Kook is already upset.
The tone of his voice...
(He could tell how upset Jong Kook
was by his tone.)
He's definitely upset.
Why didn't they stay inside?
I didn't go there to protect them.
(His anger grows as time goes by.)
I just don't understand.
They could've stayed in the house.
(And his back muscles got pumped
because of his anger.)
My gosh. Those punks...
You know...
Why would they...
(Kicking)
- Hey, don't kick it.
- I don't understand.
- What if someone is under there?
- What? Hold on.
(What? Hold on.)
(After the furious kick,
he looked at the blankets again.)
(Will Haha avoid getting caught
this time as well?)
Wait.
(He got caught this time.)
(He couldn't avoid
getting caught twice.)
- Oh, my. Look at him.
- That was perfect.
It was perfect.
- How did you know I was here?
- Indeed.
I heard you guys leaving earlier.
Who covered you with the blankets?
There must've been someone
who covered him.
Gosh. Why was he hiding in there?
I just have to find Ji Hyo now.
That tall punk.
- Gosh, Ji Hyo.
- That tall punk...
Ji Hyo!
Wait.
I think it's likely
that the tall one...
is hiding on the mudflat.
- That tall punk.
- Ji Hyo.
(Kwang Soo has been weathered
and aged hiding between the rocks.)
(Kim Grand Award is heading toward
the mudflat to find Kwang Soo.)
I think he's over there.
(But right behind them,)
(Ji Hyo is hiding!)
(Please don't look back.)
Where is he?
(Ji Hyo is in the visible range.)
- He must be somewhere around here.
- What?
(At that moment,
Jae Suk looked back.)
(If Ji Hyo gets caught,
Team Yoo Grand Award will win.)
She's not here.
(But he didn't see her!)
I'm pretty sure that Kwang Soo is
somewhere around here.
(While looking around
to find Kwang Soo...)
(He found Ji Hyo!)
Where's Ji Hyo?
(As soon as he spotted Ji Hyo,
he took Jae Suk to another area.)
- Ji Hyo!
- Follow me.
Ji Hyo!
(I'm safe now.)
I should find Kwang Soo.
(Jong Kook wins if he finds
Kwang Soo avoiding Ji Hyo!)
He must be crouching down
in a corner.
I felt like my heart was
going to stop.
Where's Ji Hyo?
(Drone, quiet down!)
(Jong Kook can't go to the mudflat
because of Ji Hyo.)
Where is she?
(Yoo Grand Award is
desperately looking for Ji Hyo.)
- Where on earth is Ji Hyo?
- Gosh, that tall punk. Wait.
Gosh. Where is she hiding?
(Jong Kook is searching while
preventing him from finding Ji Hyo.)
- Let's find Ji Hyo.
- Where is he?
(At that moment!)
(He found a cameraman
filming someone on the mudflat.)
(Cameraman Yun Sang is filming
Ji Hyo from a distance.)
Wait.
(Something's fishy here.)
(Rushing)
(He started running
while Jong Kook was distracted.)
(There's someone down there.)
No, wait. Stop.
(If Ji Hyo gets caught,
Team Yoo Grand Award will win!)
Aren't you Ji Hyo?
(Aren't you Ji Hyo?)
(Found you.)
(All members of Team Kim Grand Award
are out.)
Why were you hiding
in a place like that?
Gosh, seriously.
- Team Yoo Grand Award wins!
- Oh, yes!
- Why were you hiding there?
- Jong Kook.
I saw Kwang Soo running
toward the ocean.
- What?
- Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, come out now!
Kwang Soo, we won!
Gosh, it's cold. It's so cold.
I'm so cold.
(He's shivering in cold without
hearing the news of victory.)
Oh, man. It's so cold.
I want to go home.
(It seems that the Prince of Asia
needs to be rescued urgently.)
Gosh.
(Waves are getting closer
to the shore.)
Oh, the tide is coming in.
(Cameraman Yun Sang is
coming to rescue the mudflat lover.)
- Kwang Soo, it's over.
- Yes?
- It's over?
- Yes.
We should get out of here now.
The tide is coming in.
- I didn't get caught, did I?
- No.
Oh, yes.
Did he actually go to the mudflat?
He went into the mudflat.
- What?
- He's unbelievable.
He's amazing.
He practically gave himself
a penalty.
Hey, did you say
he went into the mudflat?
Why did you go all the way there?
- What happened?
- We won.
We won? Yes! Okay!
I think that you guys
planned all this.
- That's not true.
- I think it was intentional.
- No. Don't be ridiculous.
- We tried to hide well.
I'm sure that you guys
conspired together.
- Never. Trust me.
- That's not true.
Go away! I'll be alone on my team.
- Don't forget that you signed...
- Go!
- the oath.
- You promised not to get mad.
- Go away!
- Come on, Jong Kook.
- Go!
- Show him the oath.
- He told us to leave.
- Give me the oath. This won't do.
Jong Kook is looking at the mudflat.
- He's looking at the mudflat.
- Jong Kook, please.
- He must be so cold.
- I'm so cold.
- Put this on.
Put on your jacket. Why did you...
- First of all,
- What's wrong with you?
- you should've set the boundaries.
- It's so cold.
- How could I find him?
- Put it on.
Move!
Besides, I told everyone...
that I wouldn't let Jae Suk
go into my house.
Keep your promise, Jong Kook.
- I don't need any of you.
- Actually...
- Take off your jackets.
- Don't be like this.
- I don't need you guys.
- Come on. Don't take it off.
- I can't do this anymore.
- Don't be like this.
What's the point of signing
the oath?
I was wrong.
- You...
- I didn't expect them to win.
Don't even think of joining my team.
I'll be alone.
- I can't believe her.
- She already moved to that team.
She moved to that team already?
Jong Kook, look at this.
And don't get the wrong idea.
I think she did this
to make us laugh.
But I thought it'd be helpful.
- Show him.
- What did you write on it?
She painted over his eyes, crossed
off "Kim", and wrote "Yu".
- I had no expectations from her.
- That's unbelievable.
When she came into my room
and buttered me up,
I felt that something was fishy
about her.
Team Kim Grand Award lost
five points,
and Team Yoo Grand Award earned
six points.
- Okay!
- Good job!
- You can turn the game around.
- Exactly.
I'll make my team lose
and choose one person.
I'll choose one of the members
who joined me in the first round.
- He can't seem to drop it.
- I'm serious.
- I've made my mind.
- Show him the oath now.
- I'm willing to get a penalty.
- Give me the oath.
- I'll receive a penalty.
- You signed this 30 minutes ago.
You, Mudflat!
I'll teach you a lesson.
- Me? Why?
- You irk me more than anyone else.
Why?
I'm going to choose you.
You irk me for no reason.
- Why?
- "For no reason".
- What do you mean by that?
- Keep up the good work.
You even went into the mudflat.
Why didn't you dive in the ocean?
- Why?
- You see,
- I searched with Jong Kook.
- I won't team up with you guys.
- I understand why he's upset.
- Of course.
As soon as we started searching,
he took me to my house.
And we saw Suk Jin
just lying in the bed.
- You call that hiding?
- He wasn't even hiding.
Did you faint?
- You should've made an effort.
- He was so halfhearted.
It wasn't like that. Listen.
Ji Hyo was just standing outside.
I was confidently telling you
that I was there.
It was your fault.
You shouldn't have taken the covers.
Why were you hiding in his house
not mine?
I clearly told you guys
that I wouldn't come into my house,
and that you should stay
in the house.
When did you tell us that?
What do you mean? I told you
that I wouldn't let Jae Suk...
go into my house
since we would be tied together!
Ji Hyo, are you okay?
That was scary.
Read the oath again.
- Why did you even sign it?
- There's no point.
What's the point of signing it?
- Here you go.
- I won't win the race.
"I, Kim Jong Kook, hereby assure
that I dearly love..."
(I, Kim Jong Kook, hereby assure
that I dearly love...)
(all the cast members to the point
that I'd pick the stars for them.)
(I promise not to get upset
even if they don't choose me.)
(I also promise to listen to
and respect their opinions.)
- Yes, I know.
- You signed here.
(Additional Terms: 1. No eye contact
that lasts longer than 3 seconds)
(2. No speaking
in a threatening tone)
- He broke his promises.
- You signed this.
- What's the point?
- He broke them so many times.
Let's drop it. That's enough.
It's time for the second mission.
Before we begin the second mission,
you will choose your team again.
We won the first round
despite the disadvantage.
- Absolutely.
- You're amazing, Yoo Grand Award.
We won eventually.
Shall we go to our rooms now?
The team leaders should go first.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Please put on a blindfold and leave
in the same order as before.
Why should we put on a blindfold?
I've already made up my mind.
I'll choose the same team.
Let's get some
good energy from him. Okay.
(Haha chose
Team Yoo Grand Award again.)
Hello, Yoo Grand Award.
- Oh, my. Welcome, my comrade.
- Oh, my.
Of course. I'm too scared
to join the other team.
My dear comrades.
The other team is so scary.
(Suk Jin's choice is...)
I should be loyal.
(He chose Team Kim Grand Award.)
- Let's do this!
- Suk Jin.
I'm a loyal man.
I decided to stick with you.
You said you'd leave my team
if we lost. Why did you come back?
We'll win this time for sure.
- But you should know...
- No, we won't.
that no one else will
join this team.
- Someone's coming.
- What?
Se Chan, I knew it.
(Here comes the man with a flower.)
Don't give him things like this.
- Please take this.
- Don't give me that.
Please trust me. You know it was
a good place to hide.
- Seriously...
- We don't need any more people.
The three of us would be enough.
Let's do this.
Jong Kook, I won't let you down
this time.
(Kim Grand Award's allies are
gathering one by one.)
Hey, Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo is here too.
(Ji Hyo apologizes on her knees.)
The same goes for her.
She should've hidden in the house.
- Let me explain.
- Why were you out on the path?
- I thought...
The beacon does not shine
on its own base.
That's ridiculous.
The cameraman was...
filming you sitting out there.
Exactly. Hey! Where is he?
That cameraman was so slow-witted.
Who was that?
- It was Yun Sang.
- Stop it.
You could just tell he was
filming someone.
It's okay. We can win this time.
What should I do?
What would be the best move?
(Meanwhile, only the 2
troublemakers are left.)
I can't think of a solution.
Next, please go.
What should I do? I'm off.
(So Min is leaving
with heavy steps.)
Why did Jong Kook get mad at me
when I wasn't on his team?
He yells at me regardless of
whether or not I'm on his team.
What does he want me to do?
Does he want me on his team or not?
Next, please go.
(Kwang Soo is the last one to go.)
I hope one more cast member of
our show wins the Grand Award.
My gosh.
(The person
who chose Jae Suk is...)
Who could that be?
Who is it?
- Oh, my.
Yoo Grand Award!
- You're just unbelievable.
- Yoo Grand Award!
- My gosh. She's...
- I've made up my mind.
- I know.
- Yes.
(And Kwang Soo chose...)
- What?
- Hello!
- Kwang Soo, you chose our team?
- Right.
(Glaring)
- Good.
- I always wanted to join this team.
- Kwang Soo is here.
- Why did you come here?
- I always wanted to join your team.
- Let's win this time.
- Hey.
- I'll make sure we'll win.
- You irk me most.
- Why?
You and So Min are
in the bottom two.
- Don't hate me.
- I will...
- receive a penalty today.
- Don't say that.
- Why will you get a penalty?
- All I'm thinking about is...
which of you two I should choose
to get the penalty with me.
- It'll be a segment of the show.
- I didn't have enough time.
- "A segment of the show"?
- Yes.
Who else joined the other team
other than Haha?
- So Min.
- So Min? That team is weak.
(Team Yoo Grand Award:
Haha, So Min)
(Team Kim Grand Award: Ji Hyo,
Se Chan, Kwang Soo, Suk Jin)
- Shall we go now?
- Everyone.
- Yes?
I'll explain the second mission.
The first game was too advantageous
for the other team.
- True.
- But fortunately,
- with the other team members' help,
- Yes.
we won.
- Stop bringing that up.
- Are you talking about me?
Don't mention it again.
- You see,
- I know I was wrong.
it helped me let go of my burdens,
so I think I can be more relaxed
throughout the shoot.
My gosh. He moved to the other team.
Gosh, that brat.
- So Min, you surprised me.
- But...
I didn't accept him fully
in my heart...
when he joined my team
in the previous round.
- You were ready to let him go.
- Exactly.
- That team wasn't right for me.
- I know.
Through the second mission,
we'll see how witty and smooth...
the two Grand Award winners are
as MCs.
It's Do As I Say.
- What is this?
- Do As I Say?
- What is it?
- It sounds difficult.
One member from each team
will play each round.
The players stand facing each other
with a bowl of water between them.
Okay.
When the MC calls out
a certain body part,
the players must touch it
with both hands.
When the MC says, "Bowl",
the one who grabs the bowl and pours
the water on the opponent wins.
The game requires agility.
What does the abilities of an MC
have to do with this game?
- It requires agility.
- I see.
I'm not good at games like this.
Jae Suk gets extremely nervous
whenever we play games like this.
- I'm not good at games like this.
- So Min is the worst.
Each of you has to play
several rounds.
And Haha, since you have
an injured back,
- please be an MC.
- Understood.
- Okay. We'll definitely win this.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook, just enjoy the victory.
- We'll win this for sure.
- I'm not expecting that.
- We'll definitely win this.
Jong Kook, don't be like that.
- Let's see how it goes.
- Don't be like that.
I have one simple question.
I want to know if Kim Grand Award
is upset right now.
(I want to know if Kim Grand Award
is upset right now.)
- No, I'm not.
- What?
- I'm very excited now.
- Of course.
- He says he's not upset.
- He's smiling.
- I smile all the time.
- He denied it.
- I smile all the time, you know.
- Your team members look...
- He's smiling right now.
- Okay. I accept that.
- Don't get the wrong idea.
- Exactly.
By the way,
why do the team members...
- comfort and encourage the leader?
- That's not true.
Isn't it usually
the other way around?
Well... I know.
So who'd like to compete first?
- First...
- How about Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo, set an example.
- Got it.
- Then...
- Jae Suk or So Min...
Okay.
- Jong Kook, you'll host the game.
- Me?
Kwang Soo, you have to do well...
if you want to get
on Jong Kook's good side.
- I'll win for sure.
- Got it.
- Let's do this.
- Touch the body part he names.
Grab the bowl only
when he yells the word "Bowl".
Okay.
Here we go.
(Both are tense.)
- Eyes.
- This isn't easy.
Nose.
Mouth. Knees.
Right toes.
Now, left toes.
Left toes, right toes.
Hold on a second.
(Gradually moving forward)
- What?
- Stop walking toward it.
- You were moving forward.
- This is wrong.
- Got it.
- That's wrong.
- Right toes.
- That's how he lived his life.
Left toes.
Left toes, right toes.
Top of the head.
Please stand back up.
- Please stand back up.
- He's close to calling it.
- Left chest.
Right chest.
Left chest.
- Jae Suk, lower your hands.
- Lower your hands!
- You...
- Lower your hands.
- Hey!
- Your hands were up too high.
- Your hands should be here.
- Don't be ridiculous!
- Lower your hands.
- That's absurd.
They should be down here.
- Right here.
- No way.
When you work out at the gym,
I bet you go like this.
No way. Hey!
Jae Suk.
Are you kidding me?
- Like this?
- Grab where your chest is at.
(His nipples can't fight gravity.)
- Seriously?
- Grab where your chest is at.
Got it.
(He lowers his hands a bit.)
- Left knee.
- All right.
Left knee, right knee.
Left toes.
Right toes.
Left heel.
He'll soon call it.
(It's about time
he calls for the bowl.)
Top of the head, bowl!
- What?
- Look.
I ducked.
(Kwang Soo grabbed the bowl.)
(But Jae Suk quickly ducked.)
I ducked.
(Yoo Grand Award outplays
Kwang Soo.)
- Kwang Soo wins.
- Nice!
- Okay!
- Good job.
- Nice.
- Only one bowl remains.
That was close.
The score is 1 to 0.
- Good.
- That was close.
Kwang Soo, you're doing good.
I didn't expect him
to say it without pausing.
All right.
Ears.
Eyes, nose, knees.
Left knee, right knee.
Right shoulder, left shoulder.
- You should stand up straight.
- Hey!
- Are you kidding me?
- I was just getting ready.
- Stop that.
- Got it.
- He doesn't take sides.
- Right chest.
(Right chest)
- Stand up straight.
- Lower your hands.
This is the spot.
This is the actual spot.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
It's already quite low.
- This is the spot.
- That's quite low.
- My nipple is here.
- Okay.
Head.
Stand up straight.
Head, shoulders, knees,
the buttocks, bowl!
(Jae Suk was faster this time.)
(He gets splashed in the face.)
(He's nimble with accurate aim.)
It's a tie now.
- The score is 1 to 1.
- Who's up next?
Okay. You did well.
- Then...
- Hold on.
Why am I against Suk Jin again?
I always seem to be up against him.
He sensed that So Min
would be up next,
so he volunteered.
- Jae Suk will host the game.
- Okay.
(The weakest members
go head to head.)
Sure.
Here we go.
I've been going up against
Suk Jin a lot lately.
(He slowly takes off his jacket.)
Bowl!
(Bowl!)
No, wait.
I was taking off my jacket.
(Splash!)
(He gets splashed while laughing.)
Why...
Nice one. We scored, right?
- That counts.
- No, it doesn't.
I was taking off my jacket.
How is this fair?
- That's not fair.
- But the game was on.
The game's supposed to be
between those two.
- That's 2 to 1.
- All right.
That's why...
- How is this fair?
- You should've called a time-out.
Why didn't you call a time-out?
And he's the one who got splashed.
- Why are you still dry?
- Suk Jin, what was that?
Why did you take off
your jacket at that moment?
Anyway, good job.
- Good job.
- Okay.
- Nice teamwork.
- Good job.
- Talk about good teamwork.
- Let's go.
- Unbelievable.
- Please take a step back.
Call a time-out if you need one.
(The unfair match
begins once again.)
- You need to overcome this.
- And go.
Pants.
(Pants!)
(Pants?)
Pants?
Yes, pants.
(Maybe he meant to say, "Bowl".)
- Wait.
- Don't be flustered...
and grab your pants.
Just grab your pants.
What would you have done
if I were wearing a skirt?
- A skirt?
- Unbelievable.
That's so annoying, you know.
All right.
Thankfully, they're both
wearing pants.
(Jae Suk hosts the game
just to entertain himself.)
All right.
(Everyone collects themselves
and the game restarts.)
Head.
- Shoulders.
- Ears.
Second toe.
Second toe?
Grab it with two hands.
- I like how he is detail-oriented.
- With both hands.
All right.
The right fifth toe.
Darn it.
(He grabs his toe.)
Mouth.
(Mouth!)
Mouth?
What the...
- What?
- After touching our toes?
- Jae Suk.
- What's wrong?
I can't believe
he made them touch their mouth.
I mean...
- After the toes...
- He's just being a menace.
- That was a good one.
- What was wrong with it?
- There are hygiene issues.
- That was a good one.
- Be careful with it then.
- The mouth after the toes?
Who cares, right?
Be careful with it.
- Why?
- You've got this.
But I won.
Let's move on to the next round.
- Should I go next?
- Sure.
- Haha, go ahead.
- Okay.
- Is Jae Suk playing?
- From this point on,
you'll play one round each.
- Se Chan will probably win.
- Here we go.
- Let's begin.
- Let's keep the winning streak.
Let's agree to this
being our basic pose.
- Okay.
- This will be our basic pose.
Good idea.
He can hinge at the hips well.
Look at how flexible he is.
- Check that out.
- Look.
- All right.
- It hurts.
Please shake hands.
- Sure.
- Good game.
High-five each other.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
- Play fair.
- The game will begin.
Applaud!
(Wow!)
- Massage each other's shoulders.
- Each other's?
Yes, each other's.
You're giving us useless orders.
Those are some weird orders.
I like the friendly vibes.
Please rub your forehead.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Now your eyebrows.
- Okay.
- And applaud.
- Applaud!
- Hike up your pants a little.
- Got it.
While eating kalguksu
with manila clams.
- Kalguksu.
- All right.
- We're eating.
- And...
applaud!
Are we at a market?
Pants, pants,
pants, pants,
pants, pants, pants, pants,
p, p, p, p,
p, p, p, p, p.
(The beat intensifies.)
(Are you ready?)
(Dance break!)
Nice!
Nicely done, Haha.
(He bounces like crazy.)
Good one, Se Chan.
Don't forget
you're playing this game.
- Nice.
- Keep going.
(He's lost in the dancing.)
- Pants.
- Go, go.
(Things heat up on the dance floor.)
(Singing)
(The heated dancing...)
(reaches its climax.)
Bowl!
(Jae Suk was quicker to the bowl.)
(Se Chan was drunk on the fun
to properly reach for the bowl.)
Nice!
Your performance was great though.
- Nice.
- Your performance.
You were too invested
in your performance.
- Next up are So Min and Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
Nice one.
Okay, show her what you've got.
Ji Hyo, I'll have my eyes on you.
- Jong Kook...
- You can make up for this.
All right.
- Right.
- Here we go.
Let's go!
- Let's keep it speedy.
- I'll start off with an easy one.
- Head.
- Ji Hyo will definitely win.
Shoulders.
Knees.
Stay on alert.
Toes, knees.
- He's close.
- Toes, knees.
Use your upper body too.
Toes, knees. Toes...
- Is this a workout?
- Why are you making them work out?
This isn't a workout program.
- Your upper body should...
- Is this a workout?
- Unbelievable.
- What's with the hands?
- Why...
- They aren't here to work out.
- Quality over quantity.
- Don't make them do squats.
Do it properly.
Toes, knees, toes, knees. Like this.
- Why are you making them work out?
- Just do it for me.
Lift your torso up slightly.
Toes, knees.
- You're not a gym teacher.
- Toes, knees.
Is this a workout program?
They're listening
to his instructions though.
Grab your knees.
Toes.
- Knees.
- Check him out.
- Toes, knees.
- He's loving it.
- Look at them.
He's close to saying it.
Seriously?
(The deadlifts summon Bad Ji Hyo.)
Just say it already.
- The game should be played.
- Right.
How long must this go on?
She's right.
- Right.
- I wanted you to work out.
- An exercise...
- She's right.
I just wanted you to work out.
Ji Hyo, just bear with him, okay?
Take deep breaths.
- Ji Hyo, you've got this.
- Take deep breaths.
You have the perfect pose though.
Ji Hyo, I'm glad you did it.
(Bad Ji Hyo said
what the others couldn't say.)
Ji Hyo, good one.
Toes, bowl.
(So Min takes the win
over an exhausted Ji Hyo.)
- Wow.
- Nice.
(I won!)
Nice.
You gave her a hint,
but it didn't work.
You did well though.
The score is 4 to 4.
- Okay.
- So this'll be the last round.
- One last round.
- Right.
- It'll end with this round.
- This'll decide who wins.
- Yes.
- This'll be the last round.
- Our team will host the game.
But Suk Jin once
hosted "Star Golden Bell".
But it's our turn...
to host the game.
Let Se Chan do it this time.
Sure, Se Chan can host the game.
(Bitter)
- Nice.
- We've done it many times,
- so Se Chan...
- Suk Jin should.
Suk Jin seems disappointed.
No, I'm good.
- Suk Jin.
- I'm good.
Let Suk Jin host the game.
- I'm fine.
- Suk Jin's sulking!
Let him do it, darn it.
- I'm fine!
- Seriously?
- Guys, wait.
- Just go ahead.
Suk Jin, go ahead.
He's the former host
of "Star Golden Bell", remember?
(Suk Jin reluctantly steps over
to the center.)
Let's go!
- Remember "Six Heroines"!
- "Six Heroines".
Catch rats, catch rats,
squeak, squeak, squeak
Here we go.
This'll decide who wins, right?
I like your tone!
- Let's go, let's go!
- Let's win this.
- Let's go!
- It's the final round!
Okay!
(The current Grand Award winner
of "SBS Entertainment Awards")
(He aims to bring down
the previous Grand Award winner.)
(The opponent is Jae Suk who holds
more Grand Awards than anyone.)
(And the master MC Big Brother
who's suitable for the big match)
(The big match
with perfect participants)
(What will be the result?)
Head.
Ears.
Nose!
Eyes. Eyes, nose,
ears. Ears.
- He fell asleep!
- Jae Suk!
(Because Suk Jin's
way of hosting is boring,)
(Jae Suk slowly fell asleep.)
- Jae Suk! Wake up!
- You're in the middle of a game!
- You're playing a game!
- Give him some time.
- Hey! What are you doing?
- You're in the middle of a game!
- What do you think you're doing?
It was so boring.
- He fell deeply asleep.
- It'll get fun soon.
- Give him some time.
- Jae Suk.
- He was hosting it.
- Jae Suk!
- I'm so sorry.
- Give him some time, Jae Suk.
- I apologize.
- I can't stand it when it's boring.
- You know how he's like.
- It'll get better soon.
- He has his own style.
- He was just getting warmed up.
- It'll get better soon.
Everyone!
Everyone, if you play with that
mindset, it's bound to be boring.
- You need to be open-minded.
- Jae Suk...
I knew he'd do that the moment
he let Suk Jin host it.
He was going to do that.
I guess you're enjoying this.
- I'll let you enjoy all you want.
- Okay.
- Are you serious?
- Of course.
I can't stand it when it's boring.
- Do you find this fun? Okay.
- Yes.
- It's okay.
- He was about to say...
something fun right after that.
He has his own tactics.
You should all give him some time.
I'm sorry that I fell asleep.
- I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
- If you keep this up,
- it'll get boring.
- I'm sorry.
- Give him some time.
- Eyes.
- Nose.
- Ears.
- Poke your nostrils. Mouth.
- Poke your nostrils.
(This is where it's supposed
to be funny.)
Poke your nostrils.
(He told them to poke their nostrils
out of nowhere.)
(A bystander passed out
after hearing Suk Jin.)
- Ears.
- This is terrible.
- Aren't you having fun?
- Sir, please get up!
- Excuse me.
- Hey, hey!
- Hey!
- He passed out. Hey!
How can you pass out
when we're rolling?
Sir, please get up!
(A couple of professional
TV personalities passed out.)
(How can you pass out
when we're rolling?)
- You shouldn't fall asleep.
- It's not time to be sleeping.
- Get up.
- Did you find that boring?
- Wake him up.
- Were we in the middle of a shoot?
- But...
- Get up, you guys.
- Get up! Get up, So Min.
- Wake them up.
- We are in the middle of a shoot.
- Get up!
- We were rolling?
- What's wrong with me?
- If you give me more time...
If you play with that mindset,
- it's bound to be boring.
- Get to your senses.
Who told you that you can
fall asleep during the shoot?
Who dares to fall asleep?
Who...
Who told you that you can
fall asleep during the shoot?
(I need to come to my senses!
I need to wake up!)
- Gosh, that was so boring.
- That's enough!
- What's wrong with me?
- I said that's enough.
Let me open the door.
Let's get some fresh air.
- Let the fresh air in!
- Come on.
Please open the door.
- Why am I so sleepy today?
- It's okay.
It's okay, everyone.
Everyone, come here.
You need to wake up.
We need to wake up!
- Did you get some fresh air?
- Yes, it's nice.
- Nostrils? That was...
- My gosh.
Look at these ungrateful jerks.
- Why would you curse at us?
- No, I meant...
You're having so much fun,
aren't you?
- I'll make this fun.
- Okay.
- Knees.
Knees, toes.
- I'm so excited.
- Knees, toes, toes.
Put your foreheads together.
- Put your foreheads together.
- What?
- You can't fall asleep here.
Put your foreheads together!
(Put your foreheads together!)
(Ji-rasoni who's been holding back
finally explodes.)
Just do as you're told!
Put your foreheads together!
Do the finale pose
for Andre Kim's shows!
- But we're wearing caps.
- But...
- How could we...
- You should've checked...
You should check in advance...
- before telling us anything.
- He's right.
- Everyone, if you keep this up,
- Okay, okay.
it's impossible for you to have fun!
- Hey, hey! Kwang Soo!
- What's wrong with you?
- Don't pass out. Kwang Soo. No.
- Kwang Soo...
He's sleeping with his eyes open!
- Don't fall asleep!
- Hey.
Don't fall asleep!
- What was that?
- Don't fall asleep.
(He gets startled and wakes up.)
- Kwang Soo, you can't.
- Were we in the middle of a shoot?
(A first-class MC who laughs
even when he's struggling)
Don't fall asleep.
(He washes his face with cold water
when he's sleepy.)
- Don't fall asleep.
- Are you okay?
(It's impossible to play the game
with Suk Jin hosting.)
Okay, I got it. Since the atmosphere
is all ruined, I'll finish it fast.
- I'll finish within 3 seconds.
- 3 seconds? Okay.
- I'm not in great condition.
- Forehead.
- Eyes.
You're not sleepy, are you?
Forehead, eyes. Knees!
Forehead.
(Keeping the tension as it's
the last game, the game continues.)
Guys!
Eyes, ears.
Nose.
Bowl!
(Bowl!)
(He finally yelled out "bowl"!)
Why aren't you grabbing it?
- Yes!
- Are you asleep? He's asleep!
- He fell asleep!
- He's asleep.
(While they were in the middle
of the game,)
(he couldn't fight against
the boredom and fell asleep.)
(Are you asleep?)
(He's asleep!)
- We won!
- He fell asleep.
- Is it over?
- We were in the middle of a game!
It's over?
But I just dozed off!
(The final round was over
while he dozed off.)
It's over already?
- Yes!
- But I just dozed off!
- We won.
- Isn't that cheating?
I dozed off only briefly!
- You should take responsibility!
- Why did you doze off?
- What a shame.
- Listen!
- Were you sleepy?
- I dozed off only briefly.
- You must've been sleepy.
- I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Haha.
- We won.
- I had no idea.
So he had a strategy all along.
- Of course.
- That was his strategy.
That was his strategy.
- He used his skills though!
- But this is...
- It's cheating! That's right.
- It's cheating.
Didn't he hypnotize me?
It's not fair!
He made us fall asleep.
Didn't he hypnotize me?
But Jong Kook overcame
the boredom...
- and rightfully won.
- I had a good sleep in a long time.
- That's good.
- That's why I didn't fall asleep.
That's the power of deep sleep!
(Getting deep sleep is the best!)
Thanks to Suk Jin's hosting,
Team Kim Grand Award won.
(Thanks to Suk Jin who induced
sleep, Team Kim Grand Award won.)
- I guess there's no other option.
- Yes!
Everyone on Team Kim Grand Award
earned 10 points.
And everyone on Team Yoo Grand Award
got minus three points.
- So what's going to happen?
- So Min...
Look at So Min.
The team she's on always loses.
I'm sorry.
- What do I do?
- So Min,
- it's okay.
- What do I do?
- I have such few points.
- I feel so refreshed.
Thank goodness
I had a deep sleep last night.
- I had a pig dream last night.
- I had a good sleep.
We'll now have lunch.
- Okay.
- Wow.
The team leaders should wait
in their rooms.
This time, there aren't any points
on the line.
The rest of you will step outside,
and you'll head to the room you want
with your bowl of rice.
- You can have your lunch there.
- Okay.
- Since we won't...
- Someone I want to have lunch with?
Since no points are involved,
this is a popularity contest, right?
- That's right.
- All right then.
- Let's go.
- Oh, we're just having lunch.
- It's not about our looks.
- I slept too much.
Everyone had a good sleep.
(Yoo Grand Award's room
during lunchtime)
What's this?
Oh, it's ramyeon.
(Ramyeon?)
Ramyeon is good enough for us.
We don't need to eat much
for lunch.
(All instant foods are prepared
for a ramyeon lover.)
I love the menu.
(He's satisfied.)
Are they having ramyeon too?
(What's Kim Grand Award
having for lunch?)
What do I do?
(The rest of the members
have to make their choices.)
- What do I do?
- I've made up my mind.
- Who are you picking?
- I want to eat comfortably.
You're picking Jae Suk?
I also want to eat with Jae Suk.
But you have to think carefully.
He'll get upset for real.
- But lunch is okay.
- Don't think about that.
- Lunch is okay.
- So only when we play games...
- But you'll go to Jong Kook...
and be adored by him.
I'm not one to be adored by anyone.
He should be adored by me.
What are you saying?
- You did a lot of cute acts today.
- He's right.
It's humiliating.
- He did cute acts when he's 50.
- That's not true. I didn't do that.
With eyes filled with love,
- he wanted to be adored.
- I'm not the one to be adored.
He's just a younger brother
who needs a pat on the back.
Then I'll go first.
- You can go next.
- Let's just close our eyes.
- I'm off then.
- Okay.
I'll go next.
(Se Chan chooses the room first.)
(He picked Jae Suk.)
- My goodness.
- My goodness, Se Chan.
I should eat with you...
- to be comfortable.
- Of course.
Se Chan...
He doesn't eat ramyeon, you know.
Of course we should have ramyeon.
There you go.
The girl who likes soups is here.
We're having ramyeon.
- I love ramyeon, Jae Suk.
- I make delicious ramyeon.
Who is going next?
You should set off, Haha.
I'm going to Jong Kook's room.
I'm picking Jong Kook too.
(The minions of Jong Kook
are on their way.)
Which room are you picking?
I don't know. What should I do?
Let's divide the members in half.
If too many people go to
Jong Kook's room,
- I'll go to Jae Suk's room.
- To Jae Suk?
Yes.
(But he picked Jong Kook.)
- I'm loyal to you, Jong Kook.
- Suk Jin.
Our lunch is like the penalty.
Our lunch is the penalty.
Look at this.
We prepared the foods
Jong Kook likes.
You can have chicken breast
and low-sodium food for lunch.
He doesn't eat like this!
He loves tangsuyuk and fritters!
I eat cup noodles these days.
- That's right.
- He doesn't eat these.
How can we have almonds with rice?
Why did they give us almonds?
We could've been in big trouble.
If he ate this alone...
That'd be horrible.
If that happened, I'd have
removed the photo of us smiling...
that's hanging in our restaurant.
But this is just a game.
- No, it's not.
- Okay?
Don't put your entire life on this.
You picked Jae Suk for both rounds.
- That's...
- You could've picked me once.
- Don't you agree, Suk Jin?
- Haha.
If you remove Jong Kook
from the photo, put me in.
(Pro investor Ji found a chance
to invest his money.)
Suk Jin, why would you
grab that chance?
Suk Jin, go ahead.
You can go ahead.
My goodness. So Min.
(So Min picked Team Yoo Grand Award
this time as well.)
Can I put the noodles in?
Where? The water is not boiling yet.
Do you have ketchup?
- I love...
- The ketchup is here.
how you're being considerate.
- "Can I put them in?"
- Thank you, Ji Hyo.
Aren't we kind?
If it was Jong Kook,
he'd have said this.
"Don't put it in."
- "It's not good for your health."
- "Don't put it in, you punk!"
"You're so thoughtless."
He'd have said that.
(Kim Grand Award is not
good at expressing his love.)
This feels like a ramyeon club.
- Right?
- Yes.
The egg looks like a flower.
(The egg looks like a flower.)
It looks like thick clouds.
I've never seen anyone who makes
meringue out of ramyeon.
I love how no one is negative here.
- Let's eat now! Get your portion.
- No one is negative. Now?
Look at this.
(They share the ramyeon in peace.)
- This is how you should eat.
- Oh, like that?
- Thank you.
- The noodles are cooked perfectly.
There's more, so help yourself.
- How did he make it so delicious?
- This is amazing.
The noodles are so chewy.
- Let's add gochujang.
- Add the chicken breast here.
(Kim Grand Award loves
the protein-based meal.)
(Putting chicken breast
into the chicken shake)
That's the worst.
It seriously is.
How do you eat it like that?
It tastes okay because
the chicken breast doesn't smell.
(Kim Protein, the PR ambassador
of chicken breast)
It doesn't smell at all.
(Kim Grand Award gets excited
for consuming protein.)
- This is good.
- You're smiling?
Try it. Try it like this.
- It must be good. He's smiling.
- Okay, okay.
- Kwang Soo, try it.
- I like it.
Try it like this. It tastes okay.
Try it, Kwang Soo.
Try it with the shake.
Please come out!
I feel sleepy now.
Goodness, I'm so full.
We had chicken breast.
I heard you had chicken breasts.
This place serves good food.
We had ramyeon,
- meatballs, and sausages.
- We had meatballs too.
- Sausages too.
- We even added eggs to ramyeon.
How will you face Jong Kook now?
What? It's okay, it's just a meal.
But Jong Kook is really upset
right now.
I won't see him then.
(He acts tough.)
- I'll run away.
- You've got some guts.
I decided to stay on this team
for good.
Ji Hyo must be sleeping in the room.
(Ji Hyo must be
sleeping in the room.)
- Really?
- She's really sleeping?
She must think we are at Boracay.
(Kim Grand Award's room)
(Exclaiming)
We're going out?
- She's unbelievable.
- She must think we are at Boracay.
- Hey.
- We're not at Boracay, Ji Hyo.
- You fell asleep?
- What's happening?
We're not at a vacation spot.
- Why did you fall asleep?
- What's wrong with you?
Why did you come out of that room?
Come to your senses, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo has been sleeping
since earlier.
She fell asleep when you were
hosting, and she just got up.
- I made you fall asleep?
- I'm sorry.
- She even missed lunch.
- Thank you, Suk Jin.
I slept soundly thanks to you.
My youngest daughter hasn't been
able to sleep well recently.
Could you host the game
at my place once?
I'll pay a visit.
- Oh, gosh.
- What's wrong?
(The staff member who was behind
suddenly fell down.)
You see?
Someone just fell asleep again!
- She fell asleep because of you!
- Hey!
We need Jae Suk here!
- Suk Jin will get mad for real.
- Don't do that to Suk Jin.
Why do so many people
pass out these days?
Go and wash your face
with the seawater.
(Go and wash your face
with the seawater.)
Washing your face
wakes you up right away.
Is today's special
about superpowers?
Did you take a potion or something?
(Did you take
a potion or something?)
Is today really about superpowers?
All right. Now this will be
your last mission.
Your choice of team
will be very important.
- That's right.
- I'll go first.
(Ji Hyo sets off confidently.)
It's cold outside, and they're
taking longer than I thought.
(Opening)
Oh, dear.
(She opened the door confidently,)
(but fell down right away.)
- Ji Hyo.
- Gosh, it hurts.
Hey, are you okay?
Why would you greet me
with your foot?
- Hey, well done.
- I was glad to see you.
- You made the right choice.
- You see, I...
Your last team should be my team.
I should be with you until the end.
Right. Well done.
(Who will the other members choose?)
Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk!)
(Suk Jin chose
Team Yoo Grand Award.)
- Hey, Suk Jin.
- I chose your team at last.
I think your team will win
the last mission.
Gosh, you and your skill
to make everyone sleep.
I'm choosing you no matter what.
- My goodness.
- It depends on the game though.
I think...
we'll be having a quiz.
See? They set up everything for it.
Gosh, I think
I'm really quick-witted.
This is insane.
Jae Suk!
- Darn it, it's Suk Jin!
- Hey, Haha.
- Hey.
- Haha is loyal.
- My goodness.
- I'm loyal, aren't I?
- I ate with Jong Kook, but...
- Haha.
- Hello, Jae Suk.
- Hey, Jae Suk.
- You're here, Kwang Soo.
- The empty-headed ones are here.
- I'm back home.
- Gosh.
- Kwang Soo.
You ran away from home though.
This is what they set up
for the last game.
- You need to sit here.
- It's a quiz.
- It's the last game, but...
We'll win no matter what.
Another one is here.
Hello, did you enjoy your lunch?
- My goodness.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Everyone's joining Jae Suk?
- I can't believe it.
(Things are getting worse
and worse.)
We're family since we ate together.
- There are six of us.
- You should've gone there.
- You should join his team.
- Why?
- You decided to just...
- This is driving me crazy.
Look what they set up here.
- What's happening?
- Another one?
(What's happening?)
- Hey!
- Oh, no.
(Another member chose Jae Suk?)
- What's happening?
- Another one?
(Even So Min is joining
Team Yoo Grand Award?)
- What's happening?
- But Jong Kook...
Ji Hyo is the only one...
(If So Min is here as well,)
(then Ji Hyo is the only one
who's with Jong Kook?)
There's only two of them?
- Jong Kook must be really upset.
- Too many people are here, Bo Pil.
Too many people are here.
Jong Kook must be extremely upset.
- I'm sure he's furious.
- Jong Kook must be upset.
Then we...
(Right then, the door opens again.)
- Oh, gosh.
- You scared us.
(Very tense)
- You chose us too?
- Jae Suk.
- Darn you!
- Jae Suk...
Open the door quietly!
Jae Suk is totally scared.
What's going to happen?
I'm feeling anxious.
Everyone has chosen their team.
- They're done?
- Your team member...
is Ji Hyo.
Let's proceed
with the third mission.
Jong Kook!
It's okay. Don't worry. Well done.
It's fine. I made up my mind...
- But...
- to play alone anyway.
What's going on, seriously?
My gosh.
(He's on his way to meet them.)
Gosh. Fine.
I've already chosen
who'll get the penalty.
(The door to Team Yoo Grand Award's
room has finally opened.)
(He's here.)
- Hello.
- Oh, gosh.
(Look at these guys.)
(We can only hear them dry coughing.
The atmosphere is icy-cold.)
Hey, Jong Kook.
Don't look at us like that!
Don't look into my eyes
for more than three seconds.
- Why not?
- It says so on the contract!
- 1, 2, 3.
- No, I'm not looking at you.
- What's wrong?
- You're only allowed two seconds.
Ji Hyo, come.
Where do you want to sit?
- Where do you want to sit?
- Why did everyone...
- Come sit in the center.
- You're wearing matching shirts.
Of course we should.
My goodness, this is...
I thought we'd be playing a game
Jae Suk is good at.
- I see.
- My goodness.
Sure, I don't mind.
This is another segment anyway.
- I think they're giving us a quiz.
- I think so too.
All right. You can turn the tables
through this mission.
- My gosh.
- Can I just turn them over?
(They're about to be
turned over by Jong Kook.)
That's not what he meant.
Don't forget our contract.
- I have a contract to protect me!
- What? What's wrong?
Your eyes are...
Don't stare at us
for more than 3 seconds.
The way he talks...
If they lose this time, they'll...
- lose a lot of points, right?
- Minus six points.
That's right.
They'll lose six points.
I'm sorry,
but are you his girlfriend?
- Is she...
- They look good together.
You look good together!
- You really do.
- You look good together.
(They look like a couple from
the 1990s visiting Ganghwa Island.)
I can't hold his arm
because his arm is too thick.
We've been dating for a long time.
- You've dated for a long time?
- Yes.
- That's cute.
- We've been dating for a long time.
- We've dated for a long time.
- That's nice.
- How do you date for so long?
- Don't we look like a family?
"How do you date for so long?"
You can turn the tables
through the last mission.
It's a mission to check
the intelligence of two smart men.
- It's a quiz.
- It's called The Uncanny Quiz.
- Yes!
- It's a quiz!
Yoo Jae Suk!
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- It's okay! Don't worry.
- It's okay! It's fine.
- Yoo Jae Suk!
However, it's not an ordinary quiz.
We've prepared fun questions
where you can use...
your reasoning skills
and creativity.
We'll give you a point if all of you
put your heads together...
and manage to find the answer first.
- We need to put our heads together?
- That sounds a bit off.
But I have no reasoning skills
at all.
Empty Head!
Okay. Okay, I got it.
(They're in trouble too.)
Maybe they'll tell us
to write a letter each.
- But that's...
- Then it will be...
- a total mess.
- Six fools are... Oh, no.
What did you just say?
(Six fools)
(What did you just say?)
What?
- Hey, come here.
- Let go!
- Hey.
- Darn you.
(The six fools flew into a rage.)
- Let's drag him out of here.
- Hey, you.
- Hey, did you call us 6 fools?
- "6 fools"?
- It's "having many fools".
- I'm so offended.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
He meant to say that to us!
- Did you call us fools?
- He meant to say that to us!
But he was looking at me
when he said it.
- All right.
- He meant our team.
Nice job.
It's a mission where you need
one genius rather than many fools.
- Okay.
- You'll get...
- a chance for each question.
- A chance.
If you can't answer within three
minutes after hearing the question,
one member of the team
can go outside...
and look for the hidden hints...
for three minutes.
- Okay, okay.
- We are good at finding hints.
Are you telling me
to run around all day long?
Se Chan, it's cold outside.
Put on a jacket.
Put on a jacket now.
You might have to run outside.
Ji Hyo, let's wear a coat.
(Ji Hyo, let's wear a coat.)
Let's wear a coat.
It will be nice to stay warm.
It will be a 1-on-1 match
between me and Ji Hyo.
Kwang Soo, put a jacket
around your shoulders.
It will be a match.
- I will reveal the first question.
- Okay.
The first question.
(Move one match to complete
the equation.)
(However, do not touch
the equal sign.)
What?
(Thinking)
(Slapping the table)
(Does Jae Suk have an idea?)
- The equation...
- Let me answer.
- Will you answer right away?
- Yes.
(Did Jae Suk figure out
the answer already?)
What?
Let me answer.
I will move the match here.
That works.
You can't touch the equal sign.
- Gosh.
- Let me answer.
Let me answer.
There is a plus sign, right?
Move the vertical match
so that it becomes an equal sign.
No! Let me answer.
- 1 equals 1 equals 1.
- Let me answer.
- Correct.
- Okay!
(Suk Jin changed the plus sign
to an equal sign.)
The multiplication sign.
- No, no.
- The equal sign works.
The equal sign works.
1 equals 1 equals 1.
Okay.
(Suk Jin completed the equation
by moving one match.)
All right!
1 equals 1 equals 1.
Okay.
(Team Yoo Grand Award won 1 point.)
Haven't you figured it out yet?
- What did he say?
- I figured it out.
- It just stood out to me.
- You make the same sign.
Se Chan, you make
the same inequality sign.
I thought you had to make
the multiplication sign.
(He just claps.)
I get it now.
But why is 1 equals 1 equals 1?
The numbers are the same.
- We did it!
- Okay.
- Let's go!
- Let's keep going.
Did we win?
- Yes.
- How did it end so soon?
- Do you get it now?
- No.
Let's keep going.
- Jong Kook, it's okay.
- It's okay.
(Team Kim Grand Award
lost a point to the 6 fools.)
- Here comes the second question.
- Okay.
(The second question)
(Move 2 coins so that the sum...)
(of the vertical and horizontal
lines is 70 cents each.)
(However, you must maintain
the shape of a cross.)
- Let's make it.
- 70 cents.
As it is, the vertical line makes
70 cents...
and the horizontal line
makes 50 cents.
(The vertical line makes 70 cents
and horizontal line makes 50 cents.)
- This works, right?
- Do we need to move two coins?
Yes.
Do we need to move two coins?
Like this?
(Kim Grand Award stacks the coins.)
That's right.
You must maintain
the shape of the cross...
and have each line make 70 cents.
No.
In total?
That's right.
You must maintain
the shape of the cross...
and have each line make 70 cents.
- And we can only move two coins.
- Yes.
(Suk Jin is thinking by himself.)
This isn't easy.
- And we can only move two coins.
- Yes.
Should we stack the coins?
If we do that...
This isn't easy.
(70 cents and 60 cents)
(The vertical line makes
70 cents...)
(and the horizontal line
makes 60 cents.)
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
- It's 60 cents.
- Get another coin.
Move two coins.
If we stack two coins...
We did it. We are done.
(Are they done already?)
This is how you do it.
Let me answer.
Stack the top coin
and the bottom coin in the center.
- Okay.
Stack the top coin
and the bottom coin in the center.
- Okay.
You stack the coins.
(The problem required creativity.)
Hey.
I solved it,
but Suk Jin butted in at the end.
- We solved it together.
- That's right.
- This is great.
Ajou University!
(The man who went to Ajou University
did well.)
This one will be hard.
Team Kim Grand Award,
here comes the question.
I will go and find the hints.
You will get a piece of paper.
Connect the dots
in a single stroke...
without going over
the same dot twice.
What?
(Connect the dots
in a single stroke.)
In a single stroke?
Can you return to the line you drew?
No, you can't.
- You can't go over the dots twice.
- No.
You can't go over the dots twice.
(With bated breath,)
How do you do this?
Like this?
(everyone focuses on
finding the solution.)
By the way,
are we entering a program
for gifted children?
This is so hard.
I feel dizzy.
- I have no idea.
- I think I have motion sickness.
I feel dizzy.
- Try again.
- I am done.
- Let me see.
I did it.
- I think I solved it.
- Really?
Is he a genius?
Suk Jin is on fire today.
I will give it a go.
He is incredible.
- Watch.
- Okay.
You make a horizontal line first.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Then you go here.
Here, here, here,
here, here,
here, here, here, here, here.
- I did it, right?
- You missed a dot.
- He did it.
- I did it.
- What? He did it.
- Suk Jin, you missed a dot.
He did it.
I just need to connect it.
- I can do it again.
- Did he succeed?
- I did it.
- What is up with Suk Jin?
Really?
- What?
- Suk Jin was a genius.
"Finding Genius".
He became a genius at the age of 56.
- Watch.
- Go ahead.
- What?
- Suk Jin was a genius.
What is up with him?
- You make a horizontal line first.
- "Finding Genius".
He became a genius at the age of 56.
Here, here, here,
here, here, here,
here...
That wasn't what you did.
Here, here,
(He would have succeeded
had he gone up.)
here...
(He ended up going to the side
because he was in a hurry.)
(They failed to win a point.)
That wasn't what you did.
You succeeded earlier.
- For goodness' sake.
- Try again.
No, no.
No, no. You fool.
If you follow this method,
one part gets left behind.
I couldn't do it on the board.
- This is hard.
- Here, here...
I couldn't do it on the board.
(The old genius has a bad memory.)
- I did it.
- You did it.
- Let me show you again.
- I did it.
- You did it.
- Let me show you again.
- I said it first, right?
- I did it.
- It worked.
I was mistaken. I did it.
I can do it. I can do it.
- Watch.
- Okay.
That's right.
(After making a horizontal line,
he connects the outer dots.)
- Go up.
- Okay.
(Go up!)
That's right.
Here.
- Okay, okay.
- I did that first.
(The old genius ended up giving
the answer to someone else.)
I did that first.
- Suk Jin.
- I didn't draw the last line.
- You were so close.
- Why didn't you draw it?
I didn't draw the last line.
- Seriously.
I gave him the hint
on the horizontal line.
What's the point of being a genius
if you can't get a question right?
I didn't look at what you did.
Come on, Suk Jin.
- I figured it out right away.
- Why didn't you draw the last line?
"Finding Genius Suk Jin".
("Finding Genius Suk Jin".)
For the next question,
I will give you the props first.
What is this?
It's like "Die Hard".
Move one cup...
to make the bottom arrangement.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Let's arrange the cups.
- Okay.
- So 2, 3, and 4...
- should be filled.
- Firstly...
So we can either move a cup...
or pour out the water from a cup.
(Find a way to put 3 full cups
in the middle.)
- Shall we begin?
- Yes.
- Is this possible?
- I am sorry, but...
- We can only move one cup, right?
- Yes.
I can pour out the liquid...
and put the cup here.
(He reached the answer the fastest.)
- What?
I can pour out the liquid...
and put the cup here.
Okay.
- What?
I did it, right?
Okay, okay.
Everyone knows that!
What was that?
- What?
- I did it.
Anyone can pour out the liquid
and put the cup at the end.
The last question was much harder.
Why didn't you do it
if you knew the answer?
We were thrown off
because the last question was hard.
Why were you thrown off?
It was so easy.
By the way,
you guys are surprised, right?
We are really good at this, right?
We are good at figuring out tricks.
Now comes the last question.
The palm is facing up.
From that pose,
keep your wrist
and shoulder unmoving...
and make the palm face down.
You start with the palm facing up.
- Can't we just do it?
- Both hands?
No, one hand.
But you can't turn your wrist.
So we need to make
the palm face down.
- Hold on. This is...
- This is...
So we can't turn the wrist.
Like this?
We can't turn the wrist.
The back of the hand
needs to face up.
This isn't how you do it, right?
Hey, isn't this the solution?
From here,
you can lean forward.
Then your arm will get twisted.
You will hurt your back.
The hand needs to be like this.
The body will stay the same.
How?
- How about this?
- You can't turn the wrist.
- Like this.
So you can't do this.
Doesn't this count?
I figured it out. Come here.
- How?
- Let me answer.
- Come here.
- How?
- Put your head down.
- What?
Your hand is like this, right?
- Come here.
- What are you trying to do?
- Get him up.
- What? How?
1, 2, 3.
Like this?
Is this the solution?
(The tall man is upside down.)
(He feels like he has been forced
into a roller coaster.)
- Is this the solution?
- Keep your head down.
- Incorrect.
- Is it incorrect?
- Hold on.
You can't use the wrist.
Don't turn the wrist.
Don't turn the shoulder.
(There is a way
to make the palm face up.)
(The answer)
(Bend the arm
at a 90-degree angle 6 times.)
From here...
- From here...
- You can't turn the twist.
(What if you roll forward?)
(The hand stays the same!)
Nice.
How does it work?
That doesn't work.
- Like this.
- What is this?
Like this.
Can't you do it
without moving the shoulder?
Oh, the wrist.
(Suk Jin got a hint
from Jong Kook's movement.)
- Like this.
- Let me answer.
Let me answer.
From here,
- do this.
- Okay.
Then you do this and this.
(What?)
- Do it again.
- Right? From here...
It's correct.
- It's correct.
- Go down and come up.
(Suk Jin came up
with a unique solution.)
- It works.
From here, fold the arm.
- Go down.
- Then do this.
- Come up.
(Fold, go down, and come up.)
(Suk Jin's answer is correct.)
(The old genius got
the last 1 point.)
- I can't believe it.
- Suk Jin!
I can't believe it.
(The production crew's answer)
From here, fold the arm.
- Go down.
- Then do this.
- Come up.
(A new answer by Suk Jin)
Jong Kook gave away the answer.
I can't believe Suk Jin.
You did this.
It was an answer we didn't expect.
Really?
- This didn't occur to me.
- It's fascinating.
When you get this kind
of question correct, you look sexy.
- You look sexy.
- You look different.
Our score is high.
(Suk Jin won
the Empty Heads' envy.)
This team won 12 points each.
Well...
This team lost two points each.
The first place will receive a prize
and be exempt from the penalty.
The 7th and 8th places will receive
the penalty.
As for the penalty,
we put three flags outside.
- Bring one each.
- What?
Where are the flags?
- That's the worst.
- The flags are in the water.
- Okay.
- I will announce the results...
on the board.
- It's right.
- What is up with So Min?
- The points...
- Kwang Soo.
When did that happen?
With 28 points,
Kwang Soo is the 1st place.
Okay!
He is exempt from the penalty.
(The 1st place will receive a prize
and be exempt from the penalty.)
I will now present the prize.
- What is that?
- It's a trophy.
- That's incredible.
(Big Thumb Trophy)
- He loves prizes like that.
- What is this?
- What?
- It's a trophy.
(The gold-toned prize
makes his eyes go wide.)
We didn't know who would win.
I will write down the name now.
- What is that?
- On a piece of paper?
- That's...
- It looks authentic.
- Is that gold?
Are you writing down the name?
2021 SBS Running Man,
Real Grand Award.
(He wrote the name
without much consideration.)
- Congratulations on winning.
- Congratulations, Kwang Soo.
The big toe resembles Kwang Soo.
It's not a big toe. It's a thumb.
It's made of iron.
Iron.
This is...
- When some time passes,
- I know.
if would be hard
to find a place for it.
(It would be the hardest
to find a place for it.)
The members at the bottom are
Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.
Pick a member...
who will receive the penalty
except for Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo survived.
Okay!
Get ready, okay?
- The one with long hair.
Get ready.
Okay!
(They are the 3 members
who will receive the penalty.)
- This is great.
- Game over.
- The other members can go home.
- Okay.
- I feel bad.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
The weather is warm.
(The trio gets ready
to enter the mudflat.)
Do we need to put on rubber boots?
One of you needs to take off
the rubber boots.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- All right.
- Play or lose,
- rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay!
(So Min wins.)
I will take them off.
(Okay!)
(Singing)
(From head to toe)
(You are lovely)
She is such an eyesore.
(So Min the traitor
gives an annoying ceremony.)
I can go in barefoot, right?
Bring a flag each
to complete the mission.
I will go that way!
Gosh, this will make me so healthy.
Be careful. Your feet will sink.
(Staggering)
Your feet will sink. Be careful.
What should I do? I am stuck.
(She's the one who got stuck.)
(While Ji Hyo was staggering,
So Min took the first flag.)
Let's get off work. Let's go home.
Let's hurry up and go home.
Bye.
(Yoo Grand Award is the one
in my heart.)
(She gives an annoying ceremony
and goes home.)
Bye.
Let's go home.
- Okay.
(The last duo takes the flags
as well!)
I got the flag!
(This time, they open agencies!)
(4 new agencies appear!)
- No way.
- Just come in here.
(To sign a contract
with an A-list free agent,)
(they use all sorts of methods.)
We do need that piece of paper.
(A big-time free agent, Jessi)
(Soliciting)
(A big-time free agent, Woo Young)
(After signing a contract
with the stars,)
(they work hard
to bring up their price.)
(It's the best!)
(They reveal Jae Suk's weakness
for the audience!)
(They succeed
in bringing up the price!)
(But their contract price...)
(continues to skyrocket.)
(Some agencies
even go out of business.)
(The proud celebrities continue
to make excessive demands.)
(Kwang Soo cuts his mullet!)
- Why?
- It's weird.
(In this cut-throat industry,)
(will the CEOs be able
to save their agencies?)
I will get ready to sue them.
- Why?
- You ridiculed me before everyone.
(Catch the Stars Among Free Agents,
Stars' Contract War)