Today's special is Running Man Rewritten.
(Running Man Rewritten 2)
We will rewrite...
some of the content on Running Man's website that has stayed the same...
(The members will rewrite some of the content...)
(on Running Man's website that has stayed for 11 years.)
- for 10 years now. - Really?
Does anyone know the production objective that Cho Hyo Jin wrote?
Isn't it "Don't walk, run."?
(Do the members remember the production objective?)
It's "From landmarks stuck in the city..."
"Landmarks that represent Korea."
(The big laughter that no one could imagine)
"Running Man will let you know about them."
"They will do missions everywhere to win games..."
and escape from that place before the next morning.
- It was like that in the past. - This really must be changed.
- It was still like this. - But there is a need for change.
(The production objective on the website needs to be changed.)
There's also something else. "MC Yu" is the nickname,
(And each member has their nickname and a one-sentence comment.)
and there's a one-sentence comment.
I wore that for Episode 100.
(Their outfits...)
"He has a charm where strength and softness exist together."
(and characters...)
- Where is his softness? - That makes no sense.
(are frozen in time 11 years ago.)
It says "He has a strange charm."
(The old photos and comments show the time they've spent together.)
(Unlucky Rising Star, Yang Se Chan)
"Unlucky Rising Star"?
You must have not had any nicknames.
(They even found a nickname they made up carelessly.)
That's really written carelessly. I really hate you.
(The introduction of the 8 members needs an update.)
So if you write everyone's nicknames,
(They are asked to write everyone's nickname, )
one-sentence comments,
(one-sentence comments, and production objective.)
and production objective from your ideas...
The winner's content will be posted on our website.
(The winner's content will be posted on the website.)
We will spin a roulette at the end of today to decide a winner.
(The winner will be decided by spinning a roulette.)
The entire website will be changed?
(Everything will be changed as the winner wants.)
- The whole thing will be changed. - This is hard.
We must pay some attention to this then.
(That's how the members started to rewrite the introduction.)
"Variety shows are disappearing these days."
- Gosh. - Gosh, Jae Suk.
- The introduction is good, right? - That's right.
(Variety shows are disappearing these days.)
"Beyond Korea" is too...
(Beyond Korea)
It sounds too much like bragging. Isn't that right?
- But we need that. - It's kind of our pride.
(They are writing it seriously with dignity and pride.)
- Right. - We need that.
"The pride of Korea's variety shows."
"Based on a worldwide fandom beyond Korea..."
"A giant scale."
"A tremendous amount of production cost."
(The production objective has all kinds of modifiers.)
That's cool. That's like a blockbuster.
Here's the production objective.
(They start to present the production objective they wrote.)
"The eight people who grew up on love will make you laugh."
"'The fruits of studying hard will show themselves later.'"
(Production Objective)
"Do you all know that saying?"
"It means something good."
(He's good.)
"Open your eyes. Fun on a big scale will come."
"Open your mouth. Laughter on a big scale will come."
"Open your heart. A great lesson will come."
Bravo!
(Se Chan's objective is going to make a big hit.)
"Growing the long hair on his ear to live long,"
(Member introduction)
"he's a hard-working man who is soon-to-be 60."
(Ji Suk Jin, a man who is soon-to-be-60)
I don't have a long hair.
"He's Protein Monster who's got the surprising ability..."
(Name: Protein Monster)
"to make people uncomfortable with his excessive love."
(He also came up with the perfect introduction of the members.)
"He doesn't care about B Class actors."
"He only cares about A Class actors."
What's wrong with him?
He's "Mr. Dirty Mustache Who Pretends to Be..."
(Member introduction)
"the Youngest Among the Celebrities Born in 1979."
(Mr. Dirty Mustache)
He's "Mr. Dirty Mustache Who Pretends to Be..."
"the Youngest Among the Celebrities Born in 1979."
(Dirty mustache)
That's his nickname.
His nickname is "Mr. Dirty Mustache".
"Keeping its place for 10 years."
(Next up is Mr. Dirty Mustache, Haha's presentation.)
"It's the gateway to becoming a star."
"Running Man is the best man out there!"
"It involves all of the above."
(He tried to include all of the young people's vocabularies.)
"It's beyond amazing. Get ready to have fun."
"Song Ji Hyo."
"She once had a crush on Haha and was heartbroken."
"But being a cool guy, Haha asked her to be his sister."
"Now, she and Haha are the cutest Mapo Siblings."
(Haha's self-centered introduction)
You are crazy, aren't you?
"He went from a gangster to a Grand Award winner."
"He went from a gangster to a Grand Award winner." Love it.
"He's cute and sexy. It's crazy."
(Name: Haha)
"He's popular but humble."
"Haha is cool enough to let Jong Kook win the Grand Award."
"What will he do next?"
What is that?
(Who's up next to present the production objective?)
- What is that? - He says that all the time.
- Kim Jong Kook. - Kook Jong.
(It's Jong Kook's turn to present his production objective.)
Me? I didn't write a lot.
(Because of Se Chan and Haha's funny presentation, he feels pressured.)
It's okay. Make it short.
Gosh, I think this is too formal.
"With the global fandom beyond Korea,"
"Running Man has become the center of Korean variety shows."
He must be shy. He seems anxious now.
"It's the gateway to becoming a star."
(He speaks fast because he's shy.)
"Through talks and games that attract viewers of all ages,"
(Production Objective)
"Korea's representative variety show spreads K-Culture."
This is real. He is serious about this. I love it.
(Serious about K-culture)
It sounds like SBS wrote it.
We also need things like this.
"Yoo Jae Suk. His nickname is 'Unchanging Goofball'."
(Short)
Is that all you wrote?
The thing is...
(He failed to distribute time evenly.)
- I wrote the others first. - I love it.
- I was going to come back to this. - I like it anyway.
- You like it. - I do.
- "Unchanging Goofball". - Good.
(Satisfied)
"Ji Suk Jin. The Lynx of talk shows called 'Ji-rasoni'."
"He's burning the last embers of his variety show career."
(Laughing)
- Good. - Hey.
When will your last passion come to an end?
Last? It's not like...
(His small passion never turns off.)
- "The Last Leaf". - It's like eternal youth.
- Good luck. - Go, Ji Suk Jin!
"Kim Jong Kook. 'Anyang Tantrum' who throws a tantrum when he's mad."
(He starts introducing himself.)
He admits it too.
(He admits that he's a tantrum.)
"He's a singer. He sings well and has many hit songs."
(Member introduction)
"But he's better known as an entertainer now."
Okay.
(Shy)
- That was about him. - Gosh.
(His introduction consists of heavy facts.)
"Haha. Short Guy, Small Guy,"
"Haha PD, A Guy Who's Short but Happy".
"He's an indispensable seasoning in Running Man."
"But he's more focused on his YouTube these days."
Is he a seasoning?
(He's a seasoning, not a main ingredient.)
- Seasoning. - "Lee Kwang Soo."
"Just Crazy, Forever Star Butler."
(Star Butler always follows him.)
Why do you keep saying "Star Butler"?
"He's ugly, but he finds it hard to accept the fact."
"His fans spoiled him."
What?
(What's that?)
- Exactly. His fans spoiled him. - That can't be my introduction.
(You're cute. Asia Prince. Go, Kwang Soo. You're so handsome.)
It's the fans.
(3 second Lee Sun Kyun)
They didn't spoil me.
They say he's handsome, so he thinks he's handsome.
(Excessive love from fans around the world)
"He finds it hard to accept the fact." It's hilarious.
- My gosh. - He can't accept it.
(He still can't accept it.)
- This is crazy. - "Yang Se Chan."
"Yechani, Yang Sebastian, and Gum Angel."
(Gum Angel loves it.)
Good. I like my nicknames.
"Kim Jong Kook's favorite doll."
"But he badmouths me behind my back."
"He's pretending to be innocent, but once there's proof, I'll kill him."
This is a declaration of war.
(It's a declaration of war under the mask of introduction.)
I didn't badmouth you.
(Whining)
- Who's up next? - I made it short.
(After Jong Kook, it's Kwang Soo's turn.)
- It's simple. - Good.
Make it short.
I was serious about the production objective though.
(Proud)
This stuff can last a while.
"It's spreading to the whole world beyond Korea? No, to outer space."
(Production Objective)
"The members make up for each other's deficiencies."
"The piller of Korean variety shows that the whole family can enjoy."
- Okay. - Good.
"Piller?" Does it say "piller"?
- "Piller?" - What?
(He doesn't know what's wrong.)
It's "pillar", you punk.
(Flustered)
- It's a typo. - It's not a typo.
You also said "piller".
"The piller of Korean variety shows that the whole family can enjoy."
(He clearly pronounced the word, "piller".)
- Okay. - Good.
- It's a typo. - It's not acorn jelly.
(Embarrassed)
It's not a dialect.
It's "pillar". Do you even know what a pillar is?
- What? - Do you know what it means?
It's like a support.
(Pillar is a tree to keep an object stand.)
That's it. Just move on.
- Please change the spelling. - It's okay.
If Kwang Soo wins, you should go with this.
(If Kwang Soo wins, Running Man becomes a "piller".)
Member introductions. "Ji Suk Jin. I'm still vigorous."
"I'm still vigorous."
"Yoo Jae Suk."
(They love it.)
"Bring it on."
"I will stay ranked eighth by looks no matter who comes."
Gosh, that was...
(He's in 1st place from behind.)
- I love it. - He's crazy.
(He's the only one who can't accept it.)
"Kim Jong Kook. My heart is like a soy sauce dish."
(My mind is as narrow as a dipping dish.)
"My heart is like a soy sauce dish."
Are you saying he's petty?
(It's a four-character idiom for Jong Kook.)
(The dipping dish will teach you a lesson.)
- Good. - "Haha. Old Fossil".
"Come to me if you want to get an earful."
I'm talking now!
- Good. - "Song Ji Hyo."
"Go ahead and text me."
"I'll ignore it anyway."
I love it.
(It's a short but powerful blow.)
"Jeon So Min. It's me who made Running Man PG-15."
(Member introduction)
"I'll make it Rated R in 2021."
(She will raise the viewer rating as well as the age limit.)
- Good. - "Yang Se Chan."
- "Poop". - Hey!
Hey!
(He just wrote one word, "poop".)
What's that?
I lost my concentration toward the end.
It doesn't mean anything. It's just one word.
(Se Chan's not good enough for the star butler.)
- I lost my concentration. - It's funny though.
- I like it. - How could he say that?
I like it. It's short and good.
(1 shot, 1 kill)
"Lee Kwang Soo. We didn't know..."
"how charming he was."
Gosh, I hate him.
(Scoffing)
(It's true that his fans spoiled him.)
It makes me want to vomit.
Mine is short too.
(After Kwang Soo's presentation, next is Jae Suk.)
The production objective. "Variety shows are..."
"disappearing these days."
"Running Man is Korea's favorite variety show that's been..."
(Production Objective)
"on Sunday nights for over 10 years."
"The members play games and clear missions with various guest stars,"
"as they go around to different places."
"Among various fun factors,"
"this show only focuses on laughter."
This is the true production objective.
(Exclaiming)
I hope this will go on the website.
This is how Jae Suk thinks of Running Man.
The writers are giving him a big hand.
Why are you clapping your hands?
(The king of jealousy)
"We only care about laughter."
- Cool. - Right.
It's not like you're submitting a report.
(Jealous)
"Ji Suk Jin. He was going to leave the team in the first year."
"But now he says Running Man is the best."
(Knocked out)
- Jae Suk! - That's just a message to him.
- "His behavior is frowned upon..." - That's just a message to him.
- Hey. - That's basically a letter.
(Only a few people know about his heartbreaking past.)
That's just something we say among ourselves.
This is my introduction. It's mine.
(It's up to me.)
It's like...
It's like an article for the tabloids.
(At a loss for words)
Yes, that's right. The tabloids.
It's just how I feel about him.
(Mr. A was to get off of the show at first, but he's frowned...)
"His behavior is frowned upon by many."
(by everyone as tells people that Running Man is the best now.)
- It's excessive. - It's totally for the tabloids.
- You praise the show excessively. - He's right.
- I'm not excessive. - And everyone hates it.
My goodness.
"Yoo Jae Suk."
"The official prankster of Running Man, Yooruce Willis."
- Okay. - Ji Suk Jin.
(He agrees.)
"Kim Jong Kook."
(Called "Kim Nipple" in summer and "Enema Kim" in other seasons)
"Called 'Kim Nipple' during summer and 'Enema Kim' in other seasons."
"Also known as 'Go Large' and won the Grand Award in 2020."
(Also known as "Go Large" and won the Grand Award in 2020)
- Congratulations! - Congratulations!
"And won the Grand Award in 2020." Congratulations!
(The Grand Award winners...)
(praise each other again.)
- Congratulations! - Congratulations!
(Quite displeased)
How long do we have to congratulate him for the award?
(How long do we have to congratulate him on his award?)
"Song Ji Hyo. Real name is Cheon Seong Im, Cheon Su Yeon."
"Nickname is 'Jeoktoma'."
"We can't say that she gets along well with the members,"
"but we also can't say that she doesn't."
"To cut a long story short, Ji Hyo is funny these days."
(Jae Suk loved Zoned-out Jeoktoma.)
Next is...
"Haha. He's the dad of three kids. He's officially an old fossil now."
(Haha is a father of three children. Official old fossil of Running Man.)
- "But he still doesn't know it." - Why am I an old fossil?
(He doesn't admit that he's an old fossil.)
"He doesn't want to admit it."
"Recently, he sent me half-dried herring".
- "He sent me half-dried herring." - Why tell us that?
Is it necessary to write about that in his introduction?
I wanted to write about things the viewers don't know.
(I chose to include it.)
Who is "me" in the introduction?
- That's me. - It's you?
(Meaning Jae Suk)
- You can't write about yourself. - All right.
(He turns an official website into his social media account.)
"Lee Kwang Soo. He can grow taller but he doesn't try harder."
- He doesn't try harder. - Hey.
You keep saying that.
- Then try harder. - Yes, drink some milk.
(He filed the same complaint...)
- He's right. - Why won't you try harder?
(the last time when they wrote what upsets them.)
- Drink milk and play basketball. - What are you talking about?
(He wants Kwang Soo to be a bigger person in the new year.)
Next is Jeon So Min.
"I've seen her for a while and she really is crazy."
"Yang Se Chan. Yang Se Hyeong's brother. Has handsome gums."
"It seems he has a girlfriend."
(He raises a personal doubt.)
- I don't. - That's all I have.
- Okay. - Okay.
It was good.
(It was like reading his diary.)
- It was very neat. - It was, wasn't it?
I thought it'd be better to write a lot about the show.
(Next up is Ji Hyo.)
(Filled)
You wrote a lot. It's very long.
(The length makes them look forward to it.)
"A show that makes the entire country, and beyond, run as one."
She's actually right.
(She wrote the production objective with sincerity.)
"Running Man carries out missions like we only live today."
"Eight members with different colors go through many troubles..."
"to deliver a great deal of joy and extraordinary entertainment."
She used all the fancy words she knows.
"Stay tuned for the charm of the eight members..."
"which we will show you anywhere and in any situation."
- Ji Hyo, I love that. "Stay tuned". - "Stay tuned!"
(An expected declaration by Ji Hyo)
- Stay tuned. - Okay.
Next is...
Who's the thug?
- "Kim Thug." - Okay, "Kim Thug".
(Kim Jong Kook, also known as Kim Thug)
"You'll be sorry if you judge him only by his muscles."
(Member introduction. Name: Kim Thug.)
"No one can catch up to his good sense and witty words."
- "All Mighty of all higher beings." - She's right.
"He likes to reveal his adorable side sometimes."
(Kim Nipple in the summer)
"He is unexpectedly charming."
- You're so right. - Yes.
You know exactly who I am.
(What did she write about Haha?)
"Small business owner."
"President Ha, small business owner in Mapo-gu."
That is funny.
- Small business owner in Mapo-gu. - That is funny.
"How capable and resourceful is he?"
"He's capable of both running a business and running on the show."
"President Ha is a greedy man who wants it all!"
Do you think it's appropriate...
to write that in the member introduction?
(The introduction is of no help for the variety show.)
You can't write about his personal business.
"He's capable of running a business."
(More like "Live Today" than Running Man)
- Well, he does a lot of things. - Hey.
It's my business.
- I wrote "a small business owner." - She can't compliment him...
(Ji Hyo found the appropriate word, a small business owner.)
for running his business well in the member introduction.
- What about Song Ji Hyo? - "Song Ji Hyo."
(Member introduction. Name: Song Ji Hyo.)
Well, I wasn't sure what I should say.
So I wrote, "Finally, she's trying to step out into the world."
Maybe that's how you feel.
"She's learning how fun it is to be out in the world."
"Song Ji Hyo is stepping out into the world."
Congratulations!
"Song Ji Hyo is going out into the world."
(Ji Hyo coming out to the world)
Congratulations!
Yes, you should communicate with others.
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo breaks out of her cave!)
(She steps foot out of her cave after 11 years.)
You're finally stepping out into the world?
Finally.
Song Communication.
(Song Communication followed by Song Jeoktoma)
Okay, Song Jeoktoma!
(Jae Suk is more excited about Ji Hyo's big decision.)
- Song Jeoktoma. - Yes, come on out. And call me.
Let's have a meal together.
We're supposed to be social distancing.
(Quickly apologizing)
(Pitying)
- Suk Jin. - In spirit only.
- Be with her in spirit only. - Sure.
(The gesture is enough.)
- In spirit only. My apologies. - All right.
Next is Ji Suk Jin.
(Anticipating)
"He doesn't know himself."
"He's the Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong who pretends to love his family."
I love it.
(Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong. He pretends to love his family.)
- "The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong." - Today...
Ji Hyo is stepping out into the world.
"The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong."
(She learns the gift of gab coming out of her cave.)
It was great.
"Find yourself falling for his charm."
"The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong."
What's that?
- It's kind of ambiguous. - Hugh Grant.
I'm not offended but can't say I'm pleased.
It's good since it's Hugh Grant.
Hugh Grant is amazing.
(It's still Hugh Grant.)
Yes, it's good that she compared me to him.
We got two amazing nicknames today.
(They gain a lot today.)
- "The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong." - And "Mr. Dirty Mustache".
(Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong and Mr. Dirty Mustache)
- Yes, "Mr. Dirty Mustache". - That's right.
"The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong" is funny.
(The originator is pleased.)
All right.
Hello, everyone.
(Next up is So Min.)
- Hi. - The production objective.
"The funniest show ever in Korea and in any country in the world."
(Production Objective)
"The only show you can enjoy both the old and the new."
"You can bite, chew, and taste. We are the real deal."
"The one and only semi-real variety show."
- "Semi-real variety show". - "Semi-real".
- It's a bit more than half. - Actually, it's 100 percent real.
- "The dealer of semi-real variety". - "semi-real".
(Production Objective)
"We guarantee your laughter, longevity,"
"love life, marriage,"
"and success in life."
Shouldn't it be "the leader", not "the dealer"?
Oh, right. It's "the leader".
(Byword)
- Wait a minute. - It's "the leader".
- He's right. - Wait a minute.
(Flustered)
- What is "a dealer"? - My goodness.
(The actress is more familiar with the word, "famous line".)
How can you make such a mistake?
How hard is it to make a PowerPoint? Am I right?
- No, no. It's a typo. - What is "the dealer"?
(Writer Jeon has a limited vocabulary unlike her sentiments.)
It's "the leader".
I knew the correct word.
I wrote "piller" as a typo too.
(Appealing)
I thought it was written correctly.
(Laughing)
"Piller" was a typo.
(She read it so naturally that no one noticed it.)
I confused "the leader" with "the dealer".
- Whatever. That's what you wrote. - It's "the leader".
- It's "the leader," everyone. - Okay, what's next?
(Moving on to the member introduction)
- Let's move on. - I knew the actual word.
Next is Ji Suk Jin, known as "The Senior".
- Gosh, it says "Ji Seok Ji". - What's "Ji Seok Ji"?
(Ji Seok Ji)
- Gosh. - You can't fix it now.
(Flustered once again by a ridiculous mistake)
She can't fix it.
(Name: The Senior, Ji Seok Ji)
What's "Ji Seok Ji"?
She can't fix it now.
No, she can't.
- If she wins, I'll be "Seok Ji"? - Sure.
You're "Ji Seok Ji" even if you say it backwards.
(The name, Ji Seok Ji, rhymes itself.)
It's the same even if you say it backwards.
"The lucky charm, the adorable, the youngest Jeon So Min."
(She acts cute when introducing herself.)
"No one knows who she really is."
"Running Man unveils her mysterious charm."
(Her introduction is quite long.)
(Flinching)
"She's good at acting, comedy, writing, and cooking."
"The perfect entertainer this generation wants."
"The best entertainer. How much more can she be charming?"
(Impatient Jae Suk steals the presentation.)
"We're lucky to have her!"
(She still does the move she prepared.)
All right.
- It's Suk Jin's turn. - I think...
(Suk Jin has been waiting for a long time for this.)
everyone's good enough to be picked.
- Yes, everyone's good. - Right.
(Their introductions are above average.)
- They're not bad. - If I win,
- mine will be posted, right? - Yes.
(Confident)
All right.
(Production Objective)
The production objective.
"The new hearth of Running Man,"
- "Ji Suk Jin leads the new show." - "Hearth"?
"The new hearth of Running Man, Ji Suk Jin leads the new show."
- "Hearth"? - Running Man.
- Wait. - What?
- Are you nervous? - No.
(Laughing)
Wait a minute.
(Finding a reason to tease him)
- Well, I think... - I'm not nervous.
it's been a long time since he was in the center of attention.
You said, "The new hearth of Running Man."
(His "hert" exploded as he was too nervous.)
- "Every week, Ji Suk Jin..." - Don't be nervous.
"fights against the seven losers."
(Ji-rasoni's presentation is facing difficulty from the beginning.)
Don't be so nervous.
All right.
Just hang in there.
Hugh Grant!
(Jamwon-dong Hugh Grant makes you want to cheer for him.)
- Hugh... - Please be quiet.
(Gentle)
"He can't be fooled, but he pretends that he is."
(He brings a big laugh from the start.)
"His name tag can't been ripped..."
(Production Objective)
"but he lets them rip it off."
The word spacing is terrible.
It's not "can't been ripped". It's "can't be ripped".
("Can't be ripped")
Other words are wrong too.
(His lonesome fight began not long after one line.)
- Just let it go. - I can't believe him.
His grammar is terrible.
Just let it go.
"I sacrifice myself to giving hope to the younger members."
(Grammatical errors)
"I is the Giving Tree, Captain Ji."
(He makes 3 grammatical errors in a row.)
Shouldn't it be "am" not "is"?
"I is"?
(He's dying of laughter.)
"To giving hope"?
He wrote, "to giving hope".
(Trying to come up with an excuse)
It's because...
the keyboard arrangement is different from my generation.
Is it a regional dialect?
Your generation didn't even have a keyboard.
- "The Giving Tree, Captain Ji." - What's wrong with you?
(He firmly resumes his presentation.)
"It's not just a variety show anymore."
What's wrong with him?
"In the endless cold betrayal betrayal..."
Why did you write "betrayal" twice?
What does that mean?
- I'm sorry I wrote it twice. - What does that mean?
(In a tricky situation of betrayal betrayal...)
My goodness.
You're unprepared.
(They criticize him for repetitive words that were clearly not...)
Why would you write "betrayal" twice?
(effective in emphasizing the meaning.)
My goodness. This is making me cry.
(His production objective is hard to read without tears.)
- Gosh, this is so funny. - That's not it.
- Gosh. - This is...
He was surprised too.
"Endless cold betrayal betrayal..."
(He froze on the second betrayal.)
- He was like a broken record. - Wait a minute.
I'm sorry that I wrote the word twice.
(Admitting it)
Okay, member introductions.
What's this? "Jan Seo Min"?
I'm so sorry.
- My goodness. - Why so many typos?
(He keeps stopping because of typos.)
- Suk Jin. - "Any litle?"
(Adding Jan Seo Min to Ji Seok Ji)
- It's just the order. - It's "Any little thing."
"Any little thing can make her go crazy. No one can control her."
(Typos)
- "The biggest fool on the show." - Why did he make so many mistakes?
"Buckteeth Se Chan"
(Filled with criticism)
"The ugliest."
"He's all talk but no sincerity."
It's witless.
Song Ji Hyo. I named her "Zoned-out Girl."
(You can't tease him for saying the truth.)
(Trying to ignore them)
Song Ji Hyo. "Zoned-out Girl."
I named her "Zoned-out Girl."
(Yawning)
It's not witty.
"Zoned-out Girl," the next "Young Gu".
(Continuing)
- "Running Man's new fool." - Wake up, Haha.
(Ji-rasoni the icon of patience tries hard to keep going.)
We're still filming.
Wake up, Haha. We're still filming.
(He faints as the boring story is told.)
Wait a minute. Wake up, Haha.
(Ji-rasoni loses his temper after Haha faints.)
Jae Suk, Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk! - We're filming.
Jae Suk, wake up!
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk is also acting.)
Jae Suk, wake up.
- What? - We're still filming.
(Ji-rasoni's lonesome struggle continues as expected.)
Okay. Look alive, guys!
I fell asleep.
Hang in there, guys. He's almost done.
- Gosh, I fell asleep. - He's no fun.
(Acting up)
- Okay. "Lee Kwang Soo." - He's not done yet?
(But this can't stop Ji-rasoni.)
"Now he's 350cm tall."
- "He entered the Guinness Book." - It's already morning.
- Haha! - "How tall will he get?"
(He tries to bring up the energy with a loud voice.)
Okay, next.
- This is exhausting. - "Kim Jong Kook."
(Member Introduction. Name: Kim Jong Kook, New Race Starter)
- Another typo? - "The starter of the new rase."
- There's another typo. - "Experienced much muscle loss."
(His voice becomes smaller compared to the start.)
"He suddenly lost so much muscle."
"His thighs are as slim as Suk Jin's arms now."
"Now he's the weakest member of Running Man."
(He squeezes out all his might, )
It's like the principal is giving a speech.
(but it ends up becoming a school principal's speech.)
- Suk Jin. - What?
- What? - Your face turned red.
No, no. I'm fine.
It's not funny at all.
- Suk Jin. - Just keep your mouth shut.
(Actually, I'm not okay.)
- It's really not funny. - Don't say a word.
- "It's really not funny." - Next is Haha.
(Acting up)
I laughed so much my stomach hurts.
I'm talking about Haha, you punk.
Suk Jin, are you upset?
(Acting up)
Yes, I am upset, you punk!
(The prankster is the most excited when he's teasing Suk Jin.)
- He's embarrassed. - Are you all right?
I'm fine.
- Okay, next page. - My mouth hurts.
(He calmly continues with his presentation.)
Gosh, my cheekbones hurt.
"Ji Suk Jin, known as 'Ji-rasoni'."
- "He's there." - Suk Jin.
Suk Jin noticed it.
He just scanned the entire room.
- Hey. - He sensed it.
(Suk Jin instinctively realized that it'll be no fun.)
Stay quiet.
"There is no need for further explanation."
(Stubborn)
- Is that it? - "Yoo Jae Suk."
It says dirty.
"Yoo Jae Suk announced his retirement this year."
"This is his last work."
- "Pay attention to him." - He's Ji Grant.
Give me a white towel.
- We don't have a white towel. - Get him one.
(They want to protect Ji-rasoni by throwing a white towel.)
Get me a white towel.
Suk Jin is about to cry.
It's hilarious.
(Goodness)
Gosh, it was so funny.
Suk Jin, is it over?
What?
(He says mean things half-seriously, half-jokingly.)
Why are you swearing?
(Ji-rasoni finally loses his temper after 11 years.)
- Why are you swearing? - Why are you taking it off?
- Why are you swearing at us? - Why are you upset?
(Despite his anger, he takes off his jacket to do no harm.)
Why?
What's wrong?
(He even walks out of the site.)
- Fine. Do what you want! - Come here.
- It's so funny. - Suk Jin.
(I laughed so hard that my stomach hurts.)
- Come here. - Suk Jin.
(He acts reluctant to return as other members escort him back.)
- Don't be upset. - Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin sulks for the first time in 11 years.)
(Now he finally shows his humane qualities.)
Why are you swearing?
All right. You can watch Suk Jin swear on YouTube.
It's called "Spicy Version Ji Suk Jin".
(Running Man Camera: Spicy Version Ji Suk Jin)
It's so funny.
I'm sorry I lost my temper.
(As always, he quickly apologizes.)
I laughed a lot.
(Extremely pleased)
It's hilarious.
(An event that happened for the first...)
It's killing me.
(in 11 years ends peacefully.)
This is so funny.
I want you guys to pick...
the worst introduction each.
- Can I say it? - Hey.
- Don't do that. - You're really mean!
(Laughing)
(After mocking Suk Jin, they try to scapegoat someone else.)
- There's no need to say. - Do you really not know?
No need to say it.
- Why do you even ask? - Do you really not know?
(Don't misunderstand. Everything is going according to the rules.)
You should pick the worst one.
(Who had the worst introduction?)
- 1, 2, 3. - I can't pick.
Who picked Suk Jin?
(5 out of 8 members picked Suk Jin's as the worst.)
- Me. - Me.
- Me too. - Four people.
- 5 people. - There are 5.
There are five.
(5 out of 8 people)
Jae Suk, Se Chan, and Kwang Soo got one vote each.
(Who had the worst introduction?)
And Suk Jin got five votes.
Like I said, today's special is Running Man Rewritten.
(Running Man Rewritten Race)
The winner's content will be posted on our website.
(Only the winner's content will be posted on the website.)
I'll have mine go on the website.
We have two kinds of roulette here.
(There are two types of roulettes.)
The first one has your names on it, and we will spin it at the end.
(The first roulette: a roulette of names)
It has 40 spots with 5 name tags each.
(It has 40 spots with 5 name tags each.)
We will spin it to decide the winner.
(The name that is picked during the final round will be the winner.)
And the other roulette is about benefits.
(The second roulette: a roulette of benefits)
The winners of each mission will spin this roulette...
(The winner of each mission will turn and win the benefits.)
and win the benefit they pick.
According to the roulette, you will have more...
(According to the result of the benefit roulette, )
or less name tags on the roulette.
(the number of name tags on the roulette can change.)
And you will get paid as much as the number...
(They will get paid as much as the number...)
(of their name tags on the roulette.)
of your name tags on the roulette.
- Really? - Good.
If you have more name tags on the roulette, you'll get more money.
(If they have more name tags on the roulette, )
(they'll have higher chances of winning and more money.)
It increases the amount of money.
We will start the first mission once you get changed.
(They will start the mission after getting changed.)
- What is this? - What's that?
(They move to the first mission site.)
What is this thing?
(A mysterious advanced rail...)
It's getting more advanced.
I'm really curious. Who comes up with games like this?
(and balloons filled with something inside welcome them.)
This is amazing.
- My goodness. - There's flour. Is this flour?
What? Is that flour?
(It's not flour, it's whipped cream.)
- I think this one is better. - What's that thing?
- Are they marbles? - Marbles.
(This is...)
It might break my head.
- It can't break your head. - This is the worst.
(Don't exaggerate.)
I might break my head.
(At his age, he must watch out even for the falling leaves.)
This one is...
It's like jelly. It's called frogspawn.
(It won't break your head.)
- That's just... - It's not hard.
How can someone be so untrusting of our production crew?
A member like that...
I can't believe this.
(That's him.)
You should have a meeting and rule him out.
The production crew wouldn't put metal marbles in there.
(Ji-rasoni kicks him.)
(He takes out the remaining anger from the previous presentation.)
Hey, stop it.
I saw Suk Jin punch the wall in the restroom earlier.
- I almost cried now. - Why?
Suk Jin just kicked me, but it didn't hurt at all.
Come on.
(Just like how an old parent's whip doesn't hurt at all...)
- Jae Suk, that's so sad. - Hey.
(Everyone is in tears knowing his kicks don't hurt anymore.)
I just kicked you gently.
- I just kicked you gently. - What should I do?
(Poor Suk Jin.)
Kook Jong, it makes my heart ache.
(Jae Suk cries out loud thinking of weak Suk Jin.)
I know how you feel.
(When everyone worries about Big Nose...)
This camera is only for me.
(She discovers her camera.)
(She dominates the camera.)
- Hey, it's not for you. - It's not for you.
It's for all of us. It's for a full shot.
(So Min turned the full shot camera into a selfie camera.)
Jong Kook should be on the camera too.
This is for a full shot. Lean back.
(She blocked the full shot camera.)
We can be on the camera too.
- Don't block the camera. - She's right.
(She ignores them and continues to dominate the camera.)
My goodness.
We're rewriting the production objective for the year 2021.
(Let me introduce you to today's race.)
So we prepared missions that require a good hunch...
(Today's race is about returning to the beginning.)
and good wit which are necessary skills for Running Man.
(The missions require good hunches and wits.)
This is what I'm good at.
(It's habitual bragging.)
I have a good hunch.
Goofball is acting up again.
- What are you good at? - Goofball is acting up again.
(They can't help but laugh at Jae Suk's bragging.)
I really want to see you do something well.
- A good hunch and what? - I'm good at this.
I'm sure you will be covered in a floury mess in 10 minutes.
(Jae Suk's face will be covered in whipped cream soon.)
- Hey, stay quiet. - I'm pretty sure.
I can imagine that.
(The first mission to test their good hunches and wits)
The first mission is...
Know How It Feels to Run.
(Know How It Feels to Run)
You will give it a try one by one.
(A person will lie on the cart and stamp his or her feet once...)
You will lie on the cart and stamp your feet once...
to get as close as possible to the wall.
(to get as close as possible to the wall.)
And you will see...
(Yellow, green, and red zones denote the distance.)
the yellow zone, green zone, and red zone here.
- And the cart has an arrow. - There's an arrow.
(The distance will be measured based on the arrow of the cart.)
If the arrow stops on red, the water balloon will burst.
(Red: Water balloon)
If it stops on green, the marble balloon will burst.
(Green: Marble balloon)
If it stops on yellow, you succeed.
(Yellow: success)
If you fail to control the speed and bump into the wall,
(If the person fail to control and the cart hits the wall, )
the bell will ring,
(the whipped cream balloon will pop above his or her head.)
and the whipped cream balloon will burst.
That's the worst.
It'd be better to try it later.
- No. - No. That's not true.
(A united offense by the two Grand Award winners.)
Why are they being like that to me?
- Why? - You two should sit apart.
(I hate it.)
- But why? - Just sit apart.
(A Grand Award winner must know how to tease Kwang Soo.)
Why do you think it'd be better to try later?
- That's not true. - Why is that?
(Tell me.)
What?
(He stutters at the charisma of Kim Grand Award.)
I mean, I can see how hard it should be...
- Kim Grand Award. You're right. - All right.
(A great teamwork)
- I know. Why would it be better? - This is crazy.
(Two Grand Award winners will join this mission.)
Only the 1st and 2nd places will...
(Only the 1st and 2nd places will spin the roulette.)
- get to spin the roulette. - Only the 1st and 2nd places?
- Okay. - The order is important here.
(The order is important.)
Who will go first?
Suk Jin said he'd go first.
- Really? - When did I say that?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - He told me that.
(Suk Jin has no idea that he volunteered.)
- When did I say that? - Before we got in here.
- When did I? - You did.
- I didn't say that. - He said that.
(In Running Man, they always respect the elderly.)
It would be disadvantageous for me to go first.
- Will you go first? - Jam Hugh!
(Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong)
Do I get any advantages?
- Advantages? - Any advantages?
(Suk Jin stutters when he's flustered.)
- I need something. - Show us what to do.
- You're the oldest one here. - I'll go first then.
- Okay. - Are you serious?
(Jae Suk gives it a try bravely.)
He's cool.
I will give you a chance to practice.
- A chance to practice? - Okay.
(If that's the case...)
I'll go first then.
I'll do it.
(No.)
I want to go first.
(Jam Hugh hesitated and lost his chance to practice.)
Hey, this is... It goes like this.
(Lucky Jae Suk got a chance to practice.)
- I get a practice round, right? - Yes, you do.
Let me push it back for you.
(He tests with his feet.)
Look at this.
This is more sensitive than I thought.
(He gets talkative when he gets nervous.)
This is for practice.
- It's a practice. - You can practice it only once.
(There's only one practice round.)
Right.
(Where did Jae Suk stop?)
It's red.
- It doesn't slide well. - It's water.
(Water balloon)
- It's red. - You should push it hard.
(It's a lot harder than it looks.)
In this case, the water balloon bursts.
If it were a real round, the water balloon would've burst.
(If it was real, the water balloon would've fallen.)
Did you get the hang of it?
(Do you get it?)
He has no idea.
(You can tell.)
You should stop on yellow.
Are you trying it now?
No. I'll do it later.
- Why? - I'm not doing this.
(After just a quick try, the coward retreats.)
- Why? - You practiced it already.
No. I'll do it later.
Why?
I think we should decide the order again.
(His nose is blocked.)
- I'll go first. - Okay.
I'll go first.
(If that's the case...)
- Do you want to go first? - Yes.
- I knew it. He's Kim Grand Award. - Kim Grand Award.
(Kim Grand Award volunteers.)
Kim Grand Award steps up.
He's setting a good example after winning the Grand Award.
A gangster to a Grand Award winner.
He's "Protein Monster".
(He is the man who turned his life around.)
He's the Grand Award winner indeed.
(Kim Grand Award steps in!)
His heart is like a soy sauce dish.
(However...)
(He'll be different and live up to the name of the award.)
- You're amazing. - Since it's the new year,
- You're the best. - I should change my life pattern.
(Kim Grand Award will reborn as a person with a bigger mind.)
- I should stop waiting. - That sounds good.
(He got more talkative after winning the Grand Award.)
So I should stop there.
(Kim Grand Award gets ready.)
I can look at it, right?
- You can practice once. - Yes. This is a practice.
(Kim Grand Award gets to practice it once.)
- What was that? - Why?
(My mind is as narrow as a dipping dish.)
- Soy sauce dish. - Soy sauce dish.
(He was being cowardly pushing the cart.)
The practice is over.
- You should start now. - Start.
(It's a real game now.)
- You should start now. - Here I go.
Can I start?
- It should be twice as hard. - It slows down quickly.
(Will he clear his name...)
(and show the dignity of a Grand Award winner?)
It's water.
- Is it marbles? - Okay.
(It's the marble balloon.)
(Falling off)
This is the best one.
(The marble jellies fall straight onto his face.)
What was that? It wasn't so bad.
It just feels bad.
It just hurts your feelings.
(It's only a very light psychological attack.)
He did a good job though.
(Jong Kook ended up in the green zone.)
- This is pretty. - Okay.
- Feel them. - Didn't I succeed?
(The penalty isn't as bad as I thought.)
- No. - These are the marbles.
Who's up next?
- I'll go next. - I'll go next.
(The two cowards volunteer after seeing the weak penalty.)
I'm ready now, so I'll go first.
You should stomp your feet hard.
(Jae Suk quickly takes over the seat.)
You're right.
Jae Suk, you should start immediately.
(He's tried it before, so he gets ready quickly.)
- All right. Here I go. - Let's go.
Will he make it to the whipped cream?
Let's go.
(Jae Suk got the hang of it...)
(after a practice round. What about now?)
(He commits a foul.)
(With Kwang Soo's assist, the cart hits the wall.)
Oh no.
(He just committed a foul by force of habit.)
Gosh, this is...
(It's a whipped cream balloon.)
What's that?
- Oh no. - Gosh, this is...
(The grasshopper is covered with whipped cream.)
What's that?
(That's ugly.)
You pushed it too hard.
What's that?
(He pretends he doesn't know anything.)
(The fresh cream pack is good for skin-lightening.)
You can't do that already.
What should the rest of the members do now?
(Kwang Soo already started to cheat again.)
(I think someone just pushed me.)
- You can't do that already. - Are you all right?
(The victim is quiet while the assailant has a lot to say.)
You shouldn't have pushed it too hard.
It splattered all over.
(The conman aptly blames someone else.)
It was too hard.
What should the rest of the members do now?
(After 11 years, the unfair competition and fouls are normal.)
- Hey. - You pushed it too hard.
Didn't someone kick the cart?
You pushed it too hard.
(Acting innocent)
You should've done it in moderation.
I mean, I thought...
I pushed it at the speed of Mach.
(Flying beyond the stratosphere to reach the space)
- You just pushed it too hard. - It exceeded the speed of sound.
(He experienced the speed of light.)
- It was fast, wasn't it? - He's really strong.
Didn't someone push it?
- It just feels that way. - You have strong legs.
(That's not true.)
Gosh, I'm afraid to go next.
(Shaking in fear)
Suk Jin.
We shouldn't commit a foul anymore.
(From now on, there shall be no fouls.)
- "Anymore"? - We can't play the game this way.
We can't play the game.
(No fouls are allowed after Jae Suk.)
- No one should stand close. - We should play the game.
I think someone kicked me.
Me?
Ji Hyo, did someone kick me?
No. You just pushed it yourself.
Is it just my feeling?
- It's your feeling. - You just feel that way.
(Even So Min and Ji Hyo lie to Jae Suk.)
I think someone kicked it.
No, you pushed it too hard.
- Really? - It was really hard.
- Did I push it too hard? - Yes.
So you mean it's my fault.
(Are you saying...)
How many times do you have to ask that?
(Running Man members show great teamwork.)
Next up is Suk Jin.
(Meanwhile, Suk Jin is now ready to take off.)
I feel sad as I see him lie down on here.
Eternal youth.
(They get scared every time they play a game lying down.)
I hope you live young forever.
You need to kick a little hard to succeed.
(With their tearful advice, )
- Okay. Got it. - Okay.
(Suk Jin tries.)
It's hard to reach the wall. See?
(Will he succeed just like this?)
(Pushing the cart)
(Rapid acceleration)
Oh, no. That was so close.
(Hitting)
(He couldn't hold back and cheated again.)
Oh, no. That was so close.
He almost succeeded.
(Whipped cream fell.)
(Goofball couldn't resist it.)
- Is this how we'll play this game? - Come on, Jae Suk.
- Really? - What's the point?
(If this is how you're going to play...)
I'll just volunteer to get the whipped cream on my face.
That's a shame.
I didn't know it was a downward slope from here.
Oh, I think you're right.
It must be sloped here.
(Pretending not to know)
- It's flat. Trust me. - It seems...
Did you push me?
(Did you push?)
No, I didn't push you. I was standing over here.
(That's strange.)
- Really? - You kicked too hard.
(The production crew had no idea.)
Hold on. We can't...
Let's all sit on the cart from now on.
(The production crew had no idea about Jae Suk's cheating.)
- Right. That's a good idea. - Someone pushed me, right?
- Hey, someone... - This isn't fair.
- He did kick hard. - Did someone push me?
- No one pushed you. - Suk Jin.
- Are you sure? - Sorry?
(He can't even get mad because there's no evidence.)
- You kicked hard, Suk Jin. - Did someone push me?
By the way, my hunch was right.
I didn't know why, but I wanted to go first.
(He had a good hunch.)
- Exactly. - Isn't it strange?
(The energy of Grand Award continues in the new year.)
- Right? It's strange. - He kicked too hard.
(That's annoying.)
Did no one push me? I think someone pushed me.
I can't get mad because I'm not sure.
Suk Jin, you never lose your temper.
(What are you talking about?)
That's true.
True.
- He never gets angry. It's amazing. - Exactly.
(Suk Jin never gets angry in any situation.)
- I wonder why. - Why do you not feel anger?
If I were him, I would've gotten angry earlier at the opening.
(Teasing)
Suk Jin would never get angry over things like that.
- You see... - He has a big heart.
(Teasing)
- It's not that I hold back... - Let's keep provoking him.
- my anger. I don't feel anger. - Let's make him angry.
(He's trying to speak in a generous voice.)
He has such a big heart.
He plays along with any jokes. He's great.
I would've thrown my coat and made a scene.
He's so cool. I would've sworn harshly at everyone.
- He's a man with good manners. - Indeed.
(A big heart who has never gotten angry before)
- He really has a big heart. - Absolutely.
- You know I didn't get angry. - Of course, we know.
- I wasn't angry earlier. - He's so cool.
- Why would you swear? - Why did you take it off?
(He never swears or throws his coat on the floor even if he's angry.)
Why would you get mad?
(He never kicks a chair even if he's angry.)
I just did it to make you laugh.
(Suk Jin never gets angry even when they tease him.)
- I know. - He should publish a book.
- Are Suk Jin and Jae Suk out? - Yes.
- Hang on. - Can't you give us another chance?
(They suffered because of other's help.)
It's because you guys tried it in the beginning.
You can give us a disadvantage instead.
(He never nitpicks even if he's angry.)
- Deduct our score, for example. - Sit down, will you?
Jae Suk, we'll give you another chance if you want.
- I'll try again. - Because there was cheating.
Didn't anyone really do anything when I tried it?
(He still doesn't know to the end.)
- No. - No one did anything.
- Be honest with me. - You should kick hard, Se Chan.
Are you serious or what?
(Do you really not know?)
Honestly, I'm not sure.
(The production crew didn't know that Jae Suk cheated.)
There wasn't cheating.
I guess there was. There was cheating.
(He figured out later.)
I didn't see anything.
If Bo Pil says he didn't see it, he didn't see it.
(Because there's no evidence, Jae Suk gets to retry.)
Next up is Song Jeoktoma.
(Next is Ji Hyo.)
Here comes Song Jeoktoma.
(Here comes Song Jeoktoma.)
She said, "Here comes Song Jeoktoma."
She called herself Song Jeoktoma.
(Song Jeoktoma who acknowledges her identity waits in the lane.)
- That's good, Song Jeoktoma. - She's so funny these days.
- Song Jeoktoma, good job. - Where? Here?
(Song Jeoktoma's ready to run.)
Right, Song Jeoktoma. Let's go.
Push it hard, Ji Hyo.
(Song Jeoktoma looks stable.)
- Hard? Should I push it hard? - Yes.
(Song Jeoktoma who runs forward carries everyone's expectation.)
- Ji Hyo, this isn't a practice run. - Okay.
- Go, Song Jeoktoma! - Ji Hyo, kick hard.
- Here goes Song Jeoktoma. - Kick hard.
(Song Jeoktoma runs!)
(Where will Song Jeoktoma arrive?)
- Gosh. - Oh, boy.
She'll stop at the water balloon. She's the first.
(She soon stops.)
She got the water balloon.
(Popping)
Gosh.
- Song Jeoktoma. - It's a water balloon.
It's a water balloon.
(The water fell right on her belly.)
- Hey, Song Jeoktoma. - The water fell on her belly.
- On her belly. - That was funny.
(Song Jeoktoma took it with her stomach.)
- Gosh. My belly... - I told you to kick hard.
- It fell on her belly. - Song Jeoktoma.
- It fell on her belly. - It hit her belly.
(Her belly got wet.)
- It hit my belly. - I know.
- Did you hear the sound? - Song Jeoktoma.
(Song Jeoktoma who couldn't run fails.)
It fell right on my belly.
Good job.
(Following Ji Hyo, Se Chan, Haha, and So Min tried!)
No way.
(Only Se Chan reached the yellow zone.)
(Haha stopped in the green zone and came in 2nd.)
Did he succeed?
If Kwang Soo succeeds,
(Except for Jae Suk who'll retry, Kwang Soo's the last to try.)
the 1st and 2nd places may be changed.
(He's lying down on the cart bending his knees.)
It feels...
(He gets ready with a resolute face.)
- Kwang Soo, go down a little. - Go down.
- Go down. - A little more.
Kwang Soo, go down. Go down.
(Hitting)
- Hey, stop it. - Go down.
(His gesture has an inappropriate intention.)
- I'm just giving him a signal. - That's enough.
(I went down for sure.)
- I'm just giving him a signal. - Stop it.
- To tell him to go down. - Stop it.
- That's enough. - Darn it.
- Okay. You're almost there. - Stop it.
You're almost there. Okay.
(He barely calms down and gets ready.)
- Kwang Soo, come up a little. - What?
(Hitting)
Move up a little.
- Go back down. - Gosh. What are you doing?
(The playful guy can't hold back when he sees something funny.)
- Go down. - We're trying to help you.
- So you won't hurt your head. - Exactly.
(He's being considerate.)
- They're helping you. - You should trust us.
- All right. - Kick harder than you think.
(Kwang Soo tries after receiving a lot of care.)
Whenever you're ready.
- Trust me. - Kwang Soo, kick hard.
(If he succeeds, he and Se Chan will get to spin the wheel.)
I have a feeling that he'll succeed.
- Me too. - I think he'll do a good job.
You may begin.
(Stretching out his legs)
- That's good. - Because he has long legs,
(His long legs are perfect for the game.)
he's at an advantage.
Look at him. Because he has long legs...
(He reached the one-third point just by straightening his legs.)
He looks so ugly. His face is annoying.
(He stares at the goal with a blank look.)
My gosh.
Kwang Soo has a well-proportioned body.
(How well could he do using his optimal physical condition?)
(Kwang Soo started moving by kicking the board hard.)
(Will he continue the momentum and succeed?)
Goodbye.
(Cream fell on his face.)
(The whipped cream hit the mark.)
How could it fall right on his face?
(It fell right on his face.)
It fell right on the target.
That was perfect.
(The whipped cream fills his face completely.)
- It was placed in the right spot. - Nice.
- Good shot. - Kwang Soo, go back to your seat.
(Good work.)
Good shot.
You did such a great job, Kwang Soo.
- Go on. - I did that, right?
(Did you push me?)
- Yes. You did it perfectly. - Yes. No one touched you.
(Kwang Soo fails even after playing without disturbance.)
- I'm next. - Now...
Oh, right. Jae Suk will try again. Okay.
(Lastly, it's Jae Suk's turn.)
- Right. - We'll give you another chance.
- Of course. - It wouldn't be fair.
- We won't touch you. - Right.
He's a cool guy.
(He gets ready to replay after getting a promise to play fair.)
Here. You should wear a nose clip.
Hey, I don't need it.
- Hey, that's okay. - Really?
- You're such a weakling. - But if whipped cream...
- Stop it. - Your nose will run.
- Your nose will run. - I don't care.
(They think they saw him showing off earlier.)
Jae Suk, go down.
- After the shoot, he'll say, - Go down.
- "The cream keeps coming out." - Go down already.
- Go down. Come on. - Hurry up and go down.
(Suk Jin's worried about Jae Suk getting hurt.)
- Go down. Put your head on it. - Your head.
- Go down more. - A little more.
- Okay. - Good.
(He tries again after a warm touch.)
- Okay. - Watch me.
- Are you ready? - Go, Jae Suk.
Show everyone your accuracy.
- Watch how I do this. - That's great.
(His warmup seems frivolous.)
Let's go. Oh, my. He looks so skillful.
- I think he's calculating. - Watch me.
- Watch me closely. - Is he calculating?
- Watch me. - He's playing with the cart.
- Watch this. Watch how I do this. - He's playing with it.
- Here he goes. - Watch me.
(His crazy footstep controls the cart.)
Let's go. Bounce off of it. 1, 2, 3. Go.
Here I go.
(How well will Korea's best MC who focuses on laugh do?)
- Come on. - What's that, Jae Suk?
(He easily reaches the green zone.)
- Come on. - That's disappointing.
- Gosh. - Come on.
(Calm and quiet)
What's this? It's neither funny nor impressive.
- That's disappointing. - Try again.
(Everyone groans as it's boring.)
- What was that? - Gosh.
- He's the Grand Award winner. - He said...
I focus solely on laugh.
(He only pursued laughter, but he failed to make people laugh.)
I'm so disappointed.
- Neither whipped cream nor success. - It's hard to get what you want.
(Clucking)
It was boring.
Why did he have to try again if he would make it so boring?
He's disappointed in himself.
(He gets blamed for trying again.)
- Gosh. - I'm so upset right now.
(Everyone stops laughing.)
- Oh, man. - It wasn't funny or impressive.
- Jae Suk failed. - Is someone in there?
Bo Pil, edit this part out.
(The 1st mission ended as he asked to edit his part out.)
Gosh. That was disappointing.
I'll announce the result.
(Announcing the result of the first mission)
- Se Chan is in the first place. - Oh, yes!
- Haha is in second place. - All right!
Let's move to the next location to continue the second mission.
(They move to spin the roulette.)
- Okay. - It was disappointing.
(They have time to restore before the next mission.)
- Shall I call your stylist? - Hey, can you...
Can you bring a fresh team uniform...
(They have to get changed...)
(because of whipped cream and water balloons.)
and a T-shirt to wear under it?
(Everyone calls their stylists.)
Because it's wet. Hurry up. Thank you. Okay.
- It's sticky. - Do we have extra uniforms?
(Time goes on as they wait for their stylists.)
I'll call your stylist again to tell her to come back.
- What did you say? - Come again?
- Who pushed you? - I heard that you pushed me.
(Jae Suk)
- Yes, I pushed you at the end. - I know.
(Playing innocent)
Who pushed me? Was it Kwang Soo?
Yes, Kwang Soo did it.
(They're passing time again confirming the truth.)
It looks like your stylists...
(They need more time for their clothes to arrive.)
stepped out together and are coming back now.
- They'll be back in 5 minutes. - 5 minutes?
(They can't shoot in a white t-shirt.)
- Really? We should wait then. - Yes.
(So they started to wait again.)
- I didn't know. - I was surprised...
Or would you like to continue dressing like that?
Like this?
Hey... My gosh.
- I wouldn't mind, but... - Don't they look pitiful?
- Hey! - Don't we look awful?
(The trio in white t-shirts gets angry.)
- You guys look great. - Wearing this stained shirt?
(With whipped cream)
- But you look great in it. - Answer me.
- My gosh. We... - Then can I borrow a towel?
(They're embarrassed because of the dirty white t-shirt.)
- To cover the neckline? - Okay. All right. Let's do this.
- You guys look great. - Let's do this.
- You look great. - Those shows you direct.
(Angry)
I'll see how successful they will be.
It's not like that.
You want me to be on the show when it has yellow stains?
(The celebrity's outfit is extremely humble.)
You're on Running Man, so put on your running shirt.
- "Running Shirt Man". - Gosh.
- "Running Shirt Man". - Did you throw up while lying down?
- Why is your shirt clean? - The clothes are here.
(At that moment)
They're here.
Where have you been?
(Jae Suk's stylist arrives first to save his face.)
- Why hasn't my stylist come yet? - I brought you fresh clothes.
Where have you been?
I'm worried.
Could I be the only one without fresh clothes?
Suk Jin, you should...
I'll change my clothes so we can start the shoot.
- Wait. - Run, Jae Suk.
(Goofball is excited to make fun of Suk Jin.)
Let's hurry up before Suk Jin's stylist comes.
(Making a fuss)
- Come on. Hurry up. - Change your clothes.
- Hurry up and give me the shirt. - I look like a beggar.
Let's hurry up.
I should hurry up to prevent Suk Jin from changing his clothes.
This is driving me crazy.
- Hurry up! - What did you do?
(He opened the door and got surprised.)
- Come here. - Ji Hyo is in there?
(Ji Hyo was getting changed in the room he entered.)
What is wrong with you?
- Ji Hyo is in that room, Jae Suk. - Gosh, Jae Suk.
(Catch him.)
Jae Suk, why did you come in?
- You're unbelievable. - You startled me.
(Restless)
- What's wrong with you? - Goofball.
- Are you out of your mind? - You punk!
(Fortunately)
- Beat him up! - Come here.
(The naughty-boy-punishment team is on the move.)
We should teach him a lesson.
- She had her clothes on. - We'll punish you.
(Fortunately)
- Why did you do that? - Playful Child.
(She was actually changing her outerwear, and she was done.)
- He screamed after a long time. - I'm relieved, Ji Hyo.
- He startled me. - Ji Hyo, I'm relieved.
(Such a relief)
- You startled me. - She had finished changing clothes.
(His heart is still racing fast.)
- Gosh, seriously. - He hasn't screamed like that...
(They finally got something on Goofball.)
- in a while. - He screamed when he opened it.
(Screaming)
- Hurry up! - What did you do?
(Goofball may be playful, but he has a pure heart.)
I was the one who should be screaming, but he screamed.
(It was so funny.)
(Meanwhile...)
- Gosh, Goofball. - What is taking my stylist so long?
(Kwang Soo and Suk Jin's stylists haven't arrived yet.)
Suk Jin, why are you wearing a cartridge belt during a shoot?
(He puts on the wet clothes.)
- Oh, this is... - Let's begin the shoot.
(Kwang Soo wants to make fun of Suk Jin, )
- I need to change my clothes too. - He's wearing a cartridge belt.
(so he puts on Ji Hyo's clothes.)
- Kwang Soo, isn't that my shirt? - My stylist, where are you?
(The white T-shirt war between Kwang Soo and Suk Jin)
Look at Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, your uniform just arrived.
What is it? This is what I wore earlier.
- Just put it on. - My stylist!
(He grabbed whipped creamed clothes in a rush.)
Just put it on, Suk Jin. We'll begin the shoot now.
- Where are you, my stylist? - Let's go.
(While he shouts for his stylist, the shoot's about to start.)
- Where are you? - Let's begin.
- Wait. I haven't changed... - Good. The semi-real variety show.
- That's great. - This is a semi-real variety show.
(The semi-real variety show begins with one person half naked.)
This is unfair. You guys changed your clothes.
- That's why I told you to wear it. - My stylist!
- The next mission is... - Excuse me.
The next mission is...
Excuse me.
(Suk Jin got surprised.)
- Hey... - The semi-real variety show!
(The semi-real variety show is satisfactory.)
- This... - Suk Jin, wait.
(A semi-real variety show where it's real for only one person)
- This is true entertainment. - Nice.
- Nicely done. - Right?
(He finds something that will save the celebrity's face.)
This is of a similar color.
It's Chan Hee's.
- But... - There you go.
Unbelievable.
(An edgy style is accomplished...)
I love it.
(thanks to his friend Chan Hee.)
- But... - I love it.
I look like an old man who lives alone.
(The true face of a semi-real variety)
I love it.
- Live forever, Suk Jin. - Nice.
What's that?
- It suits you. - Live forever, Suk Jin.
(It suits him better than his clothes during the opening.)
It suits him, doesn't it?
It's time to spin the wheel for the first time.
(The first roulette will be spun.)
Se Chan and Haha, you will spin the wheel.
(The 1st and 2nd places of the 1st mission)
If the wheel...
lands on the section labeled "swap name",
you'll swap others' names for yours on the big wheel.
(They can replace someone else's name with their names.)
The one that says "absorb all seven names"...
means that you can swap out one of their names each...
(They can take all 7 members' spots with their names.)
for your own.
Land on "2 left and 2 right of the selected",
and you'll be able...
(Their names will be on 2 spots on both sides.)
to swap the name in which the big wheel lands on...
as well as 2 on its left and 2 on its right.
Some will land you at a disadvantage though.
(But they're not all good.)
If you're told to add the name of the worst member,
(The worst member they selected earlier today...)
the worst member you selected earlier today...
(will replace their names.)
will have his or her name replaced with yours.
Suk Jin, stop trying to look good.
- Wear it like you did earlier. - Why?
(The man with the padded vest dressed up again.)
Why did you make it look cool?
I had it on backward earlier.
(Even his clothes are semi-real.)
The tag was on the outside.
- Gosh. - Are you all right?
(Pretending to be worried)
- Are you okay? - No, and it's no thanks to you.
(I hate you the most.)
I can still smell the whipped cream.
(He feels the happiest when teasing Suk Jin.)
You should just head home today.
(Worried)
I will if you do.
(Clenching his teeth)
- Go home. - Haha, you're up first.
(Haha who was in the 2nd place will spin the wheel.)
Okay, let's do this.
- Here we go. - Sure.
(Haha can win the chance to change up to 7 slots with his name.)
(It can elevate one's chance of winning.)
Let it be the worst one.
Okay, here we go.
No way. Not that one.
(Which will it land on?)
Is it mine?
(He gets to change three slots in his name.)
Three slots in my name!
(Everyone's disappointed.)
- How boring. - Could it be more boring?
(It's neither boring nor too good.)
- He got one of the best ones. - How bland.
Swap out the names of the ones you hate.
(Haha can replace someone's name with his name.)
- You've gotten all boring. - The one you hate.
Yes, the one I hate.
Why would that be me?
You called me Mr. Dirty Mustache.
- He's right. - Darn it.
(He gets rid of the originator of Mr. Dirty Mustache.)
Mr. Dirty Mustache!
(Se Chan's chance of winning and prize money have decreased.)
- Yes, take out Se Chan's name. - Right.
- Take out Se Chan's name. - He called me B-rated.
(Well done, Haha.)
There's one over here.
(He gets rid of So Min and Suk Jin's slots...)
- No, it's better over here. - Of course.
(and puts his name on them.)
- Why are you taking out my name? - Of course, he should.
Se Chan, go!
(Now it's Se Chan's turn.)
- Go. - Let's go.
Nice!
Go round and round.
Land on the one with seven slots.
That's what you'd expect from a comedian.
(Laughing)
Go round and round.
(Yang Se Chan, Comedian)
(Every moment is exaggerated.)
Did you see that?
- He's just like Se Hyeong. - You're more like Boom.
(Which slot will it land on for the born comedian?)
- No, not that one. - Just one slot!
(He gets to change one slot which is even more boring.)
He only gets to change one slot.
- This is what I get for winning? - Nice.
(Disappointed)
Take one of Haha's slots.
(Se Chan can take off one name.)
But it's better to have my name up here.
(Touching Suk Jin's)
Why would you take my slot?
Of course, he should.
(He touches Suk Jin's name tag as everyone is after Suk Jin.)
Suk Jin's the one you hate.
- Right. - Take both off.
Why would you take my slot?
- Take Haha's. - He has the most right now.
Haha has the most.
- Is this you being angry? - Of course not.
(By any chance...)
"Of course not."
That was never the case.
(This true gentleman has never been angry for 11 years.)
- I'll take this one. - That's the correct choice.
Don't listen to others and go with your gut.
(Se Chan takes the slot that Suk Jin currently occupied.)
- Okay. - All right. Nicely done.
- How are we supposed to sit? - What's this?
(Ji-rasoni finally changes into the new uniform.)
We should sit in two rows.
Here's the last game.
(The long-awaited final mission)
Just like the previous games,
this one will require your wits,
(The final mission requires...)
your concentration, and gut feeling.
(their wits, concentration, and gut feeling.)
- Again? - Concentration too?
(Joint Responsibility Quiz)
This is the Joint Responsibility Quiz.
- Joint Responsibility Quiz? - A quiz?
(It's a quiz. I'm done for.)
- A quiz? - I'm doomed.
- Gosh... - Okay!
- Hold on. - All right!
(Fluttering)
Don't touch me.
I'll make him be more active.
Okay!
He's showing more excitement now.
- That's the spirit. - Let's do this.
None of this makes me angry.
- Okay! - Get him excited.
- I'll get him to be more active. - All right.
Like this.
(Suk Jin becomes a human guitar.)
(Big Brother Big Nose turns 60 soon.)
That tickles!
Suk Jin's loving it.
(Bringing up the energy)
That tickles!
(Big Nose enjoys his new character.)
- There. You're all good. - You can sit back up.
- You're to stay later on. - All right.
(He makes light of Se Chan.)
Why are you only saying that to me though?
Jong Kook can just go.
(Jong Kook)
The last game...
will be played in groups of 2.
(The last mission will be completed in teams of 2.)
You and your partner will answer the questions...
(The partners will take turns to answer the quiz...)
given by the staff.
Get it right and you'll earn 10 points.
(and get 10 points if they say the correct answer.)
The team with the highest score will win this game...
(The team with the highest score gets to spin the roulette wheel.)
and get a chance to spin the wheel.
I should at least get a chance to spin it.
Team play is required, right?
(As it's Joint Responsibility Quiz, teamwork is very important.)
So we must answer one each.
I won't be favored then.
You can't discuss with your partner,
(But they cannot discuss among themselves in the middle.)
so choose your partner wisely.
- We'll select the teams then. - Sure.
(Time to choose their partners which is critical to the mission)
We ranked you...
by how well you did on the quizzes...
(We've determined the ranking of the members...)
throughout 2020 on Running Man.
(based on their quiz results in 2020 on Running Man.)
- Really? - You never know.
I'll reveal the ranking starting from up top,
(The rankings will be revealed from number 1.)
so raise your hand if you wish to partner up with that person.
(They can raise their hands if they want to be partners with that one.)
The person will choose who he or she wants as a partner.
(If there are more than one, the person gets to choose.)
- Okay. - Good.
Let me reveal who had the highest score.
I should raise my hand every time.
(The weakest at quizzes)
Getting the most answers on quizzes in 2020 was...
It has to be Jae Suk.
(2020 Running Man Quiz, 1st place)
Getting the most answers on quizzes in 2020 is...
Do you know what hyeongseoljigong means?
(Here are the candidates.)
Well...
Something complex...
An area!
He's demonstrating hyeongseoljigong right now.
I mean...
(During the proverb quiz)
1, 2, 3.
- Quail eggs. - Being hungry!
Being hungry! Did you say quail eggs?
(Pure and innocent)
And you'll make it out alive.
Be a nutjob!
What's the name of the vice-president?
(Despite their lack of knowledge, )
- Kamala Harris. - Jeoktoma!
(we still saw hope in 2020.)
(Who's number 1 in 2020 that made countless funny scenes?)
Getting the most answers on quizzes in 2020 was...
It has to be Jae Suk.
- It's Yoo Jae Suk. - Okay.
Me!
(They all raise their hands.)
Everyone raised their hand.
(Sighing)
Suk Jin...
- Everyone raised their hand. - Me.
(Reluctantly)
Suk Jin reluctantly raised his hand.
(Laughing)
Suk Jin raised his hand too late.
That can happen, you know.
(He defends himself worried he might have a disadvantage.)
He was late to raise his hand.
Suk Jin raised his hand late.
- That can happen, you know. - It can't.
- Suk Jin, lower your hand. - Lower it.
(Suk Jin is eliminated.)
- Lower your hand. - We all raised ours instantly.
I raised it before hearing your name.
(Jae Suk will choose his partner among them.)
Our team will be too hard to beat.
- We shouldn't team up. - Exactly.
Jong Kook is on the smarter side,
- so we shouldn't team up. - But...
I'll probably win if I team up with Jong Kook.
(Feeling good)
- That's a high possibility. - We'll be unbeatable.
(He decides not to choose Jong Kook for the balance of the game.)
You should take him then.
(The weakest)
- 1 or 2... - It makes better sense.
Take me or Ms. Toma.
Ms. Toma or...
I should team up Ssaebssaeb,
(The candidates, Ms. Toma, Se Chan, and Kwang Soo)
- Ms. Toma, or... - Kwang Soo.
(Also known as the worst quiz players)
- I'm not as bad as them. - Or Haha.
- But... - I'm not as bad as them.
There's also Haha.
- What about So Min? - He's not as bad.
(Among the embarrassing candidates, )
- And Haha. - He's not as bad.
It'll be either Ssaebssaeb or Kwang Soo.
(Jae Suk has Se Chan or Kwang Soo in his mind.)
Kwang Soo isn't as bad,
- so take Empty Head. - Empty Head?
- How cool of you. - Empty!
(Empty!)
I love your confidence.
(At least Empty Head is number 1 in terms of confidence.)
Shouldn't you take me with you?
Team up with me,
(The other Empty Head gets anxious.)
and if I get to swap five slots...
Three?
(Quiet!)
Take Se Chan instead.
I was wrong just now.
(Jong Kook's touch had him lower his hand.)
I need to take a short break.
I need to rest a bit.
Okay, raise your hand!
- 1, 2, 3. - Me!
- I'll take Se Chan then. - Okay!
(Se Chan raised his hand alone while Kwang Soo can't raise his.)
Why didn't you raise your hand?
- Why can't you raise your hand? - You should've raised it.
- Kwang Soo... - Call me Kim Jong Kook.
- I choose Se Chan. - Okay.
(Pouty Mouth Brothers unite!)
I want to team up with Suk Jin.
- Okay. - Okay, good.
I want to team up with Suk Jin too.
(Suk Jin gets popular as they think he'll be in the 2nd place.)
I want to team up with Suk Jin.
I want Suk Jin as my partner.
- I want to team up with Suk Jin. - I want Suk Jin...
(Big Nose thinks about who he should pick.)
In second place...
is Jong Kook.
(Embarrassed)
Why did you stand up?
(He gets embarrassed expecting good news too early.)
Why on earth did you stand up?
- Sit back down. - His legs must be numb.
(He can't seem to take his seat as he's disappointed.)
I don't understand why you stood up.
Director Choi.
- Sit back down. - Are you sure he's in second place?
We counted all of the questions.
(He blames the statistics out of embarrassment.)
- But... - This is hilarious.
Why did you stand up?
(Followed by the 3rd place announcement)
In third place...
- is So Min. - What?
(3rd place, So Min)
- I'm in third place? - Really?
Are you sure you counted this correctly?
- I'm in third place? - Are you kidding me?
(Writer Jeon is better than they expected.)
- Me? - Hold on.
I remember her getting a lot of them correct.
(Man...)
- Suk Jin's in fourth place. - That's not so bad.
Haha's in fifth place.
In sixth place is Kwang Soo.
In seventh place is Ji Hyo.
And in eighth place is Se Chan.
Why? I already knew.
(Se Chan is the last place in quizzes in 2020.)
Se Chan's in eighth place?
Jae Suk, isn't it obvious?
Don't pretend to be okay with this.
- What do you mean? I'm fine. - You're upset with the result.
Why am I in third place though?
(Empty Head's tearful acting)
- I... - Se Chan, my gosh.
- I... - So raise your hand if you want...
(Those who wish to be on Jong Kook's team will raise their hands.)
to team up with Jong Kook.
If you want to team up with Jong Kook.
(He's in demand.)
- Because... - Teaming up with me though...
- Suk Jin. - We'll be a tough team to beat.
(Se Chan asks him to choose someone in low rank for balance's sake.)
Don't choose those of a higher ranking.
Come on.
He's right. Don't choose anyone of a higher ranking.
- Then... - Choose someone in the bottom.
The one in third place should give others a chance.
(Number 3 willingly gives others a chance.)
- I'll swap for you. - Hold on.
- Choose one of these two. - Exactly.
(Now he has Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo left.)
Either Kwang Soo or Ji Hyo.
These two are my only choice?
(The two candidates are seriously similar in their competence level.)
Kwang Soo or Ji Hyo.
Choosing Ji Hyo will humiliate me.
Jong Kook, I got Jeoktoma right.
(She makes him know that she got Jeoktoma right.)
- Jeoktoma? - Jeoktoma!
That's what you're bragging about?
- Why can't I? - "I got Jeoktoma right."
(Her glory from 5 weeks ago burst out at crisis.)
That happened weeks ago though.
Team up with Mr. Mullet.
(He chooses Mr. Mullet in 6th place by taking advice from number 1.)
- Okay, I'll take him. - Okay!
It's a good choice.
Please put on your vests and sit in rows.
(Jae Suk and Se Chan, Jong Kook and Kwang Soo, )
(So Min and Ji Hyo, Suk Jin and Haha)
All right.
- Let's go. - All right.
(They must solve quizzes in teams of 2 during this mission.)
Out of the many categories,
- I'll reveal the first one. - Sure.
The first...
(The first is the song quiz.)
- will be the song quiz. - Yes!
- I love quizzes like these. - You're good at this, right?
Yes, I am.
- I'll count on you then. - Two songs will play...
(Two songs, A and B, will play...)
and you will name the artists and titles respectively.
(and they will name the artists and titles respectively.)
You will hear three seconds of the first song's intro...
(They will hear 3 seconds of the first song's intro...)
(and then 3 seconds of the second song's outro.)
and then three seconds of the second song's outro.
- The outro of the second song? - Yes.
The intro and outro will be...
(Each member of the team will guess 1 song.)
from two different songs.
When you say that you'll answer,
(The producer will point at the person...)
I'll choose the one who'll answer first.
(to say his or her answer first.)
- Randomly? - Yes.
You will name the two songs...
(Who gets picked first is as crucial as the ability to guess the songs.)
- in that order. - Okay.
Artist or title?
The first one is to name the first song.
What's this?
(The Pirate Roulette Game seems to have a purpose.)
- It must have a purpose. - It seems that way.
We don't know...
- who he'll pick first. - All right!
The first song must be named first.
Here's the first song.
(Amidst tension, )
(the first round begins.)
Cue.
(The intro of song A)
(The outro of song B)
- Let me answer! - Okay.
(The intro of song A)
(The outro of song B)
(They'll succeed if they guess the song A and song B as a team.)
- I don't know the second song. - Let me answer.
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo goes first.)
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
PSY's... You know, this dance...
- Wrong. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
(They lose the opportunity only after giving away Psy.)
- We were faster. - Let me answer.
What's the song title, Ji Hyo?
(Jae Suk from Team Yellow Green was faster and got the chance.)
- We were faster. - Let me answer.
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
"New Face" by PSY.
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer. - Wrong? Really?
"New Face" by PSY.
(Is it not "New Face"?)
- Let me answer. - Wrong? Really?
"Gangnam Style" by PSY.
- Let me answer. - Wrong?
- Kim... You said the wrong one. - Let me answer.
(Why would you start with the second one?)
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
- Let me answer. - You said the wrong one.
(Team Yellow gets the chance to steal the answer.)
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
PSY's "Gangnam Style".
(But it's wrong.)
- No? - Let me answer.
Is the first song wrong? No, I'm sure it's the one.
(Didn't we correctly guess the first song?)
No. We all got the first song right.
We got it right.
(He's starting dancing.)
The song was so popular.
(He hummed the latter part.)
We used to sing this song whenever we went to a club.
(Song A is definitely "Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.)
- We sang it so many times. - Hold on.
- The song ends like that. - Exactly.
(Isn't Song B Psy's song?)
- We danced to the song too. - Yes, we did.
(The actual outro of "New Face" is actually...)
- That's why. - A strange woman
- I think it's PSY's "New Face". - I think so too.
(The outro of "New Face")
(The outros of Song B and "New Face" are slightly different!)
(The outro of Song B)
- Let me answer. - Isn't it "Gangnam Style"?
Haha, you go first.
PSY's "Face".
- What? - What's that song?
You should've said Kim Jong Seo's song.
(They can't get over "New Face".)
- Is it an old song? - Let me answer.
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
PSY's...
- "Hwitturu Matturu". - "Hwitturu..." Gosh.
Let me answer.
(Whenever he puts out a bait, Kwang Soo takes it.)
- Hey. - Wait.
Let me answer.
(Suk Jin raises his hand again.)
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
What's the point when I don't know the second song?
Can we hear it again?
- Let's hear it again. - We need to hear it again.
(Suk Jin just irresponsibly throws him under the bus.)
- Can we hear it again? - Let's hear it again.
(Song B still remains a mystery.)
- We need to hear it again. - PSY's "Gentleman".
(The songs will be played again.)
Yes, we should.
- No. - This is driving me nuts.
(The songs are being played.)
- I think it's the correct answer. - Jae Suk.
(Se Chan gets up as if he knows the answer.)
Let me answer.
- Jae Suk. - I heard off-beats.
Do you know the answer? Let me answer.
Se Chan goes first.
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
PSY's "New Face".
(He said "New Face" again.)
What are you doing?
Why did you even raise your hand when you didn't know the answer?
(He's a fool who only knows "New Face".)
How many times did they tell us it wasn't the answer?
- Why did you do that? - Why did you say the same song?
(A perpetual canon of "New Face" with only people changing.)
If you didn't know the answer...
They already told us it wasn't the answer.
I thought you knew the second song.
- But he let me answer first. - Hey.
I still think it's the correct answer.
(Only Se Chan knows the second song.)
- Try to guess the song. - I have no idea.
It has been changed.
(He tries to share the answer.)
- What are you two doing? - They're discussing.
That's not allowed.
(They got caught right away.)
- You shouldn't do that. - Is it not allowed?
- Hey, what are you doing nay? - You knew that.
"What are you doing nay?"
- "What are you doing nay?" - I mean, what are you doing now?
- Pardon? - You must've lost your mind.
- "You must've lost your mind"? - What did you say?
Don't be disrespectful to your senior comedian.
(Comedians)
- Why would you... - You were whispering to each other.
- Why would you speak thoughtlessly? - I didn't speak thoughtlessly.
Suk Jin, you've crossed the line.
How dare you?
(Playing with his glasses)
(It's the best way to stop a squabble.)
- He played with my glasses. - Come here.
I hate it the most. How dare you do that?
(Feeling insulted)
- You've crossed the line. - I hate it the most.
(Jae Suk stopped the squabble by touching his glasses.)
- Is that so? - How could you...
- If you... - Please sit down.
(Their attempts of a foul play failed...)
- You lose points if you discuss. - I was so surprised.
(and they return to their seats.)
- They shouldn't get to answer. - Let me answer.
From now on, if any team gets caught discussing,
(Points will be deducted if they're caught discussing.)
- the team will lose points. - Understood.
We're not allowed to whisper to each other in any case?
- Correct. - Let's just say it out loud.
It's obvious.
(Upon a consensus, they listen to the music a little longer.)
You really shouldn't do that.
- Here goes Level Four. - I'll go first.
- You should. - He picks the one to go first.
(The songs are being played.)
Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - Kwang Soo, you go first.
(Kwang Soo who didn't try last time gets to go first.)
- But we were faster. - Kwang Soo, you go first.
- Me? - Yes.
- 3, 2, - Kim Jong Seo's...
One.
(He only recites the name of Song A.)
- Okay. - "Beautiful Restriction".
Let me answer.
Okay. Jae Suk, you go first.
(Finally, Jae Suk goes first.)
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
"Up and Down" by EXID.
- Okay! - Okay!
(Correct!)
Let's get ready to dance.
(They happily dance to the girl group's song.)
Gosh. Hey.
- That's not how they dance. - What is this?
- This is... - What is this?
- What is this? - That's not how they dance.
It sounded like "New Face" earlier.
(Team Yellow Green gained 10 points.)
This is their dance move.
(Song A is "Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.)
(With the legendary song from 1996 as background music, )
(he's doing his frivolous celebratory move.)
He's annoying.
(He expresses the joy through silly dance moves.)
Gosh, I'm so upset.
Gosh. He's so...
(Annoyed)
- That was good. Great. - We did great.
(So the top and bottom duo gained the 1st 10 points.)
Up, down, up, up, and down
I thought it was "Like a Cat" by AOA.
(It's time for the next song.)
Here goes the second question.
Aren't there any common knowledge questions?
(Who will guess the next two songs?)
- Level 1 of the 2nd question. - Here we go.
I love this game. It's fun.
(The intro of Song A)
(The outro of Song B)
- I love this game. It's fun. - Let's do this.
(The songs are being played.)
Let me answer.
- Jong Kook, you go first. - I know the first song.
(Jong Kook raised his hand first this time too.)
Sharp's...
3, 2, 1.
- Let me answer. - I don't know the second song.
(Time's over.)
- Okay. - Jae Suk first.
(Team Yellow Green gets the chance.)
"Tell Me, Tell Me" by Sharp.
- I don't know the second one. - Let me answer.
- Gosh. That startled me. - What's this?
(At that moment)
(They messed up the order again.)
- What's that? - Let me answer.
- I don't know the second song. - What's that?
- Gosh. That startled me. - What's this?
(3 mysterious balloons fell without warning.)
- What's going on? - What is that?
(Confused)
- Happy birthday - What's this?
(They're singing a birthday song?)
- To you - Wait.
Is there something inside the balloon?
(However)
- What is it? - That was so sudden.
Is there something inside the balloon?
(Jong Kook popped a balloon and found something.)
- What is it? - That was so sudden.
He found something inside of it.
(He rushes to the pirate roulette.)
There's something in the balloons.
- He found something inside. - What is it?
What is it? What is this for?
(He finds swords from the balloon...)
- What is this for? - Can we just stick it in there?
(and places them inside the roulette.)
- The singer and the song title? - What is this?
(The pirate roulette was placed before the mission began.)
- The first one... - What's this?
The 1st one should say the 1st song.
(The quick-witted Jong Kook found it suspicious.)
- It must have a purpose. - You're right.
- What is this for? - Can we just stick it in there?
(Rushing)
Hey, wait. Wait.
- What is it? - Just stick it in.
(Ji Hyo popped a balloon late, and found a sword too.)
- What is it? - What is this?
It doesn't fit in the slot. Come on.
What? It doesn't fit in the slot.
(But the sword doesn't fit?)
I think we got the wrong swords.
There are real swords too.
(The secret behind the pirate roulette)
See? I popped the balloon as soon as it fell.
- I'm sure it's the right one. - Right.
(There are real and fake swords...)
(hidden in balloons that fall!)
- What is it? - What is this for?
(Se Chan picked up the real sword that Ji Hyo dropped.)
It doesn't fit in the slot. I think we got the wrong swords.
- I popped it right away. - It's a real one.
- I'm sure it's the right one. - Right.
- You can't try several times. - You can do it just once.
You have just one chance.
I thought... I found one...
- I didn't know... I thought... - It doesn't fit, right?
- You have just one chance. - Does yours fit in the slot?
(She tries again on the same spot.)
- Does it fit? - It doesn't fit, right?
It fits in the slot.
(Kwang Soo forces in a fake sword.)
Okay. Stop it. Hey, you punk.
- Gosh, seriously. - Gosh, you.
(Kwang Soo broke it.)
(The one with a fake sword caused trouble.)
You little...
- I'll stick mine in it. - Okay.
(Jae Suk has the last remaining real sword.)
If it pops out, do I get something?
Then you'll win.
(Can he gain any benefits if the pirate pops out?)
Stick it in and see what happens.
- Do we get a hint? - Maybe there's a hint.
Please. Please come out.
- Please. - Maybe there's a hint.
(Will Jae Suk's sword make the pirate pop out?)
Will it pop out?
(Anxious)
It won't pop out anyway. Just get it over with.
- Please pop out. - He's right.
(After much deliberation, )
- We didn't put in many swords. - So this is how it works.
(Jae Suk chooses a spot.)
- Gosh. - I told you so.
(Nothing)
So we need to stick a real sword in the right slot.
The person who makes it pop out will win.
(Finding a real sword is the key point.)
- Okay. - The quiz doesn't matter.
- They tricked us. - This is so difficult.
(The truth behind the pirate roulette no one knew!)
You get 10 points when you get 1 question right,
(10 points for a quiz, )
and you get 50 points when the pirate pops out.
(50 points if the pirate pops out of the roulette.)
This is a faster way to win.
Oh, boy. I should find out what the second song is.
(Finding the real sword is more important than quizzes.)
- Now, - They must be waiting upstairs.
we'll play Level Two.
(They try to resume the music quiz game.)
Wait. I'm sorry.
- I think someone just farted. - What?
- Why are you looking at me? - Gosh, Suk Jin.
- Why are you looking at me? - Hang on a second.
It can't be just a fart.
Do you have a diaper by any chance?
I'm serious.
- I mean... - You guys...
(Mr. Ji, the likely suspect)
- Due to extreme nervousness... - You guys...
(Is it a tragedy born of extreme nervousness?)
- He must be embarrassed. - He was laughing to hide it.
- Honestly, I don't think... - Don't try to set me up.
- it was you. - Okay.
The breeze is coming from that side.
(She suspects Ji Hyo.)
It wasn't me.
- Was it really not you? - No.
- What are you doing? - Gosh.
It wasn't me.
(She tried to submit evidence.)
- What are you doing? - Gosh.
- Ji Hyo, what's wrong with you? - I didn't do it.
You've been saying I smell bad since last week, but it wasn't me.
(Song Jeoktoma only looks forward.)
- It wasn't you? - Trust me. I didn't do it.
By the way, you've become so good at improvising.
It wasn't me.
(Precious Sisters saved their skin with Ji Hyo's wit.)
Let's move on. Play the music.
(The songs are being played.)
(Glancing up)
(Everyone seems to know Song A.)
Let me answer.
- Kwang Soo first. - All right.
- This must be the correct answer. - I know this song.
(It's important to guess Song B.)
Kwang Soo first.
- This must be the correct answer. - I know this song.
- I know this song too. - I listen to it very often.
"Tell Me, Tell Me" by Sharp.
"One Man" by Kim Jong Kook.
Okay!
(Correct)
- This is... - I can't believe this.
- This is unfair. - I recognized it right away.
(Song B with the familiar outro is "One Man".)
I did great, right?
(It's Jong Kook's hit ballad song that won women's hearts in 2004.)
Thank you.
(This is the outro they just heard.)
- You can't play his song. - He's right.
What's wrong with playing my song?
- Play my song too. "I Know". - What's wrong with it?
It was advantageous for him.
(This one-time singer is questioning the fairness.)
Your song wasn't a hit song, but mine was.
- What does that have to do with it? - No wonder it sounded familiar.
(Bickering)
Exactly.
(Balloons fell right then.)
(As soon as the balloons fell, )
Darn. It's a fake sword.
(everyone started fighting to get a balloon.)
(Find a real sword.)
(Meanwhile, So Min got lucky and picked up a real sword.)
Darn. It's a fake sword.
(She's going straight to the pirate roulette to stick the sword in it.)
(He threw a sword in the air!)
- It's a fake one too. - Hey, why did you do that?
(He spread fake swords to confuse the other members.)
You punk!
- It's a fake one. - Is it a fake sword?
(After a while, the members find all the real swords.)
- I didn't find any. - Like I said,
(But Team Yellow didn't get any real swords.)
don't get too excited when you find a sword. Okay. Good.
This is a fake sword, right?
(Team Red tries to put in the sword.)
It didn't pop out.
She stuck it right into the slot.
(Song Jeoktoma pulled it off.)
I did it. I made it pop out.
- We made it. - This is unfair.
(Precious Sisters earn 50 points.)
- I'm so excited. - This is so pointless.
It's not bad.
(They may not be good in quizzes, but they're extremely lucky.)
We're doing all right.
We won 50 points.
- Nice. - Oh, man.
(Feeling void)
Let's take our time.
Song Jeoktoma is the best.
(Team Red instantly wins 50 points, 5 times more than the quiz.)
- What a shame. - Song Jeoktoma made it.
You see, this is like dog training.
I can't help but look up.
Just like Pavlov's dogs drooled when they heard the bell ringing.
(They're conditioned to respond to balloons.)
- Like dog training. - It'd be funny...
if they throw balloons in front of us.
I don't understand. What was the point...
of ranking us for our quiz?
It's pointless.
You didn't choose him for the quiz anyway.
Jae Suk.
You chose me for the quiz, right?
- Of course. - Thank you.
We won a lot of points thanks to the game.
(The comfort doll is more useful for morale than quizzes.)
Please sit down. You're blocking Kwang Soo.
Was he hidden from view all this time?
- I didn't know. - Sit up straight.
(He barely secures the camera after 10 minutes.)
No wonder. I couldn't see anything.
Kwang Soo is better suited for group shots anyway.
Come on!
(A group shot for Kwang Soo)
There's no such thing.
Here comes the next quiz.
(With a customized camera angle, )
(the third set of songs is being played.)
Play the music.
(Intro of Song A)
(Outro of Song B)
- Hang on. - I know the first one.
Then answer it.
(Jae Suk always hits the nail on the head.)
I'm not sure about the first song. Hold on.
(They don't have a clue yet.)
Can you play it longer?
Level three. Play the music.
(The intro and outro are played again.)
(Music playing)
I know this song!
You do? I know the second song.
- I know the song. - All right. I know the second song.
(They got Song B.)
- I know the 2nd song too. - I know the 2nd song too.
(They need to guess Song A.)
- You know the 2nd one? - We got the 2nd song.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
"I Have a Girlfriend" by Park Jin Young.
- "A Winter Story" by DJ DOC. - Let me answer!
(Incorrect)
- "A Winter Story"? - Let me answer. I was faster, no?
Go ahead, Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook tries first.)
"I Have a Girlfriend" by Park Jin Young.
"Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung.
That's not it. Let me answer!
(Incorrect)
- Park Jin... - Haha, go first.
(Haha of Team Blue tries first.)
Park Jin Young's "That House Is Mine".
Let me answer.
- What kind of song is that? - "My House Is Yours".
- Let me answer. - I thought he knew.
(He summarizes the lyrics simply.)
- "Your Baby Is Mine Too". - Two...
- Let me answer! - Se Chan, go first.
(Se Chan shouts in confidence.)
- You'll all be surprised. - Hurry up.
(Making a fuss)
- 5, 4, 3, - It's Rain's...
- 2, 1. - "How to Avoid the Sun".
- 3, 2, 1. - Let me answer.
"Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung.
- That's it! Jae Suk! - You gave them too much time.
(Correct)
(Team Green got the answer twice in a row.)
- They were too slow! - That was fantastic.
Come on.
(They're showing an unsightly ceremony again.)
Don't throw the balloons just yet! Watch our performance first.
Don't throw the balloons just yet!
(The audience turned their backs on the stage.)
Watch our performance first.
(Desperate movements to attract their audience)
Give them to us now!
- Watch us, Suk Jin. - Throw them now!
(Untact spectating)
(Responding to their performance without even watching)
- Throw them now! - Watch us, Suk Jin.
(Without audience or balloons, the ceremony ends.)
- Gosh. - That one was...
- Seriously. - You counted for too long.
- Give us a break. - You're playing favorites.
(Give us a break.)
- Don't count the second one. - We didn't discuss at all.
(The participants complain as the answer took time.)
- Let's not count it. It's absurd. - You went too easy on them.
- Don't count it. - Who didn't know the answer?
Then let's have the Grand Award winners play rock-paper-scissors.
(They suggest Grand Award winners play rock-paper-scissors.)
- With whom? - The Grand Award winners.
Gosh, you want me to play rock-paper-scissors with him?
(The rock-paper-scissors will decide who gets 10 points.)
So if I win against Jong Kook, everything will be settled?
That's not it. Listen.
If Jong Kook loses, let's not argue against it anymore.
- Okay. - Make sure to win, Jae Suk.
- All right. Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- All right! - It's the best of three.
(Jae Suk wins.)
- Come on! Stop it! - We lined up behind him.
- All right! - It's the best of three.
(The class of the Grand Award winner who goes back on his word)
- Stop it. - He said they lined up.
(Let's cut him some slack.)
We even lined up!
- Goodness. - Yangsebari, come here.
Yangsebari, come here.
- At least two people should play. - I'm sorry,
- but did you win the Grand Award? - No...
- Then he's not qualified to play. - That's not it.
(He's not qualified.)
He's just a research subject.
I'm one to get vaccinated first.
You're the first one to get vaccinated?
- If you want to play, come closer. - You have to win one more round.
If you want to play, come closer.
(The three steps hurt his pride.)
- Why do you want to play it? - You must come closer.
Why do you suddenly want to play rock-paper-scissors?
(He can barely move.)
Come closer if you want to play.
- Just play one more round for him! - I mean...
- If you want to play... - Come this way.
- I mean, if you want to play... - If you want to play, come closer.
(Distance expanding in real time)
If you want to play, swallow your pride and come closer.
I'm going to you.
(He gives up on the pride as a research subject.)
If you want to play, follow us.
- He can win it, you know. - It's so funny...
- He can win it. - Suk Jin is following them.
- Let's play it. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- All right, I won. I won! - Darn it.
(Suk Jin lost.)
He lost. Goodness.
All right, I won against him.
- He even threw away his pride. - How annoying.
(The research subject returns after giving up his pride and losing.)
The protruding mouth brothers are getting ahead!
- Okay. - Just give it to them.
(Round 1 ends with Team Green receiving 20 points.)
- But this is absurd. - Just give it to them.
- Here come the next quiz. - Okay.
(The production crew tries to explain the next quiz.)
Kwang Soo, you have to listen to the rules.
Kwang Soo, you're in charge of the balloons.
(Empty Head can only rely on balloons.)
- Okay. - This time,
you'll be playing the Guess Who Quiz.
(It's a quiz on foreign figures.)
We'll show you a picture of a foreign celebrity.
You'll have to guess their full name.
(They have to guess syllables in a foreign celebrity's name.)
- Gosh, this is... - Okay.
You have to take turns saying syllable by syllable.
We have to say the syllables?
For instance, if I tell Haha to go first...
(Bill Gates)
That's how you should say the answer.
(Correct)
You have to take turns saying syllable by syllable.
(As soon as they heard it's about foreign celebrities, )
We have to say the syllables?
(they gave up.)
For instance, if I tell Haha to go first...
(Someone gives up.)
Let's catch the balloons instead.
- Gosh, this is hard. - It is.
(Guessing the full name is quite hard.)
- We have to say the full name? - Yes, that's right.
- We excluded the middle name. - Okay.
- There's a middle name too? - Yes.
There's a middle name too?
(They certainly never heard of the middle names.)
- Okay. - Here comes the first question.
If you call your answer, I'll tell whom to go first.
(They have to say one syllable each.)
Then you'll have to say the syllables right away.
- Say it right away. - We have to call to answer first.
(First question)
- I'll do that. - Let's begin.
(Joe Biden)
- Let me answer! - Go ahead, Haha.
- You know who he is. - Mister...
(Time's up for Haha.)
- Let me answer! - Go ahead, Jae Suk.
- Jo. - E.
- Let me answer! - Go ahead, Kwang Soo.
(Incorrect)
- Joe. - B.
- Kwang Soo. - Ji.
(Incorrect)
- Darn it! - Let me answer!
Go ahead, Se Chan.
- Joe. - B.
- I. - Den.
(Correct)
Darn it, you punk!
- We stole their answer! - Darn it!
(Team Green got it.)
- It's Joe Biden! - "Joe Ji"?
(Then the balloon drops.)
(They missed the balloons as they're busy dancing frivolously.)
"Joe Ji"?
"Joe Ji".
- What's happening? We missed them. - What's happening?
(It's a balloon.)
- Darn it. - That's our target.
- That's ours! - Did you get them?
(A kick that has nothing to do with the balloons)
- Kwang Soo, we got it. - What was that?
(Screaming)
- Have you lost your mind? - We got it.
(I'll protect it.)
- Give them to me. Hand it over. - No.
(Kwang Soo became a wreck while giving the swords to Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook even uses his teeth.)
- Okay. - Kwang Soo got the chance.
He even used his teeth.
- Hold on. - Hey, we got it.
Who put their hands in my underwear?
Someone hit me from behind regardless of the balloons.
We have to give it a try. Hand me one.
It was already over. Why did they hit me?
Gosh, how unlucky of me.
(Angry)
- Are you upset right now? - No, I am not upset.
I forgive you for not getting Joe Biden.
(He may be weak in a quiz, but he's strong in a fight.)
- I got this for us. - Yes, you did.
- I forgive you. - The pirate will pop up.
It's a relief that you're contributing to our team.
(If the toy pops out, they get 50 points.)
- All right. - This is worth 50 points.
- You can stick one in. - Okay.
I forgive you for not getting Joe Biden.
(If he succeeds, he gets a high point that would forgive it all.)
- Gosh. - I think it will pop up.
- You have one, right? Let's go. - Yes, I have one.
- It'll be a relief if they fail. - Give it a go.
(I believe in you.)
Go ahead, trust your gut.
- Have you forgotten who you are? - No, I'll give it a go.
You're Lee Kwang Soo, for goodness' sake.
I should've caught one.
Just stick one in indifferently.
He's timid with things like this.
(He believes in his terrible luck and shoves it in.)
- That's it. Just stick one in. - He has no luck with it.
(Failed)
- Just stick it in. - It didn't pop up! Okay!
(Jong Kook also fails.)
- Darn it. - That was...
(Things never work out in a situation like this.)
- That was cheap of you. - Let's go, Kwang Soo.
- All right. - I'll catch the next one.
- Let's move on. - This is too much.
(Team Green gets 10 points for answering the question.)
- Well done. - This is too hard.
I... We...
(So Min who gave up lost interest a long time ago.)
I knew he was Biden, but I didn't know his last name was Joe.
We weren't in a good position to catch the balloons.
Hey, his last name is not Joe.
There's no such last name as Joe.
Then what about Joe? His last name is Biden?
Then is Michael Jordan's last name "Ma"?
Do you even know who he is?
Do you even watch the news?
- I mean... - Then is his name Biden Joe?
I know he's the president of the US.
- That's right. - He's the president-elect.
You all know who Joe Biden is, right?
(I've never met him before.)
I knew who he was, but I didn't know his last name was Joe.
I didn't know his last name was Joe.
That's not it. His first name is Joe.
- Biden is his last name. - Oh, it's the other way around.
- Okay, I got it. - "The other way around"?
(It's the other way round for westerners.)
Oh, it's the other way around. Okay, I got it.
Why would you pronounce it like that?
(He says hi spitting.)
You should memorize the name of the US president.
- President Joe. - President Joe, got it.
"President Joe".
- Then how do we call him? - It's not President Joe.
- It's President Biden. - Biden? Okay.
Let's settle with that.
Here's the next question.
(Congratulations on becoming the president.)
There are two ways of reading his name.
We'll accept both.
Of course you should.
All right. 1, 2, 3.
(Abraham Lincoln)
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
- Kwang Soo, go ahead. - A.
- "A". - Let me answer!
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer! - Go ahead.
- A. - B.
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer! - Why?
- A. - B?
(Team Green got it wrong.)
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
A.
- Bu. - Let me answer!
(Incorrect)
- I got it! - What?
- A. - Why is it wrong?
- "A". - B.
- Ra. - Ham.
- Lin. - Coln.
- Correct. - All right!
(Correct)
But I said the same thing!
I said "A" also.
- He didn't say that! - That wasn't correct.
(Protein Monster strongly appeals.)
- He didn't say it. - A, "A".
A, "A".
You can't pronounce it like that.
(You must pronounce it properly.)
You pronounce it that way!
It's just another way of saying it!
(LA Lover)
- You have to say either... - Abraham, Abraham.
(Shouting)
"A"!
Do you have a daughter in the US?
He probably said it with a Texan accent.
(Jong Kook, a parent from LA)
My accent is a little Texan.
According to the Korean dictionary, there are two ways of saying it.
(The Texas resident who's weak in English)
Why did you pronounce it that way, you punk?
(He can't stand his temper and kicks.)
- Good job. - Okay.
(Team Blue gets 10 points.)
- You know, - We did a good job.
Kwang Soo and I thought...
- Who did you think he was? - We were like,
"Is he Einstein?"
- Einstein. - I couldn't see the photo well.
(Lame excuse)
- Me neither. - I couldn't see the photo well.
It's confusing since it's a black and white photo.
Empty Head.
The next person.
(Third question)
- There must be one Korean in there. - 1, 2, 3.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
(What?)
Jong Kook.
(Albert Einstein)
- Three. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - Jong Kook.
(Albert Einstein)
- E. - In.
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer. - Se Chan.
(Team Green's turn)
- 3, 2. - What?
- Let me answer. - He wouldn't know the first name.
(They must start with the first name.)
- E. - In.
- It's incorrect. - Let me answer.
Al.
E.
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer. - Ji Hyo.
Al.
F.
(Incorrect)
Me!
- Let me answer. - Haha.
- Al. - Ber.
- Ji. - Let me answer.
(Incorrect)
Jae Suk.
- Al. - Ber.
- T. - Loan.
- My goodness. - Let me answer.
(Incorrect)
- Al. - Ber.
- T. - Loan.
- My goodness. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - Empty Head.
(Empty Head's wrong answer makes Jae Suk sigh.)
Let me answer. Let me answer.
(The 9th-tier financial service, Empty Head's Albert Loan)
- Jong Kook. - Al.
- Ber. - T.
- E. - In.
- S. - Te.
- In. - Okay.
(Correct)
For goodness' sake.
What in the world is Albert Loan?
Albert.
(While he's getting scolded by the king of knowledge, )
Do you think...
he is from the financial circle?
(the balloons drop.)
- Okay. Grab it. - Here.
(Team Green gets the sword.)
- We sat down. - We sat down.
- We sat down. - We get to go.
- Here I go. - Come on, Se Chan.
What is it?
The chance is high this time.
- It will come up. - There are four slots left.
(2 out of 4 failed.)
It didn't pop up.
It was shaken up earlier.
This is driving me crazy.
(They have only two swords left.)
Push in another one. We need to win 50 points.
- Please let them fail. - The last one.
(Failed again)
- Please let them fail. - How many knives are left?
- None? - Let's get over this.
(There's only one sword left.)
- There are 7 slots. - 1 out of 7.
(Will they be able to win 50 points with the last sword?)
Then the probability is only 15 percent.
1 out of 7.
- Okay! - That was insane.
(Popping)
(They succeeded to win 50 points!)
That's so annoying.
(They succeed to obtain a high score after shouting Albert Loan.)
- I didn't want to see that. - That's so annoying.
Nice!
- Nice! - That's so annoying.
We won with Albert Loan.
Albert Loan sounds like a stock item.
That's so annoying.
Is it a biotech stock?
(He lost money from investing money in Bio stocks.)
Nice!
(Current score)
- You changed the seats, right? - Yes.
Do you want to change the seats?
(They switch the spot before the next round.)
- Okay. - Do you want to do it?
- Yes. - All right.
Let's change the seats. Move.
Stay there.
(Too lazy)
- They changed the seats. - Kim Grand Award,
- change seats with him. - All right then.
(Willing)
Why did you listen to him when you didn't listen to me?
- He is a senior. - For goodness' sake.
- A junior who won the Grand Award. - Come on.
Jong Kook didn't even budge when he kicked him.
(He doesn't even budge.)
You won't budge?
He is a junior who won the Grand Award.
So you won't budge.
It looks like you won, Suk Jin.
I am dusting the cushion.
(With the cushion, he touches the Protein Monster's face.)
He is provoking Jong Kook.
(He provokes Jong Kook in the timidest way.)
Thank you for sitting still.
(He quickly thanks Jong Kook after provoking him.)
We are set.
It will be funny if we end it here.
(Holding hands tight)
Don't air my apology.
(Last pride)
I wondered what I should do...
if you got up. Thank you.
Suk Jin hit him with his hands trembling.
(The man who makes people shake their hands smiles.)
- All right. - Let's go.
(The quiz on figures ends.)
This time, you will have a quiz on capital cities.
(Capitals quiz)
- Capital cities. - Capital cities?
- Yes. Capital cities. - Okay.
(Empty Head feels confident in capitals.)
I am good with capitals.
- Let's go. - When I give you the country name,
(They have to say one syllable each after hearing the country name.)
- say a syllable... - Let's go.
- each. - Come on.
The first country is...
- Mongolia. - Let me answer.
- U. - Lan.
- Ba. - To.
(Will they succeed?)
- To. - R.
- Isn't it "Ulaanbaatar"? - Is it correct?
(Correct)
- To. - R.
(They get the correct answer right away.)
- Isn't it "Ulaanbaatar"? - Is it correct?
(They can't believe Empty Head continues to answer the questions.)
- Ulan Bator. - It was too easy.
Is it "Ulan Bator"?
Is it?
- Ulan Bator. - It was too easy.
Is it "Ulan Bator"?
(He can't believe himself.)
"Ulan Bator" is a correct way of saying it.
- Is it "Ulan Bator"? - Yes.
Jae Suk, we got it right!
Is it "Ulan Bator"?
I have good pronunciation.
Ulan Bator.
- That was great. - It was a clean answer.
(It looks like he is ready to get permanent residency in Mongolia.)
How could he be so annoying?
- That was so much fun. - The next capital.
(The next question)
- Iraq. - Let me answer.
(The answer is Baghdad.)
Haha.
- Let me answer. - Kwang Soo.
- What? - For goodness' sake.
"What?"
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Se Chan. - Ja.
No, no.
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer. - Iraq.
B.
(You should know now.)
- Io. - Let me answer.
Bio.
- Ba. - Gh.
- Da. - D.
(Correct)
Nice!
(Kwang Soo, I can't believe you said "Bio".)
- We are on a roll today, Jae Suk. - Bio!
(I got it again.)
Here come the protruding mouth brothers!
- Let's go! Nice! - Nice!
(Every time he answers, he celebrates for at least 3 minutes.)
- It was amazing. - We are getting everything right.
I was the master of the quiz.
(It turns out...)
Jae Suk,
(Empty Head realized the fun of playing quiz.)
I am no longer Empty Head when I am with you.
Kwang Soo's answer was so funny.
He said "Bio".
(He got sick from Bio.)
- Seriously. - My goodness.
Baghdad.
(Proud)
The Iraq War.
(Tale)
I remembered the Iraq War.
You are doing great today.
(He seems as if he participated.)
I wasn't Empty Head.
Bio.
Here comes the next question.
Don't you know "Baghdad and the 50 Thieves"?
(Pretending to know)
That's Ali Baba.
It isn't "Baghdad and the 50 Thieves".
It's "Ali Baba and the 50 Thieves".
Empty Head.
(Even Suk Jin couldn't avoid the Empty Head Syndrome.)
The next capital.
(The next question)
Se Chan is really good at this.
- Norway. - Let me answer.
(What's the capital city of Norway?)
- Haha. - Van.
Das.
("Vandas" is incorrect.)
- Let me answer. - Se Chan.
(Team Green's turn)
I don't know.
(Proud)
Let me answer.
- Suk Jin. - My goodness.
Suk Jin.
- Van. - Hel.
Sing.
(Incorrect)
- That's a movie. - Isn't "Van Helsing" a movie?
(Isn't that a movie?)
- Is it a movie? - Isn't it a movie? Let me answer.
- Se Chan. - Wasn't it something like that?
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
Van.
(Annoyed)
- Is it incorrect? - Are you going to be like that?
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Jong Kook, go ahead.
- O. - Sl.
Ram.
(Incorrect)
- What? - Let me answer.
You said it's Oslram.
- Se Chan. - What?
- O. - Sl.
- Bi. - For goodness' sake.
("Oslbi" is incorrect.)
- O. - Sl.
- Bi. - For goodness' sake.
(Empty Head's stupid answers are more harmful than acid rain.)
Oslbi.
(He said "Oslbi".)
(The ridiculous answer makes the king of knowledge speechless.)
- Hey. Hey. - Oslbi.
What kind of an answer is "Oslbi"?
Let me answer.
- Oslbi. - Give me a chance. Let me answer.
(It's Team Blue's turn.)
- Let me answer. - Haha, go ahead.
- O. - Sl.
- O. - Yes.
("Oslo" is correct.)
- Okay. - It was Oslo.
(Team Blue gets 10 points.)
- It's okay. - It's okay to make a mistake.
("Oslbi" wasn't the correct answer, but it made everyone laugh.)
- "Oslbi" was a funny answer. - Oslo.
When Oslbi falls early in the morning
- Three umbrellas walk - Side by side
(Singing "Oslbi" out loud)
I knew it was Oslo.
Here they come.
(Balloons fall at that moment.)
- All of them popped. - For goodness' sake.
All of them are fake!
Okay, okay. I sat down!
All right.
- You can't do that. - You can't do that.
(Taking away)
- We sat down. - We sat down.
(You can't steal it.)
- Hold on. - So Min.
- So Min. - So Min.
- We sat down. - I received a tip-off...
about the bad odor that came...
- when the balloons popped. - No, no.
No, seriously. When the balloons popped...
No!
Okay, okay. I sat down.
Jae Suk, why do I smell something sour...
after the balloons popped?
No, seriously.
(When the balloons popped earlier, the smell also began.)
- When the balloons popped, - No!
- I smelled something sour. - No.
- So Min. - It really wasn't me.
- So Min. - It wasn't me.
(Denying)
- My goodness. - I smelled something sour.
(There's a suspicion, but no evidence.)
We sat down.
- Hurry up. - We need to catch the culprit.
There's someone who smells sour among us.
(Among us)
Okay. Let's try this slot.
(Team Red fails to get 50 points!)
Yes!
(Last question)
This is the last question on capitals.
- Hungary. - Let me answer.
(What's the capital of Hungary?)
(Suk Jin yelled out, but Haha looks uncertain.)
- Haha. - Bu.
- Da. - Pe.
- S. - T.
They got it right. Budapest, Hungary.
("Budapest" is correct.)
(Team Blue got 10 points for answering the last question.)
My goodness.
- The balloons... - What?
(The last set of balloons falls.)
Where are the balloons?
(It's a ruckus.)
Hey, these are fake.
No.
Jae Suk!
(While the mullet marks Empty Head...)
I figured it out.
It's the smell of someone's feet. I figured it out.
I figured it out. It's the smell of someone's feet.
(So Min proposes a theory that it's the smell of someone's feet.)
- Someone has stinky feet. - It's the smell of someone's feet.
- Someone has stinky feet. - Throw it.
Haha!
(They were about to smell Ji Hyo's feet.)
It popped out!
(He made the pirate pop out.)
Did it pop out?
(The pirate that popped out after the quiz...)
(won Team Yellow 50 points.)
We were fighting.
Seriously.
Okay, okay.
Find the person who has stinky feet.
(Pleading her innocence)
- Who is it? - It isn't me.
- Find the person. - Who is it?
- It isn't me. - It isn't me.
- Ji Hyo. - It isn't me.
(Everyone smells their feet.)
Ji Hyo's feet were stinky last week.
It isn't me. It wasn't me last week either.
(Everyone says it's not them.)
Let's have Bo Pil smell our feet for fairness.
(Bo Pil becomes the judge of stinky feet.)
That's right.
- That's right. - That's right.
That's right. Bo Pil.
- Gosh. - No!
- Stinky feet. - Really?
(The member with the stinky feet gets caught.)
- No! - Stinky feet.
- Good job. - Come here.
(You're busted.)
Come here.
(Sniffing)
- For goodness' sake. - Gosh.
(He was the root of the sour smell.)
(The aged smell of his stinky feet is on another level.)
Hey, it smells like fart.
(His socks get removed.)
- Take them off. - Hey.
(Directly delivered stinky feet diffuser)
Throw them outside.
(Sniffing)
Hey.
- It was Se Chan. - It was you.
No wonder the sour smell...
kept circling me.
(They finally found the source of the smell.)
I wondered where it was coming from.
It was coming from my feet.
- I am sorry. - Hey.
Don't you wash your feet?
Wash your feet!
- Gosh. - It wasn't me.
So Min and Ji Hyo, I am sorry.
(Meanwhile, the protection is put on the stinky feet.)
- It was the smell of his feet. - That was funny.
I suspected you guys for a short while.
It wasn't us.
I came to my senses.
- His feet don't stink now. - Hey.
(The poisonous gas is sealed.)
My goodness.
There we go.
(The stinky feet ruckus ends.)
Please sit down.
The result is out.
(Announcing the final result)
Haha and Suk Jin placed last with 30 points.
(Team Blue is in 4th place with 30 points.)
So Min and Ji Hyo placed 3rd with 90 points.
(Team Red is in 3rd place with 90 points.)
The other 2 teams are co-winners with 130 points.
(Team Yellow and Team Yellow Green are tied with 130 points.)
The two teams will have a question of the Guess Who Quiz.
(The two teams will have a question of Guess Who Quiz.)
We got a lot of questions right.
We got a lot of questions right too.
For goodness' sake. Don't be like that, Jae Suk.
You should know better.
You have won a good award.
(Whispering)
- You will lose, so sit down. - Sit down.
(You're having too much fun.)
All right. I will be objective with this question.
(The last question will determine the winner.)
- Okay. - Okay.
Guess Who Quiz.
(Mark Ruffalo)
Let's go.
Let me answer.
Kwang Soo.
(If they get it right, Team Yellow will win.)
- Let me answer. - Kwang Soo.
Hul.
(He was thinking about Hulk.)
Does that work?
No, he has a name.
His name is... Hold on.
(The Korean Hulk can't think of the actor's name.)
- I don't remember. - Let me answer.
Mar.
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer. - Is it right?
- Kwang Soo. - Mar.
- K. - Wal.
(Incorrect)
Come on.
- Let me answer. - I got it.
- Let me answer. - Jae Suk.
- Mar. - K.
- I don't know. - I will answer. Let me answer.
- Do I go 1st? - Kwang Soo should go 1st.
(Jong Kook knows the answer.)
- Mar. - You should have let me go first.
K.
Long.
(Kwang Soo obviously has no idea.)
Let me answer.
(Team Yellow gets another chance! Kwang Soo goes first.)
Kwang Soo, go first.
Mar.
Is he going first again?
- You should give us a chance! - Hey!
- Mar. - Mark.
(While Team Yellow is caught in the trap of "Mark"...)
- Back. - Again.
- Let me answer. Mar. - K.
Ru.
- Pa. - Let me answer.
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer. - I figured it out.
- Mar. - K.
- Ru. - Hey.
(They messed up the order again.)
- What are you doing? - Hey.
- He doesn't know the answer. - Kwang Soo should have gone first.
- Seriously. - Phi.
(Kwang Soo always gets the important word.)
Phi.
- Is it Mark Loan? No, no. - Mark Loan?
Why do you like loans so much?
- Mark Loan? - Mark.
(Even a new Mark Loan appears.)
It sounds like macaron.
Let me answer.
- Mar. - K.
- Ru. - E.
Let me answer.
(Incorrect)
- We are set. - What's the answer?
(It's Team Yellow's turn!)
- Mar. - K.
- Ru. - Ffa.
- Lo. - Okay.
(Correct)
Okay!
I knew the name.
(After correctly guessing the last question, )
- Ruffalo. - Ruffalo.
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook are the final winners.)
Mark Ruffalo.
- We did it. Okay. - Mark Ruffalo.
- Jong Kook and Kwang Soo won. - Okay!
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo get to turn the roulette.)
- Mark Ruffalo. - Decide who will spin first.
Okay.
- Mark Ruffalo. - We fought well.
(The two Empty Heads' quiz battle ends.)
Ruffalo.
Who will spin the roulette first?
(The members can add their names on the main roulette...)
(using the benefit roulette.)
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook spun the benefit roulette.)
If you add it...
(The current number of name tags on the roulette)
(Kwang Soo 8, Haha 7, Se Chan 6, Ji Hyo 5,)
(Jae Suk 4, So Min 4, Jong Kook 3, Suk Jin 3)
It's time to spin the roulette one last time.
(It's the final roulette!)
The chosen one will have his or her comment on each member...
(The chosen one will have his or her comment on each member...)
and project objective on the website.
(and project objective on the website.)
- So this is the final decision. - Yes.
The chosen one will also receive the prize money...
(The chosen one will also receive the prize money...)
of 100 dollars per name tag on the roulette.
(of 100 dollars per name tag on the roulette.)
It will be like a writer's pay.
(Since Kwang Soo has 8 name tags, he could win 800 dollars.)
(Haha 7, Se Chan 6, Ji Hyo 5,)
I have a chance.
(Jae Suk 4, So Min 4)
I have a few name tags on there.
(Suk Jin and Jong Kook have 3 name tags each!)
Why don't we have a staff member spin the roulette?
(The website will change after the program is aired.)
Then Sun Myung should spin it.
(One of the production crew members will turn the roulette.)
- Sun Myung. - Yes.
- This is the last roulette. - Spin it hard.
(The winner lies in the hands of Sun Myung!)
Sun Myung, let's see it.
Here it goes.
- Sun Myung! - Sun Myung!
(Who will be the lucky winner?)
- Let's go. - You followed me a lot.
Get mine.
It all depends on luck.
(He's in the last place.)
That's right.
All right! It's me!
It's me!
(Will it be Suk Jin?)
(Or will it be Jae Suk?)
- It's me! - Is it Jae Suk?
(Jae Suk got chosen!)
Jae Suk.
- What is this? - Hey!
He didn't put his name tag once.
(He got chosen with 4 name tags on the roulette.)
- This is absurd. I feel cheated! - How did this happen?
(Jae Suk's production objective and comments will go up.)
This is ridiculous.
(Kwang Soo with the most name tags is devastated.)
I feel so dejected.
Sun Myung, thank you.
How did this happen?
This show must be Yoo Jae Suk's Running Man.
It suits the production objective.
It's 100 dollars per name tag,
(It's 100 dollars per name tag, )
so he will receive 400 dollars in gift cards.
(so Jae Suk will receive 400 dollars.)
Jae Suk's production objective and comments...
(The new introduction of Running Man...)
will go up on the website. If you want to add something...
(will be uploaded to the website after the program is aired.)
I will combine what everyone wrote...
(I will combine the best of everyone's ideas.)
- and use the comments I like. - Okay.
- My production objective was nice. - What?
(Please use mine.)
- My production objective. - All right.
Please use "Mr. Dirty Mustache".
I will add it. Don't worry.
Se Chan's feet continue to stink even without the socks.
(However)
He needs to wash them.
Come here for a second. I will wash your feet.
(Se Chan must first wash his feet.)
No.
- You are a celebrity. - My shoes...
(Se Chan washed his feet thoroughly afterward.)
(We introduce Running Man on Jae Suk's words.)
Variety shows are disappearing these days.
(Running Man production objective written by Jae Suk)
Running Man is Korea's favorite variety show that's been...
on Sunday nights for over 10 years.
The members play games and clear missions with various guest stars,
as they go around to different places.
Among various fun factors,
this show only focuses on laughter.
Open your eyes. Fun on a big scale will come.
(In addition to the production objective...)
Open your mouth. Laughter on a big scale will come.
(written by the winner Jae Suk, )
Open your heart. A great lesson will come.
(you can see the member introduction hand-picked by Jae Suk.)
Yoo Jae Suk. The Unchanging Goofball of variety shows.
He is the pride of Running Man.
Ji Suk Jin. The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong...
who pretends to love his family.
Kim Jong Kook. In summer, he is Kim Nipple.
In other seasons, he is Enema Kim.
Haha. Mr. Dirty Mustache who is the worst at acting young...
(Old fossil)
among celebrities who were born in 1979.
Song Ji Hyo. Her real name is Cheon Seong Im, Cheon Su Yeon.
Her nickname is Jeoktoma.
Lee Kwang Soo. The butler of A-list actors.
Jeon So Min. The Crazy Poet.
Yang Se Chan. Yang Se Hyeong's younger brother.
Has handsome gums.
Yoo Jae Suk's production objective and the comments on the members...
(Yoo Jae Suk's production objective and the comments on the members...)
(can be seen on Running Man's website.)
can be seen on Running Man's website.
(Running High School is located deep in the mountains.)
Isn't this a delinquents' school?
The guitarist.
(Band club, )
We are in the dance club.
(Dance club, )
- Turn off the music. - Be quiet!
(and Student Guidance club have come together!)
What does your father do? Look at these students!
(Teachers gave up on these delinquents.)
Why would you swing that in school?
(A transfer student is the loyal man of the century!)
Loyalty.
(Kim Bo Sung, Defconn)
- Loyalty. - Loyalty.
(They are here to save the delinquents.)
Let's go.
(Thanks to the loyal transfer students, )
(the atmosphere and spirit liven up!)
- There we go! - Did he take a bribe?
(But the club activity fund disappears.)
For goodness' sake!
Get your acts together, okay?
(There is a traitor among them.)
I can't do this.
Friends should help each other! Student guidance club is the worst.
(The loyal man explodes upon hearing about the traitor.)
- Why did you come here? - I came...
(The club period is their last chance to check the loyalty.)
- to protect. - Did you find it?
(Will they stay loyal or betray their clubs?)
- Kwang Soo. - What are you doing?
I will never visit this show again!
(What will be the result at the Running High School?)
Let's go!
(Race for the Club Activity Fund, The Burning 18 Again)