(Running High School is known
to have unique students.)
- Are we all friends?
- Are we supposed to be friends?
- Hello.
- My goodness.
Hey, Ji Hyo.
(Today, Running High School
has school activities.)
Hello.
(Running High School's beauty,
Ji Hyo is the first one to come.)
Ji Hyo, wait for me.
Hurry up and come, Se Chan.
Ji Hyo. Why are you alone?
(Se Chan doesn't seem like a student
who's ready to study.)
- Hey.
- Hello, Haha.
Are you ready?
He's our leader. Leader Ha.
- Let's warm up.
- Okay.
All right then.
We're Dirty Mustache.
Let's play the music.
1, 2, 3, and 4.
(Dirty Mustache's masterpiece,
"Jauji Jangjijiji")
(It's a school band
made up of pretty Ji Hyo...)
(and the visually unpleasant
Se Chan and Haha.)
(Empty Head: The youngest
member of the band)
(Song Jeoktoma: Vocalist,
Dirty Mustache: Leader)
Good. You've still got it.
- You're our main vocalist for sure.
- She's amazing.
(They've been performing
only this song for 3 years.)
- You're our main vocalist.
- Shut it!
- Hello.
- I can't believe you guys.
- Are you a returning student?
- No, I'm not.
You punks.
- You're here.
- What's that?
- He's just a gangster.
- Why do you have a dumbbell?
You punk.
My gosh.
- Behave yourselves.
- We're friends.
Are we friends, you punk?
I repeated the same year
for five years.
- Five years?
- What?
- He's lying.
- It's a lie. It was for 10 years.
You repeated the same year
for 10 years.
- It was five years.
- Hey.
They are my friends.
- Sure.
- What?
Ji Hyo.
What?
You're pretty.
Ji Hyo, you look passionate today.
- Do you have a boyfriend?
- The main vocalist of our band.
(As the boys get interested
in Jo Hyo with a pretty face)
You have your own style? I see.
- Hey.
- What is it?
(She turned on the music.)
What? We're the dance team.
You're the dance team?
Gosh, what are you doing?
(The school band
gets ready as well!)
(The dance team members
show terrible dance moves!)
(This dancer specializes
in the Im Ha Ryong dance.)
Is this a school for troublemakers?
It's a school for troublemakers.
(No discipline at all)
(Dancing machines!)
So Min's very flexible.
This is a school for troublemakers.
Come on. We're the dance team.
You should be better.
(Tiger Moth, the tenacious one,
Big Nose, the founder of the team,)
What is that?
(and Protein Monster,
the protector of the members)
- This is not a school.
- The setting is weird.
I haven't done this in a long time.
(Strange dance team)
My goodness,
our dance team is really...
(Blowing a whistle)
What was that?
What is it?
- What is it?
- Turn off the music.
- Quiet down!
- It's the Apgujeong Whistle.
What are you, a zebra?
Turn off the music.
- He's turning it off himself.
- Yes, you do that.
(Which club are they?)
- Student guidance club?
- Who are you guys?
What's with the noise
so early in the morning?
(Yoo Jae Suk, the top student,
the leader of student guidance club)
(Lee Kwang Soo, the informer
of student guidance club)
- They're the student guidance club.
- My gosh, student guidance club.
What's with your hair?
Are you out of your mind?
- What's with your mullet?
- Your mullet is weird too.
- Get a haircut.
- Yes, get a haircut.
- Gosh. Hello, sir.
- Hello, teacher.
- Good to see you, sir.
- Gosh, You're not a teacher?
I'm not a teacher.
I'm a friend of yours.
- Aren't you the vice-principal?
- I'm a friend of yours.
Who told you to dance?
I apologize, sir.
- Hey.
- We'll control them.
But we're the dance team.
- What?
- We're the dance team.
But you can't dance
in front of the school.
You like to dance too.
I know you're the dance team, but...
Actually, he...
- failed the audition for our club.
- You're really good.
- He failed the audition.
- What's with that move?
He's doing this
because he failed the audition.
How can a student dance like that?
You're really good at this move.
(She learned the travel bus groove
at an early age.)
She's our best dancer.
Hey.
I can smell cigarettes
on your breath.
- Hey, leave him alone.
- Come here.
- Hey.
- Let him be.
- Give me your hands!
- Let him be!
- Hey!
- Give me your hands.
- I didn't smoke!
- Just give me your hands.
- Hey.
(Ouch!)
(Slip)
How could you smoke
when you're a student?
- I didn't smoke!
- Are you out of your mind?
I said I didn't smoke.
I know you're much
older than we are.
- That's right.
- But you're still a student.
- You should listen to us.
- Hey.
- What?
- Actually, the cigarette smell...
is from Song Ji Hyo.
Gosh, that hurts.
They're tied to my real hair!
It hurts when you pull!
It hurts!
(The fluorescent hair
is tied to his real hair!)
It's tied to your hair?
- Hey.
- It hurts!
I'm sorry.
- Gosh, it really hurt.
- He didn't know.
- I'm sorry.
- Wasn't it attached to the hat?
What's wrong with you?
Wait a minute.
Which club are you from?
- Me?
- Dance team. We're the dance team.
The dance team.
- Why are you holding a dumbbell?
- This?
He's just a bully.
- You're a bully?
- Not a dance team member.
He looks like a bully
no matter what he wears.
He always looks like a bully.
As a member of
the student guidance club...
you should go
talk some sense into him.
Yes, talk some sense into him.
Or you could hit him.
(Staring at him)
- Talk to him.
- What?
(The leader of the student guidance
club never meddles in.)
- You were saying?
- Talk to him.
Just let me hit you once.
Then when it's all over,
I'll wire 50 dollars
to your account.
(Intimidated by the bully
from the dance team)
Step by step
- What?
- Who is it?
- Oh, baby
Who's that?
Gosh, who's that?
Some more bullies are here.
- Step by step
- What is this?
Oh, baby
(Defconn, the heavyweight dancer
of the dance team)
He's a dance team member.
- Hello.
- Loyalty!
Loyalty!
(Kim Bo Sung, student guidance club
member who lives and die by loyalty)
Loyalty!
- Hello.
- Loyalty!
Loyalty!
- That hurts.
(50 percent of his conversation
is made up of "loyalty".)
That hurts!
I'm sorry.
Brother.
- How have you been?
I've been good.
- Hello.
- It's good to see you.
Why do you look so nasty?
I'm a dance team member.
- Dance team?
- You're a dance team member?
- We're the dance team.
- You're one of us.
- Yes, you're one of us.
- Okay, good.
- I'm on student guidance club.
- You are?
Move.
You're a student guidance club
member and you have sideburns?
You have a problem with it?
(Throwing his bag without notice)
He's serious. This isn't acting.
- Hey.
- What was that?
(You can't predict
what he's feeling.)
Gosh, he just turned violent.
Brother.
He reacts right away.
Yes, he does.
He doesn't give you notice.
How come a student guidance club
member has such a long mullet?
Yes, he has such a long
mullet and sideburns.
Student guidance club members
should set good examples.
How could you both have long hair?
Hey, quiet down.
- It's Gyu Jin.
- Hey, Gyu Jin.
Gyu Jin's here again?
Quiet down.
(Shin Gyu Jin
who paints a big picture!)
(On Comedy Big League...)
("Yang Se Chan,
when you're alone on Running Man,")
("you're not able to
paint a big picture either!")
(He gives Se Chan harsh criticism.)
(And when he was on Running Man
to paint a big picture,)
(he failed to paint a big picture.
Not even a rough sketch.)
(So he returned to the base.)
(Have you ever been on Running Man?)
(Then Shin Gyu Jin shows off
that he was on Running Man!)
Gosh, it's Gyu Jin.
- Then...
- Oh, he's here.
Gyu Jin's here again?
Gosh, it's Gyu Jin.
I thought his role was gone,
but he's back again.
(Shin Gyu Jin, the dean of students
is very nervous right now.)
- Hey, Gyu Jin.
- It's been months.
My goodness. Look at these brats.
Gosh, he really is like a teacher.
- What's wrong with you?
- He's like a real teacher.
It's been a while since we saw you.
Why do you look so haggard?
Hey, hey. Be quiet.
- But...
- Quiet down.
Don't you think you're the same as
the prison guard you played before?
- He's the dean of students.
- Which prison guard?
I don't know what you're
talking about.
- His acting is amazing.
- So today...
What happened to your skin?
It's rotten.
It's because
I didn't sleep well last night.
- Maybe the teacher's nervous.
- Were you nervous about today?
Why can't he sleep the day before
coming on Running Man?
Well, that's not what's important.
I am here today for a reason.
I'm here because today is
the day of dress inspection.
The dress inspection?
- He's checking our outfits?
- So everyone...
put all your personal belongings
on the floor.
Put your hands on your heads
and stand still.
- Personal belongings?
- Hurry up.
I don't want to hear you grumbling.
- Put everything on the ground.
- My goodness.
- Come on.
- Stop grumbling.
- Sir!
- First thing in the morning?
- This is too much.
- You can't do this to us.
Hey, hey.
This school is set in the 1980s,
so we have corporal punishment.
Corporal punishment?
We're in the 1980s?
- We're in the 1980s?
- He can hit us.
- Yes, they hit students back then.
- You're right. They did.
We got hit by the teachers
in the old days.
Okay, then.
- My goodness.
- Okay.
My goodness.
What is this?
Are you a gangster?
It's my father's.
- Your father?
- What's with the accent?
- "What does your father do?"
- Why is he using a weird accent?
Your father?
My goodness.
(The dean of students looks pleased
to role-play like he expected.)
Come here.
What does your father do?
(Confident)
My father is a gangster.
A gangster?
(A gangster?)
- He doesn't know what to say.
- He can't improvise.
(He doesn't know how to improvise
after his first line.)
- So your father's a gangster?
- He can't improvise.
(What should I say?)
- Gosh.
- So your father's a gangster?
- Yes, take off your watch.
- I've seen this somewhere.
Sir, you saw him last week.
- What's wrong with him?
- The teacher is too nice.
Your hairstyle isn't appropriate
as a student.
Well, it's because
I'm a band member.
Do you need to have long hair
to be in the band?
- But I got permission.
- From who?
- From you.
- From me?
- Yes.
- It's my first day at this school.
So you're new here.
You get three penalty points.
My goodness.
You didn't pay for these, did you?
(Did you pay for this?)
This belongs to Dream.
- Gosh.
- Don't mess with Dream.
It's the only thing
you can't mess with.
- He has a child.
- You can't mess with his kid.
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
The teacher is too kind.
He has no backbone.
- Gosh, what's wrong with him?
- So kind.
It's so easy to convince him.
- Anyway, you get penalty points.
- All right.
- Remember that.
- Yes, sir.
Who's next?
- Hello, sir.
- It's been a while.
Yes, it has. You know me, don't you?
- Yes.
- Right.
- From his previous school?
- Yes, maybe.
Yes, I met him
at the previous school I went to.
- I just transferred to this school.
- You're a new student here?
Gosh, look at yourself.
- What do I do with you?
- What do you mean?
The shape of your hat is ruined!
Make it right.
(His unnatural acting
suddenly kills the mood.)
It's becoming slightly corny.
- "Make it right?"
- It's like a boring comedy show.
All right,
what do you want me to do?
- All right.
- Yes.
Let me see.
Doesn't your mom iron your uniform?
He doesn't know what to say.
Anybody would think that
his inner shirt is inappropriate.
- That's right. The scarf.
- His scarf is inappropriate.
Are you playing favorites with him?
Se Chan,
you don't get any penalty points.
- Oh, thank you.
- What?
- Thank you, sir.
- What was that?
- I'll be good to you tomorrow.
- Good, good.
- Are you two meeting tomorrow?
- No, we're not.
You're filming
Comedy Big League tomorrow, right?
- You brat!
- Gosh, you can't do this.
This darn world runs on
regionalism and kinship.
No, we're not.
Actually,
you can't call it that.
They have school ties.
He's right.
- Well, whatever it is...
- Suk Jin.
This isn't about
regionalism and kinship.
This is about school ties.
I can work with regionalism
but not kinship.
Now quiet down.
Ji Hyo is next.
Gosh, what do I do with you?
- Inside your uniform.
- She worked hard to look nice.
- You tried too hard to look nice.
- Seriously.
So you wore
a colorful turtleneck sweater.
Yes, but I did because
it was too cold.
(Talking in a cute voice)
Of course you did.
- My goodness, what?
- What on earth are you doing?
- Sir!
- What can you say? She was cold!
It's so cold these days.
All right, Ji Hyo.
Let me see your hair.
What is this? Isn't it
inappropriate for a student?
- It's funky style.
- You can't get a perm.
- I went to a beauty salon today.
- Yes.
And they told me it suits my style.
Yes, it does.
My goodness.
- What's he doing? It's ridiculous.
- You do look nice.
You should point out her problems.
- Is this your bag?
- Yes.
Let me check it.
- Hang on.
- Gosh, that...
- Please be careful.
- Why?
Nothing.
Am I not supposed to open it?
You can open it.
We're going to start it
from the Lunar New Year.
What is this?
I'm in the school band.
I carry a microphone around with me
so I can practice all the time.
Are you the vocalist?
- Sure.
- Actually, this is a lighter.
Hey, stay quiet.
I'll give you one penalty point.
You are spreading false information.
You get one penalty point.
Anyway, you have too many
colorful pins in your hair,
- so you get one penalty point.
- Good.
All right. One point.
Who's next?
I'm in the student guidance club.
How dare you
look down at your teacher?
- I'm in the student guidance club.
- All right. Student guidance?
- Sir, he has very long hair.
- But he doesn't shower.
- He's so filthy.
- You should cut his hair.
- Gosh.
- If you cut my hair,
- I'm okay with that.
- What?
Get him some scissors.
- I'm okay with that.
- What?
(Is he really cutting
Kwang Soo's hair?)
Do you not know
the school regulations?
If you want to cut my hair,
I'll let you do that.
- Really? Okay.
- Yes.
(The student with the long hair
is so into the skit.)
If he wants to cut it,
I have to follow him.
- Here you are, sir.
- It's longer than I thought.
- Really?
- Is he serious?
Isn't this a skit?
Are we doing this for real?
We have no choice though.
- What?
- We have no choice.
The movie shoot is over.
- Here you are, sir.
- Really?
Cut it short please.
- It's too long.
- I know.
Isn't this a skit?
Are we doing this for real?
Cut it short please.
Sir, if you cut it...
Gosh, I think you've been
growing your hair for years.
- Yes. You can cut it.
- Are you okay with that?
- Sure.
- I think he's cutting it for real.
- He's really doing it.
- He's cutting the hair.
- I'm cutting it for real.
- I mean... Sure.
I'm not familiar with stuff like
this. I'm cutting it for real.
- Hey, he's doing it for real.
- This isn't a joke.
Are you sure about this?
- Sir.
- It's okay to cut it.
Go ahead and cut it.
He should get a haircut anyway.
Stop hesitating and cut it.
But the problem is...
If you get your hair cut,
Bo Sung will have to do the same.
(If you get your hair cut,
Bo Sung will have to do the same.)
(Me?)
- Bo Sung should do that too.
- So...
You should just get penalty points.
- All right.
- You should get penalty points.
- I get it.
- Just cut it.
Give me that.
So I will just...
- Give him penalty points.
- I'll give you five penalty points.
- Okay.
- This isn't acceptable.
All right. Next.
He's here. He's a member
of the student guidance club.
Gosh, his bag is like...
Hang on.
What is this?
Leather gloves.
- What are these?
- Gloves.
I know they are gloves.
But what's with the bumps?
In case of emergency...
- You're a student.
- It's called LA.
The loyalty of an angel.
(The loyalty of an angel)
- I always protect the weak.
- I see.
I protect the underprivileged.
- It's the student guidance club.
- Right.
You should give him
penalty points for his hair.
- Oh, his hair.
- He has long hair.
This is too long. What do you think?
You can cut it if you want.
Hang on. No, I won't...
I don't think I have to cut it.
You have very thin hair.
(I don't think I have to cut it.
You have very thin hair.)
(The angel's hair is very thin.)
You're being too serious.
- I mean...
- Sir, don't make fun of his hair.
- It's humiliating.
- Don't make fun of his thin hair.
- You should keep it to yourself.
- That's so mean.
You should show him something.
(He starts to swing chain sticks.)
He's your teacher.
(Swinging them hard)
(Stepping back)
Why are you swinging them at school?
- He hit his head.
- Tidy your hair.
He got hit in the head.
- Are you all right?
- It didn't go well.
Why are you swinging them now?
About your sunglasses.
Are those prescribed?
- Say yes.
- No, they're not.
They're not prescribed?
Then you should get penalty points.
- He's so nice that he can't lie.
- He's nice.
- He can't lie.
- He doesn't know what to say.
He just can't lie.
- Just say anything.
- He's so innocent.
- He just can't lie.
- He has such innocent eyes.
We're just doing a skit now.
He's got the eyes of a deer.
Go ahead and say a lie.
He didn't get
that many penalty points though.
- Hang on.
- Yes?
- Nice to meet you.
- Three penalty points.
Already?
I didn't do anything. Why?
You have a tough-looking face.
- What's wrong?
- And...
I was born this way.
What should I do?
And I understand you are
a growing student,
- but you should shave your face.
- What is Bo Sung doing?
What is he doing behind there?
Look at Bo Sung.
(The master martial artist doesn't
know the right time and place.)
- Why are you swinging those?
- What's wrong with you?
I didn't do it right earlier.
- Why do you keep swinging them?
- He has regrets.
All right. Next.
- I will check your uniform anyway.
- Okay.
But your headphones are
not connected to anything.
- They are in my bag.
- Those are hearing aids.
- Really?
- Hearing aids?
Hang on. The gold necklace...
It's a health necklace.
This is a health necklace.
Is it germanium?
Sir, he drives an electric car.
Why are you saying that?
- Why?
- We're doing this seriously.
- Why can't I say that?
- He cares about the environment.
- I do.
He's driving
an electric car already.
Really?
- You want to protect the earth.
- I do.
Next.
All right.
- They finally met.
- All right.
He's here.
(Hesitant)
(What should I do?)
- What is he going to do?
- I've been waiting for this moment.
- Gosh, this is...
- He wouldn't budge.
- Hey, kid.
- "Kid"?
Do you want to pick a fight with me?
Why is your posture so...
What's wrong with my posture?
- You look aggressive.
- Sir, he is...
addicted to protein.
He is?
- Sir.
- Yes?
Make sure you don't
run into me on the street.
(Make sure you don't
run into me on the street.)
(The protein addict
provokes his teacher.)
He's saying that to his teacher?
(He takes up
the protein addict's challenge...)
(without a backup plan.)
- He's taking off his watch.
- Sir.
He finally took off his watch.
- Get down.
Get down.
Go ahead and get down.
- Oh dear.
- You should punish him.
- You should hit him for real.
- It's okay. Go ahead.
- Get down.
You can do this for real.
Let's do this for real.
- All right.
- He's got a broad back.
You sound very rude to your teacher.
There you go.
(He sounds firm,
but his eyelids are fluttering.)
(Things are getting extreme,
but no one's trying to stop him.)
All right. There you go.
- Sir.
- Hang on.
(Hitting gently)
- The sound...
- Hang on.
- Wait, sir.
- What was that?
He's terrified.
What was that?
- My gosh. Sir.
- What are you doing?
You should be strict.
- I mean...
- You're the dean of students.
You're the dean.
It should have some impact.
- Why did you...
- It was just a gentle pat.
Anyway.
- Give him penalty points.
- Okay.
Just relax your chest.
I didn't tighten my chest.
You are threatening
enough already.
- So...
- He's intimidated.
You can't button up your jacket,
so you get one penalty point.
What about his fierce glare, sir?
- The defiant glare.
- What? You're still aggressive.
- He should get down again.
- He deserves five points.
I should look you in the eyes
when you talk.
His glare deserves
five penalty points.
- It deserves 5 points.
- He should get 15 points.
The teacher's authority is damaged.
You have to establish it already.
Sir, show us what you've got.
- Sir.
- You can do this.
How many penalty points?
- You're right.
- How many penalty points?
- Teacher.
- Tell him to lie down.
(The rookie comedian gets
carried away by their cheering.)
The teacher's authority
has been damaged.
- Get down.
- Show us what you can do.
- This is your last chance.
- Get down!
(Reckless)
(At this moment...)
- Tell him to get down.
- I'll get punished instead of him.
- Bo Sung.
- Go ahead and hit him.
(The angel of loyalty
steps up suddenly.)
Bo Sung.
Go ahead and hit him.
Teach him a lesson.
- You are a loyal friend.
- Loyalty.
- He's loyal.
- I'm loyal.
(The loyalty of an angel
protects even the strong.)
Hit him hard.
Hard?
- I'll hit you just once.
- He's so cool.
- There you go.
- You can hit me 10 times.
- I'll hit you just once.
- Loyalty.
- All right.
He's so loyal.
(Making a fuss)
(He got carried away
and lost control of his power.)
Hey, he's in his 50s.
Hey, Gyu Jin.
(It's so hard to be
an angel of loyalty.)
Bo Sung is...
Why did you hit me so hard?
(Why did you volunteer to get hit?)
- I was...
- You hit him gently earlier.
You are very loyal.
You know what?
What's really hilarious is...
that there was a puff of dust
from Bo Sung's pants.
Let me tell you why I got hit
instead of him.
He's really loyal.
In the show, "My Little Old Boy"...
If you don't want to get hit again,
just come here.
He gave me a padded vest.
- Just come here.
- He gave me...
- a padded vest as a gift.
- That's enough.
I'm a giver, actually. Not a taker.
He gave me a padded vest.
- All right. Next.
- It's in my car.
If you do something wrong again,
Bo Sung will get hit again.
- Okay.
- Behave yourself.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
- Loyalty!
- Bo Sung is so cool.
He's a loyal friend.
He's the man of loyalty.
- Hello, sir.
- All right. You're very polite.
- The turtleneck sweater.
- Yes.
- One penalty point.
- I'm wearing it because it's cold.
Is that because it's cold?
You should try to endure it.
(He sounds shy but firm.)
- One point.
- So Min, that doesn't work for him.
- So Min, your wink doesn't work.
- Don't fall for her tricks.
He's as firm as a rock.
What is this thing?
The kids in the dance club
won't hang out with me...
if I don't wear these.
- She sounds annoyed.
- No, I'm not.
You should care
about your dance skills instead.
(She already has dance skills.)
She's a good dancer.
She does dance well.
- She's a good dancer.
- She's good.
- She dances well.
- You've got good dance skills.
- Right.
- You dance well.
- I go to school for...
- She's really good.
She's good.
This is how she comes to school.
(Please don't give me
penalty points.)
- Is this your jacket?
- No, this isn't mine.
- It's yours.
- You can throw this away.
- This belongs to Suk Jin.
- Is it mine?
I think it's Bo Sung's.
- Isn't this yours?
- Sir, I saw Bo Sung was wearing it.
That belongs to Bo Sung.
Right. It's Bo Sung's.
- Teacher.
- This is yours.
- It's not mine.
- It's yours. Put it on.
- This is yours.
- No.
I've never seen this before.
I saw that too.
- I saw him wearing it.
- It fits him perfectly.
- It really isn't mine.
- It looks good on him.
- It's not mine.
- He's genuinely flustered.
- He doesn't want to be punished.
I'll let it slide just this once.
Now...
Let me think. I think that's enough.
I got too many penalty points.
- Thank you, Teacher.
- Why did I get so many?
- I got too many...
- You got 12 points?
- I got too many penalty points.
- You got six points?
- Se Chan got no penalty points.
- He got 18 points.
Why didn't you
get any penalty points?
- I don't know.
- Exactly. Why didn't he get any?
- Gosh, seriously.
- I don't understand.
Today, we'll find the best club
in Running High School.
It's The Burning 18 Again.
- "The Burning 18"?
- The Burning 18 Again.
You'll be divided into three groups,
which are the student guidance club,
dance club, and band club.
The club that gains
the most club fund will win.
All the members of the winning club
will receive a scholarship.
- All right.
- Great.
Meanwhile, regardless of
the club fund,
there's a penalty point system.
The three students who get
the most penalty points...
will stay after the shoot
to carry out an annoying penalty.
I hate annoying penalties.
I hate it the most.
- That's what I hate the most.
- I hate it too.
As for the penalty points,
just like he did earlier,
the dean of students will watch you
during the missions,
and announce the final results
at the end of the show.
During the club activity time
after each class,
you will have a chance
to steal another club's fund.
Okay.
If you give school support donations
to the dean of students,
your individual penalty points
will be deducted.
- So use this chance wisely.
- It won't be easy.
School support donation? Gosh.
Each club's fund will determine
the winning team.
- Let's go to the first classroom.
- Okay.
- Yes.
(They will move to the classroom
for the 1st class!)
(This is where Running High School's
classes will officially begin.)
(The club name is written
in front of each seat.)
- The dance club is the best!
- We're the dance club.
The dance, dance, dance club.
(The dance club members are
the 1st to arrive.)
(Stay with me)
(Forever)
Haha, the song suits you.
He looks like the singer too.
Right. He does look like the singer.
He looks a bit like Lee Moon Sae
if you cover his eyes.
Not just a little bit.
My nickname was Lee Moon Sae.
- Really?
- Little Lee Moon Sae.
Some people confuse me with him.
Mr. Shin, are you going to
be with us throughout the shoot?
Yes, Ms. Jeon, to the end.
I see.
He spoke formally to her.
Don't you have a meeting today?
- Oh, yes, I do,
- Yes.
but I play in the same comedy skit
with Mr. Yang.
I see you speak very politely
in real life.
- I didn't influence the decision.
- Is that so?
(Glancing)
(Jae Suk looked aside
and suddenly started giggling.)
(Why is he laughing suddenly?)
The stock prices of all the other
companies are going up...
except for the ones Suk Jin bought.
- What could be the reason?
- Suk Jin.
Why won't they go up
when the market is so rosy?
- Well, I guess...
- It's hard to believe.
And why did he get the blue sign?
He needs a red one.
- He's wearing red socks.
- You see,
I'm not joking. Only the ones
he bought won't go up.
- What's the reason?
- Why is that?
I don't know. I don't understand.
Why...
The first class is the subject
that you guys are worst at.
It's a moral education class.
- Gosh.
- What? I'm good at it.
- I'm really confident in it.
- Don't you know that?
My name is Moralconn.
I'm such a moral person.
- Moralconn?
- I'm Moralconn.
My nickname is Kim Moral.
The result of this class...
won't just determine...
- your club funds.
- Okay.
After the mission ends, Mr. Shin
will announce your penalty points.
You will get penalty points...
if you don't contribute
to the team's success...
or if you don't make people laugh.
All those things will be considered.
- We have to be funny too?
- Really?
Then do we gain an advantage
if we do something really funny?
- Of course, you do.
- Is that so?
(As soon as they heard the answer,
they started acting funny.)
(Imitating guitar sound)
What song is this?
- I don't know.
- All you guys do is scream.
- That's not funny at all.
- Exactly.
- Respect, respect, be respectful
- Be respectful
Do it with Ji Hyo.
- Respect, respect
- She can do it well too.
It ended when I took my mic out.
(Shouting together)
Hey, Ji Hyo. That doesn't suit you.
That's not true. What makes you
think so? I can pull it off.
Let's go, Song Jeoktoma.
(Let's go, Song Jeoktoma.
Giddy-up!)
(Imitating a running horse)
Ji Hyo is doing it reluctantly.
She didn't know what to do.
You didn't know, Song Jeoktoma.
- That was tacky.
- "Let's go, Song Jeoktoma."
- You say that first next time.
- By the way,
I want to join the band club.
Right? Didn't it make you
feel excited?
- They seem so energetic.
- Defconn.
- Let's do it too, Defconn.
- They give off a good vibe.
- That was exciting.
- We can do it too.
- We're the dance club.
- They're so cheerful.
You're right. We can do it.
- Suk Jin is a dance club member,
- We're the dance club.
but he's sitting
with his arms crossed.
- Dancers don't cross their arms.
- Exactly.
- Are you really in the dance club?
- Yes, I am.
- He just showed up one day.
- Oh, he just...
He joined the club
of his own accord.
Ji Suk Jin is in the dance club.
- Oh, that was what he meant?
- Yes.
- He joined us of his own accord.
- Loyalty!
Bo Sung, loyalty!
- Let's say "Guidance" instead.
Guidance!
- Good job.
- That's so him.
He's like a machine.
He does everything he's asked to do.
- He's like a machine.
- Are you really a human?
Aren't you a robot?
In the first class, you will learn
to be considerate of one another.
It's Break Up Strawberries
with Loyalty.
- Loyalty!
- Break Up Strawberries?
The strawberry game.
(You have to break up the syllables
of "strawberry" to the given beat.)
(1, St-raw-ber-ry)
(2, Straw-berry-straw-berry)
(3, Straw-berry
-strawberry-strawberry)
(4, Strawberry-strawberry
(They've played it before.
How well will they do this time?)
My goodness.
(You understand the rules, right?)
I don't think Bo Sung can
play this game.
It must be difficult for Bo Sung,
but Jae Suk is also
really bad at this game.
- We'll play the strawberry game?
- Yes.
- This is driving me nuts.
- Strawberry-strawberry
I'm worried about Bo Sung.
However, this time,
we'll have a team match.
For example, one of you said,
"Band, three."
The first member must begin.
If he says, "St-raw-ber-ry",
the other members have to
say twice more.
(St-raw-ber-ry, St-raw-ber-ry)
(St-raw-ber-ry)
And then you can attack
the other team.
(Student guidance club, 4!)
- I get it.
- The first member...
It's like the loyalty game.
It's a sort of loyalty game.
If someone says, "Dance, four",
Jong Kook will begin
as he's the first member.
I say, "St-raw-ber-ry".
- And you say, "St-raw-ber-ry".
- Oh, I get it.
- He says, "St-raw-ber-ry".
- St-raw-ber-ry
- I say, "St-raw-ber-ry".
- That's four.
Then I attack the other team.
Or he can say strawberry twice.
- And you say it twice too.
- I see. I get it now.
What does this game have to do
with moral education?
It's like the loyalty game.
It's a sort of loyalty game.
Can one person do it all at once
and attack the other team?
Yes.
But the maximum number
for 1 person is 4.
Correct. You can say it
up to four times.
- Let's do some practice.
- St-raw-ber-ry
I'll attack you.
Bo Sung, three.
- St-raw...
- No. You're already out.
He just wants to get his penalty
points deducted.
- My gosh.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Just to get his points deducted.
- Let's try it one more time.
- Bo Sung, three.
- Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Oh, okay.
- Again. Three.
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Bo Sung, three.
- Bo Sung...
- Bo Sung.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
It's so difficult for me.
I'll be honest.
I bet the student guidance club
will do worst among us.
Kwang Soo, it's hard to master
in one day.
Then there's no way we can win.
Team leaders,
play rock-paper-scissors
to decide the order.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Won't anyone
from that team come out?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Bo Sung, play rock-paper-scissors.
No, not with me.
Please keep it together.
- I'm confused.
- He can't keep it together.
- You don't play it with me.
- Okay. Here we go.
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors
- Oh, yes.
- You didn't win.
- She's playing the game too.
(He got excited
when no one won.)
- She's playing the game too.
- Oh, right.
He can't even play this game. How
will he play the strawberry game?
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Great.
- Good job.
- You did well.
- You guys go first.
- He won with a rock.
- We'll go first.
- Okay.
- How exciting. Let's go.
- This is exciting.
- Let's go
Let's go!
I really don't want to
let that team win.
Let's begin. Ready. Here we go.
- I like strawberries
Band, seven.
(The student guidance club is
attacking first!)
St-raw-ber-ry
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(Ji Hyo made a mistake.)
- Okay!
- Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
(Okay. That was good.)
You chose seven. That was brilliant.
- 7!
- 7 was a good choice.
That was unexpected.
Haha, I didn't know
how many times you said it.
- But... I mean...
- Oh, yes!
Jae Suk, we needed to do
some warm-up first.
You should've called a number
between 1 to 4.
- But you called seven.
- I don't care.
- Seven was a good choice.
- It was difficult.
- Let's call 6.
- I think 7 is the best.
- Why don't you...
- You two...
Bo Sung, just say it once.
Or maybe twice?
- Okay.
- Say it just once no matter what.
- St-raw-ber-ry
- That's all you have to do.
- Let's begin.
- Don't try anything else.
- We'll fill the rest.
- We'll begin.
- Okay.
- We're ready.
- Ready, go. I like strawberries
- I like strawberries
- Student guidance, six.
- Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
(Strawberry-strawberry
-strawberry-strawberry)
St-raw-ber-ry
(Bo Sung, the one they worried about
the most, succeeded.)
(They will succeed
if Jae Suk says 1 strawberry.)
Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Great.
- Why?
- You said...
- It was six.
- He said 4 strawberries.
- I did 4.
- Oh, you said it 4 times.
- And he said 1.
- You didn't have to say it.
- I thought you said it three times.
- This is driving me nuts.
- No, he should've said it once.
Or Bo Sung should've said it twice
and attack another team.
I said it four times.
- Only you know how to play this.
- You should have...
- I should've said it once.
- That's right.
Bo Sung, keep saying it just once.
Okay.
You say it just once too.
- Okay.
- My goodness.
- Is Jae Suk teaching him?
- Got it.
- This is crazy.
- Just say it once.
- Take that.
- They're all so stupid.
- It's my turn.
- Ready, go.
- I like strawberries
Dance, eight.
- Straw-berry
- He skipped his turn.
Gosh, Jong Kook.
Dance, eight.
(Straw-berry)
(Jong Kook skipped his turn.)
- Why didn't you do anything?
- Was it my turn?
- He said "Dance".
- Why didn't you do anything?
It's confusing because he called
our team name.
- Nice!
- We're the dance club.
- Let's call a number under five.
- Good job.
- High numbers are good for offense.
- Okay.
I didn't know we were
the dance club until now.
- Relax, everyone.
- Okay!
- The name makes it confusing.
- Just relax.
- We're the dance club, right?
- Ready, go.
- I like strawberries
- Student guidance, seven.
- Strawberry-strawberry
(Strawberry-strawberry
-strawberry-strawberry)
St-raw-ber-ry
Strawberry-strawberry
-strawberry-strawberry
I'm sorry.
Strawberry-strawberry
-strawberry-strawberry
(They picked a lot of strawberries.)
I'm sorry.
- Nine strawberries!
- He's an idiot.
- He's so stupid.
- Idiot, idiot.
- Why are you so nervous?
- All you had to do was...
- That was so funny.
- You should've said it once.
- By the way,
Bo Sung really does
as he was told.
This strawberry game is...
Bo Sung, are you a robot?
(Whatever number is called,)
(this loyal man says
only st-raw-ber-ry like a robot.)
Bo Sung, are you a robot?
- You should've said it once.
- Bo Sung is...
- Bo Sung...
- You should count it.
It's too hard to count it
while thinking about the beat.
- You have no choice.
- It's easy if you can count it.
- Bo Sung, always say it once.
- They're so stupid.
From now on,
if any one of us makes a mistake,
- he gets a slap in the face.
- Okay.
- A slap?
- Yes.
Gosh. Keep it simple then.
And go.
- I like strawberries
- Dance two.
- St-raw-ber-ry
St-raw... Ry
Seriously?
(He ignores the standard beat.)
- Suk Jin!
- He wasn't wrong though.
He only twisted the beat a little.
- It was him being laid-back.
- That's not allowed.
St-raw-ber-ry
- See?
- Seriously?
- I got confused.
- How can you get this wrong?
- I mean...
You said two.
- Only one.
- We agreed to do one each.
- 1 each.
- Why did I hear 2?
- Unbelievable.
- Seriously?
- Hey.
- Do it properly, will you?
- You got it wrong too, you know.
- What?
You got it wrong earlier too.
- Hey, you.
- Did you just hit me?
- What do you think you're doing?
- Seriously?
- I'm sorry.
- Listen to the teacher.
- The teacher's here.
- The teacher's with us.
Hear me out though, sir.
We're all allowed to make mistakes.
You made a mistake
on an easy one though.
- Jong Kook!
- Yes?
You've been
making too many mistakes.
Me?
You...
Bo Sung, get out here.
- He's already limping.
- But...
Why him?
- Can't you see he's limping?
- Just let him be.
- Get on the floor.
- Hold on.
I'm not kidding when I say
Bo Sung's on the older side.
Bo Sung, you can get up now.
I talked to the teacher.
- You can get up now.
- That's right.
(He gets a pass
thanks to his old age.)
Jong Kook. Make a mistake...
- and Bo Sung will get punished.
- got it.
- Don't intimidate others.
- Got it, sir.
- All right.
- Let's go.
Okay, let's get this party started!
- Let's party.
- Begin the party.
- I'd love to join that club.
We can be just as festive, you know.
Let's have fun too.
- As if.
- Just do one. Don't get confused.
- All right.
- Why don't we swap seats?
Just do it once.
St-raw-ber-ry
That's all you have to say.
Just the one.
Before we begin,
when they call our group,
start by saying "Loyalty" first.
Let's do this.
(The familiar word
has him all confused.)
What are you doing?
- He's messing with me, right?
- Of course.
- Right?
- Just say "St-raw-ber-ry".
Are you kidding me?
Bo Sung...
Bo Sung was actually considering it.
Se Chan told Bo Sung...
to say "Loyalty"
before playing the game.
And Bo Sung actually considered it.
(The innocent man
almost fell for the trick.)
Don't say it, okay?
- Got it.
- All right?
- Don't confuse me.
- Got it.
- Don't overdo it.
- We'll start with Haha.
- Haha goes first.
- Let's do this.
- 1, 2,
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I like strawberries
Student guidance, five.
St-raw-ber-ry
(He got confused
and missed his beat.)
You had me all confused.
The beat was off.
Let's practice, all right?
- St-raw-ber-ry
- Repeat after me.
- St!
St-raw-ber-ry
- Yes, say just that.
- Right.
Okay, let's make them lose.
We can't seem to go
back and forth though.
And go.
- I like strawberries
Dance, three.
St-raw-ber-ry
- Why?
- Defconn!
- St-raw!
- How is that so difficult?
- St-raw-ber-ry!
- Seriously?
- St-raw...
St-raw, st-raw.
- St-raw-ber-ry
- Do better yourself!
What do you mean?
I'm not doing so bad.
Was the beat off?
When Suk Jin was told
to do better himself,
he stepped backward saying,
"What do you mean?"
- Do better yourself?
- What...
- Stay behind after school.
- Ji Suk Jin, shut it.
- Shut it!
- Get out here.
- Shut it.
- Are you kidding me?
- Bo Sung!
(He's truly startled.)
- Bo Sung.
- Seriously?
- Why...
- What's wrong with you people?
Get back here.
- Why...
- Why are you twirling that?
- This...
- Why are you angry at me though?
Is this even real?
Well,
he gave me his jacket, right?
So you were defending me?
- That's right.
- You were being loyal.
- Loyalty!
I should give him one too then.
I'd rather you be better
at this game.
St-raw-ber-ry
Okay, got it.
- Strawberry.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- 3, 4.
- I like strawberries
- Band, four.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
That's wrong!
- What's wrong with you?
- Unbelievable.
- You should've said 1 or 2.
- How could you say 3?
- You said three.
- How clueless are you?
When you add 2 and 2,
it's is 4, isn't it?
- I said 2, remember?
- Why add on 3?
Even Dream would do better!
Why won't you listen to me?
Dream is watching, you know.
- Unbelievable.
- I'm trying to be funny!
Okay, let's go!
- Nice.
- All right!
- Let's go!
Can't we just play the game?
(I'd love to join the band club.)
- What?
- Straw, straw, straw!
I like strawberries!
- I like strawberries
(He's embodying Lee Bak Sa.)
- Must they be this loud?
(Being a member of the dance club,
So Min dances to the rhythm.)
- 1, 2.
- Seriously?
1, 2, 3, 4.
- Let's party, guys!
- We're the dance club, guys.
Let's do this.
- Just do it already.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I like strawberries
- Dance, four.
- Straw-ber-r-y
(Straw-ber-r-y)
- Dance, four.
- Straw-ber-r-y
(Straw-ber-r-y)
- Seriously?
- Defconn!
Just sit down, will you?
I mean...
- I can't do this.
- Are you kidding me?
- What on earth was that?
- Is this a joke?
- After all that practicing?
- Unbelievable.
- Come on!
- It's st-raw-ber-ry.
Let's not play this game!
Why can't you focus?
- But he...
- Let's sit back down.
Didn't you play games like this
on "2 Days and 1 Night"?
Not games like this.
This is driving me crazy.
- Right.
- It's your turn.
- Just give us a game console.
- Suk Jin, take his seat.
Can't we play games
like Street Fighter?
- Change seats.
- Okay, we'll change seats.
The smartest member should go first.
Can you be this bad?
I wouldn't be as bad as you though.
You're all so bad.
- Suk Jin, do well.
- Don't you worry.
Don't worry.
- He'll be all right.
- I'm not bad, you know.
- Are you sure?
- 1, 2,
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I like strawberries
- Why though?
- I like straw-berries
- I like them all.
- But why?
- I just do.
- Why?
- I just like them all.
- I just do.
- But why?
- Sweet, tasty, and sour.
- What about apples?
What about apples?
Apples?
Apples are tasty but expensive
(He was robbed of his timing.)
- Just do it already!
- Strawberries...
How about grapes?
I hate the seeds!
Strawberry seeds
burst pleasantly in your mouth
How about grapes?
Then what about muscat?
Muscat!
Expensive!
- How about grapes?
- It's 25 dollars for 3 clusters
- Muscat!
- What about geobong?
What if it's made into juice?
In order to make juice,
we need a juicer
Which means I need 50 dollars
to buy the juicer
I need 50 dollars to buy the juicer
I have no money, no money at all
I have no money
- I'd rather have strawberries!
- Game...
- Let's change the game to this.
- 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I like strawberries
- How about apples?
(Wasn't it over?)
How about apples?
Apples are only good in the morning
(Apples are only good
in the morning?)
- I like strawberries
- How about kiwis?
(The questions continue.)
New Zealand kiwis are the best
I like kiwis.
4 kiwis at the price of 10 dollars
When on sale,
you can get 6 for 10 dollars
- How...
- When on sale?
Why are they more expensive
when on sale?
- When on sale?
- Why though?
- They're more expensive on sale.
- How's that possible?
I'm proud of you.
Why aren't you starting the game?
(He brings out
his nunchucks again.)
Just start the game!
You startled us.
Why would you run out like that?
This isn't how you act here.
- No?
- Of course not.
He's the one you should be angry at.
So shut it!
- Okay, fine.
- It's so funny that I'm crying.
The game just won't start.
I'll make sure that Suk Jin
can never start the game.
I love the strategy.
Shut it. Just shut it!
- I'm proud of you.
- He keeps answering me though.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I like strawberries
- Band, four.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
Straw-berry-straw-berry
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
Why?
What I said made four.
- Really?
- Then you should've attacked.
Right, I should've.
I was going to,
but you beat me to it.
- Really?
- You idiot!
Even Dream could do better.
What did you just say?
(Dream's father explodes.)
(Swearing)
(Jong Kook gets up.)
You...
Did it end with you?
Yes, I said enough to make four.
Bo Sung...
- Bo Sung took out his nunchucks.
- Hold on.
- He...
- Did you see that?
Why do you keep
taking out your nunchucks?
(His nunchucks appear every time
someone challenges Jong Kook.)
Why do you keep
pulling out your nunchucks?
We're one unit, you know.
What kind of winter jacket
did you give him?
(Could he be loyal
to the padded jacket?)
- Loyalty.
- Loyalty!
All right.
The three teams are at a tie.
All right, then.
We only need to get it right once.
It's all about who you attack.
Just one.
We only need to get it right once.
Right.
The dance club will be called.
(The band club gets ready
once again.)
(Haha, the vocal drummer)
(Yang Se Chan, backup vocals)
(A cappella instrumental band)
- Strawberries
- Are you hearing this?
Strawberries, strawberries
When will they be in season?
(Song Ji Hyo, main vocalist)
When will you begin the game?
(Song Jeoktoma's dance break)
- Ji Hyo doesn't want to do it.
- She hates it.
- She...
- Did you see her?
Just get on with the game!
Stop fooling around
and begin the game!
Ji Hyo would probably want
to be in the student guidance club.
- We're just as strict, you know.
- The student guidance club.
- I like strawberries
- Student guidance, five.
- Straw...
- St-raw-ber-ry
- Why would you say it?
- Hold on.
(He called
the student guidance club, but...)
Why would you say it instead?
- Why...
- Suk Jin, why?
I killed 2 birds with 1 stone.
Why would you say it...
when he targeted
the student guidance club?
The two clubs start with
a completely different letter.
- Why didn't you target us?
- S and D, right?
Before...
- I'm not even angry anymore.
- But...
Were you hearing things?
Why would you answer...
when he targeted the other team?
I'm sorry.
Would you like
to go first this time?
Nice.
- But...
- Just know...
that this isn't an easy position.
All you have to do is say one.
- Just one.
- It's not easy at all.
- All you have to do is say one.
- Then take the seat.
Just do one each.
We're the dance club,
so let's dance beforehand.
- I'd rather not.
- But we're the dance club!
But we're the dance club.
- What kind of dance club...
- Why...
(She's dancing alone in the end.)
- I like strawberries
- She's dancing alone.
- Hold on a second.
Hang on.
This is practically
a school talent show.
- Let's dance together.
- You guys...
- They look like the parents.
- You let her dance alone.
This is not So Min's talent show.
- Why would she dance alone?
- Let's dance together.
Strawberries, strawberries
Let's dance together.
- Why won't any of you do it?
- Okay. Let's do it.
- Let's do it.
- Jong Kook won't even listen.
- I'm so upset because of him.
- Strawberries, strawberries
- I'm not in the mood for dancing.
- Straw-straw
- Straw
- I'm so upset.
(He got excited
without grasping the situation.)
- Strawberries
- How about pineapples?
Pineapples have so many spikes
- Strawberries are the best
- Then what about shine muscat?
(This is crazy.)
(They begin the game
before it goes on longer.)
- I like strawberries
Student guidance, eight.
Guidance-guidance-guidance
(Jae Suk was taken aback.)
Give me another chance.
Let me do it over again.
- I was preoccupied.
- Only Bo Sung must be at ease.
I was preoccupied.
- The dance club!
- Bo Sung's position is the best.
- You should focus on the game.
- I know.
We're the winning team now.
- Nice.
- It's hard.
- We must not be in last place.
- We can do this.
Bo Sung will begin the game.
- Okay.
- You can attack another team.
- Attack?
- Attack.
Attack the band club, Bo Sung.
- Okay.
- Attack the student guidance club.
- No, attack the band club.
Why did you say okay?
We're the student guidance club.
- Hey!
- Don't say "student guidance".
- Never do that.
- Never say "student guidance".
Got it. Understood.
(Se Chan could have tricked
Bo Sung again.)
Do you want us to play
the cymbals?
- Should we be ambitious?
- Straw-berry
(Imitating cymbals)
(The band club's performance
before the final round)
Here goes Jae Suk
(Dancing)
- Come on.
- Here goes Jae Suk
We're the dance club,
but we never dance.
(The other members
won't even budge.)
(Chug, chug, puff, puff)
(Chug, chug, puff, puff,
chug, chug, puff, puff)
(The strawberry train is
about to leave.)
(How exciting.)
(A cheer captain got on the train
out of the blue.)
When are you going to begin?
Hurry up.
- Strawberries, strawberries
(The final chant is
getting close to the climax!)
- 1, 2. 1, 2. 1, 2, 3, 4.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I like strawberries
(Bo Sung will begin the round.)
Student guidance, eight.
(Student guidance, 8!)
(The most hilarious finale)
What just happened?
- You should've continued.
- You should've said it.
- Why didn't you say it?
- You should've said strawberries.
- No. They failed.
- You should've continued.
- We won.
- No. Hang on.
- This isn't fair.
- It's all because of him.
- I mean, he...
- My gosh.
- Just admit it.
- No, it's not fair.
You should've said it
because he called your team.
I told you that we're
the student guidance club.
- No, it's okay.
- You could've continued.
- It's okay, Bo Sung.
- No, we couldn't.
- You could've said strawberries.
- The game would've continued...
if you had said it.
- It's either dance or band.
- We would've accepted it.
Exactly. We would've continued
the game if they said it.
The band club won the game.
(The band club came in 1st.)
The dance club is in second place,
and the student guidance club is
in third place.
It's not so bad.
You will receive the club funds
in a little while.
- Let's go.
- It's over. It was nice.
- It's over.
- That was funny.
- Good job, everyone.
- Thank you, Sir.
(It's time to announce
the penalty points.)
Some of you got penalty points
while playing the game.
- Why five points?
- What?
Why did I get penalty points?
Yoo Jae Suk got five points.
- Great.
- And...
- Why did Defconn get 3 points?
- Why did I get 5 points?
Why did I get three points?
First, Jae Suk did such a poor job
playing the game.
(He got penalty points
because he was bad at the game.)
- That's true.
- He can't deny it.
I gave him five points because
he ruined the flow of the game.
Then what about me?
Se Chan, you were too sly.
That's true.
You were too sly.
- So I gave you three points.
- What about me?
Defconn, you failed to keep
your appearance neat and tidy.
But he was like this
from the beginning.
Aren't you just teasing him?
- My appearance has nothing to do...
- He keeps saying it.
Does that mean he'll get
penalty points in every mission?
Will he get penalty points
every single time?
You could cover yourself a little.
- Cover what?
- How? What should I do?
Aren't you just teasing him?
Now, I'll explain to you
about the club activity...
- after the lunch break.
- Okay.
- Each club will receive funds.
- Yes.
After that, go to your club rooms,
and hide the money
in different places in the rooms.
However, you must hide
all the money you receive.
You shouldn't keep any of it.
You're not allowed
to hide the money...
- on your bodies.
- Got it.
Next, choose one member
from your club.
To find the money?
That person will be blindfolded...
Blindfolded?
and will guard the club room.
As for the other club members...
They have to go to
the other club rooms...
and find the money
hidden in the rooms.
You can hit them
with a toy hammer.
- That means you're out.
- Exactly.
- If you get hit by the toy hammer,
- Yes.
- you're automatically out.
- Oh, I see.
The total amount of the money
you steal...
and the money you keep safe
will be your club fund.
Also, if you think you got
too many penalty points,
you can give me
school support donations,
and I'll deduct 1 point
for 10 cents.
- 10 cents?
- So...
if you want to get a deduction,
come to see me quietly.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
- I'll give you your club funds now.
- How much is it?
The club in first place...
- Only 1 dollar?
- 50 cents, 70 cents, and 1 dollar.
- How much?
- 50 cents.
Now, you may go to
your club rooms.
We should hide our money well
and find their money well.
The dance club!
The dance, dance, dance club.
(The club rooms are decorated
just like the old days!)
All right. Let's hide our money.
Let's go.
(No mullets)
- Think about where to hide it.
- Okay.
We shouldn't hide it where they can
see upon the entrance.
(The band club members actually
started their club activity.)
(I like it so much)
(Americano)
(I like it)
(What should I do?)
I only try to make myself look cool.
That's all I care about.
Even when I'm so bad at singing.
(They started playing a song
inspired by the strawberry game.)
(They're too busy
making themselves look cool.)
(It looks like a religious meeting
to worship strawberries.)
Gosh, those punks.
They're so loud.
(They're annoying the other teams
by making noise.)
I want to perform
in front of people.
Like a busker.
Although I'm a lousy singer.
Did you enjoy my song?
(He's only trying to look cool.)
Well, I think I haven't even done
half of it yet.
- Are you ready to have fun?
- Yes!
Next, I'm going to sing a song
by the singer you all love...
- Do you know Jason Mraz?
- Yes.
I'll sing "I'm Yours".
(He'll really sing
such a romantic song?)
("I'm Yours".)
Give me the beat.
(Here comes the beat.)
(Singing gibberish)
(Half air, half scat)
(He turned the song
into a scat song without lyrics.)
I don't know the lyrics.
(Bas, bo, okay)
(Singing gibberish)
(His weakness is
his poor English proficiency.)
(I'm yours)
You may start hiding your money.
We should start hiding the money?
(The other clubs started
hiding their money!)
Roll it and put it inside
so they can't see it.
(Jae Suk is leading the team
as if he has a lot of experience.)
Okay.
(Where should I hide it?)
But you see...
Jae Suk, wouldn't hiding it here
stall for time?
- They'll find it easily.
- Really?
- That's not good enough.
- Is that so?
(While pretending to be
helping them, Kwang Soo...)
It might take them a long time.
They might waste their time here.
(He's taking out the money he hid
while looking at them.)
(Kwang Soo stole the money
while Jae Suk was looking away.)
How about under the cushion?
(He's planning to use it
to get his penalty points deducted.)
(Jae Suk and Bo Sung
didn't notice it.)
How about under the cushion?
- Shall we hide it under there?
- I'm not sure.
(While the members of the 3 clubs
are busy hiding their money...)
(Looking around)
Here you go.
(Haha gave
a school support donation.)
You got a lot of penalty points.
The team in 2nd place
received 70 cents,
- so get three points deducted.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo, we'll be fine, right?
Here.
(Haha got 3 points deducted
thanks to his loyal club members.)
You will leave your club rooms
in 10 seconds.
You can kill them
with that toy hammer, right?
- Of course, I can.
- Okay.
- I can hit them with my fist.
- 10,
9, 8...
- Grab them first.
- Can I grab them?
- 6, 5...
- Keep our money safe.
- Okay.
- Three.
- Loyalty!
- Two.
- 1.
Loyalty!
- The loyalty of an angel.
- Find their money.
- Here we go. We can do it.
- Let's go!
- Good luck, guys.
- Jong Kook, good luck.
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo are going
straight to the dance club room.)
(Solemn)
Are you going to tell me
if someone comes in?
(He already got scared
by how he looks.)
(It means he won't let anyone
steal even 10 cents.)
(Jong Kook's
impenetrable defense...)
(scared them and made them
walk out for now.)
Gosh, I'm so scared.
(She's terrified.)
I'm so scared of him
that I can't live anymore.
(Bo Sung is swinging the hammer
in the air.)
Loyalty!
The loyalty of an angel.
(However...)
(The loyal man can't notice
people coming in.)
(They came into the room
without any problems.)
(Loyalty! Loyalty!)
(Relaxed and worry-free)
(The dance club members are
targeting the loyal man.)
Has it begun?
Yes, it's begun.
(Following the dance club members,)
(Kwang Soo came into
the student guidance club room.)
(Kwang Soo left the room
with Jae Suk earlier.)
(After giving the money he stole
as a school support donation,)
(he boldly came back
to his club room.)
(He quickly took out the money
hidden in the tissue box.)
Loyalty!
(He starts stealing
money for his club.)
(Right then,
Defconn spots Kwang Soo.)
It's not here.
(Betraying Kwang Soo captured.)
- Did you find it?
- Loyalty!
(Bo Sung approaches them
after hearing the noise.)
- What's this? Who is it?
- It's me.
- Who is this?
- Kwang Soo is out.
How can I be killed
by my own team member?
- You can!
- Kwang Soo is out.
I can kill my team member?
- You can.
- So why are you here?
- But...
- Why are you here?
To protect you, of course!
- Why would you protect me?
- What's this?
Kwang Soo, you're out.
Come this way.
- No, I found this.
- Darn it.
Kwang Soo, come here.
Stand here.
Stand against the wall.
You...
I told you
to stand against the wall.
(He pays the school support donation
even when he's caught.)
- Stand against the wall.
- How dare you steal from us?
That's not it.
Stand against the wall
with your hands up.
You have one minute left.
(Jae Suk snuck into the band club
to find Kwang Soo's money.)
(Scared)
(Haha couldn't catch anyone
as he was busy making a fuss.)
Let's go, guidance club!
He's right there!
To your right! Over there!
- He's right there!
- Time's up.
Time's up, everyone.
(There's already 60 cents
for the school support donation?)
- Is it over?
- It's over.
- I couldn't find any.
- Right?
- I know.
(Who else paid the support donation
besides Kwang Soo and Haha?)
- What are we playing this time?
- It's table tennis!
Wow, it's going to be so fun!
Let's play a game.
I'm really good at table tennis.
- There he is! The king of...
- Come on!
(The table is surrounded
by the bluffers already.)
- This is what I'm talking about!
- Yes, I love table tennis.
The 1988 Olympics generation.
We are the 1988 Olympics generation.
(They begin their practice rally.)
It's a rally.
(Swinging)
Bo Sung is not that good.
- You're bad at it.
- You're pretty bad at it.
- Bo Sung's not a good player.
- He's worse than I thought.
How strange. I'm usually good.
No, wait a minute. Let me try again.
Let me try again.
Come on.
He can't hit a backhand smash.
Which sports are you good at?
(Which sports are you good at?)
- There you go.
- Give him a chance.
- Bo Sung...
- My gosh.
- Bo Sung.
- You can't just hit randomly.
- He's so bad.
- That's not how you hit.
Are you playing
badminton or something?
(Will Bo Sung be able to
take a part in this mission?)
Let me tell you the rules
of the final mission.
According to the result
of the moral education class,
the band club won 1 dollar
as they won 1st place.
- They won 1 dollar?
- The dance club won...
- 70 cents as they won 2nd place.
- Okay!
The student guidance club won
50 cents as they came in 3rd.
Now, tell us
how much you have in total.
- We have 60 cents.
- 60 cents.
We have 60 cents.
Someone took our 10 cents.
- We also have 60 cents.
- We have 50 cents.
- We have 60 cents.
- That's right.
- 60?
- Because he found 10 cents.
We have 30 cents.
(The student guidance club
has 30 cents.)
We must win this mission.
The second class, our last one,
is a PE class.
- All right, PE!
- I love it!
- That's ours to win.
- We're actually a sports club.
You'll be playing table tennis
to expand your territory.
Expand our territory? What's that?
Unlike the standard table tennis,
three people will play on each side.
Each club can designate a member
to receive a penalty point.
In return, you can add two squares
to the other team's table.
That means the other team
will have a harder time winning.
Oh, we must be using these.
- We'll be using these.
- Really?
- I think so.
- Oh, this one?
- Really?
- We can add more space here.
I've never played a game of
table tennis like this.
We'll have more space to hit.
(To buy a part of their territory,
one of them has to sacrifice.)
But you must choose a member
to receive a penalty point.
- It's like hopscotch.
- We need to buy a lot then.
You can purchase their territory
anytime you want.
Each team will play against
different teams...
to decide the final winner.
If every team has a win and a loss,
we'll decide the winner by points.
The teacher will be watching you
in this class as well.
- Okay!
- All right.
- Let's play against the dance club.
- That sounds great.
Okay, bring it on.
- We want to buy their territory.
- Okay!
(Student guidance club
versus band club)
Where shall we place it?
Shall we place two at the back?
Since we must win,
- we need to buy a lot.
- We'll be buying penalty points.
We'll be giving 2 pieces
for 1 penalty point.
Then we'll buy around 20 pieces
with Bo Sung's penalty points.
(We'll buy around 20 pieces
with Bo Sung's penalty points.)
(With my penalty points?)
We can only buy up to 20?
- Shall we buy 10 pieces first?
- 10?
- We can win this.
- It'll be fine if we win.
- Really?
- It's our last chance.
If you approve it, then you'll be
getting the punishment.
No, Bo Sung.
Don't be tricked by them.
They should also get
the penalty points equally.
- You said you can take a lot.
- He's being a jerk.
- Is he?
- He's a total jerk.
It's time to flex your muscles.
He's a total jerk.
- You need to flex your muscles.
- Yes, I got 17.
(He flexes his muscles right away.)
- You have 17?
- Yes, I got 17.
It doesn't even hurt that much.
- He's a jerk.
- Bo Sung, you're...
- We must win so that...
- Come here, Bo Sung.
- You need to divide the points.
- Kwang Soo has 17 points.
Then we have Bo Sung receive...
2 penalty points.
We'll buy 4 pieces.
Only four?
- Let's buy more later.
- We need at least eight.
Let's buy four first.
- Kwang Soo, are we set?
- Bo Sung, let's use one more point.
- Sure, that's fine.
- Thank you so much!
(Sure, go ahead.)
Kwang Soo, place it here.
Shall we place one here
so that it can get in their way?
- Okay, let's place one there.
- Sir.
We'll be placing them like this.
Se Chan, how about we put ours
on the side?
- Sure, let's put them here.
- Let's put them on the side.
Then we can go after their side.
That's a good idea.
- You're expanding both sides?
- That's how you'll place them?
- That won't help anyway.
- Let me warn you all.
We won't be this petty.
We'll win with our skills.
- We'll use our skills.
- Move.
Don't we have to play
the standard game first?
- Of course!
- They placed them too early.
It's because they're bad
at table tennis.
Whose penalty points are you using?
We'll be using Se Chan's.
(We'll be using Se Chan's.)
What are you talking about? You said
we'll play rock-paper-scissors.
But you have no penalty points.
Let's use your points first,
- then we'll take turns.
- Okay.
- You're using 3 points?
- Yes, 3 points. Okay.
You should shout out "my ball".
Say "my ball"
when you want to hit the ball.
Can we start now?
Let's play a round to decide
who serves first.
Okay, let's do that.
- Bo Sung took off his sunglasses.
- He did.
- Now, he's...
- Bo Sung took off his sunglasses.
- Show us what you got now.
- Okay, sure.
All right, this is a game
to decide who serves first.
(The game to decide
the first server starts.)
There's no need to rush.
There you go.
(The ball stably goes
back and forth.)
Slowly. There you go.
(They keep hitting
to Jae Suk's side.)
Haha is pretty good.
- All right!
- Nice!
(Se Chan missed it.)
- Jae Suk is our ace.
All right, we're doing great!
- I'm more serious than ever.
- This is an important match.
Let Bo Sung join in too.
- Let's go, Bo Sung!
- Let's go!
- Show us what you got.
- Sure.
- He's so ugly.
- Hit it, Haha.
- Okay!
- Yes!
(He's so ugly.)
- Hit it, Haha.
- Okay!
He was so ugly... Isn't it cheating
to make an ugly face?
You're supposed to throw the ball
before you serve.
- But he did this.
- That's not how you serve.
- If you do that...
- No, it doesn't matter.
This should be allowed though.
Since this is a variety show,
you should throw it a little.
- Okay, then.
- Okay.
You should serve, Bo Sung.
It's okay as long as
you pass the ball to the other side.
Bo Sung, show us a fiery serve.
Shoot a sharp serve.
You can do it!
(Okay...)
You need to throw the ball.
- Wait a minute.
- Wait!
He needs to throw the ball!
- You can do it!
- You need to throw the ball.
(Using a table-adhering,
magical serving method)
He needs to throw the ball!
What was that?
- He did it.
- What was that about?
- What's wrong with it?
- You can't serve like that.
You should go easy on the guests.
Go easy on the guests.
- This is a legit way to serve.
- It's his first time playing.
- This is allowed!
- We can serve like that?
- This is allowed then?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- This is allowed.
(It's Bo Sung's serve again.)
You should receive it.
- Nice!
- You should receive it.
(Bo Sung got them again.)
- How did he do that?
- This shouldn't be allowed.
(Scoring 2 points
with a table-adhering serve)
- How do you do that?
- All right.
- How does he serve like that?
- You just push the ball forward.
- It's allowed.
- What is that?
Push the ball forward.
That's a slider.
- No, that's a curveball.
- How does he do that?
You're good. You should serve.
You want me to serve again?
He serves weirdly.
- His ball is slow,
- He hits there.
- but it doesn't stop.
- It's better for us if they win.
- Okay!
- All right.
(There you go!)
- Okay!
- All right.
- He should serve again.
- It's weird.
- He's so...
- We need one more point.
- That's right.
Let me tell you the official rules
as a professional player.
- You should...
- Suk Jin, move.
The ball needs to leave your hand.
- Move, move.
- Hey!
Go away.
- Hey! Bo Sung...
- Move.
- Move!
- The ball needs to leave your hand!
- All right.
- Let's play now.
- The ball needs to leave your hand.
- He can't serve from there.
- He should step back.
- There you go.
- The ball hit the net.
(Se Chan's smash)
Okay!
(Se Chan hit the ball
right at the territory they bought.)
- There you go.
- Okay!
Well done, Se Chan!
- You're good.
- Let's bring back the momentum.
- There you go.
- I want to play too.
- Okay!
Don't hit the ball to Se Chan.
- Okay, I got it.
- You shouldn't give it to Se Chan.
- What about it?
- Hit it quickly.
(The band club
sustains the momentum.)
(Okay!)
Smash it. Okay!
(He succeeds
in hitting 3 smashes in a row.)
- Okay!
- Hold on! Time out.
- Let us use your penalty points.
- We turned the tables on you.
- Hang on.
- Let us buy more territory.
- In an instant.
- Let us buy two more pieces.
- Let us buy more territory.
How could you get...
- smashed instantly?
- Se Chan is quite good.
Se Chan. Se Chan is really good.
Give me the ball.
(Clenching their teeth)
We're buying more territory.
Whose penalty points are you using?
Bo Sung's.
Stop bullying Bo Sung!
- It's okay.
- We're using Bo Sung's points.
Why would you let them
take advantage of you, Bo Sung?
I'm ruined already.
We need to win first.
It'll be fine if we win, Bo Sung.
We're all set.
Let's play now.
We must get this.
Why don't you take turns to serve?
Only one person is playing.
- Let Ji Hyo play too.
- Okay, Ji Hyo.
- Let her play.
- But I'm not good.
- It's okay. The ball...
- It's okay if you're bad.
needs to hit our table first
and theirs.
- So this is how you play.
- It needs to hit our table first.
- There you go. That's how you play.
- Spike!
No, that doesn't count!
(A powerful return)
- Hey.
- That was...
You can't do that.
All right. We won.
- We won.
- That's so mean.
- Kwang Soo must be upset!
- We won.
- Good job.
They lost.
- That little...
- Kwang Soo must be upset.
- Kwang Soo is upset.
- Okay!
- He's so annoying.
- Ji Hyo must be hurt.
- Okay!
Kwang Soo.
I'll throw the ball, you serve.
(Whispering)
Who should hit the ball? Me or you?
Jae Suk, let Bo Sung join in too.
(A team play of their own)
Let him join in too!
Why would you leave him out?
- It's not like that.
- Let him join in too.
Are you only using Bo Sung
for penalty points?
- Let him join in too.
- No.
Bo Sung, I'm sorry.
They only use Bo Sung
for penalty points.
- Yes.
- Go.
Okay.
That's it. It went in.
(He even scored a point.)
- Wait a minute.
- It went in.
- But he hit it from here.
But Bo Sung just did it
without discussing it with us.
- It went in.
- We were planning something else.
- But...
- He's sly.
- It went in.
- That's nice.
What you did had
no sense of loyalty.
- Let's stack them.
- This won't do.
It's too large.
There won't be any outs this way.
Just use mine then.
How many points is that total?
- Yes.
- Do you have five penalty points?
How many are you stacking?
- Is Bo Sung buying more?
- You have to buy them.
- With whose points?
- Are you buying them?
- With Kwang Soo's points.
- Wait a minute, I...
- You can't add to my points.
- I'll do it.
- I didn't agree.
- Okay.
- We'll add to Kwang Soo's points.
- I have 17 points.
- Just buy two.
- What?
- You're buying them with my points?
- Yes.
- Wait, I didn't agree.
- Let's add 9 and 2 more.
It's funny though.
It expanded up to there.
You should hit an unexpected ball.
- We don't know who'll hit a serve.
- I'll hit it.
- Come.
- Go.
(A copy and paste
table tennis ball show)
Pin the ball down.
- He's out.
- He was too greedy.
- He should have succeeded.
- He has to succeed to survive.
- That's right.
I also want to try that.
- Okay.
- My shoulders hurt.
- Let's go to the finals. It's fun.
- Let's go.
You will go to the finals?
Oh, my. What is happening?
(What?)
(Their ambush failed.)
- That was really fast.
- It's the finals.
- You shouldn't have said anything.
- They won.
- It was the finals.
- We won because of that.
- If you were going to feint...
- I'm sorry.
- If you going for an ambush...
- You shouldn't have said anything.
If a team scores one more point,
the game will be over.
It's okay as long as we win, right?
- Kim Bo Sung, you can do it!
- Yes.
(They reconfirm their determination
since victory is before their eyes.)
(Se Chan's serve)
- Hit it lightly.
- Is it the match point?
- Okay.
- That's good.
(Se Chan passed the ball
toward Kwang Soo.)
- Oh, my.
- Nice!
(He hurrahed as a reflex.)
- What did he just do?
(Kwang Soo avoided the ball, but it
settled safely on their territory.)
- The band club won the first round.
- We won.
(The penalty point donator is
feeling bitter.)
- They won because of this.
- We lost.
I couldn't hit the ball
because of this.
(This result was caused by expanding
territory only on one side.)
- Good job.
- We did a really good job.
Let's try a rally.
- Good.
- Let's do a rally.
- Let's do it once.
- Please let me play.
- Okay, wait a minute.
- Wait a minute.
- If we have some extra time,
- we will let you play.
- Gosh.
- I...
- Do you want to put this in here?
I will give up five of
my penalty points to play.
(They're preoccupied
with playing table tennis.)
- Gosh, So Min.
- Jong Kook.
I will give up five of
my penalty points to play.
I want to play.
- I also want to play.
- You're good.
- I will give you five points.
- Everyone...
- I also want to play!
- I'm good.
- Let's play one more time.
I also want to play!
- So Min, play.
- Okay.
- I'll give you five points.
- Okay, let's go.
- Join in.
- And...
Please decide who she will play
against for the first round.
You Small Fries should come out.
- Yes, student guidance club.
- Small fries, come out.
- That'll be a real match.
- So Min, you should go first.
- Give up 1 point each.
- I'll buy So Min's 5 points.
We will serve.
Okay, go first.
- Show them an unexpected ball.
- Bo Sung.
- His ball is really unexpected.
- It really is.
- It's hard to block.
- I'll block it.
I can block it.
(Big Nose who is about
the same age is confident.)
(The unexpected ball sets off.)
You can block it like this.
- Okay.
- Oh, my.
You can block it like this.
(His arm was too short.)
- He got caught.
- It was too long.
- Gosh.
- Hey!
- Don't laugh.
He's really so annoying.
Okay, good.
Okay.
It's okay.
- He's really enjoying it.
- It's okay.
Don't be affected by him.
- Don't be affected by him.
- I'm not affected at all.
Good job.
(The dance club lost a point.)
- He's not teasing you.
- Did you see that, Jong Kook?
- Not at all. It didn't bother me.
- Hey.
- He's not scoffing at you.
- No.
(Bo Sung continues to serve.)
- That's right!
- Gosh.
(He's too short again.)
- It's okay.
- There's a distance, so it's okay.
- Okay.
- We can't let them off now.
- Spread some more territory.
- You also have Jeon So Min.
- Okay.
- So Min.
- That's right.
- Okay.
It's okay.
- It's okay.
- I was warming up.
- So Min, just sit down.
- It's okay.
- No, I was warming up.
- Come to the center.
- Good job.
- It's funny to see...
So Min make a vain effort.
We just have to score
five more points with this spirit.
(The student guidance club is
in high spirits now.)
We scored a lot of points.
- Wait a minute. Time out.
- We scored a lot of points.
Jong Kook kept pushing me with
his arm to tell me to leave.
- He told me to leave.
- No, So Min. You are completely...
(Stealthily)
(He stealthily pushed her again.)
- Just be in charge of the corner.
- I kept moving to the center,
- and you said, "Leave."
- Just be in charge of the corner.
Just the two of them are playing.
- Where should I stop?
- No, right here.
- It's a match.
- Right here. That's good.
(Guest "Dae Buk Gon" is
also excluded from the match.)
It's a really important match,
So Min.
Wait a minute.
Both of them have a sense of
pride when it comes to table tennis.
- Can you hit from the side?
- Yes?
- From the side?
- This is perfect.
If the ball crosses the net,
it's yours, okay?
- Okay, I understand.
- How can I hit it from here?
If the ball crosses the net,
it's yours.
Wait a minute.
- What?
- Okay.
Suk Jin, why did you take
your jacket off?
You said you were the representative
of something.
- What do you represent?
- Gosh.
- I'll stay back later. You...
- Are you losing?
- Let's play like doubles.
- Try it. No.
- No.
- I'm also here.
- But...
- No, I'm also here.
- He said it was a doubles game.
- The audio isn't being recorded.
- No, but...
Where is my mic?
- Your mic...
- My mic doesn't matter right now.
I added territory here
with my five points.
I have a share.
I think we will lose
when I didn't even play.
No, I'm sorry, Defconn.
It's an important moment right now.
(The members become this serious
when they play ball games.)
Be careful of feinting.
- Gosh.
- Stop saying "Gosh" and just...
- That's good!
- Gosh.
Stop saying "Gosh" and just...
(Gosh...)
- Look at that.
- Hey.
Add more territory.
- No, it's okay.
- It's okay.
Hey, we can't reach it!
(He teases with all his might.)
(Ignoring his taunts
isn't as easy as it seems.)
(He exaggerates with all his might.)
That's it.
(His face turned red.)
(Jong Kook becomes full of humanity
whenever he plays ball games.)
I'll try it once
and then you should try it.
- It's because we both...
- Okay.
- try to do it at the same time.
- I got it. Let's try that.
(The outskirt table tennis player
penetrated the center.)
(Meanwhile, she's doing an intense
simulation in the center.)
She's really incredible.
So Min is really incredible.
She tries endlessly.
- She's like a weed.
- She's really incredible.
- She won't die no matter what.
- Jeon So Min is incredible.
Spread some more territory.
They can reach it, but we can't.
- It's disadvantageous for us.
- We can't reach the short ones.
Anyway, are you angry?
I'm not angry at all.
- Angry? I'm smiling right now.
- You look angry.
- But after you came here...
- I'm not angry at all.
(While the eldest brother was
putting his anger aside...)
Bring that over here.
(The guest is buying
territory quietly.)
Excuse me... Anyway...
- Just do it.
- We should also...
- I'll receive short serves here.
- Okay.
- Okay, that's good.
Hit a serve toward here.
- Defconn, aren't you going to play?
- Why won't you let him join in?
- Jong Kook.
- Look after the guests!
Defconn is sullen.
Suk Jin, let him play.
Let him play.
- Defconn.
- What's the point of playing now?
What's the point of playing now
when you have ruined the match?
You can be in charge of reactions.
- Reactions, my foot!
- Reactions.
(Reactions?)
I will never visit this show again!
I will never visit
this lousy show again!
(This guest curses the show
on his first visit.)
- We need to win.
- Come on.
How dare you treat a guest
like this?
It's the producer's job
to tell the members to switch!
- Defconn.
- You seem younger than me too!
I am sorry.
I apologize for my outburst.
You can play in the next round.
- All right. Okay.
- All right.
Suk Jin told him
to show reactions and go home.
"Defconn, show reactions
and go home."
(Defconn's mood improves
since he can play the next time.)
We have the worst teamwork.
You agree, right?
Everyone is playing individually.
Also, Suk Jin is trying to play...
all by himself.
- I could do this alone.
- He is like Nolbu.
(Like Nolbu, he is declaring
that he would rather play alone.)
- You need to win.
- All right.
You need to do better.
- That's right.
- For goodness' sake.
Stay there until the ball comes.
- Think of it as doubles.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay, okay.
- Tell me when to come in.
- Let's go.
- No, no.
I could do this.
- Come on.
- Stay there.
- So Min, stay there.
- Here it comes.
Here it comes.
There you go.
- He sent it over.
- Hey.
(Jong Kook's two backhands in a row)
There you go.
(Kwang Soo hits it again.)
- Hey!
- What was that?
(The match ends
because of Suk Jin's mistake.)
For goodness' sake.
Take it off. All of it.
- What was that?
- Suk Jin.
- Loyalty!
- We won.
The last match is between
the dance club and the band club.
Let's go!
(The result
of band club versus dance club)
- All right.
- We won thanks to you.
Since all three teams have
1 win and 1 loss,
we got the rankings by the points.
By earning 1 more point,
the 1st place winner became...
the student guidance club.
- Okay!
- Really?
Why? Did they place first?
- Student guidance club?
- Didn't we place first?
The band club placed second.
Is it us?
The dance club placed 3rd
with 25 points.
- Did they place last?
- Did we place last?
- This is great.
- The 1st place gets 2 dollars.
- 2 dollars?
- Then 1.50 dollars and 1 dollar.
Two dollars?
(They need to protect this money
in order to win!)
You did well with PE.
During PE, I watched everyone...
- and assigned penalty points.
- Really?
- Suk Jin, three points.
- Why?
Despite being the oldest member,
you neglected the guests.
- It's true.
It's the oldest member's fault.
He told me to show reactions
and go home.
- It's the oldest member's fault.
- I heard it.
- Three points.
- It's the oldest member's fault.
Jong Kook, seven points.
What?
Seven points.
You used your strength to push
your fellow club member.
He pushed me.
I saw you do that twice,
so I gave you seven points.
Se Chan, where does he live?
- Him? He lives in Yeonhui-dong.
- Yeonhui-dong?
He lives close.
Jae Suk, 3 points. Haha, 3 points.
They tried to make
the club members lose points.
- Bo Sung.
- Yes?
Kwang Soo is the most dangerous one.
I think he came in earlier
and stole club funds.
- Our club funds?
- That's right.
This time, we should have
Kwang Soo stay here...
in a blindfolded state.
Okay.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
You will be blindfolded this time.
You should do it this time.
(Freezing)
- I can do it, but...
- You should do it.
Isn't Bo Sung the best at this role?
No, no. I tried it earlier.
It was so suffocating.
You got caught too early on
the last time.
- It was so suffocating.
- But...
I think you got caught on purpose
the last time.
Isn't that right?
Be honest.
Jae Suk.
Let's forget about the past
and start over...
- Forget about the past?
- You took all the money, right?
Kwang Soo, you are exactly
how you seem on TV.
(Bo Sung won't be fooled this time.)
I am very disappointed in you.
- Give us one each.
- I expected more from you.
(He pays up 20 cents.)
I will give you one each,
but the hammer...
You need to hold the hammer.
(Either way, Kwang Soo is it.)
If you don't hold the hammer,
you will steal the money again.
- Rock-paper-scissors...
- No, no.
Kwang Soo will be it.
Please hide the club funds.
Kwang Soo, wait outside.
- What?
- Come on.
How will I find it
with my eyes covered?
- Wait outside.
- I am a club member too.
- Wait outside?
- Wait outside.
- We should hide the funds together.
Wait outside. Wait outside.
I mean... This is driving me crazy.
13. 15.
- How many do you have?
- I have six.
We have 21.
We are in first place.
We shouldn't turn in money.
- We shouldn't turn in money.
- No.
- You should be it.
- I will be it.
- Again?
- I have done it before.
- Let's go! Good luck!
- Let's go!
(They try to turn the tables
with Operation: Kim Jong Kook.)
Put it in the same spot.
1, 2, 3, 4.
(The band club
finished hiding the money early on.)
("Hot Issue" by 4MINUTE)
(It's a total cacophony
that hurts the listener's ears.)
(The band club gives a ceremony
to celebrate their victory.)
Let's begin. Let's go.
(After the performance, it's time
to search the other rooms.)
The last club activity will begin.
(The last search starts.)
(So Min searches
the student guidance club's room!)
(The student guidance club
took 2 dollars,)
(but the money is
nowhere to be seen.)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo is protecting
the band club's room.)
(Se Chan enters.)
(Se Chan said they should save up
and win.)
(He is stealing from his own club.)
What?
(He goes to all the hiding spots
he remembers.)
(Haha enters as well.)
(Haha approaches
with a thief's facial expression.)
(He steals a small amount of money
and runs away.)
(Dazed)
(Thus, the band club faces
a crisis.)
(But Se Chan and Haha aren't
the only ones.)
(The students grow bold.)
We are getting
a lot of school support donations.
(Which club will save the club funds
and emerge as the winner?)
I will announce the result.
Show us the remaining club funds.
We have a thief...
within the club.
- They are unbelievable.
- I saw it with my own eyes.
Se Chan stole from his own team.
- Good job.
- Hey.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- That's the band club.
- The band club.
- You are unbelievable.
Haha is the worst.
- Haha is the worst.
- No, Se Chan is.
Do you know what Se Chan is like?
- He steals from the staff members.
- Ji Hyo is annoyed.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- If a cell phone goes missing,
it's his fault.
- All right.
- We left a lot of money.
Earlier...
(The dance club's
final amount is...)
- 15.
- 9 and 6, right?
15.
- 15.
- 15?
Kwang Soo. Where is one?
(It's the student guidance
club's turn.)
One.
- I didn't donate it.
- You didn't donate it?
(Kwang Soo was it
for the 2nd round.)
(If they have less
than 1.50 dollars,)
(the dance club will win.)
We have two.
- 2?
- That's 20 cents.
- Didn't you hide the funds?
(What happened?)
We have the result
of the club activity.
With 1.50 dollars,
the dance club won...
and acquired the scholarship.
(The dance club wins
with 1.50 dollars!)
- We won.
- Look at this, Defconn.
We won in the end.
- That's right.
- We won.
- I did my best.
- These are gift certificates.
Are those actual gift certificates?
Who gets the penalty
is unrelated, right?
Okay. It's my goal to avoid
the penalty.
Kwang Soo might avoid the penalty.
- The penalty...
- That's right. You never know.
This team submitted 15
for the school support donation.
- 10 should have been enough.
- Seriously.
You never know.
(Which 3 members will get chosen
for an annoying penalty?)
Did you enjoy the classes?
Yes, we did.
I will reveal...
how many penalty points
each student received...
during the classes.
Check your points.
- 22 points?
- 13 points?
I didn't do that badly.
(These three members are likely
to get the penalty.)
- But this isn't important.
- Why not?
- The rankings changed.
- Of course.
There are students who submitted
lots of school support donations.
Because of those students,
the rankings changed a lot.
You know
that the bottom three students...
have to stay behind
and carry out a penalty, right?
- Yes.
- We know.
The penalty...
involves composing
a written apology...
- on a sheet of 400-letter paper.
- I hate that.
- Really?
- That's insane.
- I hate that.
- You have to write it.
The written apology...
will go up on
Running Man's social media account.
- What?
- You have to fill up the paper.
- I hate it.
- But it's my first time here.
This student received
the least amount of penalty points.
To be honest,
we didn't do anything wrong.
The first place.
I will announce
the changed rankings.
The 1st place has 2 penalty points.
Two points?
Jae Suk.
He stole 20.
(During the 2nd club activity)
(The duo got to work as soon as
Kwang soo put on a blindfold.)
(They stole their own club money.)
Bo Sung, you are out.
(While Bo Sung showed his loyal side
and held Kwang Soo back,)
(Jae Suk stole 200 dollars.)
I will donate.
That's 10, right?
I will donate for Bo Sung.
(Half of it went to Bo Sung!)
(Both Jae Suk and Bo Sung lost
10 penalty points.)
I trust Jae Suk wholeheartedly.
It's loyalty.
- 10.
- 10?
(Jae Suk placed 1st
and became Bo Sung's savior.)
The second place is...
Ji Hyo. Then come Haha, Se Chan,
Bo Sung, and Defconn.
(Ji Hyo, Haha, Se Chan,
Bo Sung, and Defconn are exempt.)
Now comes seventh place.
This person is the last one
to be exempt, right?
That's right.
The last one to be exempt is...
I bet it's Suk Jin.
I didn't have
that many penalty points.
Please. I am sorry. Please.
(One member survived at 7th place.)
So Min!
(So Min is exempt at 7th place.)
I was a good student!
- I was a good student!
- That means you didn't donate.
I didn't donate.
- Seriously.
- You are a good person.
Of course I am. Trust me.
- That means you didn't donate.
- I didn't donate. Seriously.
The 8th place is Jong Kook
with 16 points.
You did it.
No, I got the penalty.
The 9th place is Suk Jin
with 17 points.
The last place is Kwang Soo
with 18 points.
Do I still have 18 points?
(He still has 18 points.)
In any case,
you did well with the classes.
Everyone can go home...
- except for the bottom three.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- Running Man, let's go!
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Loyalty!
You really need to compose
a written apology.
I will do it with seriousness.
How could you steal
during the first club activity?
(He regrets the day.)
This is insane.
Sometimes, I cheated.
I should have attacked
my own team...
- to collect money.
- I should have survived...
- by betraying the others.
- Jong Kook kept me from doing it.
If I ever have a child...
- A child... Gosh.
- A child... Hey!
I will teach him or her
at a young age...
to survive...
You are confusing me.
Jong Kook, be quiet.
I messed up because of you.
You are confusing me.
"At a young age..."
- And...
- My dad said, "Be honest."
"Be honest." Hey.
Hey.
For goodness' sake.
Come on!
- I only wrote five lines.
- I am sorry. I am sorry.
(You can check them out
on Running Man's SNS account.)
You should walk in the snow.
(Deep in the snowy mountain,)
(the members seem to be isolated.)
I really don't have it. I don't.
(They seem to be
looking for something.)
(Big sister, help me!)
(Do I have a big sister?)
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin lost.
(The strong sister, Kim Jae Hwa)
(The cheerful sister, Cha Chung Hwa)
(The ambitious sister, Shin Dong Mi)
(How dare you challenge
the Shin family?)
(Will there be a fight
between the Shin and Cha families?)
(The love between
the siblings shine.)
(They get the right
to distribute the allowance.)
(The siblings' love
is put to test.)
(The younger siblings
become obsessed with the allowance.)
- It's a war.
(What will become
of the three families?)
(The Charismatic Sisters,
The Ugly Siblings)