(It is snowing in large snowflakes
to turn the whole world white.)
- Old Fossil?
- I'm okay with anything else.
- What's wrong with Old Fossil?
- I really hate it.
That's my least favorite nickname.
You're old enough to be called
an Old Fossil.
If you were born in the Joseon era,
you would've been dead already.
- Suk Jin.
- The average life expectancy was...
You would've been reborn already.
(They are sharing snow-white
feelings in the morning as always.)
You're probably right.
(They are sharing snow-white
feelings in the morning as always.)
Gosh, it's chilly. Hello.
- Hello.
- This is amazing.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Gosh, it's cold.
- We got this again.
- I feel all warm inside.
Hello.
- It's from the fans.
- The fans sent us coffee again.
It's really warm. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- We keep getting stuff...
- from the fans. I'm so grateful.
- They don't have to do this though.
But we feel really sorry
to keep taking stuff like this.
Anyway, we should enjoy it
with due gratitude.
- That's true.
- We are very thankful.
- But if we take this,
- It's really warm.
other fans might feel like...
- they have to send something.
- They'd want to send something too.
- They might feel burdened.
- So,
- it's really okay.
- Sure.
It's us who should be
treating the fans.
You were the first one in line
to get coffee though.
What? A zebra is talking.
What? My gosh.
- Zebra.
He's just a filthy horse.
No, it's a zebra.
Isn't this a military drill uniform?
- No.
- It's yellowish.
I thought he was wearing a military
drill uniform from a distance.
- A military drill uniform?
- Gosh.
Did you guys check
the updated website?
I did. I didn't like it though.
Why did you do that?
Your profile picture is ridiculous.
The number of visitors to
our website has increased sharply.
- Really?
- It's the talk of the town.
- They want to check the updates.
- The server went down.
- Really? The server went down?
- Seriously?
- It went down?
- Thank you so much.
What is this? It's a cartoon.
It's time to change this.
Your photo is the worst.
- What's with the photo?
- What about it?
Mine is a picture of me
with a runny nose.
Then you should've won the race.
His picture is like an idol star
cartoon character.
Yes, he's the only one
with an animated character.
Actually, Writer Yaongyi
drew that for me.
Why didn't the writer
draw something for the rest of us?
Hey.
- Why would the writer...
- Writer Yaongyi, how could you?
Why would Writer Yaongyi
draw your character?
Sister Ongyi,
draw something for us too!
She's much younger than you.
Younger sister.
- She's not older than me?
- No way.
I'm so sorry.
Jae Suk, why did you use
that picture of Jong Kook?
Why is his nickname "Kim Nipple"
when we can't see his nipples?
When he wears sleeveless
shirts in summer...
Right. You can see them
from the side.
Yes, you can see them from the side,
so he's "Kim Nipple".
- I didn't know they showed.
- Of course they do.
I didn't know that.
When you're talking with us,
your nipples are peeking out
like this.
- Like they're shy or something.
- I see.
I've seen a picture of myself
that was taken at the airport.
- And I saw them.
- Really?
So I thought,
"My gosh, I should be more careful."
- I've seen them a lot.
- Gosh, that's not right.
You're called
"Kim Nipple" domestically.
But you are
"Nipple Kim" internationally.
("Kim Nipple" for domestic market,
"Nipple Kim" for export market)
- "Nipple Kim".
- It's cute.
- It's the other way around.
- Yes, the other way around.
Nipple Kim.
So today,
you will have
the Sister's Diary Race.
Guests who will play the role of
your older sisters are here.
- Really?
- Older sisters?
Someone old enough
to be my older sisters?
Is Sa Yeon here again?
- Maybe Park Mi Sun is here.
- Please come in.
Older than me?
(The sisters who have
such old younger siblings?)
- Hello.
- Gosh, hello.
- My goodness. Hello.
- They really are older sisters.
We enjoy their dramas so much.
Gosh, thank you for coming.
Hello.
(She's Park Bo Gum's loyal manager
in "Record of Youth".)
(She is amazing in all genres.)
(Shin Dong Mi, the actress
with 24 years of experience)
Hello.,
This is unbelievable.
(She changes herself for each
character like a chameleon.)
(She's charismatic
in "Good Manager" too.)
(The irreplaceable and indispensable
actress, Kim Jae Hwa)
Hello.
Oh, hello.
(She's in every hot drama
these days!)
(She plays Court Lady Choi
in "Mr. Queen".)
(The scene-stealer
in "Crash Landing on You")
(Actress Cha Chung Hwa
guarantees a drama's success.)
Oh, hello.
- Hey, Chung Hwa.
- Hello.
This is unbelievable.
- I loved "Crash Landing on You."
- Thank you.
Let me introduce them to you.
- Amazing.
- Kim Jae Hwa, Shin Dong Mi,
and Cha Chung Hwa.
(Kim Jae Hwa,
Shin Dong Mi, Cha Chung Hwa)
Big sister!
Let's talk to Jae Hwa first.
It's so nice to have you here.
- I'm glad to be here. Hello.
- It's amazing.
It's the first time I've seen her.
Yes, this is the first time
we're meeting in person, right?
Yes, it is the first time.
How did you feel
to be invited to Running Man?
- To be honest, I was surprised.
- All right.
I thought, "Why would they
want me on their show?"
You're too modest.
(Her shy but genuine laughter)
Because I'm not that popular.
- You think you're not?
- No.
Being here means you are popular.
(You're right!)
Thank you.
That's nice.
I like their reactions.
They have great reactions.
- You're right.
- Such strong reactions.
Yes, she keeps clapping.
Very strong.
I think Chung Hwa and Jae Hwa
are similar characters.
But Dong Mi is...
- She's just nervous.
- She doesn't know where she is.
She doesn't know
what she's doing here.
(Big sister Dong Mi
looked nervous from the start.)
(Strong reaction 1)
(Strong reaction 2)
(Walking on eggshells)
(She's even conscious of Suk Jin,
which has never happened before.)
Yes, you're right.
Let's talk about Jae Hwa.
I've seen her on "Radio Star".
She imitated animal sounds
on the show.
- It was quite popular for a while.
- Right.
- I've seen it too.
- Which animals?
Just show us then.
Well, it's really nothing.
It's nothing. Chicken.
Chicken sounds.
- Chicken sounds?
- Okay, chicken sounds.
Gosh, wait a minute.
(My goodness.)
- My goodness, guys.
- She's really good.
She's amazing.
- So good.
- But why the arm?
What's with the arm?
Because it's weird to do it
while standing still.
(She can't belt it out
with tension in her body.)
- I can't do it right.
- I understand.
- But when you move your arm?
- Yes.
- To control the volume.
- Right.
(Cock-a-doodle-doo!)
Yes, it sounds different.
(It feels fresh
as if it's the crack of dawn.)
(A new kind of personal talent)
- It's so funny.
- Is there anything else?
- I did elephant sounds too.
- Elephant? Okay.
Kwang Soo can imitate
elephant sounds too.
Why don't you show us?
I have never imitated
elephant sounds in my entire life.
Suk Jin, were you
confused with someone else?
Haven't you imitated
elephant sounds before?
Actually, Sae Ho did that...
- when he was on our show.
- I see.
Oh, it was Sae Ho.
So why haven't you tried it?
Then you should start today.
Why haven't you tried it?
- Why haven't you?
- Me?
Try it.
You're good.
- He's good.
- Yes, you're good.
Jae Hwa, why don't you show us?
My goodness.
(Howling)
- My goodness.
- Isn't it a wildcat?
It's too much.
It sounds like an elk.
Didn't it sound like
she was blowing her nose?
- I'm sorry.
- Try chicken again.
Chicken.
(Regaining her reputation
with the chicken sound)
(It becomes an all-round cheat key.)
I love how she moves her arm.
Yes, her arm.
- It's so funny.
- Yes.
I love how you move it.
- They're good.
- It's funny.
It seems like you're about
to transform into something.
- Yes, you're right.
- Here we go!
(A perfect harmony of voice,
facial expression, and movement)
Gosh, I'm going to laugh
every time I think about this.
- Yes, she's the best.
- Every time it pops into my head.
Next is Cha Chung Hwa.
- Hello.
- It's good to be here.
(So lively)
Actually,
Cha Chung Hwa is currently...
starring in "Mr. Queen",
and she did...
- "Crash Landing on You".
- Yes, I know.
I loved the show.
So Chung Hwa...
- you were on tvN dramas too.
- Yes, tvN.
And you were so amazing
in all of them.
I guess you get along well
with tvN dramas, right?
(Flustered)
You get along well with them too.
- You're on many shows there too.
- What are you doing?
Isn't this an SBS show?
It's okay to talk about
other broadcasting stations.
- Really?
- Yes, of course.
You're on two tvN shows.
- Two shows?
- Maybe you get along well.
Stop talking.
Maybe you don't get along well.
And Chung Hwa...
has great facial expressions.
- She has great expressions.
- I can see that.
A happy face or a sad face.
- Well...
- Kwang Soo's good at that.
Yes, of course.
- I can do it.
- Happy and sad at the same time.
- He's good.
- Yes, he can do it.
He can express happiness
and sadness at the same time.
- Sure.
- He can do it.
Yes, Kwang Soo can do it.
The picture of him on the website
is exactly that.
- Yes, you're right.
- His expression is so funny.
He looks happy and sad
at the same time.
So show us the expression
of happiness and sadness.
- I don't know if I can do this.
- One...
- 2, 3. Cue.
- Can he do it?
(He's happy and sad
at the same time.)
He's sad. Sad.
Now he's happy.
Now be happy and sad
at the same time.
(Happy and sad at the same time)
That's it.
That's it!
Right there!
Is this it?
- I should remember the feeling.
- This is it!
- That's it!
- Hold it.
- Take a picture.
- Wait.
- Hold it!
- Wait!
Okay, take it.
That's good.
This is it.
This is great.
I really hate the expression though.
- I really hate it.
- You can't see it anywhere else.
- So Chung Hwa.
- Yes.
- Can I ask you to show us?
- Show you what?
Why don't you start with happiness?
(Starting with happiness)
I'm happy but sad.
(Begins a one-woman play,
happy but sad to win an award)
Gosh, she's good.
- That's it.
- Yes.
- So good.
It's when you win an award.
Thank you so much.
Happy but sad.
- Show us happiness.
- She's amazing.
- Happiness?
- Gosh.
(Suddenly flips the mood completely)
It's happiness.
- Now sadness.
- Yes, sadness.
Now happy and sad.
Stop it.
(Stop it!)
(Punching)
She tried to punch him.
- My goodness.
- She tried to punch him.
Good reaction.
Actually, Chung Hwa is showing us
one of Rain's dances.
Seriously?
- Amazing.
- We should see it.
(She's giving
a dance performance too?)
- Show us.
- Chung Hwa.
- Actually, I didn't prepare it.
- Go ahead.
Chung Hwa is...
- good at dancing.
- She is?
- She is.
- Really?
Gosh, my socks.
- Okay.
- Wait.
- Calm down.
- All right.
- Excuse me.
- Let me...
- Dong Mi, you look uncomfortable.
- No.
Because you have to do something
after she gives her performance.
Just wait for a while.
Everyone is showing their talents.
- So you're...
- You don't have to.
- I don't have any talent.
- That's all right.
- Because of my legs. Just in case.
- All right.
(Talented Chung Hwa
is ready to give a performance.)
I'm not really good at dancing
so I'll do facial expressions.
So she's dancing with her face?
(Facial expressions
followed by a facial dance?)
Music. Cue.
("Switch to Me" by Rain,
duet with JYP)
(The facial expression is now on.)
She's lip-syncing.
(Drawing the audience in
as soon as she starts)
It's totally my style.
(Exactly to their tastes)
This is amazing.
She's good.
So cool.
Let's dance!
(Bounce, bounce)
(Powerful dance)
Gosh, she's good.
She's so good.
(She's a great dancer.)
(No one expected her
to be this good.)
She's good.
- Cha Chung Hwa!
- You're amazing!
So good.
(These guys have
nasty dance DNA in them.)
(The scene of discovering a guest
with super high spirits)
Gosh, she's really good.
(Introducing herself with
a performance like in the old days)
(A perfect ending shot)
(Can't help but give her a big hand)
She's so good!
(A shameless fan service)
I'm a big fan!
(She shamelessly
stole So Min's heart!)
- Amazing.
- She's like a comedienne.
Chung Hwa, you did it.
- Switch to me
(Chung Hwa knows exactly
what these comedians want.)
- She's an amazing dancer.
- Isn't she?
Thank you.
But this is what Se Chan said.
He said, "She's like a comedienne."
Yes, if you didn't
become an actress,
I'm sure you'd be a senior comedian.
I'm sure of it.
My heart is still pounding.
She was so cool.
- That was amazing.
- Right.
(While everyone is impressed
by her boldness and dance skills...)
(Restless)
- It was unbelievable.
- If we knew...
she'd be that good,
we would've let Dong Mi go first.
Good luck!
- You can do this!
(In the middle
of the crazy dance party,)
(there was one person
who couldn't enjoy the moment.)
(She looks depressed
as things are heating up.)
Dong Mi doesn't know what to do.
- She's under a lot of pressure.
- You can do this!
- It's not over yet!
I heard Dong Mi has a connection
with one of us.
- She did a drama with Ji Hyo.
- Right.
I saw you two hug each other.
- They seemed really excited.
- They seemed close.
I was surprised
to see Ji Hyo hug someone.
(Ji Hyo is known for her calmness,
but she hugged Dong Mi right away.)
That's surprising.
Dong Mi and I did
two dramas together.
- Right.
- Really?
(Ji Hyo and Dong Mi were sisters
in the drama, "Ex-Girlfriend Club".)
you should've paid my money back.
(They're close enough
to send a coffee truck.)
You two look like sisters.
- They look similar.
- Right.
Dong Mi, what was your first
impression of Ji Hyo?
- Ji Hyo?
- Yes.
She's really pretty.
And she's so nice.
(She's just a pretty
and nice friend.)
You don't sound very close.
She doesn't seem
to have much to say.
- Tell us more about her.
- It's like she's making things up.
What else is there
other than that she's pretty?
- Dong Mi, tell us.
- Say more.
I want to know more about Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo is pretty and...
You already said that.
I guess she's just pretty.
I was surprised
by how easy-going she was.
It's true that Ji Hyo is easy-going.
Can I ask you something? She doesn't
often answer your calls, right?
Actually, I rarely call her.
After we complained that
Ji Hyo rarely answers our calls,
her life has been a lot easier.
- That's true. It's a lot easier.
- Everyone knows that now.
- Right?
- No one blames me...
for not answering
their calls anymore.
- I know.
- They've accepted it.
She's always like that.
- Thank you.
- It's become her character.
- She even thanks us.
- I heard Dong Mi...
released a duet song with her
husband for remembrance's sake.
Really?
- That sounds interesting.
- No.
- Just a little.
- The sound echoes around in here,
- so it's good to sing.
- This is perfect.
- It's a good place to sing.
- It echoes.
What do I do?
I'll sing the duet song then.
- The duet song? Cool.
- Yes.
(She says yes feeling
she has to do something.)
She looks like a music professor.
What do I do?
It's okay. We have
the chicken sound.
- Don't worry.
- It was really cool.
We have Jae Hwa.
She will cut in right away.
They both did a really good job.
They are like Lee Kyung Sil
and Lee Sung Mi of the big screen.
They are a duet.
(Playing the part of Lee Kyung Sil
and Lee Sung Mi)
If they are Kyung Sil and Sung Mi,
Dong Mi is Park Mi Sun.
- That's perfect.
- It sounds about right.
It suits her, right?
- She's like Mi Sun.
- Good.
- Do you like it?
- I like it.
- I love it.
- I like the three comediennes,
but Mi Sun is my favorite.
And we have Yang Hee Eun here.
(I'm Ji Hee Eun.)
Can you sing a little for us?
(They are excited
to hear Dong Mi's song.)
(You're like a wildcat)
(Giggling)
(What?)
(You are so sharp)
(But I love you)
(They don't know how to react.)
What do I do?
Seriously, what should we do?
I'd like to ask our viewers.
(Viewer-participation event)
What would you do
if you were in our situation?
(Embarrassed)
- You did a good job.
- Make the chicken sound for me.
- The chicken sound.
- I'd like to ask our viewers.
Go dance for me.
Like Dong Mi said...
She told me to dance.
- Who?
- Dong Mi.
She told me
to make the chicken sound.
Oh, dear.
Dong Mi... Dong Mi was...
so embarrassed...
"I wish I could go back in time."
So we have Dong Mi here.
Please give them a big hand.
Thank you.
Good start!
(The three actresses' story
on Running Man begins now.)
Like I said earlier,
we are going to have
the Sister's Diary Race today.
Each family will get money
according to the results...
of each mission.
The three people with the most money
will win the prize at the end.
And the one with the least money
will get a penalty.
But the sisters will distribute
the money as they like.
If her siblings have
a problem with that,
they can use their chance
to redistribute the money.
But the chance might increase...
the number of people
to get a penalty,
so you should be careful.
(The chance might make
more people get a penalty.)
So you're saying
we're playing one-on-one.
This is an individual game.
The sisters have...
already picked
the siblings they want.
Really?
The sisters will call
the names of their siblings...
and hand out name tags
that show their order.
For your information, the sisters
decided the order too.
I see.
(Who are the siblings
that they picked?)
I envy you.
I'm sorry, but I don't
talk to the youngest member.
(They are done
deciding the order of siblings.)
I wish I had Haha
and Kwang Soo under me.
Why am I the youngest one here?
I should've tussled with them.
Gosh, those punks.
- What?
- Nothing.
(A tussle?)
(Nothing.)
Hello, Jae Suk.
(Polite)
(The 1st, 2nd, 3rd, and 4th
of the Cha Family)
You were talking to Suk Jin, right?
No, Suk Jin is also
my older brother.
I was just wondering
why I'm the youngest here.
So Min, it might be easier
to be the youngest.
(The 1st, 2nd, 3rd, and 4th
of the Shin Family)
The fourth? I don't think so.
Imagine that Jong Kook
is your younger brother.
- It would be horrible.
- I'd feel uncomfortable.
- It'd be suffocating.
- I'm so uncomfortable.
Suk Jin, hurry and come.
- Suk Jin.
- This is crazy.
Suk Jin, I'm the youngest one
in our family.
Suk Jin, you should hurry.
(He doesn't seem to like
the set-up for today.)
- I have to take care of my family.
- People would think...
you're the oldest one here.
I knew you'd get scolded.
Come here.
- What are you?
- Why do you ask?
- I'm the second.
- You're not my family.
- That's true.
- You...
He's one year younger than me.
Right. We're a year apart.
- What about me?
- You're three years younger.
So is he older than me?
(So is he older than me?)
Sure, Suk Jin.
- You should listen to your brother.
- Come here.
- This is old-fashioned.
- I've never seen you growing up.
- Did you visit my house?
- He lives next door.
I live next door. We're neighbors.
What's wrong with you?
Will you hurry?
(The 1st, 2nd, and 3rd
of the Kim family)
Hey, will you hurry?
(What?)
- Me?
- We both are the second.
- We're of the same age.
- Yes, we are.
We are both the second.
Are we the same age?
No, he says we're not the same age.
He says he's older than us.
You should get a haircut.
What's my age?
Am I younger than him?
- Sure.
- He's older than you.
- Let me take care of this.
- Is he older than me?
(Let me take care of this.)
- Let me take care of this.
- Is he older than me?
Who do you think you are, you punk?
(The third son, Suk Jin is
scolded by Kwang Soo.)
That's enough. Stop it.
- How dare you.
- You should teach him better.
He's six months older than you.
- Older than me?
- I'm older than you.
He's older than you.
This is really confusing.
Haha looks so cute.
You do look like
the youngest member.
You don't seem
like you were born in 1979.
- Me?
- Were you born in 1980?
- No.
- He was born in 1979.
Wasn't it 1980?
How old are you?
I was born in 1980.
Oh, you're not...
(Polite)
(You're not older than me.)
- Haha, you're so mean.
- She's younger than you.
You're unbelievable.
Haha, you were born in the 1970s,
but we were born in the 1980s.
- You too?
- Yes.
- Are you both younger than Haha?
- What?
It's not like that.
(The actresses are having fun
teasing Kwang Soo.)
It's not like that.
- She looks so serious.
- Hey.
She has various facial expressions.
Be nice to my big sister.
- What are you?
- Watch your mouth.
Why are you being like that
to my sister?
- Let me take care of this.
- Just have a seat.
- Sit down.
- What are you?
(What are you?)
(He wants to keep
pinching Suk Jin's cheek.)
- How dare you.
- How old are you?
Hey, what time do you think it is?
- No, I...
- At ease.
- My sister isn't here yet.
- Let me pinch your nipples.
(Pinching his nipples)
At ease.
Stand straight. What do you
think you are doing now?
Everyone's here already.
You're the youngest one here.
- You pinched my nipples.
- If you don't behave today,
- I'll tear them off.
- But you can't pinch my nipples.
Kim Nipple, just sit.
- But my nipples...
- Kim Nipple.
- Kim Nipple?
- That sounds cute.
- You should hurry.
- Jong Kook, you're younger than me.
- Really?
- Yes.
You're not my family anyway.
(He's not afraid of other families.)
- But I'm older than you.
- Teach her a lesson.
- Why would age matter?
- You should be polite to me.
You're older than me,
but you're not my family.
I don't care.
Do you want me
to pinch your nipples?
- Come here.
I can't believe this.
- Dong Mi.
- I'm older than you.
Will you hurry?
- Well, Dong Mi.
- Stay quiet.
Dong Mi. I'm sorry to say this,
but why are you so shy
around your family?
- They are your family.
- We're family.
My sister is shy around strangers.
- You should hurry.
- Okay.
You should give me a chair.
Won't you take care
of your younger brother?
You can't take all the chairs.
The guys next door...
keep yelling at me.
- Who?
- Hey, shut your mouth.
Hey, stop that.
Don't you dare yell at my brother.
(What did you say?)
Will you let her
talk to me like that?
- Things are overheating.
- Will you let it slide?
- It's getting overheated.
- I can't let it slide.
- I like your ad-lib these days.
- Well done.
- I like that.
- Hey.
I like her ad-lib. It's really good.
That's true though.
I mean, it just sounded right.
I think that was appropriate
for the situation.
- Well done.
- I'm serious.
This is what older sisters do.
Gosh, you little...
You're no match for me.
Don't mess with her.
I'm so ashamed of our third.
Let me tell you
about the first mission.
It's called Mouth Shape Acting...
which requires your sharp sight
and acting skills.
Mouth Shape Acting?
You have to guess a famous quote
from a movie or a drama...
only by looking at the shape
of the mouth to succeed.
("Is this the best you can do?
Are you sure?")
Is this the best you can do?
Are you sure?
- Those who watched many dramas...
- That's easy.
- would be at an advantage.
- We know a lot of movies.
- I'm not good at a game like this.
- I'm not confident.
I'm really bad at this.
I never watch any dramas.
I'm in trouble.
- You watched a lot, right?
- I only watch the ones I acted in.
Really?
One more thing.
When you say the answer,
if you act realistically as well,
you receive two points.
- If we act realistically?
- Yes.
We have many actresses
on our team, right?
Our team will do incredibly well.
Se Chan is good at acting
in comedy skits too.
We have 1 comedian
and 2 actresses on our team.
- We'll definitely win.
- I can act too.
- Jong Kook is good at acting too.
- Jae Suk and Suk Jin are...
(These 2 members make
their team members worry.)
really bad at acting.
The eldest sister of the team
that gets the right answer...
will choose one person on another
team and hit that person with this.
You can deduct one dollar
from the person's allowance.
(The eldest sister of the team
that gets the right answer...)
(can deduct 1 dollar
from 1 person's allowance.)
(1 dollar will be deducted.)
- Now...
- A legendary scene.
- Yes. Okay.
- The mouth shape.
- The question will be revealed.
- I'm good at this. Don't worry.
- We can do this.
- That's ridiculous.
- I specialize in this.
- That's not true.
(Jae Suk is all talk
as soon as the game begins.)
- That's ridiculous.
- I specialize in this.
- That's not true.
- What?
(Who is that?)
- That's Ha Jung Woo.
- Ha Jung Woo?
- No, that's not him.
- No. He has chubby cheeks.
- Should we guess a whole sentence?
- Could he be Im Won Hee?
- It's a famous line.
- No, I don't think so.
- The actor from the movie...
- Kim Yun Sik?
- You mean, Kim Yun Seok.
Is it a complete sentence?
- It's...
- It's a famous line.
This is a scene where the actor
is saying the line.
- Who is that?
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
- "Hey!"
("Hey!")
- No, there should be more.
- Let me answer.
Yes? That's not correct.
Let me answer. The answer is
"Why does it matter?"
("Why does it matter?")
Let me answer. "You live
in Namcheon-dong, don't you?"
- That's not the answer, you brat.
- Is it correct?
No, that line doesn't end like that.
Let me answer.
- Let me answer.
- Listen to me.
- He said...
- "Listen, you punk!"
- "I was..."
- Incorrect.
No, that's not it.
- It doesn't end with "don't you".
- Imitate the actor.
From the beginning.
- Go ahead.
- "Hey! You live..."
"in Namcheon-dong, right?"
(She seems sure.)
"You live in Namcheon-dong, right?"
- "Right?"
- Let me answer.
- Is it not the correct answer?
- Doesn't it end with "right"?
- It wasn't correct.
I'll start from the beginning.
"Let go of me, you punk!"
He doesn't say a swear word.
- But I wasn't finished.
- Hey!
- I mean, before he said it...
- Let me answer.
- Let her answer.
- Chung Hwa.
- "Hey!"
"Your uncle that jerk... He..."
Stop it.
- That was so funny.
- Let me answer.
- I remember now.
- Jong Kook, go ahead.
"Your captain lives
in Namcheon-dong, right?"
- Correct!
- All right!
- Chung Hwa, that was close.
- It was "captain", not "uncle".
- It was "captain".
- Okay!
- "Your captain..."
- "Your captain".
- That's right.
- Oh, right.
- Darn.
(The scene from "Nameless
Gangster: Rules of the Time")
Your captain lives
in Namcheon-dong, right?
- Yes, he does.
- Listen. Your captain and I...
I knew all the lines in that scene.
We'll give Jong Kook's team
two points.
- Okay!
- Oh, yes!
Dong Mi, choose one younger sibling
and hit the person in the head,
and one dollar will be deducted.
- We were so close to the answer.
- Dong Mi.
- You can choose anyone.
- He's been acting up too much.
- He keeps getting up like that.
- He's been acting up.
Oh, no. My little brother.
He's been acting up too much.
Good choice, Dong Mi.
Why him?
- What's wrong with her?
- Gosh, seriously.
- Don't act up.
- I don't like you.
My little brother who was born
in 1966.
The score is 2 to 0 to 0.
- She said "uncle".
- What a shame.
- We got two points.
- Right. It was "captain".
- I remember that now.
- Jong Kook acted well too.
- Here goes your second question.
- I'll get this one right.
- Great. Let's do this.
- Here goes the question.
- Hey! I mean, let me answer.
- Let me answer.
(Hey! I mean, let me answer.)
- Who could that be?
- Whose mouth is that?
- I think it's Kim Rae Won.
- Kim Rae Won. What movie was it?
- Rae Won?
- What scene is it?
- Who is that?
- Is it from a drama?
- Isn't that Park Shin Yang?
- Really?
- Or not.
- I think he's quite old.
- I have no idea.
If you don't know,
we'll show you the next level hint.
- We'll show you more of the photo.
- Please do that.
- Show us.
- Okay. The next level hint.
- Let me answer.
- He's Park Shin Yang, right?
"Baby, let's go. Baby, let's go!"
"Baby, let's go!"
- You're awesome.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
Baby, let's go.
(The scene from "Lovers in Paris")
What... Are you talking to me?
Baby, let's go.
(Baby, let's go.)
- You're awesome. Great job!
- It was Shin Yang as I thought.
It was Shin Yang as I thought.
- Suk Jin, what was that?
- What is wrong with us?
Why didn't you say the answer?
- I didn't watch many dramas.
- The Cha Family! The Cha Family!
- No, wait.
- Choose Suk Jin.
You should keep picking someone
on the same team.
- That's a good idea.
- We're competing with each other.
- Wait.
- Why do you hit only me?
- Dong Mi, come on.
- Dong Mi, this is unfair.
My gosh. Dong Mi.
- Dong Mi, come back now. Good job.
- Good choice.
- Why did you pick our team again?
- Good job.
Why would you keep picking
our team, Dong Mi?
I can choose anyone I want.
- This is war. Okay.
- This is war.
- This is war. Bring it on.
- Listen to me.
It's not about your family. We have
issues with that particular person.
- That's right. What?
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
(Hey! Hey! Hey!)
- Stop it. How dare you?
- How dare you?
- "How dare you?" My gosh.
- Be respectful to my family.
You want a fight between
your family and mine?
- Why not?
- Let's do that.
- You want a fight?
- Oh, goodness. Wait, Chung Hwa.
Why would you come only at me?
Oh, goodness. Wait, Chung Hwa.
(Oh, goodness. Wait.
Why would you come only at me?)
I must be the easiest target
for her.
- This is not necessary.
- He's the easiest target.
- Come on. Let's not do this.
- Calm down.
Jae Hwa, imitate a rooster again.
(Cock-a-doodle-doo!)
(The rooster declared peace.)
- That was good.
- Please sit down.
- Good job, Jae Hwa.
- I love it.
- That was great.
- I couldn't complain to Dong Mi.
It always makes me laugh.
It didn't make our hearts flutter,
so we'll give you only one point.
Why? I mean, why?
It made my heart flutter.
If we act well, will you give us
one point?
We'll give you one point
if your acting satisfies everyone.
- Make their hearts flutter.
- Really? Then we'll try it.
- Try what?
- Say, "Baby, let's go."
If you fail, you'll lose one point.
Suk Jin, give it a try.
(Suk Jin will try
because his eldest sister made him.)
(Ji Suk Jin as Park Shin Yang,
wearing glasses like Shin Yang)
(Jeon So Min as Kim Jung Eun,
99 percent similar to Jung Eun)
(How will he pull off
this romantic and chic line?)
- "Baby, let's go..."
- Never mind. It's okay.
- Why...
- It's okay.
(Never mind. It's okay!)
His team members gave up.
- That won't work.
- I tried to be gentle.
- Why did you...
- What was that?
- Why did you speak so quietly?
- That was...
- I mean...
- how we speak to an actual baby.
Like a grandfather talking
to his grandchild.
- "Baby, let's go. Oh, my baby."
- Hey.
Hey, he's my little brother.
- Don't say such a thing.
- Your little brother?
- He was born in the 1990s.
- Why should I even care?
- You little...
- What? Keep talking.
- Your eyebrows are too far apart.
- What?
My eyebrows...
I look just like my mom.
I take after her.
Hey, don't talk about
your real family.
(I look just like my mom!
I take after her!)
(He's explaining the laws of
genetics in an angry tone of voice.)
- You look just like your mom too.
- Come on. Stop it.
- Let's not mention our families.
- Calm down.
Don't talk about our real families.
- I look just like my mom.
- Let's not talk about our families.
- Hey.
- We shouldn't...
My gosh. His eyebrows really are
so far apart.
Dong Mi just said his eyebrows
really are far apart.
- Haha.
- His eyebrows really are far apart.
I must say, his eyebrows
really are far apart.
You look just like your mom too.
Gosh, Haha. Don't talk about
our real families.
- Do not mention our families.
- That was unexpected.
Will there be any actresses?
- Any questions of an actress?
- There will be.
- Yes, there will be.
- Are you confident with actresses?
- Just in case.
- But you didn't say...
You didn't say anything until now.
She doesn't know anything.
All she did was imitate a rooster.
Am I right?
(All she did was imitate a rooster.
Am I right?)
(The rooster sound resonated
in the studio so many times.)
Ms. Rooster.
- By the way, Jae Hwa...
- Did we receive money?
I don't know why,
but Jae Hwa seems like...
someone I've seen
in my neighborhood.
- I feel the same way.
- I feel familiar with her too.
- Actually, many people say...
- You feel familiar with her, right?
- that I look like their aunts.
- Exactly.
I feel so familiar with her.
You look like my aunt
on my mother's side.
- She looks like my aunt.
- Really?
- I feel so familiar with her.
- Thank you.
Here goes the next question.
(It's time for the next question!)
- Let me answer.
- Me! Me!
- Jae Hwa was faster.
- That's Na Moon Hee's scene.
"Pumpkin sweet potato!"
(Na Moon Hee's
"Pumpkin sweet potato!)
Why?
We knew the answer too. Darn it.
- We got one question right.
- I did it!
(They're celebrating
by imitating a rooster!)
Pumpkin sweet potato.
Pumpkin sweet potato!
(The scene from "High Kick!")
Are you happy now?
- Nice!
- That was good.
She's so cheerful and energetic.
- We should get some points.
- I want to get a question right.
- We really should.
- I bet we'll get two points.
- I did it.
- You get two points. It was great.
- Okay!
- Thank you.
Here you go.
How could you give them an extra
point because she has a loud voice?
How well she imitated the actress
is important.
- Take this!
- It's important.
(He dodged it successfully.)
- Hey, you can't dodge it.
- I didn't get hit.
- Why would you dodge it?
(The crazy combination
of dodging and being cheeky)
Gosh, he dodged again.
(The crazy combination
of dodging and being cheeky)
He dodged all her attacks.
(Hitting)
- Oh, gosh.
- I'm sorry.
She hit me with her fist.
With her fist.
You made her upset.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Jae Hwa did a great job.
- Are you giving this to us?
- What a shame.
We can't seem to get questions right
even when we know the answer.
- Are you all right?
- I'm okay.
- Don't worry.
- I knew all the answers.
Show them the photo.
- Who could that be?
- What's that?
- Isn't that Haha's mouth?
- Ants...
Isn't that Haha's mouth?
- Let me answer. It's you.
- Let me answer.
- Haha, go ahead.
- 3, 2, 1.
- Ants...
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
- Oh, right.
- What's that?
I got a mosquito bite on my foot
(The scene from
"High Kick Through the Roof")
(The eldest sisters don't seem
to have figured out.)
- 3, 2, 1.
- It's Kwang Soo.
The mosquito song. Let me know.
(They know the answer, but...)
- Mosquito... What was it?
- Three.
- Because it was itching
- I got a mosquito bite
A mosquito bite, it was itching
(Big Nose Mosquito can't control
his arms and legs.)
Oh, no. Why...
- Let me answer.
I got a mosquito bite last night
It itched
- Okay!
- Good job.
- Why didn't you recognize yourself?
- I didn't know.
- It was you!
- Oh, yes!
- I said the same thing.
- 1, 2...
- 1, 2, 3.
(The 3 siblings of the Kim Family
are roaring.)
- My gosh.
- That was...
Oh, my. I didn't know.
Why didn't you recognize yourself?
Does my mouth look like that?
- Yes. It looks ugly.
- I thought it was chicken gizzard.
He's the one who should be called
Mr. Dirty Mustache.
- Don't call me that.
- You called me Mr. Dirty Mustache.
- No.
- Kwang Soo should be called that.
- Gosh. I didn't know.
- We knew the answer.
- He and Suk Jin... I mean,
- But I didn't know the lyrics.
Jae Suk and Suk Jin knew
all the answers,
but they couldn't say
the exact lines.
- I got a mosquito bite
- That's because...
- we're too nervous, So Min.
- Wasn't that the answer?
- Don't be nervous.
- But they knew the answers.
- It's because we're too nervous.
We're always one second behind.
- Okay, we'll move on.
- Here's the next one.
- Let me answer.
- Answer it.
- Let me answer!
- Let me answer.
- Answer it!
- Hold on.
- Let me answer.
- Let me answer. Jang Hyuk!
Jang Hyuk.
3, 2, 1.
- Let me answer.
"As if. I'll buy you instead."
What?
Just stay still, will you?
- "How much..."
- Just stay put.
- You're embarrassing me.
- But I'm right.
"As if."
His teeth aren't straight.
It has to be Jae Suk's.
- Yes, Jae Suk's.
- No, it's not me.
- Yours...
- I think he's right.
- Mine is worse.
- I think you're right.
- Can't you tell?
- No.
Here's the next clue.
(The 2nd clue)
- Wait, it's Choi Min Su.
- Let me answer!
"Am I trembling?"
- That's not it.
- Let me answer!
- Is that not it?
"I thought I'd be able
to have you."
- That's the one.
- "I thought..."
- Okay!
- Are you kidding me?
Nicely done.
- I should've answered instead.
- It was Choi Min Su.
(Suk Jin keeps throwing away
his team's chances.)
- I...
- Nicely done.
I made it sound like the original.
"I thought I'd be able..."
- "to have you."
- You're so good.
"Because you're mine!"
- "Because you're mine!"
- My gosh.
- I thought I'd be able to have you.
- So that was the one.
- He's so good.
- Can you believe it?
- He's really good.
- I know.
I can't believe it.
- He's so good.
- That's my brother for you.
- How did you know?
- He's good, isn't he?
"I thought I'd be able to have you."
I have the worst brothers!
That team's on a roll.
She needs to hit someone.
Don't you dare hit me.
(She chooses him to hit.)
Nice one.
You're going to pay for that.
Just wait and see
how I get my revenge.
He never manages to though.
He's too weak.
- That's how he always is.
- He's all words.
- An opportunity never comes.
- There's nothing he can do.
(Suk Jin's threats can be ignored.)
We'll get it right this time.
Let's get it right this time.
Let's focus, okay?
- Say that we'll answer first.
- I was the fastest earlier.
Here we go.
Here's the next question.
Let me answer!
(So Min quickly announces
that her team will answer.)
(The Cha Family
gets the chance to answer first.)
- "Hey, it's a goal."
- No.
That's not it.
(Why would it be
a soccer commentator?)
"Hey, it's a goal."
- Is that not it?
- Me!
(Of course, it's wrong.)
I know what it is.
- Hurry.
- How can one know what this is?
- "Double or nothing."
- Se Chan!
- I think you're right.
- Okay, go for it.
"Double or nothing."
Nice!
("Double or nothing"
is the correct answer.)
- Really?
- I can't believe it!
"Double or nothing."
(The Shin Family wins two points!)
How can one know that?
- No way.
- How did you know?
(Se Chan, the teeth whisperer)
You're amazing.
I just got that feeling.
I'm just perceptive, that's all.
Double or nothing.
(From the movie "Tazza")
How can one know?
You're killing me.
- Shouldn't we at least get one?
- What do we do?
- Let's at least get one right.
- We're still at zero points.
- You've got to be killing me.
- We're at zero points.
This isn't the quiz for us.
- This...
- This isn't the quiz for us.
So Min, I bet it's uncomfortable
on that team.
- I don't know other people's lines.
- We're still at zero points.
- Don't you worry.
- My team...
Our family's a mess.
- Our family...
- We're still at zero points.
Not yet.
- We're still in this game.
- Not yet.
Our big sister
isn't doing much though.
- All she does is hit people.
- Just look at her.
She's like the family's cheerleader.
This next round will be...
just for the big sisters.
- Okay.
- Just the big sisters.
- We'll help.
- But I'm terrible at this.
(Their pride is on the line.)
- Here we go.
- But...
We won't give you any hints.
- I have face blindness.
- All right.
How can one guess
by just looking at the mouth?
- She says she has face blindness.
- Face blindness?
She's ill, you know.
Who has face blindness?
Don't you lie.
- I'm not kidding.
- Seriously?
I truly have face blindness.
I mean it.
Well, our sister has
anger management issues.
Dong Mi's the type to quietly lie.
I mean it. I'm not kidding.
Are you sure you're not
just out of it?
Seriously?
(Seriously?)
(She elegantly threatens him.)
- What...
- She says it elegantly though.
This is only for the big sisters.
- Right, go for it.
- Give us the question.
Let's do this.
Go, Jae Hwa!
(The pride of their families
is on the line.)
- What...
- Isn't that me?
- Who's that?
- Who's this?
- Maybe...
- Please keep your voices down.
(Everyone seems to be clueless.)
It's a woman.
Yes, you're right.
You can't tell her.
We can't?
- Those are the rules.
- Got it.
- I...
- If no one knows,
- I'll give you the next clue.
- Sure.
- Here it is.
- I don't think that's it.
- What...
- You know what it is!
Yes, it's you.
You know what it is!
Please keep your voices down.
Let me answer!
"I can shoot!"
(I can shoot!)
(From the movie "Tazza")
You're not wrong but...
- She got it right.
- Can you say it again?
- I never saw the movie.
- This...
"I can shoot!"
(It's not similar at all.)
- Have you not seen the movie?
- No.
- Let me answer.
- I never saw the movie.
That should count
as a correct answer.
- Let me answer.
- Unbelievable.
- Which movie is it from?
- Dong Mi?
- That's the one.
- Go ahead.
- "I can shoot!"
- Are you kidding me?
Are you serious?
- Seriously?
- Let me answer!
- Jae Hwa, you're up.
- Seriously?
"I can shoot!"
- Let me answer.
- Jae Hwa, go ahead.
"I can shoot!"
Nicely done.
That wasn't it.
"I can shoot!"
- It's not right.
- Let me answer.
Chung Hwa, go ahead.
(The Cha Family
gets another chance.)
(Eyes are wide.)
She's just putting on an act.
"I..."
"I can shoot."
- Seriously?
- That's not it!
- No way.
- You haven't seen the movie.
- Jae Hwa.
- No one saw the movie.
"I can shoot."
- No, that's not the right tone.
- It's not.
- "I can shoot."
- No way.
- That's not right.
- "I can shoot."
It was similar this time.
That wasn't right.
- There.
- It wasn't bad.
- It's from "Tazza".
- Right.
"I can shoot."
So Min's good at this. Show them.
- Show them.
- "I can shoot."
That's the correct tone?
(It's supposed to be
in a melancholy tone.)
We almost had it this time.
This is how it's done.
"I can shoot."
"Lower that gun."
"I can shoot, you know.
I can shoot."
I can shoot as well.
- That's how it's done.
- Of course.
(That's how it's done.)
"I can shoot."
Your tone was all wrong.
"I can shoot." That was just wrong.
- "I can shoot."
It was adorable though.
Is it okay for us
to take all the points though?
I'm sorry,
but can I have my seat back?
(I'm sorry,
but can I have my seat back?)
- Seriously?
- Oh, sorry.
- Don't forget our youngest.
- Where did my seat go?
- Sorry about that.
- You were hoarding the chairs.
- Get ready.
- Here's the last question.
- Let's get it right this time.
- It's the last question.
- Let's get it right.
- Let's at least get one.
We're still at zero points.
Wait, who's this?
- Let me answer.
Three...
"Do I have the face of a king?"
That's what I thought too.
I knew it as well.
I knew it too.
Okay!
(We did it.)
(The Kim Family scores 2 points.)
- In 2, 3, 4.
- 2, 3, 4.
(They can't leave out
the rooster sound.)
(From the movie "The Face Reader")
- The tone wasn't right though.
- Right.
- "Do I have the face of a king?"
- Exactly.
- That's how it should be.
- The acting was off.
Anyone who says it better
will receive a point.
- Chung Hwa, you're up.
- Go for it.
"Do I have the face of..."
Will you please watch some movies?
- She must not watch movies.
- Try watching some movies.
(All she does is give wrong answers
with over-the-top acting.)
- Jae Hwa, go ahead.
- I'll give it a go.
"Do I..."
- Are you sure about this?
- "have the face of a king?"
- You haven't seen it, have you?
- Go ahead.
Of course, I've seen it.
Why haven't you watched any movies?
- I have.
- I have too,
- but my voice...
- Go ahead.
(Suk Jin's getting into character.)
- Suk Jin's going to try it.
- Let's hear from Suk Jin.
- Let's see.
- I'm curious.
(Determined)
"Do I have the face of a king?"
(He's just doing a voice impression
of himself.)
You just said that
in your own voice.
That's just your own voice.
"Do I..."
"have the face of a king?"
That was perfect.
- Perfect.
- Nice!
- We're at zero points.
- It isn't over yet though.
- What do we do?
- We have more games to play.
- Is there more?
- Of course.
- There are more games.
- Let's do this.
There's only a one-point difference
between the winner and runner-up.
(The result of the game)
The winner is...
- It's definitely not us.
- It's already over for us.
- It's not us.
- It can't be us.
- The winner is...
- It's us.
Get ready to cry like a rooster.
- The Shin Family.
- Okay!
"I can shoot."
- "I can shoot."
- "Don't be ridiculous."
- The next game...
We'll just do well in the next game.
- Right.
- Okay.
- There are more games to play.
- It's all right.
Our family's in shambles.
- Nice.
- That was a tricky game.
We're off to a good start.
Now,
it's time for the first
allowance round.
My allowance.
The big sisters
will enter the room first...
and choose 1 out of
the 5 allowance pouches.
You'll split the money you find...
with your siblings.
I believe in our sister.
Since the Shin Family won,
the five pouches...
will have from 60 dollars
to 100 dollars respectively.
- That's not bad.
- From 60 to 100 dollars.
The team in second place...
will get to choose
from 40 dollars to 80 dollars.
Your team will get from
10 dollars to 50 dollars.
We're off to the worst start.
So the big sisters will enter
the room and pick one first.
You'll check the amount
that you chose.
Only I can know?
You're allowed to pocket...
some of the money yourself.
Once you're done...
sorting out all the money,
the other siblings
will enter the room.
- Together? Not in turns?
- Yes, together.
- The siblings will enter together.
- And then what?
Then the big sister...
will reveal
what she'll give the siblings.
I'm supposed to tell them?
They could lie about the amount...
after pocketing some themselves.
If you're not pleased...
with the amount you received,
you can negotiate
with your big sister.
- Okay.
- Got it.
If you're not pleased
after the negotiations,
you can use a chance.
It can be used
when two or more siblings...
- agree to it.
- Got it.
So the siblings have some power too.
The Mom Chance...
can be used
if you think that your big sister...
is lying.
Then you can divide the money
she hid for herself...
and her allowance equally.
(The younger siblings will take
her money if it succeeds.)
- What if she didn't lie?
- If she didn't lie,
she gets the money
that her younger siblings have.
(If it fails, the eldest sister gets
half the money her siblings have.)
But I need
the other siblings' consent, right?
Correct. More than two siblings have
to agree on using the Mom Chance.
2 siblings on this team,
and also 2 siblings on that team.
- Or you can use the Dad Chance too.
- "The Dad Chance"?
If you're not happy with the amount
your sister gave you...
regardless of whether or not
she lied,
you can use the Dad Chance.
For example, your sister
picked 100 dollars.
You can give the full amount
to one sibling in your family,
and no money to the others
based on a draw.
- That sounds great.
- Okay.
- The Dad Chance is good.
- I love it.
- It's great.
- However,
each time you use the Dad Chance,
one more person will get a penalty
at the end of the show.
- That's great.
- But it's too risky.
The Dad Chance is so risky.
- Indeed.
- I'm not sure about it.
(Each time they use the chance,
1 more person will get a penalty.)
I like the Dad Chance.
It's our style.
But you may lose the allowance
you received if you get unlucky.
- Understood.
- Okay.
- We won't get much money anyway.
- That's true.
She may pick a good one.
Pick a good one?
Our family has class.
We should trust Dong Mi.
- Of course, we trust Dong Mi.
- Yes.
I mean, she didn't contribute
much to winning.
- I'm sure she'll be reasonable.
- "I can shoot."
Now, the big sisters will leave.
- Let's go!
- Chung Hwa, go on.
- Okay.
- Dong Mi.
- Dong Mi, we trust you.
- Good luck.
I know, right?
From 40 to 80 dollars...
- If I pick 80 dollars, I will...
- Yes.
pocket some of it.
If you pick 80 dollars?
How many siblings do you have? 2?
- I have two siblings.
- My sisters.
- Dong Mi.
- Hi, Dong Mi.
What are you going to do?
- If I get a larger amount,
- Yes.
- I'll pocket some of it.
- I see.
- I'll do the same.
- You'll pocket some too?
Right.
This is an individual game.
- That's right.
- Exactly.
- It's an individual game after all.
- True.
And they would betray us anyway.
Even if we were family.
- I have a feeling somehow.
- Really?
(Chung Hwa knows Running Man
so well.)
- I think we should pocket money.
- I see.
- It's an individual game.
- We're competing too.
- Try not to lose your money.
- Of course.
- Good luck.
- 1, 2, 3.
- We can do it.
Please come this way.
- Bye. Good luck.
- Good luck.
(Will they pick a large amount
so they can pocket some money?)
Can I pick one of these?
Yes. There are 100, 90, 80, 70,
and 60 dollars in those 5 pouches.
You can choose one of them.
I see.
All right.
I pick this one.
I don't think
there's much money in here.
(How much money could there be
in the pouch she picked?)
Wait. 1, 2... And 7.
I have 100 dollars.
You picked 100 dollars.
I picked 100 dollars.
What should I do?
I must make a smart decision.
(How much money will she
give to her siblings?)
- 100 dollars...
- And the amount for your siblings.
(The Cha Family gets to choose
from 50 to 10 dollars.)
This one.
Please let me have 50 dollars.
(Chung Hwa desperately hopes
to get the largest amount.)
What do I do?
What am I going to do?
I choose this one.
(The Kim Family gets to choose
from 80 to 40 dollars.)
My goodness.
What do I do?
I didn't expect... What should I do?
Gosh, seriously. What should I do?
(Jae Hwa got flustered to find out
the amount. How much did she get?)
I think Jae Hwa needs to
go through a harsh initiation.
We should teach her
what a variety show is like.
- Okay. If we don't like the amount,
- Yes.
- let's use the Dad Chance.
- Okay.
- Come in.
- Jae Hwa!
Come on in, my brothers.
- Did you pick a good one?
- Jae Hwa.
(You picked a good one, right?)
- I'm not suspicious of you at all.
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- For what?
- You trust me, right?
- Yes, I do.
- Sit down for now.
- I trust you.
- Actually, I...
We got to choose
from 80 to 40 dollars.
- From 80 to 40 dollars?
- I see.
So the smallest amount is
40 dollars.
But I...
I tried to measure the thickness
of the pouches.
- I see.
- But...
unfortunately, I chose...
40 dollars.
(The smallest amount?)
- You chose 40 dollars?
- So...
So I'll give you guys...
(She can't even look them
in the eyes...)
(while giving 10 dollars
to each of them.)
Let's divide the money like this
for now.
Wait. You picked the smallest amount
among the five pouches?
- Yes. You have to believe me.
- It just happened that way?
You want us to believe you?
- I'm being honest. They all know.
- I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, but can Haha and I
sit together?
Wait. No, hang on a second.
(He's trying to isolate her.)
Wait. You should see what I'll do
with the remaining amount.
I'm going to...
You picked 40 dollars
even when you touched the pouches?
- Yes.
- You checked the thickness.
- You touched every pouch, right?
- Yes, I touched all of them.
I thought it was the one
with 80 dollars in it.
- So who gets the extra 10 dollars?
- I think...
the youngest one should have it.
Thank you, Jae Hwa.
You even gave him that money?
I have three children.
(The 2nd child Kim Kwang Soo is
about to snap.)
- That's one of the reasons.
- Thank you.
How do we use
the Mom and Dad Chances?
- Can we just tell you?
- If Haha agrees, you can use it.
You better not use it...
because I'm innocent.
Do you mind if we discuss this
without you?
- Will you really be like this?
- Just for a moment.
Sure. Go ahead.
- I won't hear you guys.
- Even if we use the Dad Chance,
and one more person
receives the penalty,
you won't be that person.
That's not true.
Besides, I trust Jae Hwa.
(He betrayed Kwang Soo right away.)
- What you said on our way here...
- It's not like that.
- You should keep it together.
- I trust...
- Right. You should trust me.
- Hold on.
- Little brother.
- Kwang Soo,
can't you trust her?
Listen to me.
If you guys use a chance, I'll be
the only one to benefit from it.
- Because I'm innocent.
- Right. You're being honest.
You looked me in the eyes
as you walked in.
- You two should discuss this.
- Then let's do this.
(But Kwang Soo seems to want to
use the Mom Chance.)
If you agree to be the youngest
instead of me,
(If he agrees to be the youngest,
Haha will agree on using it.)
I'll agree on using a chance.
Being the second eldest is
too much for me, to be honest.
I mean it.
It suits you better.
I agree on using the Mom Chance...
in return for switching our orders.
- We'll use the Mom Chance, right?
- The two of you are...
- suspicious of your sister,
- Yes.
so you decided to use
the Mom Chance, right?
Your sister Kim Jae Hwa...
(If she lied,
they'll get her money.)
did...
(If she didn't lie,
she'll get their money.)
- not lie to you.
- Gosh.
(Jae Hwa told them the truth.)
You mean jerk.
I told you to believe her.
- Did you really pick 40 dollars?
- Because she really picked it,
- things turned out this way.
- I really picked 40 dollars.
I think I was wrong.
(Earlier on, Jae Hwa picked
the smallest amount, 40 dollars.)
40 dollars.
I'll make them doubt me...
and use the Mom Chance
or the Dad Chance.
I'll give 10 dollars
to each of the 3 of us,
and I'll give Haha extra 10 dollars.
- 40 dollars out of the 5 pouches?
- Yes.
Also, I knew you guys would
use the Mom Chance.
I planned this to get more money.
Look how messed up our family is.
- Look who's talking.
- I mean,
I need more money.
10 dollars isn't enough.
Hurry up and give me the money.
You have to give her half
the amount you have.
- Should I give her 10 dollars?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- We'll break the bill.
(10 dollars from Haha,
5 dollars from Kwang Soo)
Thank you.
You see, I did this to make it fun.
1... 10 dollars. 20 dollars...
1, 2, 3, 4...
I didn't know she was so cheeky.
I'm sorry, but by doing this,
I got an extra 25 dollars.
This is how you should
make a deal.
- That was smart.
- I know, right?
(While the Kim brothers got tricked
by their sister Jae Hwa...)
- Chung Hwa.
- Announce the amount, Chung Hwa.
How much money did you pick?
- Be honest with us.
- How much?
- Come on. Tell us now.
- 20 dollars.
- How much?
- But I think I did a good job.
- 20 dollars...
It's not good.
It's not even the average.
- The maximum amount was 50 dollars.
- Yes.
So I asked to break the bills
into 20 1-dollar bills,
so we could
divide the money equally.
- Chung Hwa.
- Yes?
- Did you really choose 20 dollars?
- Yes.
That's weird.
- 20 dollars is easy to divide.
- Chung Hwa, look me in the eyes.
- They don't believe me. I'm upset.
- It's because...
it's not easy to pick the amount
that you can divide easily.
- Absolutely.
- That's why I changed the bills.
Can you look me in the eyes?
- How much money did you choose?
- 20 dollars.
- All right.
- He liked it.
I picked 20 dollars.
- Suk Jin liked it.
- That was natural.
- I really picked 20 dollars.
- It really was natural.
It was natural,
but she's a great actress.
Because this is my first time
on a variety show,
- I want to ride on your coattails.
- That makes me suspicious of her.
- It's so easy to divide equally.
- We've never divided team money...
equally like this on Running Man.
I'm taken aback.
- Really?
- Yes.
But I'm suspicious of her
because it's...
- I think we should trust her.
- I think we should trust her too.
- Trust her. I think it's true.
- Let's trust her.
I want to use the Mom Chance.
- The Mom Chance?
- You can't decide alone.
- You need our consent.
- More than two siblings.
Trust me and don't use it.
- Shall we not use it?
- Come on. Trust me.
- Let's not use a chance now.
- Let's not use it.
- Let's use it next time.
- Right.
- So you decided not to use it?
- We won't use it.
- We won't use any chances.
- We'll trust her.
The siblings of the Cha Family...
didn't use any chances and gained
the amount Chung Hwa gave you.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- Each of you received five dollars.
- It's not a lot.
- That's right.
- This is...
Also, the eldest,
- Chung Hwa, actually got...
- Yes?
How much did she get?
(And the eldest, Chung Hwa...)
a total of 35 dollars.
You see?
- You see?
- Hey!
I didn't know you'd share this.
My goodness, I feel so betrayed!
Chung Hwa picked 50 dollars.
- You see?
- Chung Hwa!
(Actually, Chung Hwa picked
the highest amount.)
Why would you tell them?
- That's how this works.
- You never told me that!
What on earth?
(Chung Hwa's trick
that's been revealed to everyone)
(A while ago)
No way!
I have no choice
but to take 30 dollars.
Chung Hwa, I'm a bit hurt.
We should've used
the Mom Chance, So Min.
Why didn't you tell me about that?
- I forgot.
- That's crazy!
- But that's...
- I got this. I got this, okay?
Fine! I don't care about family now.
In the next round...
Oh, no. I should've picked
a lesser amount!
I picked 100 dollars,
what should I do?
What should I do?
(She's having a lot of thoughts
after picking a large sum of money.)
Well...
- We're coming in!
- Okay!
I should take off my shoes, right?
- My sister...
- My siblings who I'm proud of.
- Dong Mi.
- Did you pick a good one?
- My siblings who I'm proud of.
Did you pick a good one?
- Did you pick a good one?
(Jong Kook checks
the smell of Se Chan's feet.)
Why is he smelling that?
- Wait a minute. Hey, Kim Nipple.
- Then...
How dare you smell my shoes?
Se Chan, your socks
are already so dirty.
No, they seem fine.
- Are they?
- They smell nice today.
Ji Hyo, smell this.
- No. Come on, Se Chan.
- What's wrong with you?
- I'll teach you a lesson.
- I can't love your smelly feet.
So... Did you pick a good one?
I'm really bad at these things,
but I picked a good one.
- Really?
- Yes, I picked a good one.
I picked a very appropriate one.
Appropriate?
- That means she picked 60 dollars.
- That sounds not right.
- 80 dollars? 60 dollars?
- I picked a very appropriate one.
Dong Mi isn't talented in anything,
- Right. I picked a perfect one.
- but I guess she picked a good one.
- That's great.
- What did you pick?
- How much did you pick?
- For Se Chan...
Yes? Are you giving it out now?
- Yes, of course.
- Right.
- Se Chan...
- Se Chan did an excellent job.
- He did.
- Thank you.
- I'll give you 20 dollars.
- 20 dollars?
- 20 dollars? I'm happy with that.
- And Ji Hyo...
- How much did you get in total?
- gets 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars?
- Then that's 30 dollars in total.
- Hold on.
- And...
- Then how much is she giving me?
- What? 5 dollars?
- 8 dollars?
- I worked hard.
- Here. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
5 dollars?
(5 dollars?)
(The youngest, Jong Kook,
gets 5 dollars.)
- You're giving 5 dollars to him?
- Jong Kook...
- gets 5 dollars.
- Dong Mi.
- How much did you get?
- We can negotiate, you see.
- I got...
- 35 dollars.
- That's a little...
- What? Come on.
- 35 dollars.
(Dong Mi keeps 35 dollars
to herself.)
- What a thief!
- Dong Mi!
- I'm going to tell Mom!
- Listen.
- Keep just 30 dollars for yourself.
- Listen to me.
- Listen.
- She got 100 dollars?
I understand you
taking more than us,
- but you're being too greedy.
- That's why I'm taking 35 dollars.
- You're being greedy.
- You're so greedy.
This show already aired.
You're a very greedy one.
Really? Then have a dollar.
Wow, she's only giving you a dollar.
- Wow.
- Dong Mi isn't so generous.
- Take another dollar then.
- You could give more than that.
- My gosh.
- That makes seven dollars.
- 7 dollars. Lucky 7.
- Look at her.
- Okay.
- Isn't it nice? It's seven dollars.
I think she got five times
more than what I got.
You took a lot, Dong Mi.
(Giving another dollar)
Why? Why are you giving me more?
I think she'll keep giving you
if we ask her.
- No, no.
- I think she can give more.
- She'll give more if we ask.
- No, that's not true.
Okay, then give me another dollar.
- Fine. I can give you another one.
- Eight dollars would be fine.
That's closer to 10 dollars,
you see.
Now that we're done
distributing allowances,
let us tell you
how much Dong Mi picked.
You're going to tell us?
No way.
She picked 100 dollars.
(Actually, she picked 100 dollars.)
(Dong Mi took
62 dollars to herself.)
This won't do. We have to...
Look at her. She's happy.
- Didn't I do well?
- We should've searched her.
What do you mean?
We're right here, and you're
asking them if you did well?
- What do you mean?
- I know, I told you.
We should've gone through her bag.
This is a matter of trust.
How could you be so happy?
You should be sorry instead.
- You're the eldest, you see?
- You should be sorry.
Ta-da.
You can't be all bright about this!
(She brags about how much she got
despite how angry the others are.)
You can't tease us like that!
- I got this much.
- We should've gone through her bag.
Easily put, she took 30 dollars,
- I know.
- and she gave me 5 dollars.
(She gave me 5 dollars.)
I'm just...
She managed to take 35 dollars.
Gosh, what a disgrace.
Let me tell you the rules
of the final race.
It's a game based on how older
siblings tell younger siblings...
to run errands.
It's called Turn Off This Light.
Soon, the lights
that are turned on...
and stickers
with each family's name...
will be hidden here and there.
The eldest has to find the sticker
with their family name...
and stick it on the light.
They have to stick the sticker
on the light.
Then I have to do a good job
of finding the stickers.
Right, when the eldest
finds a sticker...
This is what the younger ones
have to do.
You have to turn off the lights
that have the stickers...
with your family name.
It's not a good thing
to have the lights on.
You should turn off your family's.
Turn on the lights
of other families.
So we should turn on the lights
with our family name.
Right. The eldest can stick
their family sticker...
on the light that already has
another family's sticker.
The younger siblings can turn on
the lights of the other family...
and get in the way.
Oh, they can turn on the lights
with the other family's name? Okay.
When the time is up,
you'll earn 10 dollars...
for each light that's turned off
with your family's name.
So basically, the lights
with our family's name...
need to be turned off...
- in order for us to win.
- Yes, that's correct.
You can also rip off the name tag,
regardless of the lights.
If you rip off a name tag,
you earn 2 dollars.
Those who got their name tags
ripped off...
will have to freeze for 30 seconds
before they can join the game again.
When the race is over, we will
combine the amounts of money...
you earned by turning off the lights
and ripping off the name tags.
We'll decide the ranking
by the amount.
(The final ranking will be decided
by the total amount.)
- 5, 4...
- It takes me a while...
to put my shoes on.
- Right.
- Fine!
One. Race, start.
(Race, start.)
- We'll put this on first.
- Okay.
Can I check what's up there?
(The eldest has to find
the family sticker first.)
(While they're searching...)
(He found something?)
You found something?
- This is...
- What is it?
(Kwang Soo of the Kim Family
found the sticker first.)
There it is!
But this belongs to the Shin Family.
- It's not ours. It's the Shins'.
- There it is!
(They start finding
the family stickers.)
There it is.
(Which sticker did Se Chan find?)
Did you find one, Se Chan?
- Did you find one?
- It's for the Shin Family!
- Really?
- Dong Mi!
- I'll put it over there.
- Over there...
Stick it on the light
that can't be seen.
(Stick it on the light
that can't be seen.)
The light that can't be seen?
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk...)
This must be the light.
(found the light that was hidden.)
So we have to stick
the sticker on here.
- You get what I mean, right?
- Where?
What is that?
That's the light.
Oh, really?
We can turn it on or off.
- Whose light is that?
- I can find these well.
If we stick our family sticker,
it becomes ours.
(In the meantime,
So Min is making a snowball.)
Where could it be?
(Where could it be?)
(Looking around)
(Throwing)
(While she was busy playing...)
Jong Kook, don't do that.
Seriously, don't do it.
This isn't how it works.
Come on, you know it!
(Jong Kook appears while screaming.)
You can't take out the weakest!
(The weakest So Min's name tag was
ripped off as soon as they started.)
(So Min is frozen for 30 seconds.
Jong Kook earned 2 dollars.)
Gosh, I bet a lot of them
will rip off my name tag today.
This isn't fair!
Come on. This isn't how it's played.
This isn't how it's supposed
to be played. Stop it.
This isn't how it's played.
I just got my name tag ripped!
- You'll have to roll about here.
- Will you please let me go?
Let me go about, will you?
- Seriously.
- All right.
I'm going to call you "Two Dollars"
from now, okay?
Ms. Two Dollars.
There's Ms. Two Dollars!
(Jeon So Min,
also known as Two Dollars)
I guarantee you, I'll be
stuck here for at least 30 minutes.
(She fell into the swamp
of being stuck.)
Where can I find it?
Playing a game in the snowy field
makes me feel...
- like I'm back in my childhood.
- Ms. Cha!
- Ms. Cha.
- Oh, hey, Ms. Kim.
Do you want this?
(Shouting loudly)
(Do you want this?)
Do you have our sticker?
- Of course we want it.
- Do you have our sticker or not?
- Of course I do.
- Let me see.
- You think I don't?
- Show me.
These are all yours.
- I should... Suk Jin.
- Yes?
Let's rip off Jae Hwa's name tag.
- Are you sure it's our sticker?
- Yes, I'm telling you.
Look at you guys closing in on me.
I'm all alone here.
(She retreats for now.)
- Did you find our stickers?
- No.
(Haha joins to help Jae Hwa.
It's 2 on 2 now.)
Don't touch us.
(The Cha brothers
are after Jae Hwa's name tag.)
Jae Hwa.
(Haha is trying to protect
his sister.)
Come on.
(I could lose their stickers
if I get my name tag ripped.)
Oh, gosh.
(Suk Jin is taking on Jae Hwa?)
(It's a 1-on-1 match.)
(Who will be the winner
in this match to win the stickers?)
(Jae Hwa won.)
Okay!
Gosh, Suk Jin lost to her.
(Laughing awkwardly)
Suk Jin lost to her.
(Suk Jin lost to her.)
He must've been embarrassed.
He just clapped.
That was amazing.
She's quite nimble.
(She's quite nimble.)
(Meanwhile, Dong Mi is busy
checking what's going on.)
Jong Kook.
Come here.
(Jong Kook goes to Dong Mi
as she called him.)
- Turn this off! Turn it off.
- All right.
Okay, okay. All right.
(They're after the lights
instead of the name tags.)
I need to find our stickers.
(He saw the target.)
(Kwang Soo goes after Dong Mi.)
(Lying down)
(She grits her teeth
and defends herself.)
You little...
(Kwang Soo can't do anything
because she struggles violently.)
(At that moment,
Se Chan turns back and attacks him!)
You!
(Ripping)
Out.
Okay.
(The weakest member
succeeded to land her first attack.)
What? Wasn't my name tag ripped off?
It wasn't ripped off.
- I had no idea.
- I got Kwang Soo's name tag.
Your name tag wasn't ripped off.
- Kwang Soo.
- You need to pause.
We need to find the stickers.
(Jae Suk earns 2 dollars
and sets off to find the stickers.)
Do you want to buy this
for two dollars?
The Cha Family? That isn't ours.
You could sell it to the Cha Family
for three dollars.
Give me our sticker.
You are in the Kim Family.
(It's a Shin Family sticker!)
Hand it over.
- What?
- I mean...
- "Hand it over"?
- Let's exchange the stickers.
I don't need a Cha Family sticker.
Then I will buy it. How much is it?
It's originally five dollars.
- It's too expensive.
- There is a celebrity discount.
There is a celebrity discount.
Three dollars.
Two dollars.
The starting price is two dollars
these days.
I am serious. Don't play around.
- I will give it to you.
- If you don't give it to me,
- I will kick you.
- Put it down.
- I will put down the sticker here.
- Okay.
(They show their cards
for a safe transaction.)
Take one step forward.
- Take one step forward.
- Okay.
Take the second step.
(The distance between them
doesn't close easily.)
Take the third step.
No sudden movements.
Hold on.
All done. Dong Mi, run!
- Hurry up and run!
- What?
(Having adjusted to Running Man,
she steals the sticker.)
- Hurry up and run!
- What?
Dong Mi, run!
(The brother distracts
while the sister steals.)
Hurry up and run!
- I will catch you no matter what.
- What?
I will catch you no matter what.
No, no.
- Give me two dollars.
- No. Listen, Kwang Soo.
- Give me a dollar then.
- Listen, Kwang Soo.
- It was on the ground, wasn't it?
Give me a dollar!
I worked so hard to find it.
Give me a dollar.
I can't do that.
You lost the sticker already.
Do you have the sticker for me?
You lost it.
I will get you. Okay.
Okay. It's not my goal
to have the team win.
- You...
- Good job, Dong Mi!
Ji Hyo, if you go...
into the second alley,
you will find our light.
You need to turn it off.
I need to turn it off.
(She listens to Dong Mi
and goes to the light.)
I need to turn it off. Okay.
(Jae Hwa diligently puts
the stickers on the lights.)
(Kim Family)
- All right.
- Hey.
I can't remove the sticker.
(She looks around.)
(She puts the Cha Family sticker
on top of the Kim Family sticker.)
Hey! Chung Hwa!
(Jae Hwa attacks.)
(Jae Hwa attacks
after watching what she did.)
(But she is outnumbered
since it's 2 on 1.)
(She makes a narrow escape.)
How is she so good
at ripping off the name tags?
She is so strong.
I got this.
(Suk Jin joins the fight.)
(It's 3 members of the Kim Family
versus Jae Hwa.)
- She is so strong.
- Hold on.
She is scary.
(Moving her arms like a windmill)
(They become helpless
in front of her shower of punches.)
Hey.
Was she a fighter?
She is so strong.
(The streetfighter doesn't back down
even if there are 3 opponents.)
- Seriously. Jae Hwa.
- We did it.
(3 people gang up on her
to remove the name tag.)
Jae Hwa is like a bull.
Jae Hwa.
I can't believe her.
Jae Hwa,
where did you hang out
back in the day?
- She is scary.
- Seriously.
People should be careful.
She nearly pounded on us.
She is so scary.
- She nearly ended us.
- It could have ended badly.
- I work out.
- She is so scary.
I have a lot of stickers
for the Shin Family.
Really? Show me.
- These are for the Shin Family.
- I can give you your stickers.
- Okay.
- The Cha Family's stickers.
I have three.
- Let's see them.
- In that case,
- let's trade them.
- Let's trade them.
(At that moment)
(She removes 2 name tags at once!)
(She takes out two brothers
of the Cha Family.)
- Is she...
- My sister is the best!
Is she an assassin?
What was that?
Is she...
She is much better than us.
Is she an assassin?
She is like
the female Kim Jong Kook.
She ripped off two name tags
at once.
Did you hear the sound?
I knew I was out
because I heard the sound.
(He didn't even see her.)
Do you have
the Shin Family's stickers?
I have the Cha Family's stickers.
Do you want to exchange them?
- Already?
- Yes.
- How many do you have?
- One.
- 3?
- I have 2.
- Two Cha Family's stickers?
- Yes.
- Find two of ours first.
- Okay. I will do that.
- Make sure you do that. Deal.
- Deal.
- Let's make an exchange then.
- Okay.
Let's end the Kim Family.
- Deal.
- Okay.
- This is how it works.
- That's right.
Jae Hwa is annoyingly strong.
So...
- we will join forces.
- Yes.
(The annoyingly strong assassin
is destroying the Cha Family again.)
Let's join forces!
Chicken.
(Cock-a-doodle-doo!)
(The two cowards are scared
of Jae Hwa.)
(While Jae Hwa takes on everyone...)
I should receive more from Ji Hyo.
(Dong Mi quietly puts on a sticker.)
(She puts it
on top of the Cha Family's.)
The Shin Family
keeps covering ours with theirs.
(What is Chung Hwa doing
after forming an alliance?)
(She also puts a sticker
on top of the Shin Family's.)
(They learned that betrayal is
the only way to survive.)
Ms. Cha.
- Ms. Cha.
- Yes?
- Do you have our stickers?
- Yes, I do.
- You do?
- Yes.
- Shall we make an exchange?
- That's a good idea.
I also bought the compact foundation
you model for.
It's so nice.
I wanted my skin to look
as nice as yours.
I even sent one to my mom.
- Didn't I do a good job? It's okay.
- I will send it to you.
I bought it with my money,
so give me the sticker.
(It's like a conversation between
a used-goods seller and buyer.)
Give me the sticker.
I have the Shin Family's sticker.
- Cha Family's sticker.
- That's good. Let's exchange them.
Really? Don't lie.
Don't make me leave a bad review
for the compact foundation.
(She makes a cute threat
for the safe exchange.)
- Are you serious?
- I am serious. I like you a lot.
- Let's hold them together.
- 1, 2, 3.
I like you.
- I will use it well.
- Thank you.
- Please write a good review.
- Of course.
(The exchange shows
that both of them have manners.)
So Min, she is a nice girl.
- Se Chan!
Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, I found so many stickers.
- Let's see them.
- Shin Family's stickers.
- Really?
- Look, Dong Mi.
- Is there one for the Cha Family?
- I have many.
- How many do you have?
- Four.
- Check them later.
- He needs the Cha Family's.
- Who?
- Here.
- Suk Jin.
- Let's make an exchange.
- How many?
- How many do you have?
- Three?
- I have a lot. I have 20.
- 3.
We can give them to you.
- 2.
- 3.
- Here.
- Here you go.
The atmosphere is nice.
Why don't you give us
your name tag as well?
It only costs two dollars.
Seriously.
Give it to us.
- It's that kind of atmosphere.
- Come on.
It's that kind of atmosphere.
- Give it to us.
- It's that kind of atmosphere.
- Suk Jin.
- Give it to us.
Thank you.
You are the best.
- I will have my revenge.
- Okay.
Okay.
He keeps saying
he will have his revenge.
He keeps saying that,
but he can't do it.
Dong Mi, I will have my revenge.
- Okay.
- Please put this back.
- I need to wait for 30 seconds.
Okay.
Jae Hwa.
(The Kim Family is headed
somewhere.)
(They spot a light!)
- That's good.
- Let's hide it.
We need to move it.
Hold on. We should turn it off.
- Turn it off.
- Hold on.
Hold on.
I don't think it will work.
(What should we do?)
Like this.
(He hides the light with something.)
It's so obvious.
Don't use that. Use this instead.
Use this instead.
(The second brother
gets to work instead.)
Is it even more obvious?
It's so obvious.
It seems to be saying,
"Please come this way."
Five minutes until the race ends.
Jong Kook!
(The physical fights become worse
as the end draws near.)
(Ripping)
Where does he keep coming from?
Where did he come from?
(The Kim Family's assassin
awakens in full force!)
For goodness' sake.
You know, Jae Hwa...
pounds on people.
She is a warrior.
I can barely see her feet.
Boom! She goes...
Gosh, you startled me!
That little...
(The protein brother
chases after Haha!)
He looks like a bear.
We need to find the name tags.
(The Cha Family can't do anything
because of the two bulls.)
There are so many.
(Getting more lights is
the only way they can win.)
(The big sister of the Shin Family
sneaks up on him.)
- What is it?
- Nothing.
I was just looking.
If you have a Cha Family's sticker,
we can make an exchange.
- Do you have our sticker?
- Yes.
Show me.
Show me first.
A Cha Family's sticker.
My siblings will come
if I call for them.
I mean...
You shouldn't do that.
Your siblings will come
if you call for them?
I am serious.
- Come on.
- I have so many siblings.
Don't be like that.
Dong Mi, show me the sticker.
- I will call for them.
- Hold on.
The deal is off.
Se Chan!
- Don't do that.
- Ji Hyo!
Who are you looking for?
Shin Ji Hyo!
Shin Ji Hyo.
(Jae Suk leaves for now.)
You said you have our sticker.
Give it to me.
I have it. Wait right there.
Another one? Shin Family's stickers
are everywhere.
Give it to me!
How is her hearing so good?
I will give you yours.
Give me the Cha Family's sticker.
Come on.
There you go.
Okay. That's good.
- So, this is... Jong Kook.
- We have a lot left.
We shouldn't put a lot of stickers
on the lights.
Other families keep covering them
with theirs,
so we should hold on to ours.
We shouldn't have put them early on.
I didn't think it through.
What should we do?
You never think things through.
Hey.
Oh, you are my older brother.
Hold on.
- Kim Nipple.
- Se Chan.
How could you say that...
to your older brother?
You should praise
your older brother.
You never think things through.
- It's true.
- I couldn't hold myself back.
So Min, look for the envelopes.
(Jae Suk turns on
the Shin Family's light.)
- Did you turn it on?
- Yes.
(He looks around...)
(and turns off
the Shin Family's light.)
(Chung Hwa runs over.)
(Chung Hwa, put the sticker here!)
(After putting the sticker,
they turn off the light.)
What? Hold on.
(She smacks him on the head.)
It's a rule, Chung Hwa!
Don't you think you are too violent?
Are you calling my sister violent?
Your sister is the one
who brandishes her fists.
Do you know how many beatings
I took from her?
- Hey.
- The sisters are strong.
We took so many beatings
from Jae Hwa.
- Go on your way.
- I can't believe him.
This isn't the time
to put on the stickers.
(The Kim Family is in a hurry
as well.)
Are you out?
I am out. Se Chan!
- You aren't out, are you?
- Se Chan!
Are you out? You aren't!
(Haha heads somewhere
in the confusion of the moment.)
(Shin Family)
(He turns on
the Shin Family's light.)
(Kwang Soo tries to turn it off
and Ji Hyo tries to stop him.)
(He attacks with his teeth.)
What are you doing? Hey!
(The Kim Family's second brother
came to help!)
(Turning the light on and off)
(They touch the light repeatedly
as if they are playing a game.)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo grabs Kwang Soo
by his hair.)
Hey!
(Ji Hyo turns the light on and off
by herself.)
(It's a hectic dogfight
on the snowy field.)
Ji Hyo!
Will you give me
a Cha Family's sticker if I help?
Yes, I will!
(Ripping off)
(He is proud of himself
after landing a sneaky attack.)
- He... Gosh!
- Okay!
(The assassin approaches silently
and rips off the name tag!)
(30 seconds
before the end of the race)
- All right.
- We need to protect this one.
Protect that one.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Jae Suk, you can move now.
15 seconds remain.
(They need to turn off
as many lights as possible!)
- 15 seconds.
- Did you protect it?
(Jae Suk heads
to the Cha Family's light!)
(But Se Chan is protecting it!)
(The fierce on and off war)
(Wars break out
at other spots as well.)
Stop it already.
- 5, 4,
- Yes!
- 3, 2, 1.
It's over. It's over.
- I turned it on.
- The countdown ended first.
(Cha Family's light is on.)
I turned it on first.
Kwang Soo. Nice.
- They will lose 10 dollars.
- They are too much.
Nice.
(Which team will have
the most amount of money?)
(The final count)
- Everyone.
- Yes?
I will announce how much you made
by ripping off the name tags.
Jong Kook, 22 dollars.
(Jong Kook, 22 dollars)
- That's incredible.
- Did he rip off 11 name tags?
Just from the name tags?
- Half of the money is from me.
- I ripped off her name tag a lot.
Half of the money is from me.
Jae Hwa, 16 dollars.
(Jae Hwa, 16 dollars)
Did you rip off eight name tags?
(8 kills)
- Did you rip off eight name tags?
- She showed us the best scene...
in the 10-year history
of Name Tag Eliminations.
She ripped off two name tags
at the same time.
Jae Suk and Suk Jin.
Staff members call her Two Swords.
- Two Nunchuks.
- The female Park Jun Gyu.
She stood...
as if she was
on the top of a mountain.
(The charisma of a Siberian tiger)
Her gaze... Seriously.
When she smiles,
she looks a bit like Ryu Hyun Jin.
- That's right.
- She looks a bit like Ryu Hyun Jin.
- She does.
- She does, right?
When she smiles,
she looks a bit like Ryu Hyun Jin.
- She does.
- She really does.
- They resemble each other.
People will believe her
if she says that she is his sister.
(She even has
Hyun Jin's endless strength.)
- There is a resemblance.
- Next.
Kwang Soo and Haha,
14 dollars each.
- I ripped off many name tags.
- Not bad.
I will give you the results
regarding the lights.
The Shin Family
put their stickers on nine lights.
- Really?
- The lights that are off?
- That's incredible.
- Nine lights in total.
Eight lights were turned off.
(They acquired 80 dollars.)
- Did we get 80 dollars?
- Really?
(The Shin Family turned off
all the lights except for one.)
- Only one light was turned on.
- We did well.
- The Kim Family...
- We are incredible.
- put their stickers on four lights.
- Us?
- Yes.
Only four lights?
- All of them changed.
- Four lights were turned off.
- What? 4 lights?
- We acquired 40 dollars.
40 dollars.
Next is the Cha Family.
They put their stickers
on nine lights.
Nine lights.
Two lights were turned off.
(They acquired 20 dollars.)
(2 out of 9 lights?)
Chung Hwa is absorbed.
I feel like I am watching
a morning drama.
They turned on our lights.
- I worked so hard.
- We had many lights. It's a shame.
Thus,
the 1st place is the Shin Family
with 122 dollars.
The 2nd place is the Kim Family
with 84 dollars.
The 3rd place is the Cha Family
with 40 dollars.
Now comes the last step.
- The sisters will move first.
- Okay.
(The last time to distribute
the allowances)
I need to get a lot of money.
I got 100 dollars earlier.
(100, 90, and 80 dollars)
This one.
(Earlier, Dong Mi picked
the most amount of money.)
I think I picked a small amount.
We need to avoid the penalty.
(The Shin Family's
younger siblings enter.)
Okay.
It has begun.
- Did you get 80 dollars?
- 80 dollars.
- It will be funny to use a chance.
- Hold on.
Did you get 80 dollars?
- Is it a coincidence?
- Dong Mi, sit down.
- Dong Mi.
- Is it a coincidence?
80 dollars.
It's always one extreme
after another for me.
Earlier, I picked 100 dollars.
This time, I picked 80 dollars.
I can't lie about it.
Why not?
- It's 80 dollars.
- But...
- Jong Kook.
- It makes no sense...
that you picked 80 dollars.
- Seriously.
- I have more money.
Let me explain.
We placed 1st and won 122 dollars.
What?
Then distribute that money first.
- Listen.
- Distribute that money first.
No. I will do this first...
before I distribute the prize money.
She is acting strange, right?
- She is acting strange.
- You are too much.
Give us 10 or 20 dollars more.
You are in 1st place.
No. Let's say...
the other teams
picked 60 dollars twice.
If they keep the money
to themselves, it's 120 dollars.
Then I won't come in first.
Her ambition is on another level.
Her eyes are on the prize.
- She is unbelievable.
- Her ambition is on another level.
She is thinking about
the maximum amount.
I can't believe she is thinking
about that.
You want to place first
and trample on everyone, right?
You even thought about
the 60 dollars.
There is the Dad Chance.
Give us 30 dollars each...
before anything.
You can give us that much.
(She distributes 30 dollars each.)
For goodness' sake.
What will happen to the two dollars?
I will keep it.
(I will keep it.)
Jong Kook, we should kick her out
of the family.
- Listen.
- Seriously.
I gave you 50 dollars each.
- We should kick her out.
- From whom...
did she get that greedy side?
- She needs a scolding.
- We should tell Mom.
Don't do that.
I will give you two dollars.
She is too much.
- Keep it for now.
- Really?
Mom will come later...
with a stick.
She will break your legs. Get ready.
- We need to call Mom.
- Jong Kook.
I also think Dong Mi needs
to be punished...
for her greedy side.
That's good. We will call Mom.
We will call Mom.
- You decided to use the Mom Chance.
- Yes.
I couldn't be fairer.
It's impossible to do this
more fairly.
Okay, Dong Mi.
The Mom Chance revealed
that Dong Mi's words were...
(Did Dong Mi speak truthfully
about the 80 dollars?)
true.
You ingrates!
(The Mom Chance was a failure.)
I told you that
I will divide the money equally.
- We couldn't believe her.
- I told you that...
- I will give you nine dollars.
- She is like...
an experienced gambler.
(Her mind games make them wonder
about her past.)
- Double or nothing.
- An experienced gambler.
She is good at playing cards.
- She shook us up.
- Seriously.
Why did you do that?
- Dong Mi.
- Couldn't you trust your sister?
How much do you have now?
You have over 200 dollars, right?
You should say,
"I won with 200 dollars!"
Do that and see
how satisfying it is. Go ahead.
(The Kim Family
and Cha Family are done as well.)
(What will be the result?)
We were going to have one person
receive the penalty.
They must have used the Dad Chance.
Two rooms used the Dad Chance,
so three people in total
will receive the penalty.
Did one room go without using it?
(The Cha Family used
the Dad Chance.)
(1 more person will receive
the penalty.)
(2 more people will receive
They used chances.
You didn't use it. Thank goodness.
- We just need to avoid the penalty.
- Thank goodness.
I will show you the prize first.
- I am jealous.
- The prize is...
- the high-end strawberry set.
- Strawberries.
- I will announce three winners.
- Okay.
The 1st-place winner has
183 dollars.
- Shin Dong Mi.
The first-place winner!
She took all our money.
- The luxurious Dong Mi.
- It was no joke.
I will pick the red ribbon.
Thank you.
Dong Mi is incredible.
The second-place winner...
has 176 dollars. It's Kwang Soo.
(Is Kwang Soo the 2nd-place winner?)
(He succeeded to take all the money
with the Dad Chance.)
176 dollars.
(Unlike Dong Mi,
Jae Hwa failed with the mind games.)
He is the worst.
176 dollars.
The third-place winner...
has 65 dollars.
It's Jae Suk.
(He also took all the money
with the Dad Chance.)
- Chung Hwa, take it home.
- You don't have to do that.
You don't have to do that.
You are the best.
Thank you.
(Look at Kwang Soo's face.)
Look at Kwang Soo's face.
Two strawberry sets went
to the guests,
- but he is holding onto his.
- Who came in last?
(He holds onto the basket.)
(Two Swords unfortunately has
a greedy brother.)
He is unbelievable.
Actually...
Your dad will scold you.
(Winning the prize is
Kwang Soo's small happiness.)
The last place has 16 dollars.
It's Haha.
(Haha is in the last place
since Kwang Soo took his money.)
The 10th place has 33 dollars.
It's Jae Hwa.
(Is Jae Hwa 2nd to last?)
- I didn't place last, right?
- You get the penalty.
(Haha and Jae Hwa will get
the penalty.)
What is this family going to do?
(The youngest one received
the strawberries,)
(but the other siblings received
the penalty.)
You got the penalty.
The last person to receive
the penalty has 35 dollars.
(Who is the last person to receive
the penalty?)
Suk Jin.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I survived.
- So Min placed 8th with 43 dollars.
That team lost all the money.
I will tell you what the penalty is.
Today's penalty
will let you share stories...
and deepen the love
between the siblings.
- It's time for a home-cooked meal.
- What is that?
With the basic tools and ingredients
we prepared for you,
you can prepare a home-cooked meal
and eat it.
- What?
- Really?
We're supposed to have a meal?
It hasn't been long since we ate.
It's so annoying.
I hate it so much.
- But the penalties try to make...
- My wife said she cooked for me.
- us as annoyed as possible.
- But...
We can't even say
it's a painful penalty.
It's a good thing, but...
- These strawberries are a gift.
- No, it's okay.
- No, it's my treat.
- Oh, my.
- These strawberries are a gift.
- Thank you.
I hope you enjoy them.
They're really good at coming up
with penalties. How could they...
- Gosh, this is really...
- That's right.
Doing this really makes
us feel like a family.
- Yes.
- We're working as a family.
- Watching you cook in a mountain,
- Yes?
it feels like you're shooting
"Flaming Youth".
("Flaming Youth")
Your wish came true.
No, it's not my wish.
I just said it for no reason.
I said it to be funny.
Okay. After I do this,
I'm going to add a fried egg on top.
- That's too big.
- I'm also going to add this.
He still eats jelly as a snack.
- There isn't any jelly.
- I'm annoyed there's no ketchup.
(I'm annoyed there's no ketchup.)
(He's suddenly embarrassed.)
- Gosh.
- Gosh, this is so annoying.
But it's quite heartwarming
for a penalty.
It's heartwarming, but it's
quite nice to actually do it.
(We'd like to thank Shin Dong Mi,
Kim Jae Hwa, and Cha Chung Hwa...)
(for making Running Man's winter
warm like cozy snowflakes.)
"A movie-like incident where
prisoners escaped from prison..."
(These people shouldn't be
let out into the world.)
(We call them the "Penalty Men".)
Wait a minute!
(Penalty Men)
(Lee Sang Yi)
(Bae Yoon Kyung)
(Ahn Eun Jin)
(They discover the identities
of the Penalty Men.)
Are you taking us hostage?
(We're all wearing red.)
(The Penalty Men are trying to
go out into the world.)
(The humans must stop them.)
(What will become of their fate?)
(2021 New Year Driving Out Bad Luck
Race: Take My Bad Luck Away)